Previously on AMC's "Better Call Saul"...
What's our next move?
We gonna follow this guy?
♪♪
[Cellphone rings]
Yeah.
Jimmy: Changed 1261 to 1216.
My brother broke the law.
We can't just sit back and do nothing.
Jimmy: It's my word against his!
Jimmy, there's a tape.
Ernie told me.
♪♪
For this, you destroyed our family?!
Jimmy! That's enough!
Chuck: You were a witness
to what happened here?
I was.
[Insects chirping]
[Wind whistling]
[Engine rumbling]
[Rumbling continues]
[Brakes squeal]
[Air brakes hiss]
[Rumbling continues]
♪
synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
[Cellphone ringing]
[Cellphone beeps]
Yeah.
Man: May I assume that you are armed?
Yes.
I do not wish to see your gun.
And if I don't,
I promise you won't see mine.
Are we in agreement?
We are.
Expect two cars momentarily.
[Vehicles approaching]
[Engines shut off]
[Vehicle door closes]
[Insects chirping]
[Paper rustling]
You care to elaborate?
It's not in my interest
for Hector Salamanca to die...
at this time.
Who is he to you?
An associate of an associate.
Mm.
How very specific.
Who is he to you?
We had a disagreement.
He threatened my family.
I'm not gonna let that go.
But you had let it go.
You'd taken his money.
Your family was no longer in danger.
And yet, still, you robbed his truck.
Shouldn't that have settled the matter?
Most men would have walked away,
but instead...
you made an attempt on his life.
Why?
I understand that a civilian
found the driver
after you robbed the truck.
Hector murdered this civilian, correct?
He wasn't in the game.
I can't allow you to kill Hector.
However, I am not completely
unsympathetic to your...
sense of justice.
You hurt Hector when you robbed that truck.
You hurt his business,
his pride.
Quite effectively.
And if you were to hurt him
in the same manner again,
I would not stand in your way.
You want me to rob another truck.
If you feel so inclined.
I'm done with that.
Then our business here is finished.
That's it?
That's it.
No more tracker,
no more of your minions following me?
Just like that?
Just like that.
Of course...
I trust that you are done
with Hector Salamanca?
[Breathes sharply]
Goodbye, Mr. Ehrmantraut.
Wait.
You want his trucks hit
because you want to disrupt his supply line.
Hector's your competition.
Why do you ask?
Because I'm not done with Hector Salamanca.
[Telephone ringing]
[Telephone beeps]
Offices of Jimmy McGill.
How may I help you today?
- Jimmy: Hey. It's me.
- Oh, hey, Jimmy.
Listen, um, something's come up,
and, uh, I need you
to reschedule all
my appointments for tomorrow.
Oh, okay.
When do you want me to reschedule for?
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Sure thing.
Oh, and, uh, do me a favor...
tell Kim I won't be back in tonight.
Will do.
Okay. That's it.
Have a great night!
- Mm.
- [Cellphone clicks]
[Dog barking in distance]
[Grunts]
[Sniffling]
[Match strikes]
Chuck: You know you can wait inside.
You won't want to hear it,
but this is for the best.
Please, Jimmy...
Whatever you think of me,
whatever colorful names
you're calling me in your head right now,
please understand I'm trying to help you.
[Sighs]
Here's what's going to happen.
The police will arrest you,
and I'm sorry,
but I will be pressing charges.
I told you there would be consequences.
But I [chuckling] have to believe
that you'll face those consequences
and you'll come out
the other side a better man.
I know it's hard to see right now,
but, Jimmy, this is an opportunity.
That's why I'm doing this.
Not to punish you.
To show you, truly show you,
that you have to make a change
before it's too late.
Before you destroy yourself...
or someone else.
And I believe you can change.
You'll find your path.
And when you're ready,
I will be there to help you walk that path.
[Sighs]
Here's what's gonna happen.
One day, you're gonna get sick... again.
One of your employees
is gonna find you curled up
in that space blanket,
take you to the hospital,
hook you up to those machines
that beep and whir and... hurt.
And this time, it'll be too much.
And you will... die there.
Alone.
[Vehicle approaches]
There's my ride.
♪ Hurry ♪
[Police radio chatter]
♪ Down ♪
♪ Hurry down, sun ♪
♪ Hurry down ♪
Officer: Sir, I need
all your personal property,
belts, ties, phone, rings, wallet.
♪ I said, sun, won't you
hurry on, on down? ♪
♪ Struggling ♪
Need your socks and shoes
placed in that bag.
[Vocalizing]
♪ If someday my kids
are laughing together ♪
Put these on your feet.
♪ And having things that I never own ♪
Turn to the right.
♪ So bring on that new day ♪
- [Flash bulb pops]
- Turn to the left.
[Flash bulb charging]
- [Flash bulb pops]
- Face me.
- Left hand.
♪ A great tomorrow is on its way ♪
♪ Hurry, sundown ♪
♪ Hurry down, sundown ♪
[Buzzer]
- Right hand.
- Holy hell.
I thought they were bullshitting me.
- How the mighty have fallen.
- [Door clicks shut]
- What the hell happened, man?
- [Buzzer]
Nothing. Just family trouble.
You're married?
No. Disagreement with my brother.
That hardass?
I don't blame ya.
So who you got representing you?
I'll be representing myself.
- Sign here.
- Moron.
'Course, I knew that
when you left that sweet Davis & Main gig.
This way.
Hey, speaking of...
they, uh, still trying
to replace you over there?
Arms out.
How's, uh, Omar?
Why? You looking to make a change?
Well, leave all this glamour behind?
Hey, who do you think's gonna catch this?
Eh, it depends on who's
available when it comes in.
- Face me.
- You think you might be available?
Run your hands through your hair, please.
Don't you wanna throw the book
at me for old times' sake?
Mmm, I'll see if I can work some magic...
but those decisions
are really above my paygrade.
Oh, yeah? When did they
start paying you?
- [Scoffs, chuckles]
- Sit here.
- I gotta run, anyway.
- Left hand.
Just had to see it for myself...
[Handcuffs click]
Jimmy McGill,
getting fingerprinted with the hoi polloi.
Well, I'm glad you enjoyed the show.
[Sighs]
I'll check and see
if I can get your first appearance moved up.
Thank you.
It's pretty late.
Chances are, you're spending the night.
You, uh, gonna be okay?
Beats the back of a nail salon.
[Chuckles] I do not doubt that, my friend.
[Chuckles]
Oh, pick the biggest guy.
Punch him as hard as you can, okay?
Show dominance.
Right. Got it. Dominance.
You, uh, do know
how to throw a punch, right?
Yeah, all right. Goodbye.
[Chuckles]
[Buzzer]
[Lock clicks]
[Door creaks]
[Todd Terje's "Alphonso Muskedunder" plays]
[Alarm beeping]
[Music continues]
♪
[Scanner beeps]
[Handle creaks]
♪
[Air rushing]
Hey, Kim.
Can I talk to you?
Sure, Ernie.
What's going on?
Uh, Mr. McGill fired me.
- Why? What happened?
- I don't...
It doesn't matter.
I just...
Is Jimmy okay?
I feel bad, like it's my fault.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
What happened to Jimmy?
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door closes in distance]
[Footsteps approach]
[Buzzer]
[Keys jingling]
- Man: McGill?
- Guard: Yeah.
[Lock clicks, door creaks]
You're up.
[Handcuffs click, chains clinking]
[Grunts]
[Door creaks]
Woman: We've got CR-2003113081.
[Handcuffs click]
James McGill.
Yes, Your Honor. [clears throat]
Not how I'm used to
seeing you in here, Mr. McGill.
Not how I'd like to be seen.
Well, you had quite the day yesterday.
Okay.
Mr. McGill, you've been accused
of fourth degree felony
breaking and entering,
which carries a maximum sentence
of 18 months and a $5,000 fine.
We've also got petty misdemeanor assault.
Maximum six months' jail time
and a $500 fine.
Plus, criminal damage to property,
also misdemeanor with a maximum sentence
of six months and a $500 fine.
- [Door creaks]
- Victim is...
Your brother Charles?
Seriously?
I assume you're prepared
to enter a plea at this time.
Yes, Your Honor.
I wish to enter a plea of not guilty.
The court accepts
and enters the defendant's plea
of not guilty.
Now, Mr. McGill, have you secured counsel?
Kim: Yes.
Uh, Your Honor, Kim Wexler.
I'll be representing Mr. McGill
in this matter.
Judge: Just in time.
Let's enter Ms. Wexler
as the attorney of record.
Your Honor, if I may, um,
I'll be representing myself.
I strongly advise against that, Mr. McGill.
You know what they say about
a man who represents himself.
Oh, I... I'm aware, but as you know,
I've defended many people
in the criminal justice system.
Your Honor, may I have a moment
to speak with my client?
Sounds like he's not your client.
[Sighs]
Mr. McGill, would you like to take a moment
to discuss this with your...
potential counsel?
No, Your Honor. I'm all set.
- I'm gonna represent myself.
- Your Honor...
Not your client, Ms. Wexler.
I'm sorry. I'm moving on.
You two can work this out on your own time.
I'm sorry. I was gonna call you,
but then I thought I'd tell you in person.
Mr. McGill.
[Breathes sharply]
So, on to the issue of bond.
You have no priors
and no outstanding warrants.
And where are you currently practicing law?
I haven't seen you in my court in a while.
Elder law.
Judge: What a noble pursuit.
One I hope you get back to very soon.
Now, given your ties to the community,
I see no reason to deny you bond,
which I set now at $2,500.
[Gavel taps]
[Brakes squeal]
[Car door opens]
[Car door closes]
[Engine rumbling]
I fucked up.
Chuck bamboozled me again.
That tape?
He made sure that Ernie heard it, right?
Because he knew Ernie, bless him,
would tell me about it and I would come over
to try to destroy it
or steal it or whatever.
Howard was there,
and a P.I., if you can believe that,
just waiting for me
to lose my shit and bust in.
Chuck played me like a fiddle!
And schmuck that I am, I fell for it!
Moron. [Breathes sharply]
I'm sorry.
And then, I didn't call you,
which is stupid,
and I'm sorry about that, too.
But I didn't call you for a reason, okay?
'Cause this is my screw-up.
I own it, okay?
It's my responsibility to fix it.
And I know you want to help.
Of course you do, 'cause you're wonderful.
But y-you're up to your ears in Mesa Verde.
And I can't,
I won't load this onto you, too.
We have worked too hard
to let Chuck's bullshit vendetta
threaten everything that we're building!
I won't allow him to endanger our business!
No! I will fix this.
Myself. Me. Jimmy McGill.
Okay?
You have gotta let me do this on my own.
[Sighs]
Okay.
Thank you. [Sniffles]
[Footsteps depart]
[Door opens, closes]
I, uh, I finished it.
I... I mean, I just touched up the edges.
A little.
Is... Is that okay?
Oh.
Uh, sure.
It looks nice.
You mind driving me to my car?
Sure. No problem.
Um, just so you know,
this isn't a typical week around here.
Yeah, [chuckling] totally.
I... didn't think that it was.
Ah.
[Bell clinks]
[Man speaking in Spanish on radio]
[Woman coughing]
_
[Sighs] "Aaah!"
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
[Light clicks]
_
Mm.
[Inhales sharply]
_
Mm?
[Chuckles]
_
[Laughs]
- [Bell clinks]
- [Sighs]
_
Mm-hmm.
[Man coughing]
_
Mr. Clark?
The doctor is ready.
Doctor: And how may I
help you today, Mr. Clark?
I believe our mutual
acquaintance called ahead.
He told me what, but not how much.
Mm. Well, I need a package...
yea big.
[Sighs]
And what's that in grams?
Unh. This big.
[Bell clinks]
[Chickens clucking]
[Lock clicks]
[Clucking continues]
[Coffeemaker whirring]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Latches click]
[Elevator bell dings]
[Latch clicks]
[Crunching]
[Footsteps approach]
Hey.
Was somebody sitting here?
No.
[Sighs]
So, how was it?
How was what?
[Crunching] Your night in MDC.
I caught up with a few old clients.
Yeah? [Chuckles]
- Want one?
- Oh. [Chuckles]
Yeah.
This whole thing is a...
big misunderstanding.
Mm-hmm.
There's absolutely no way
it's going to trial.
Who wants that hassle? Not me.
Whichever lucky soul at the
D.A.'s office catches this,
looking at an easy clear.
There's a felony in there, right?
That would be a cla... Go ahead,
classic case of overcharging.
No offense.
Happy to have a civil conversation,
and I'm always ready to make a deal.
- Just call me Monty Hall.
- [Chuckles]
So you're looking to plea out
on this, then, Monty?
If it's the right plea.
I'm not perfect. Made mistakes.
I'm willing to own up to them
in a way that is satisfying
to both myself and the state.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
Well, good luck with that.
"Good luck with that" as in,
"I wish you well,"
or, "I accept your challenge"?
I wish you well.
Play your cards right, they may go for it.
"They"? Not you?
Prosecuting your case?
Nah, man. It's not me.
You never catch a lucky break, do ya?
- Bad timing?
- No, conflicted out.
Conflicted out?
I mean, I figured that'd happen.
You and I have wheeled and dealed together
too many times.
There was no way the boss
was letting me run that one.
[Crunching]
It's not Ericsen, is it?
The whole Albuquerque office is out.
We all know you, Jimmy.
- [Elevator bell dings]
- [Sniffles]
Well, who is it? I don't know.
They're pulling in someone from Belen.
Um... Hay?
Something Hay, I think.
I don't know.
Boss used the words "tough but fair."
[Clears throat] Ahh.
Gotta jam. [Chuckles]
[Latch clicks]
[Latches click]
[Sniffles]
Good luck.
Burger's getting cold. [Chuckles]
You want it?
- Uh...
- Yeah?
It has too many trans fats.
Ohh!
Those are the best fats.
So they let you keep the car?
- What?
- Davis & Main.
They let you keep the, uh, German car?
No.
That blows.
[Sighs]
[Engine shuts off]
[Insects chirping]
[Wind whistling]
[Keys jingling]
[Lock disengages, trunk lid creaks]
[Box thumps]
[Chirping continues]
[Shoes thump]
[Power line creaking]
[Engine rumbling]
[Brakes squeal]
[Engine shuts off]
[Window creaks]
Chuck: Ms. Hay?
- Mr. McGill?
- Chuck, please.
Meet me at the front door.
Uh, they said to put my things
in the mailbox.
Yes, please. Anything with a battery.
[Clattering lightly]
Did your brother ever
have a key to the house?
Before the recent trouble, he did.
He brought me my groceries and sundries.
But we had a falling-out.
I have an employee who does all that now.
You took away your brother's key
when you hired this employee?
I changed the locks.
Going... Going back to the confrontation,
so I have it absolutely clear,
did he strike you?
No, nothing like that.
He backed me into a cabinet.
Did he have a weapon?
Well, as I mentioned,
he used a fireplace poker
to break into my desk.
But he never would have used it on me.
Did you feel physically threatened?
My brother is a lot of things,
but even he has limits.
And you're willing to appear as a witness
even though he's family?
Unfortunately, yes.
If we continue with this,
I'll need your sworn testimony.
[Sighs]
I've had situations
involving family members before
where the injured party
has ultimately been reluctant
to cooperate with my office.
That won't happen.
I'm curious about your strategy.
Well...
as officers of the court,
I feel we should be held
to a higher standard.
I don't intend to take it
easy on your brother
just because he's a lawyer.
Of course not.
The bone of contention
is going to be the felony
breaking and entering.
Your brother's gonna want
to plead down to a misdemeanor,
but I'll hold the line on the felony.
[Clears throat]
Which means this could possibly go to trial.
[Sighs]
Now, I... I want to be mindful
of your comfort and well-being.
With, with your condition,
are you able to appear before the court?
In person?
I certainly appreciate you
accommodating me today
by coming here,
but don't worry,
I'm able to tolerate being out
for short periods
with a few minor adjustments.
Nothing that will
overly inconvenience the court.
I'll get started on this.
Unless you have other concerns.
I just...
I just keep thinking.
[Voice breaking] You know,
Jimmy has a good heart.
I'm, I'm sure he does.
It's not an excuse for what he's done.
[Sighs] But he's my brother.
[Stuttering] And I know... well, he...
well, he's emotional.
He flies off the handle.
I understand,
but this is more than flying off the handle.
I'm not going to defend his actions.
But I can't help wondering
if there's not a better solution.
For everyone.
[Clock ticking]
[Insects chirping]
[Wind rushing]
[Bird cawing]
[Engine rumbling]
[Gun clicks]
[Brakes squeal]
[Air brakes hiss]
[Engine shuts off]
[Truck door closes]
[Gunshot]
[Bullet clinks]
_
[Gunshot]
[Engine rumbling]
[Machinery whirring]
[Indistinct conversations]
-You're good.
-Hold up.
[Indistinct conversations]
Man: Okay, I can do that.
[Radio chatter]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Machinery whirring]
[Dog sniffing]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Whines softly]
Looks like we got a hit.
[Tires screech]
[Siren wailing]
[Sirens wailing]
[Brakes squeal]
Officer: Get down on your knees!
[Grunts]
[Handcuffs clicking]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Insects chirping]
[Sighs]
[Siren wails in distance]
[Chirping continues]
[Sighs]
[Spits] Jesus. How old is this?
I found it in the glove box.
- [Chuckles]
- Best guess?
From back when all the doors matched.
- [Chuckles]
- [Sniffles]
[Clears throat]
I got a deal offer from the ADA today.
And?
It's not what I expected.
Bad not what you expected?
[Sighs] It's just that...
It's different.
She's offering me Pre-Prosecution Diversion.
Seriously?
A PPD?
[Chuckles]
That's great, Jimmy.
[Scoffs]
Best I could hope for, right?
Right.
What does she want you to confess to?
All of it. The felony B and E.
Uh, misdemeanor petty assault
and property damage.
I never touched him,
but they got assault in there.
Well, could be worse.
As long as they never activate it,
it doesn't matter, right?
You gonna be able to keep your
nose clean for a whole year?
Keep "Viktor" with a "k" on lockdown?
It's not a problem, Giselle.
And if I don't, it's instant jail, right?
[Exhales deeply]
Lucky break.
She must not want the hassle of a trial.
[Clicks tongue] Guess so.
Jimmy...
this is good news.
And Chuck is gonna be pissed.
It's a big check in the "pro" column.
Actually, the PPD was Chuck's idea.
Shit.
Yeah.
[Breathes deeply] What's his game?
One condition of the PPD
is that my written confession
is immediately submitted to
the New Mexico Bar Association.
Your written felony confession.
Yeah. I thought he wanted me in jail.
He just wants my law license.
[Sighs]
What are you gonna do?
Well...
I knew the bar was gonna be an issue, right?
So I figured I'd plea the charges down
to a couple misdemeanors, get a censure,
and maybe a little suspension, but...
a confession to a felony?
Grounds for disbarment.
Yeah. And if I take it to trial and I lose,
I face the bar anyways
and jail time, most likely.
[Sighs]
He's got me boxed in.
You can fight this.
The disciplinary board listens
to extenuating circumstances.
No, Chuck knows everybody at the bar.
Hell, he made half their careers.
It's gonna be him and his cronies versus me.
Alone.
- Not alone.
- Kim.
Come on, Jimmy.
You need me.
You can't argue this yourself.
You and I both know that.
And I'm not gonna let you
fight this on your own.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
'Cause I don't...
[Sighs]
Why would you...
Come on.
This guy?
Seriously?
Let's just call it
the fallacy of sunk costs.
[Sighs]
So what now?
Now?
Now we, uh, take that PPD,
and we shove it right up Chuck's ass.