♪ We face the music together ♪
♪ And throw our hats
in the ring ♪
♪ Facing all kinds of weather ♪
♪ And not afraid of anything ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When the sun comes up,
we'll be on our way ♪
♪ And we don't care
where we land ♪
♪ And the waves are high,
but we won't turn round ♪
♪ 'Cause your hand
is in my hand ♪
♪ And, oh-oh ♪
♪ You make me feel invincible ♪
♪ 'Cause it's you and me ♪
♪ Through the wind and hail ♪
♪ Setting sail into the world ♪♪
[♪ Ben Pirani:
"Dreamin's For Free"]
♪ ♪
♪ Oh, my darlin'...
- On the hinge?
- I've seen her on the hinge.
- It's a small
bisexual community.
- I think it'd be really good.
- Thank you.
- [chuckles] Can I?
- I c...
- Very small bisexuals.
- Yes, thank you.
- Okay, that's-that's
really weird.
- [laughter]
- That's really weird.
Oh, I want this.
- What is poutine anyway?
- So, wait,
what did she text you?
[laughter]
[Sky] She texts me saying
that she isn't rich,
- but she has
multiple cashmere berets...
- Thank you, thank you.
- ...and she's an intern.
- [Billy] That is so cute.
- And I miss dating her 'cause
she would pay for my food.
- No, no, no.
I hate that fake
struggle bullshit.
She should just admit
that her parents help her out.
- Excuse me.
- ...recycling using glass.
Can we...
can we borrow your cream?
♪ Dreamin'...
Yeah. You can have it.
- Excuse me, what?! What?
How can your mom...
- Yes, it's true.
- ...hate Greta Thunberg?!
- She just thinks
- there's more to the story.
- [laughs]
Sorry. Sorry about
my obnoxious friends.
I-I just realized
that it was probably quiet
in here before we came in
and ruined it.
It's a diner.
It's supposed to be... bustling.
You an artist?
Yes, I am.
Crayons are actually my medium.
Okay.
I'm kidding.
[laughs]
Yeah.
It's just habit.
I come here with my nieces.
I'm-I'm gonna...
let you get back to it.
Thank you for the cream.
- Yeah, you're good.
- You are so cute.
- Look at him smile.
- Look at him blush.
- I'm not blushing.
- [chuckling]
Thanks.
- Receipt?
- I'm good. Thank you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Um...
You don't have to run.
I'm-I'm literally
standing still.
That's true.
[chuckles]
♪ Dreamin'...
[Sky mouthing]
So, you want me to call you?
Yeah, if-if you want.
I... But the longer
I stand here,
the more I-I realize I don't
actually know your deal, and,
uh, I might be coming off
like some kind of, uh,
- gross late-night guy.
- You're not gross.
- No?
- No.
Good.
Uh...
Well, thank you for this.
♪ ♪
[Jordan] Good night.
Uh, yeah.
Have a good one.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
[Zoe] Once upon a time,
there was a girl
who was only awake at night.
She shared the streets
with sleepwalkers,
travelers and ghosts.
For as long
as she could remember,
she had been asleep
when everyone else was awake...
...and awake when the rest
of the world was sleeping.
Oh. Thank you, Albert.
- You're the best.
- I got you.
- How's it going?
- Oh, I'm just chilling.
- Take your time.
- Thank you.
[Zoe] The moon was her sun...
...and the sun was her moon.
Thank you!
♪ ♪
The darkness was her hometown.
The only traffic,
the stars crowded in the sky.
She was a Night Girl.
And this was all
she had ever known.
♪ ♪
[Zoe] That makes sense.
I bet you're, like,
a really cool teacher.
The one all the kids
like the best. [chuckles]
- It's true, isn't it?
- I...
- I like them, too, by the way.
- I knew it.
- It's like reciprocal respect
going on.
- I knew it. I can tell.
You're, like, a people person.
Us weirdo science types
simply can't relate.
You're a scientist?
Not really.
It's just what I studied
in school.
You wanted to be a doctor?
No. Not even.
No, I...
Okay, the truth is,
and I don't usually tell this
to just, like, anybody,
- but...
- Ooh...
I actually like
thinking about physics.
- Me, too.
- Really?
No, I don't really like it.
[laughs]
What do you do for work?
Different things.
Yeah.
That doesn't sound shady at all.
[laughs]
I edit textbooks.
Which is not as boring
as it sounds.
Okay.
And I also work two times a week
at a club.
[Jordan] I bike to work.
Uh, I'm cooped up
in the classroom all week,
so I take whatever chance I get
to be outdoors in the sun.
Mm.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I know what you're thinking.
"Oh, it's dangerous
to bike in the city."
But there are a lot more bike
lanes than there used to be.
So the city's
a much more bikeable city
- than it used to be.
- Yeah. Totally.
Maybe we can go
for a bike ride one day.
Um...
Well...
[stammers]
[Jordan] So you're like a...
- vampire?
- [chuckles]
Usually, I go to bed
at 8:00 or 9:00 a.m.
and wake up around 5:00 p.m.
And what's it called?
Delayed sleep phase syndrome.
It's a circadian rhythm
disorder.
So, what would happen
if you forced yourself to...
keep normal hours?
You don't think I've tried that?
It feels like I'm jet-lagged
all the time.
Like, my body rejects it.
That's so wild.
[chuckles] Yeah,
it is wild, I guess.
I mean, there are weird aspects,
for sure.
Like, um...
I'm always confused about
what day of the week it is,
because my days change
in the middle.
Dating can be...
tricky.
But there can be perks, too.
Like, I don't have to deal
with traffic
or interruptions
while I'm working.
I always make sure
I'm back in my apartment
before the daily rush
of morning commuters.
So I can go weeks
without laying eyes on, like,
a single yoga mom or banker bro.
But the-the commuters,
the moms, the-the banker bros,
isn't that, like, real life?
It's a version of real life.
But...
there's also real life at night.
And let's be honest.
Nighttime folks are way easier
to deal with than daytime folks.
- Okay.
- [chuckles]
There is something
really magical
that kicks in when you feel
like you are the only one
in the world still awake.
Like the whole world exists
just for you.
I like vampires.
[both chuckle]
Cool.
♪ ♪
[Vanessa] So I told him
if his fucking phone
is on fucking silent
and that's why he misses every
single one of my fucking calls,
then he can either turn
that shit up
or the next time
he comes to my apartment
to watch football
because he's too cheap to spring
for the sports package,
I'm gonna barricade
the fucking door.
You get it, Zoe, right?
What?
[muffled music playing]
[phone chimes, vibrates]
[♪ Mighty Clouds:
"Now is the Time When
All the Children Sleep"]
♪ Now is the time...
- Okay, wait, so you're
in a kickball league?
- Yes.
Like, the sport
third graders play
because real sports
would be too hard?
That's a...
that's a common misconception.
[chuckles] In Canada,
they call it soccer baseball,
which-which might be an easier
way for you to conceptualize it.
Two sports in one.
- Mm.
- A super sport, if you would.
[chuckles]
I am on a date with a man
who still plays kickball.
Yes.
♪ Go to your rooms...
This is, like,
the least shadiest thing
- I've done today.
- [chuckles]
- Just trust me. Pete!
- Oh, God.
♪ Tucked beneath sheets...
- Is that Zoe?
- Hey!
Hey, what's up?
How are things going?
Pete, Jordan. Jordan, Pete.
- Hey, Jordan.
- Hey.
- My usual.
Usual? Well,
there's two of you this time.
- That's true.
- [Peter] Hold on.
[whispers] Hey...
♪ When all the children sleep...
- I got you some good ones.
- Oh, thank you.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Pete, come on.
- Stop. [laughs]
- Eh.
- See you, guys.
Nice to meet you.
- Bye.
- You, too, Pete.
- [chuckles]
Delilah,
the late-night radio host?
Mm-hmm.
You said you wouldn't judge.
I'm not.
That is an adorable first crush.
I-I used to think that...
she was dedicating
the love songs to me.
- [laughs]
- ♪ Go to your rooms ♪
♪ Go to your beds and dream ♪
♪ Tucked beneath sheets ♪
♪ And the monsters sing ♪
♪ Now is the time ♪
♪ When all the children sleep ♪♪
I maintain that,
in the history of our nation,
we've never actually had
free and open elections.
I and your mothers,
up until very recently,
were not considered citizens.
But, in our democracy, there are
procedures and consequences
- for disenfranchising
people's right to vote.
- [phone vibrates]
I maintain that most people
aren't cheated out
of their right to vote
but are lazy
and don't value its importance,
some of our mothers
and fathers included.
[Zoe] When I look
at social media,
I go into a black hole,
and I emerge hours later,
lost in, like,
the wedding registry
of the cousin of someone I hated
- in elementary school.
- [chuckles]
Yes, but isn't it the best way
of keeping track of everybody?
Why would I want
to keep track of everybody?
Oh, shit.
- What?
- It's my coworker.
Wait, Jordan, don't look.
- Ow.
- [Vanessa] Zoe?
Hey! Hi, girl.
I thought that was you.
Yeah. Hey... Oh, my God.
- Hey.
- Hi.
[whispers] Be nice.
I'm telling you,
he's Bette Midler
trapped in the body of
a 14-year-old Puerto Rican kid.
And how he could see that
as anything less than
a compliment is lost on me.
Well, my kid would shit a brick
if you told him that.
Wait, you have a kid?
- Yeah.
- You don't know
that she has a kid?
I guess you don't bring him
around the club very much.
Fuck no. Not that this one
would notice if I did.
That's Zoe.
Guys, when I am at work,
I'm working.
[all laugh]
[Jordan] No, I d...
I don't need to see it to know.
[Zoe] You are a teacher.
You are supposed to believe
in research
and informed opinions.
I don't need to research
The Real Housewives
to know that it's total crap.
Okay. You're completely wrong
on this one.
You know
it's all scripted, right?
Like, the fakest of the fake.
O-Okay. Okay.
Sometimes the situations
are contrived, sure.
You actually have to watch it
and listen...
No. Don't kiss me.
The emotions are always real.
It's honest.
Well, you make
a compelling argument.
I'm not gonna
sleep with you again
until you watch an episode.
I'll download it now.
Great.
♪ ♪
I must be dreaming.
Shh. Go back to sleep.
How can I sleep
when there's a beautiful vampire
awake in my room?
[chuckles]
Ah.
Thank you for coming tonight.
Like I would miss
the opportunity
to watch you completely dominate
soccer baseball.
[laughs]
Mmm.
It's kickball, baby.
Oh, my God, Jor...
[laughs] What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
I got to go! [laughs]
I'm already late. Bye.
Bye.
[Vanessa] Hey, girl!
Hey.
Thanks for letting me
crash your date the other night.
Oh, yeah. You weren't...
It wasn't a problem.
Your boyfriend
is, like, really nice.
Her boyfriend is,
like, really nice.
Yeah, he is. [chuckles]
- So, how'd you do it?
- Do what?
Get such a nice boyfriend.
[phone chimes]
Oh, sorry. [chuckles]
- See you in there.
- Yeah, see you in a bit.
Hey, B.
Okay, but she uses
the same excuse every time.
Like, how many
precancerous moles
are we supposed to believe
this woman has?
Totally. You know, I mean,
I don't work out for anything.
- Zoe.
- [Billy] Oh, Zoe with wine.
- Yeah. Oh, God.
- Ooh, careful.
It might suck.
It's just a nice label.
You got here just in time.
These bitches are
trying to convince me
I have too many shirtless pics
on my Tinder profile.
Wait, but isn't that,
like, the point?
Thank you.
- Hi.
- Hey, you're...
I'm sorry.
It took me a while to get going.
It's okay.
There's still
a little light left.
No, no, wait.
I want one of those.
♪ ♪
Yo, Reese.
- Hey, Zoe.
- Hey.
- Just give me one second.
- Thank you.
- [Jordan] Hi.
- Hey.
Do you think that we could
push, like, an hour?
Um, I just overslept,
and I am still waking up,
and I have a couple errands
- I need to run before.
- You know what?
I'm totally exhausted, too.
I could...
I could really just go home
and crash right now.
Wait, no. I just need an hour.
Okay. I just thought that...
I mean, if I'd known we weren't
having dinner at all,
I would've planned
my whole day differently.
Sure, sure.
Sure, an hour's fine.
Great. So,
I'll see you in a bit, okay?
- Thank you, Reese.
- See you later.
Oh. No, no, no, no.
Hey. Can you just let me in?
You guys, like, closed
six minutes ago. I just...
I just really need
to pick up a prescription.
I'll be in and out.
Come on!
I would open the door for you.
[Jordan] Uh,
can we have bruschetta,
- as well, please? And, uh...
- Sure. Yeah.
And I'll have a glass
of Nebbiolo.
You want any wine?
- What do you think?
- What?
Have a full day of work
ahead of me.
I was just asking.
Sometimes you...
Not today.
And for you?
Would it be possible
to get some scrambled eggs?
Scrambled eggs?
Yeah, and bacon.
That's really all I want
right now.
Zoe, uh...
What?
I know they have eggs because
they serve spaghetti carbonara,
and eggs is one of the main
ingredients of carbonara.
And guanciale.
That's kind of
like bacon, right?
Uh, yeah. I mean,
I can certainly check
with the kitchen if they...
[Zoe] I don't know why
you even have to check.
They can just scramble the eggs
that we both know they have
and put it on a plate
with the guanciale,
and it's spaghetti carbonara
minus the spaghetti.
Uh, chef does not generally
allow substitutions.
But is there anything else
you would like if he says no?
You know what?
Forget it. It's fine.
I'll just have a cappuccino.
Sure.
Look, toast.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
What?
Nothing.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
- Hey, hey.
Hey, man. Hey, listen.
- Yeah.
Sorry about that.
[waiter] Oh, it's no problem.
It's good.
[Jordan] She's just
not feeling well.
And-and if you could bring
the cappuccino,
that would be great.
And then if you have eggs
and you could bring the eggs,
that would...
That's fantastic.
If not, that's totally fine.
- [waiter] Yeah, of course, sir.
- [Jordan] Yeah.
- And thanks again.
- [waiter] Sure, sure.
- [Jordan] Appreciate it.
- [waiter] Yeah.
So, my mom's coming
into town this weekend.
Mm, really?
- Mm-hmm.
- I didn't know
she was visiting.
Or did you tell me and I forgot?
She's going on a cruise
with my aunt
that-that leaves from New York.
- Mm.
- And so she's flying in
a little early
to spend some time with me.
That's nice.
She wants to meet you.
Really?
And I want her to meet you, too.
I think we're there. Don't you?
Definitely.
Yeah. Okay.
So, where should we take her?
Maybe, like,
a nice dinner somewhere?
Where I don't order
- eggs, I promise.
- [chuckles]
Uh, the thing is
she-she has to be
on the boat by 4:00.
So, and-and there's nothing
that she loves more
when she's in town
than to go to this dim sum place
we both love in Sunset Park.
Oh. Okay.
So, it's kind of
a-a-a brunch type thing.
- Like, a early...
early afternoon type thing.
- Okay.
I-I know that...
I know it's not ideal,
uh, but I don't know when
she'll be back in town again,
and, uh, and like I said,
I just really want...
I really want
to meet her, Jordan.
I'm excited.
Stop worrying.
You know I'm fine.
I love spending time
with just you.
Thanks, Ma.
Sorry.
You're gonna have to tell her
it's her fault that I ate
twice as many dumplings
as I planned to, though.
I'm... I'm gonna... I'm just
gonna tr-try one more time.
[phone vibrating]
Oh, shit!
Um, I'm so sorry. I'm on my way.
Don't-don't bother.
We're-we're almost done here.
Just glad you're okay.
Yeah, I-I am okay.
I was, um, asleep,
but I think you know that.
Like I said, just wanted
to make sure you were okay.
Listen, I'm an idiot.
I didn't set my alarm
because I thought
I would just stay up, but I...
Just go back to bed.
Shit. Okay.
[muttering]
Ow.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm here.
I'm here. Oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
- Oh, wow, you so did not
have to run down here.
- Hi.
Hi. I'm Zoe.
I'm so happy
to finally get to meet you, Zoe.
Me, too. I am so, so sorry.
Oh, don't be.
It's the weekend. You're young.
- No.
- I know how it is.
No, that's actually
not what happened,
- but...
- Oh, it's okay. [chuckles]
I look forward to getting
to know you better next time.
- Me, too. For sure.
- You should get going, Ma.
Okay. [chuckles]
- Mwah. Love you.
- You, too.
- [chuckles]
- Oh.
- Have fun.
- Thanks.
- Safe travels.
- Next time.
Okay.
I love you. Bye.
- I am so sorry.
- I know you are.
- I will make it up to you.
- You can't, but it's fine.
Well, if I can't,
then it's not fine,
so don't say it's fine
if it's not fine.
Okay, then, you know what?
It's not fine.
- Okay.
- I hate that
you weren't there today.
But-but-but it's so much
more than that.
I-I... I hate that we can't
do anything normal, ever.
I hate that we can't
go for a walk
or-or coffee and-and-and brunch.
- Brunch.
- Yeah, brunch.
I-I hate that I'm tired
all the time.
I hate that I have
to make excuses for you.
I hate that I can't dream
of a future with you
because who knows
what that's gonna look like.
A midnight wedding?
A baby you can't
even take care of?
You think about
things like that?
I don't let myself,
because it seems like
a future like that
isn't possible with you.
Okay, so what
do you want me to say?
I mean, I've been upfront with
you from the very beginning.
But it's been on your terms
ever since then.
I've been subsisting
on, like, no sleep
just to hang out with you,
and you can't even set an alarm
to... to meet my mom.
It's a medical condition,
Jordan.
It's not some, like,
lifestyle choice.
I thought you understood that.
But great to know what you'd be
like if I got sick someday.
If you were actually sick,
I'd take care of you.
What does that mean?
So you don't think this is real?
Like...
just say it, Jordan.
Just say it. I can tell you want
to say it, so just say it.
Or do you save your honesty for
when you're secretly apologizing
to waiters on my behalf?
You say you have to make excuses
for me, but what you don't get
is that it's not an excuse
if the problem is real.
I just think
it's a convenient condition
for an introvert who doesn't
maybe really want to engage
- with the world anyway.
- Yeah.
Because this has made
my life so convenient.
I-I-I...
I need time.
Okay.
Just like that?
[sighs] Oh.
[scoffs]
♪ ♪
♪ A perfect, perfect moon
in the garden ♪
♪ Perfect, perfect light ♪
♪ A perfect, perfect day ♪
♪ To say another good night ♪
♪ A perfect, perfect
winter into summer ♪
♪ A perfect, perfect sky ♪
A perfect, perfect day
to say goodbye ♪♪
So, um, tonight,
your reading should cover the,
uh... the Kent State shooting.
That was in the chapter
we read last night.
Right.
Okay, um, so let-let's
go through it together.
No, three PBRs, two Heinekens.
Vanessa. Hey.
Hey, girl. What's up?
Do you maybe want to go get
some food or something
- when we're done tonight?
- That sounds nice,
but I got to go
right to sleep tonight.
I'm getting
a procedure tomorrow.
It's no big deal, but I don't
want to get anesthesia
on, like, no sleep, you know?
Anesthesia?
[door opens, closes]
[singsongy] Hello? Good morning.
- Oh.
Oh, my... Sorry.
I'm all done.
How do you feel?
Well, a little sore,
but mostly just tired.
- Hmm.
- Not as tired as you, but...
- tired.
- Okay.
Hey.
Thank you for coming.
You didn't have
to do this, and...
I know I didn't have to.
But I didn't want you
to be alone.
This stuff can be scary.
Plus, then I don't have
to be alone, either.
Oh. Come here, you.
Oh, my coffee.
- Oh, sorry.
- It's okay.
No, I kind of actually think
I would like to be in a cult.
You wouldn't have
to make any decisions.
It's kind of relaxing.
- You do love loungewear.
- [Sky chuckles]
- Uh-huh, I do.
- And prolonged eye contact.
[Billy] I should start a cult.
Make eye contact with
someone across the room.
Okay, so, the wait time
is 90 minutes,
but if we do one of
the communal tables,
it's closer to, like, 75.
Oh.
Um, you know,
why don't we just...
Just do the communal, right?
Okay. Sure.
Great. I have been dying
to try this place.
I read that they have an
entire menu just for mimosas.
♪ ♪
[subway rumbling]
[phone chimes]
♪ ♪
Hello?
Did you bring me here
to murder me?
[laughs]
Shit. There goes
my big surprise.
- Hi.
How have you been?
You?
Same.
What is this place?
A buddy of mine knows
the guy who just moved out.
You're moving?
You-you want
to check out the bedroom?
During the day, this whole
living room fills with light.
And-and at night, you can
do your work over there,
and the moonlight comes in.
Are you suggesting what
I think you're suggesting?
I think our mistake was trying
to occupy each other's worlds.
Then, uh, how will we live?
I just want to be near you, Zoe.
Asleep, awake,
it doesn't matter.
We can see each other
in the hours that overlap.
I don't care.
Okay, but what about
all the things
that you said
that day on the street?
I was pissed.
I-I lost sight of the fact
that, in a relationship,
you choose to be with someone
who is inherently living
in their own reality.
I miss your reality.
I... I love your reality.
The Day Boy and the Night Girl.
It's a fairy tale.
A witch raises two children
in captivity,
allowing the boy to see only
day and the girl only night.
And then, one day, he stays out
longer than he's supposed to,
and when it gets dark,
he's terrified.
And she finds him
shaking in the garden,
and she tries to comfort him.
She tells him how gentle
and sweet the night can be.
And since she's wide awake,
she promises
that she'll watch over him
while he's sleeping.
[♪ Devendra Banhart:
"Is This Nice?"]
And when the sun rises,
he wakes up.
[voice breaking] And now
she's scared because...
she's never seen the sun.
How does it end?
He carries her in his arms
while she sleeps until dark.
♪ ♪
♪ Is this nice?
Do you like it? ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Would you like me
to sing you this song? ♪
♪ It begins with a question ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I just asked one ♪
♪ And now I carry on ♪
♪ Some days you're gonna feel ♪
♪ There'll never again
be flowers ♪
♪ Learning to count
all the way up to love ♪
♪ Is this real? Do I mean it? ♪
♪ You know that I do ♪
♪ I wanna be here, really near ♪
♪ I wanna really be
here with you ♪
♪ Above ♪
♪ What will soon be all cloud ♪
♪ Tear in your eye ♪
♪ Yes, this is allowed ♪
♪ But you cannot give up ♪
♪ Music yet to be made ♪♪