'I promised myself I wouldn't be
the first to say goodbye.'
I can't say goodbye again.
OK.
'In the end, it didn't matter.'
# Sha-la-la, la-la
# Take away the dark clouds
# And the sun will glow... #
'It's good,
having spent that time with James.
'It's good to know that
it doesn't work.
'I thought it wouldn't.
'People say moments like this
are like ripping off a plaster.
'The problem is that,
underneath the plaster,
'there's still quite a lot of shit.'
I made a mistake.
It's not me
you should be apologising to.
I'm not.
'I could tell her about James.
'I could ask her about the letter.
'But sometimes it's easier
if you just leave the plaster on.'
Go easy on her. She was embarrassed.
And it was a lot of money.
I'm gonna pay her back.
Good.
Are there any shifts?
You can do tonight if you want.
Thanks.
I should go and see Todd.
Do you wanna change first?
Yeah, probably.
Here? You sure?
Thank you.
Go away.
# Let's go down to tea
# Let's take a walk down by the sea
# See the blood-soaked sun... #
SHE STARTS ENGINE
MUSIC: Where Is Love?
from Oliver!
# Where is love?
# Does it... #
'My dad always told me
that musicals lift the spirits.'
Oh!
You'll love this.
They're cats, but it's good.
TAPE DECK CLICKS
# I can mean
# Something to... #
'Maybe Alyssa was right.
'Maybe I HAD been carrying him round
like a mascot.'
# Where...
# ..is love? #
HE SWITCHES OFF MUSIC
Yeah?
You can't park here, James.
What are you doing?
Which way is the, um...
the...?
Where are you headed?
I have no idea.
'Todd lives with his sister.'
Hey, Iggy.
Fuck off and die.
'She's quite protective of him.'
Still carrying that around?
Yeah.
Who is it?
My dad.
How did he die?
Heart attack.
Hm. Well, that's good.
Nice and quick.
It wasn't that nice. At least
he didn't top himself or something.
No. My mum did that.
Christ.
Where you gonna scatter him?
I don't know.
What did he like?
Eating shit food.
Cars.
And my mum.
Where did they meet?
'I couldn't believe
I hadn't thought of that.'
That's a good idea.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Now fuck off.
'It's quite hard to put things right
when everyone hates you
'and you can't find your husband.'
DOOR CLICKS
Do you take sugar?
Three.
'Silent Lisa is Iggy's girlfriend.
'I've literally never
heard her speak.
'She can. She just doesn't.'
Why'd you leave?
I got scared.
You should've told him.
I know.
I'd tell her.
And...she'd tell me.
'How? With a fucking mime?'
Where is he? I have to talk to him.
He's doing something.
What?
Come on. I need to see him, please.
'As I drove away,
I started to feel calm
'for the first time in ages.
'Sad...but calm.
'I had a new plan, a new purpose.
I had to move on.'
ENGINE ROARS
'It was fine. There was probably
a perfectly good reason
'why Bonnie was now driving a car...
'..and heading towards Alyssa.'
HORNS BEEP
ENGINE ROARS
SONG: A Thousand Miles Away
by The Heartbeats
# You're a thousand miles away
# Oh, but I still have your love
# To remember you by
# You by, oh, my darling... #
Hey.
BIRDSONG
How angry are you?
Pretty angry.
All right.
I've only got one chair.
That's OK.
So, you're back, then?
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
Can I show you something?
What?
It's a surprise.
INTERNALLY: He's probably gonna push
me down a well or something.
In a way, fair enough.
This was all wrong.
Alyssa had never said
where she lived.
OK. You can open them.
I don't get it.
Front door.
Lounge.
Kitchen.
HE MAKES SWISHING SOUND
Conservatory.
Walking up the stairs...
HE LAUGHS
Um, landing.
Bedroom, en-suite.
Baby's room.
Not for a while.
And we can put a panic room
in the basement.
I've looked into it. It actually
doesn't cost that much.
I've saved up,
and I'm gonna build this for us.
For you.
Wow!
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Do you wanna come in?
I can't.
Why not?
INTERNALLY: Sometimes doing the
right thing feels like committing a
crime.
Cos I want a divorce.
Todd, wait!
I wanna talk to you! Please stop!
I'm sorry, Todd! I'm really sorry.
Why did you ask me to marry you?
Why?
I don't know.
You don't deserve to be with anyone,
because you don't treat people
well enough.
I know.
Hello?
Is Alyssa around?
No.
Who are you?
I'm a friend.
I was at the wedding.
I was at the back.
Sorry. Um...
Why are you here?
It was at this point
I realised that Bonnie probably
didn't have a sister.
She's on her way to work.
Bye.
Who was that?
I don't know.
SONG: Fall
by Lisa Harrington
# Hide your horses, hold your tongue
# Hang the rich and spare the young
# Who drain the spirits
from the jar... #
INTERNALLY: Sometimes I get so tired
that I can't feel my edges anymore.
It's like melting.
# Run on fumes, and from... #
HORN BLARES
But not in a good way.
SHE BREATHES RAGGEDLY
It wasn't ideal. Only two hours
after deciding to move on,
I was, to all intents and purposes,
stalking Alyssa again.
But I wasn't the only one,
and that was the problem.
Ow!
DOOR BANGS
Are you OK?
What?
Do you mind if I go early?
It's pretty dead.
Sure.
Cheers.
ENGINE STARTS
ENGINE RECEDES
SHE GROANS
# Meaner
# Than the sea
# She's the only one
# I am afraid of
# Wiser
# Than the trees
# She is the only one
# I ever dream of
# Meaner
# She's the one
# Wiser
# She's the one... #
DOOR ENTRY BELL RINGS
# Meaner
# Than the sea... #
Hi.
# She is the only one
I am afraid of... #
What are you doing here?
You forgot something.
# She is the only one
# I ever dream of
# Meaner
# You're the one
# Wiser
# You're the one. #
Oh!
HE BREATHES RAGGEDLY
Oh, shit!