Ladies and gentlemen...
marriage, according to the law
of this country...
is the union of one man with one woman...
voluntarily entered into for life...
to the exclusion of all others.
- Mickey here is...
- What's going on here?
What in God's name is happening here?
That is my wife!
- I love the suit.
- You married us last week.
You enjoy seeing me in a wedding dress,
don't you?
Just a little bit.
What about a Spanish Prisoner?
We haven't done one of them in years.
We could always live together first,
see how it goes.
We've got enough toasters, ain't we?
I'm sick of getting married every week.
- Next time, it can be someone else.
- What about a Leighton Buzzard?
Well, that was fun.
I haven't run like that since 1972.
- We screwed up, Michael.
- Yes, we did.
I talked to a man about a horse yesterday.
- No, Albert.
- No, Albie.
What do we do now, Mickey?
We keep calm and trust our talent.
Libation for a shocked body.
Who's that?
The woman you're gawping at,
who is she?
She is "Mrs. Katherine Winterborn...
"recently divorced from
Stephen Winterborn, businessman.
"She denied killing his dog
in a fit of pique."
She killed the bloke's dog?
"In the ensuing divorce,
she took her husband to the cleaners...
"leaving him the bare bones
of their hotel and spa business...
"and an empty dog basket."
What am I thinking, Albert?
You're thinking about doing the Congreve.
I am indeed.
- What's the Congreve?
- William Congreve. Playwright.
"Heaven has no rage
like love to hatred turned
"Nor hell a fury like a woman scorned"
We're going to stitch up
a vengeful woman.
Okay. Danny, Stacie,
book into Winterborn's London spa...
and see what information you can get
out of Katherine's former staff.
Katherine Winterborn
emerged triumphant...
from recent bitter divorce proceedings
against Stephen Winterborn...
Who managed to maintain sole control
of the Winterborn chain of spa hotels...
which Stephen is about to float
on the stock exchange.
Daniel, what did you learn?
Well, I spoke to one of the therapists.
Very sweet girl.
In my country,
the water wouldn't be so warm.
Mrs. Winterborn
was a stickler for discipline.
Strict. Aloof. Cruel when she felt like it.
Sacked staff at the drop of a hat.
But very good at her business.
Stacie? Anything else?
She had a very volatile relationship
with her husband.
One day she cut up all his suits and he
retaliated by ripping up all her drawings.
They had a row.
He went away on a business trip...
and she had his Labrador put down
by the vet.
Shouldn't have killed that dog.
- So the dog was the last straw?
- No, the lift was the last straw.
She took an ax to his favorite car,
he goes mad, locks her in a lift.
You can't really blame him, after the dog.
Except he knew
that she was claustrophobic.
She pushed him so far,
he eventually flipped.
Gave her everything
at the divorce settlement...
just kept the spa-hotel chain.
All right. Tell me about the drawings.
She attends art classes twice a week.
Crazy about it.
I think I'm going to enjoy this.
Yeah. Well, you be careful, Albie,
because she is a real psycho bitch.
What are you doing, Eddie?
Found this old cocktail book
down the Charing Cross Road.
- Angel's Tit. Do you want one?
- No, thank you.
Incredible. Moment of pure joy.
When he was younger,
Albert was the doyen of the Congreve.
He could smell out a vengeful woman
like a pig with a truffle.
What a man.
Excuse me.
- Where are you off to, Ash?
- Out.
You got a mystery woman stashed away?
Yeah, we're not good enough for her, Ash?
Where does he keep going off to?
That's his business.
I wonder how Albie is getting on.
Excuse me. It's my first time.
I'm a little nervous.
Are you talking to me?
- Yeah. I was saying it's my first time.
- Please don't.
Good evening. Let's make a start, people.
- Damien? Welcome to the class.
- Thank you.
So, if you won't mind undressing,
we'll get started.
- Excuse me?
- Please.
The new boy or girl, they always
model on their first class.
- It's just our little tradition.
- Okay.
Damien, your robe?
Mickey.
You remember June, don't you?
Yeah, thanks.
Mickey Stone. You look fabulous.
- So do you.
- Liar.
What happened, June?
Too many years
head-butting moving vehicles.
She was doing the flop
up until a month ago.
The plate in her head moved...
That's too bad.
- But Ash has been looking after you?
- Only the best.
Tell him I'm not his responsibility.
That ended the day we divorced.
Sorry, I can't do that, June.
Besides, it wouldn't be true.
Not you, too?
You're family.
And families take responsibility.
And they share that responsibility.
I wanted to tell you, but...
- Ash?
- Yes, love?
- Who's that man?
- Why, that's Mickey.
- You remember Mickey.
- Get him out!
It's okay.
- That wasn't exactly what I expected.
- Really?
May I see?
It's good. I'm always looking
for fresh blood, a fresh eye.
I own a small gallery in Knightsbridge.
Is that supposed to impress me?
Not at all. I just thought you might...
I'm an amateur. I know what I am.
Not from looking at your work tonight.
I would actually disagree.
Then you're an idiot.
Believe me,
I'm never wrong about these things.
Perhaps I could take you out for a cup of...
We could...
Do you know why
I come to this drawing class?
I imagine because...
It's the one thing I do
where I can lose myself for a blissful hour.
If I wanted an elderly roué
with an art gallery hitting on me...
I'd go to Venice. Do you understand?
- Perfectly.
- Good.
Some days she's fine.
Then, suddenly, the fog will come down
and she gets confused, upset.
She will get better?
It's partial brain damage, Mickey.
And you've been paying for that home
all this time?
Yeah, until the end of next week.
Then the money runs out.
Then what happens?
- There are cheaper places.
- No way. Not for June.
I remember when you two married.
It just wasn't something we ever did.
Well, you married Rachel.
Yeah, I know.
But she wasn't one of us, you know.
And I remember what you said:
"Just because we do what we do
doesn't mean we have to be lonely."
I admired you for saying that.
Are you going to tell the others?
She's going to get
the best care there is, Ash...
which means
we're going to need a lot of money.
But don't worry.
Albert is out there doing the business.
We'll be all right.
Katherine Winterborn
is an ogre of gargantuan amplitude.
You still think she's our mark?
She's rich, she's bitter...
and with the right key,
she'll open up like a butterfly.
Any boyfriends?
No. At least none that we know of.
That would be like
sleeping with a Nile crocodile.
Well, there's your in, then.
- You think?
- I know.
What, sex?
Wait. Please, just a second.
June means a lot to me. I proved that...
No, not you, Albie.
You're far too precious
to be sullied in that way.
Sorry, put your trousers on.
I'm ready and I'm bang up for it.
No, we don't send boys to do a man's job.
Right, Michael?
No, we do not.
Mickey can spin his charm
and still keep his trousers on.
It's his great gift.
You two go back to the spa,
get every piece of information you can.
I'll arrange a meeting
with Katherine Winterborn.
- I'm looking for Mr. Elliot.
- Mrs. Winterborn?
He said to say to meet you
in the Horizon Lounge.
- Where are the stairs?
- It's on the 40th floor, madam.
The lifts are just through there.
- Problem with the middle lift, I hear.
- Excuse me?
We got a report from the duty manager
that the left central lift was juddering.
News to me. Let me call him.
It'll take me five minutes.
I can't just leave it.
Either I fix it or I shut it down.
It's all the same to me, sir.
- Go on.
- All right.
Mrs. Winterborn.
Sorry.
What's happening?
Hello?
Sorry about this, sir.
I'll have you moving in a while.
Quick as you can, please.
I'm late for a meeting.
Isn't that always the way?
Are you all right?
No, I don't do lifts very well.
Can you hurry them, please?
Look, could you hurry it up?
There's a lady in here feeling unwell.
Yeah, it shouldn't be too long now.
- What are you doing?
- You're panicking.
Now look at me. Look into my eyes.
Think of nothing and no one else.
- I'm going to be sick.
- Look at me. Here.
Very good. Now, think, you're very calm.
You're by a river bank.
The sun is dappling the water.
The water is dark green and very cool.
There's a breeze playing with the rushes.
Can you hear it?
Yeah? Very good.
You're very calm as you sit by the bank
and splash your feet in the water.
Can you feel the cold water
against your skin?
Very good.
I spoke to the duty manager.
There was this American businessman
in New York. Or maybe it was Chicago.
Who called your company?
He got stuck in a lift for three hours.
No ventilation, no air con.
When they finally got him out,
his heart had exploded like a crisp packet.
Just hurry up and finish.
Terrible, it was.
We're moving.
We are. We're okay. Stay with me.
Now we're gonna stand up, okay?
You're doing very well.
Here we go. Very calm. Breathe in and out.
That's very good.
- You're gonna be all right now?
- Yes, thank you.
I think you owe this lady an apology.
As far as I'm concerned,
if I lose any money...
because I'm late for this meeting,
I will send you the bill.
You forgot this.
Thank you.
- And I wanted to thank you properly.
- There's no need, really.
I liked your river.
Your river.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
- You're late for your meeting.
- Yes.
Can I buy you dinner tonight
as a thank-you?
I'd be delighted.
Patrick Greene.
- Now get to your meeting.
- Yes.
Orange juice. Ice.
Mineral-water ice cubes?
Look, how many times
do I have to tell you people...
we don't do that anymore.
Sorry, sir, I didn't know.
Don't make me tell you again.
Sorry about that.
Can you imagine that?
Mineral-water ice cubes?
A bit extreme.
- Everything all right for you here?
- Great. Everything's perfect.
- You the manager?
- No, I'm the owner.
- Stephen Winterborn.
- Cindy Moore.
- Lovely place you've got here.
- Thank you.
Didn't I read somewhere...
you're floating your business
on the stock exchange?
You must read the very small print
on the financial pages.
I do.
Yeah, we're about to go public.
Exciting.
I hope so.
What do you do,
if you don't mind me asking?
I work in the city.
- Really? Doing what?
- Stephen.
- Nice to meet you, Miss Moore.
- Likewise.
Good luck with the launch.
- What can I get you?
- Dry martini.
- Sir?
- Where's your still water from?
- England, sir.
- Where in England?
- Herefordshire.
- That's fine.
No lemon. Two mineral-water ice cubes.
Sorry, sir, we only have regular ice cubes.
Made from water that has gone through
at least seven human beings.
No ice, thank you.
- What were you doing in Hong Kong?
- Making money...
seeing which way the wind would blow
once the Chinese took it back.
- Which way is it blowing?
- Back to London.
What about you?
What do you do, apart from panic in lifts?
- You don't know who I am?
- Should I?
Every other person in here would.
I'm the evil bitch
who killed her ex-husband's dog.
I read about that.
The press didn't like you very much,
did they?
I'll get over it, given time.
You can run away now.
I won't be offended.
I'm fine where I am. It's funny though.
- Don't you want to know about the dog?
- You'll tell me if you want to.
Excuse me, sir. Your table's ready.
When did you start at the spa?
Three months ago.
- Do you like it?
- It's all right.
You're pretty good with these balls.
You're a natural.
Let me get just a nice firm grip
on the end there.
So who got you in the job
in the first place?
Let me push it through. Ready?
- Wow.
- Together.
- You ask a lot of questions.
- Do I?
- Can I ask you one?
- Yeah, fire away.
What are you doing here?
Just playing with balls with you.
Where is your sister?
She's at the theater with some friends.
- That's a shame.
- Why?
She's pretty.
She could have come with us.
- Where are we going?
- To my place.
She wanted things I couldn't give her.
So she found someone who could.
- Hurts, doesn't it?
- Yeah, like a razor.
Kids?
She wouldn't have them
until I'd become what she wanted.
Would you take her back if she asked?
No, I could never give her
the things that she wants.
That wasn't the question.
You said it was funny. What's funny?
I told you about my business
and you said it was funny.
- Oh, yeah. A coincidence.
- Tell me.
It's business.
We don't want to talk business.
I like talking business.
I'm setting up a luxury hotel complex
in the southeast.
We're starting with one, but we'll create
a major chain within five years.
You sound very confident.
It's a hard business to get right.
Some British businessmen in Hong Kong
are ready to come home...
and this is what they want to do.
Each man has put in
a minimum stake of £100,000...
and my job is to get it up and running.
You'd be in direct competition
with my ex-husband.
- Sorry about that.
- Don't be. I think it's hilarious.
- How much more money do you need?
- We're all sorted.
- Fully funded?
- Why?
Thinking of irritating your ex-husband?
That would be petty, wouldn't it?
So he didn't serve your heart
on a bed of asparagus, huh?
No, not when she realized she could
use me to get back at her husband.
- She's an interesting woman.
- Interesting?
What did you talk about?
Life, love, exes.
You talked to her about Rachel?
- You don't even talk to us about her.
- She asked.
Where's Danny?
He's working
the Russian girl from the spa.
She must be interesting, too.
- Any hits yet, Ash?
- No, not yet.
You're going?
Yeah, I gotta go. I'm sorry.
Back to your sister.
Yeah, well, you know, she does worry.
Leave the money on the table.
Excuse me?
£200.
- You want money?
- Of course.
You're not a hooker, are you?
I don't mind what word you use.
Hang on a minute.
I thought we were, you know...
You thought what?
- I can't pay for sex.
- Why not?
Because I'm, you know...
I mean, you know, it's not...
I'm not a payer-for-sexer.
Well, you have to.
If you don't, they'll cut me.
Who will?
People I work for.
She's in.
- Where's she off to?
- Photograph of company directors.
She likes you.
I do believe we have her.
Let's begin stage two.
Well, what about that one?
Look at his shoes.
Handmade. Probably Jermyn Street.
It'll take too long to bleed him dry.
Well, I think... Oh, lovely.
What about that one?
Too pretty. Pretty girls don't play poker.
I can't believe you said that.
There's your mark.
Bohemian chic, roll-ups, odd socks.
Thinks he's an existentialist.
Be like shooting a fish in a bowl.
I'll see you later then.
Great. Just what we're looking for.
I've got the number
for the managing agents.
- Have you?
- Yes.
I hate managing agents, Brian.
- Do you?
- Yeah.
But I've decided I like you.
I like you very much.
Most architecture students are only
interested in building skyscrapers...
and monuments to corporate greed.
Me, I'm about bringing
great design to the underclass.
Absolutely. Yeah, they're crying out for it.
- What are you studying?
- I'm sort of... Psychology.
That's a bit bourgeois.
You might say that,
but, you know, know your enemy.
Through a study of human psychology...
I want to invert, to subvert,
the mind of the international capitalists.
Laugh away, but let me
just give you an example of that.
Never been very good with cards. I just...
It's the thing you got to clip...
Sorry, can't shuffle.
I'm gonna take five cards off the top here,
which I haven't seen. Fair enough.
But take them. Just hold onto them.
Put them in your hand, yeah?
From my knowledge of you,
I'm going to be able to tell...
just from reading your face,
which is the highest card...
in that hand. You ever been hypnotized?
Okay, just look at me.
Look at the cards, relax.
The first one is the highest.
Sometimes it takes a while.
Don't block me, all right? Look at me.
The third card is the highest one.
What you got left?
It does work sometimes,
but I'm in the first year.
You are pretty good with cards,
aren't you?
Now, don't lie to me, I can tell.
No, you're good.
We should have a game of...
What's it called? Poker.
Ready?
Right, I'm gonna put £20 down.
How many do you want?
I got £20.
- Time for me to get out.
- Check.
£20. In. I'll go for £10.
£20.
I'm out.
So what have you got?
Jack high.
Two pairs. Must be beginner's luck.
Which also means that you owe me
quite a lot of money.
You've cleaned me out, man.
So are you any good?
You know, like, being an architect?
The best in my year.
Look, I'll put my watch into the mix.
I don't want your watch.
I don't have anything else.
There must be something you have
that I want...
some skill that you possess that I don't.
Like what?
These are good, Danny.
He can't play cards,
but he does draw a lovely building.
Michael.
Here we go. Showtime.
I'd like to see Mr. Greene, please.
Do you have an appointment?
Just tell him
Mrs. Winterborn is here to see him.
That's quite all right, Sharon. Hello again.
Come this way.
I thought about you last night.
It was a good night, wasn't it?
Please have a seat.
I'd like to see your site.
- What for?
- Professional interest.
You know it's fully invested?
I'd still like to see your site.
Okay.
That would be the main accommodation
block there. Restaurant. Pool.
- Outdoor or indoor?
- One outdoor, one indoor...
both flanked by the treatment rooms.
It's a beautiful place.
Good road and rail access.
Airport in half an hour.
- Planning permission?
- All sorted.
- Staff?
- Already started headhunting.
Hard to find good people.
Yeah, but not impossible.
Your ex-husband has loads.
I'd like to see your architect.
- But we've discussed this...
- Indulge me.
Call it professional interest.
This way.
I'm impressed
you got planning permission.
- It wasn't easy.
- Bugger off! You're trespassing! Get off!
All I'd say is don't scrimp in the building
and development.
It's easy to do, the costs spiral...
and the marble effect looks nearly
as good as real marble. Don't do it.
And definitely don't cut costs
in the bedrooms.
They should be better than guests
have at home, not worse. Furnishings.
It will be unrivaled, I give you my word.
And on opening day
you can be my guest of honor.
I'd love to see his face when he finds out
I'm involved with the competition.
- He will be furious.
- But, Katherine, with all due respect...
you're not involved with the competition.
I'm going to invest £100,000
in your business.
You can't do that.
No one knows more about this than me.
Let me invest £100,000
and I'll be your consultant for free.
- Are you sure it's what you want?
- Positive.
I'll bring the papers over tomorrow.
- Two glasses of champagne, please.
- Okay.
Okay, furnishings.
Good. Would you put that
straight in the van?
Brian, thank you so much.
You're a star. Thank you for that.
I'm sorry I've wasted your time.
What made you change your mind?
For months now,
the first image in my head when I wake...
is of him and his little girlfriend,
smiling and laughing...
enjoying the lifestyle I've created.
I hate him. I want to hurt him.
Katherine, all you have to do...
But that's no way
to live the rest of my life.
Eaten away with anger and bitterness.
That way he wins again.
It would have been fun to work with you,
I'm sure of that...
but it would have been wrong for me.
I need a fresh start and this isn't it.
I'm sorry.
- I can't persuade you?
- I know you won't even try.
I hope it works out for you.
Thank you. I owe you a lot.
About the dog, it was hit by a car...
and was in great distress.
The vet said it should be put down,
and I made that decision.
So you let her walk away?
I gave her an out, like always.
This time she took it.
How hard did you try and persuade her?
That's the point.
A lot of work has gone into this, Michael.
People have expectations.
The great Mickey Bricks, falling for a mark.
It's a question of ethics.
- Ethics? What bloody ethics?
- Calm down.
- We're con men, for Christ's sake!
- We do not cheat honest people.
What about June?
We'll think of something. We always do.
- Fancy a Slow Comfortable Screw, Ash?
- No, thanks, Eddie.
Hello?
Sorry to phone you so late,
Mrs. Winterborn.
But I'm afraid that the midwife won't be
able to get out to you in the morning.
- What midwife?
- The district midwife.
I think you must have the wrong number.
Mrs. Stephen Winterborn.
Date of birth: September 13, 1983.
Your husband brought you in yesterday,
according to our records.
Mr. Winterborn no longer resides
at this address.
Never call this number again.
What made you change your mind?
When I was 23, I got pregnant.
It was a complete accident, unplanned.
But when I found out, I was so happy.
I told Stephen and he just said:
"But we're not going to have children.
We agreed."
And he was right.
We agreed the business would come first.
But I couldn't help feeling elated.
What happened?
We talked about it. He decided...
He bullied me until I had an abortion.
And that was that for me.
I'm sorry.
Now I hear he's got his little tart pregnant.
I'll give you £100,000 worth
of investment...
and you give me free rein over the spa.
I'll make it sparkle.
How did you find out she was pregnant?
I got a call by mistake from the hospital.
What time was this?
Late last night.
Don't go.
I have to.
I haven't signed the contract.
And you're not going to.
What do you mean, Patrick?
It's just not the right thing for you to do.
I don't understand.
Trust me on this.
When am I going to see you again?
Katherine,
you're never going to see me again.
Why?
That's just the way it has to be.
I'm sorry.
You're done with me, are you?
Stupid, bitter woman,
good for a shag and a few quid?
There is no hotel, Katherine.
No spa, no investors.
My name is not Patrick.
Some associates and myself
picked you out as a potential victim.
You were rich, bitter, angry, obsessed.
You were ripe to be plucked.
You're a con man.
But I will not let you be our mark.
I won't be a part of it.
Wait.
You were setting me up.
I was.
You con people for money,
that's what you're saying?
You're all the same, all of you.
£200,000.
- I'll give you £200,000.
- There is no spa.
Who said anything about a spa?
I want you to destroy my ex-husband.
A rat to catch a rat.
- Don't do this.
- £250,000. What's your price, scumbag?
I want to see him humiliated.
No, it's not what we do.
It's one thing
conning a nasty piece of work.
She is a nasty piece of work.
It's quite another
destroying a man's life for a fee.
What's this bloke like
she wants to destroy?
- He's all right. A bit full of himself, but...
- No, he's not pleasant, actually.
Forced her to have an abortion...
ran off with a younger model,
and promptly got her pregnant.
- You haven't even met him.
- I know his type.
Then why are we talking about it?
If he's that bad, he doesn't sound
any different from any other con.
And there's June to think about.
No, she wouldn't want us to do anything
just because of her.
I would, though.
Okay, then we have to move fast.
He's floating his business in two days.
- That's when we get him.
- What's the in?
I have no idea.
He's a very careful man, by all accounts.
- Women?
- He's had two in his whole life.
Revenge.
If we let him know
his wife is setting him up for a fall...
we might hook him in that way.
- I don't want her involved.
- Bloody hell, Mickey.
There must be something.
A hole in his wall.
We don't have very long to find it.
You wanna keep your voice down?
The great Danny Blue
paid for it with a Russian hooker.
- How much was it, Danny?
- Can you please just shut up?
Is it enough?
A prostitution racket
being run from his hotel spa?
Lt'll crucify him.
- So what do we do now?
- We need proof.
No. No way.
Come on, you did it once.
What's the difference?
I didn't know she was a hooker then, did I?
I've got a reputation to think of.
Every silver cane has a grubby end, Danny.
- And when needs must...
- You grab the grubby end, Danny boy.
- No.
- Danny, we need you.
If you can't get something concrete
from this woman...
this whole thing falls down.
All right.
But, I mean it, listen, no one is to know
anything about this.
Cheers, Danny.
Eddie, Danny pays for sex.
Taxi!
Hello!
Stephen Winterborn.
We met at one of my spas.
Oh, yeah. Hi. Of course.
The man who hates
mineral-water ice cubes.
- Which way are you heading?
- Back to the city.
Me, too. Shall we share the cab?
Yeah, okay.
You never told me
what you did in the city.
- You never asked.
- I did, actually.
I monitor new flotations. Advise my board
whether they should invest in them or not.
What would you advise your board
about me?
I don't know, really.
I normally follow much bigger
flotations than yours.
- No offense.
- None taken.
So where are you having the launch?
Went to a lovely one at the Docklands.
At the spa.
- Nice.
- You think I should have done more?
The most important thing
is the presentation.
I got my usual PR firm
to knock something up.
"Knock something up"?
Stephen, this is the most important
moment of your business life.
I've got a friend I think you should meet.
They're early.
The man is nothing short of astonishing.
Cindy, what on earth are you doing here?
I want you to meet my friend.
I've heard great things about you,
Mr. Cavendish.
I'm working.
Sorry. He's a brilliant PR, but very rude.
I want you to have a look
at Stephen's presentation.
Now why would I want to do that?
Because I'm asking you nicely.
... experience, which pampers
and relaxes...
while at the same time,
refreshes and energizes.
Each of our spas
offers a unique experience.
But the one thing they have in common
is indulgence.
Winterborns Hotel and Spas.
- What do you think?
- Very nice.
Reminds me of those ads you have
in provincial cinemas.
"The Taj Mahal Indian Restaurant,
just moments from this cinema."
Mr. Cavendish,
can't you just fizz it up a bit?
No, I don't do fizz.
Come on, Mr. Cavendish.
I'll make it worth your while.
So, what's up?
Open it.
So how many of the other girls
are turning tricks?
Only the Russian ones,
and the Lithuanians.
And the Ukrainian girl.
What would the management do
if they found out?
They're the ones who organized it.
You sure about that?
The Mafia guy in Moscow told me
there is a job opportunity in England...
- and I jumped at it.
- The Mafia?
So the management of the hotel
are making a lot of money out of you girls.
We have to service
at least three clients a week.
Service?
- Nervous?
- A bit.
Don't be. It's all under control.
And I hear it's a big year for you.
You and Charlotte.
The pitter-patter of tiny feet.
- Who told you that?
- I heard it on the grapevine.
It's highly unlikely. I've never been able
to have children. Excuse me.
For God's sake, be more bloody careful.
Lovely night for an execution.
- No doubts?
- He's a bastard.
This is how you deal with bastards.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello. Excuse me.
Hi. Thank you all for coming.
Tonight is the proudest night of my life...
to be surrounded by friends,
honored guests, and the woman I love.
It's taken a lot of people a lot of work
to get where we are tonight.
I want to thank them all
from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you very much, everybody.
But tonight is just a start,
the first step on a magnificent journey.
And now a short presentation. Enjoy.
Winterborns Hotel and Spas,
a retreat away from daily life.
- Something doesn't smell right.
- What is it?
Stephen said that he can't have children.
- No, he told her to have an abortion.
- I know. Somebody's lying.
Who? Yeah, speaking.
Wait, I can't hear you.
Yeah, I'm just gonna...
Bloke from the office says
he found the earring you lost.
- But I haven't lost an earring.
- She hasn't lost an earring.
Which one?
It's not the nice lady. It's the nasty lady.
Okay, thank you.
She went back to find the earring.
I was here earlier.
Well, at least I think I was.
I dropped an earring.
- There's nobody here.
- Where is everyone?
They were only here for a day.
Nice people, though.
She's known who we are all along.
This is how you deal with bastards.
Our beauty therapists
are specially trained.
From all corners of the former
Soviet Union, they come to work...
to work as prostitutes.
The Mafia guy in Moscow told me
there was a job opportunity in England...
and I jumped at it.
They cannot speak out without fear
of violence and punishment.
Winterborns, where exploitation...
- Ash, stop it.
- It's too late. I can't.
We're destroying an innocent man.
For Christ's sake,
will you stop the presentation?
I don't know anything about that.
I'll try and explain this as well as I can.
Watch the suit.
None of this is true.
I know nothing about this.
Excuse me.
How could you do this to me? Why?
Lovely night for an execution.
I owe you all an apology.
I let my guard down, and I got caught.
And the con man got conned.
Never let a mark get under your skin.
I know, and I'm sorry.
I promise you all
it will never happen again.
Anyway, what about the £250,000?
It's in our account, every penny.
- Have you told June?
- Yeah.
- Mickey, I just want to...
- No, Ash. She's family.
I spoke to my friendly DI in Vice...
told her Stephen Winterborn knew
nothing about the prostitution racket.
So at least he won't be charged.
Thanks, Stacie.
But they'll charge Mickey's woman
for running a brothel out of the spa.
Yeah, if they can find her.
She's emptied her accounts
and left the country.
What a woman.
She really had you fooled, didn't she?
- Okay, I made an error of judgment.
- Yes, you did.
"Say what you will, 'tis better to be left
"Than never to have loved"
William Congreve, playwright.
Oh, no.
- What is this, Eddie?
- The Congreve.
It's made with a lot of bitters.
Get it? Bitters. Bitter women.
I'd like to propose a toast.
- To living and learning.
- To falling in love with marks.
At least he didn't have to pay, Danny.
What's the toast, Ash?
To family.
That's disgusting.
English