My brothers and I
are the first vampires
in history...
The originals.
300 years ago,
we called New Orleans home.
Now we've returned,
drawn by a witch
who seeks to use my brother
Klaus' unborn child
as leverage in a brewing war...
Sabine, tell them
what you saw.
How was this
vision interpreted?
Your baby would bring
death to all witches.
But the quest for power
has turned brother
against brother,
leaving our family
more divided than ever.
Now that Elijah has returned,
can our family unite
to face this new threat?
So this
is what you do
the first time we're
back together
as a family...
Vampire book club.
Reading edifies
the mind, sister.
Isn't that right,
Elijah?
Yes. That's quite
right, Niklaus.
And what's
this business?
This is
a peace offering.
I presumed,
after so much time
desiccating in a coffin,
that my big brother
might be
a bit peckish.
So I explained
to my little brother
that forgiveness
cannot be bought.
I'd simply prefer to see
a change in behavior
that indicates contrition
and personal growth,
not this nonsense.
I couldn't very well
let her go to waste, could I?
Well, I suppose I'll
fetch the rubbish bin
because you're staining
a 200-year-old carpet.
Oh, yes.
"I was angry with my friend"
"I told my wrath,
"my wrath did end.
"I was angry with my foe:
"I told it not,
"my wrath did grow.
"And I water'd it in fears,
"night and morning
with my tears;
"and I sunned it with smiles,
"and with soft deceitful wiles.
"And it grew both
day and night,
"till it bore
an apple bright;
"and my foe beheld it shine,
"and he knew that it was mine,
"and into my garden stole
"when the night
had veil'd the pole:
"In the morning glad I see
my foe outstretch'd
beneath the tree."
Good morning.
Hey.
Listen. I know I'm
the only one
in this house that
actually drinks milk,
but would it kill
any of you
to make sure it's
on the grocery list?
Speaking of,
add bleach.
You know, I do hope
my siblings were
hospitable toward you
in my absence.
In your absence... as
you like to call it,
which is a
way-too-polite way
of saying that
your brother
put a dagger
in your heart...
I have been attacked by
French quarter vampires.
I've had to live in a house
with a secret dungeon
full of coffins, and I
was nearly murdered
by witches who are
convinced that my baby
is Lucifer.
Oh...
Milk.
They've been...
Fine...
Weirdly protective.
I know I have you
to thank for that.
I'm just happy
to see that you're
in one piece.
So back to the
murderous witches,
I have
some concerns.
They're evil,
and my life
is still magically
linked to Sophie Deveraux,
which is not comforting.
Yes. I think it's
time we took care
of that little
problem.
I'm all for it.
As soon as they're unlinked,
we get to leave this crap town.
Who do we have to kill?
Probably no one.
All right.
Potentially everyone.
I cook on that,
you know?
Don't get
cranky with me.
I'm the only witch
who still likes you.
Yeah. It's not like
I'm trying to save
the witch heritage
or anything.
They'll come around.
They're just
old-school and scared.
Scared of what,
your prophecy
about the hybrid baby?
Agnes and her
freak show minions
had a real field day
with that one.
Can't help
what I see, so...
Well, if you're psychic,
I'm Martha Stewart. Scooch.
What the...
Poetry about poisoned
apples from dead trees.
Looks like someone is worried
about impending daddyhood.
Nonsense.
Elijah is back.
In his presence,
all problems
turn to pixie dust
and float away.
Strange,
I don't recall any pixie dust
from the darkness of the coffin
I was recently forced to endure.
What are you doing with
mother's spell book?
Well, in exchange
for my freedom,
I promised the witch Davina
that I would share a few pages
from mother's grimoire.
It'll help her learn
to control her magic.
Thought we'd begin with
a little unlinking spell.
Wait. You want to
use her to unlink
Hayley from
Sophie Deveraux?
Sophie brought us to this town
under false pretenses.
She doesn't just want us to take
down Marcel and his minions.
She wants to take
Davina back.
So she yoked
her own cause to ours
with magic, threats,
and half-truths.
Well, no more.
As of now, our deal
with Sophie Deveraux
is null and void.
Niklaus, I need you
to come with me.
I need 5 minutes
alone with Davina.
You need to make certain
that I am not interrupted.
You stay here
and watch Hayley.
How did I get
elected supernanny?
More importantly,
who put him in charge?
Hey, is everything ok?
Can I get you
something?
Look. I know you want
a daylight ring, kid.
Little heads-up,
I got guys 80 years
ahead of you.
Noted. Sorry.
Wait.
You know
Klaus Mikaelson.
I asked you to give him
a lift home a couple times
to the palace
royale hotel, right?
Um, yeah,
the palace royale.
You see, I stopped by
his hotel to say sorry
about an argument
we had.
Turns out, he lied
about living there.
Lied.
Did you ever
hear the phrase
"uneasy is the head
and wears the crown"?
Uh, "lord of the rings"?
No. Shakespeare.
When I was a kid, Klaus
taught me how to read
with those plays,
always about some King
who gained the world
but lost his soul,
but now I get it.
See, when it's all
said and done,
you look around at
the empire you built.
The only thing that matters
is who you can trust.
There's got to be
somebody somewhere
that you can trust,
someone "to stick
"to you through
thick and thin...
To the bitter end."
Sam to Frodo,
"fellowship
of the ring."
There is someone.
We used to be
best friends.
I made you a promise.
Come in.
Bless me, father,
for I have sinned.
It's been, oh, a year
since I've had a good
conversation with you.
Camille.
You've been
avoiding me, Uncle K.
My favorite niece?
Never.
Don't lie.
This is a church.
Besides, I came about
professional advice...
About Sean.
The spell
of unknotting?
This is
a sanguinem knot.
The witches use it as
representational magic.
If you can unknot this
rope using that spell,
you'll have taken
an important step
towards control.
This is one of my
mother's later spells,
requires much more power
than you realize.
If you can
perform this,
I shall return
with another page...
Spell of your
choosing next time.
Only because
I'm a masochist,
I went by Sean's
grave today, and...
Damn it.
I was hoping to get that
cleaned up before you saw it.
I hope it didn't
upset you too much.
It didn't
bother me at all.
That's the problem.
That's why I'm here.
I've slept like a baby
every night this week,
even though
my twin brother hacked
9 priests to death
not two feet
from this confessional.
A guy I've been
seeing, Marcel,
has been blowing me off.
Whatever. I've gone on
two dates with the guy,
and I'm more upset
about that
than seeing
"murderer" scrawled
across my
brother's grave.
It's called
healing, Cami.
For month's
after the massacre,
I couldn't think
of anything else,
and then suddenly,
nothing.
I need to feel
that pain.
Without it, I feel
broken, empty,
like there's
someone to blame
and I'm letting them
get away with it.
Listen. If you
have found a way
to turn it off,
don't question it.
The only person
that is responsible
for Sean's behavior
is Sean.
Do you really
believe that?
Yes.
I do.
Let go of me.
Leave her be.
Killing me to get
to Klaus or his baby
is not the answer.
I'm not gonna
kill you, Sophie.
I was there
the day you were born.
I'm the last remaining
elder of our coven.
It is my duty
to protect our power,
and our power means nothing
if that baby grows another day.
Sabine's omen
was clear.
That baby will bring
death to us all.
What are you
gonna do?
Oh, God, no. No.
Agnes, no. No.
No! Don't you... aah!
Ah!
What
the hell was that?
Hell if I know.
It felt like
I was being stabbed.
What happened?
It was Agnes.
Her men
took Sophie.
Day one with you
in charge, brother,
and already the witch link
to Hayley
has been abducted
by zealots.
Where is she?
If I tell you
where Agnes is,
you'll just kill her.
Is it that
obvious?
Look. I know she's
a little cuckoo,
but she's our last
living elder.
That might not mean
a lot to you,
but it means
plenty to us.
The elders are
the only ones
who can do
important spells.
Like completing
the harvest ritual.
You know
about that?
Oh, you'd be astounded
by the things I know.
Allow me to
entertain you
with today's list
of priorities.
One, unlink
your friend Sophie
so she no longer
controls the fate
of the woman
carrying my child.
Two, convince
my brother to accept
my heartfelt
apologies
for some recently
dodgy behavior.
3, there is no 3.
I believe what my brother is
attempting to communicate here
is that neither the life
of this elder
nor the harvest ritual
nor your coven's
connection to magic
are of any relevance
to him whatsoever.
Now talk.
Thierry.
Marcel.
Come to punish
me again?
Someone asked
if there's anyone
I ever trusted.
I only came up
with one name...
You.
So, Thierry,
you and I
are gonna have
a little talk...
About Klaus Mikaelson.
It's time for
the demon spawn to snack.
I really wish you
wouldn't call her that.
I'm sorry. Have you
picked another name yet?
Take one. The plantation
is lousy with them.
How's your neck?
I feel fine,
which is weird.
I'm sure this
is Sophie-related.
Well, do me a favor and
don't die on my watch.
I'll never hear
the end of it.
You know, when I
first met you,
I thought you
were a real bitch.
What changed
your mind?
Oh, I still think
you're a bitch.
I've just grown
to like that about you.
Ha ha!
Well, that's sweet
of you to say.
Remember it
when I'm gone.
Gone? Where
are you going?
I only came to town
to make sure
everything was ok
with Elijah.
He's fine, and he
hasn't punished Klaus
for daggering him,
so, as usual,
they'll be thick
as thieves,
and I'll be left to
clean up the mess.
It's time for me
to fly the coop.
Oh.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Probably
morning sickness.
Oh, you're burning
up, actually.
Ah! Agnes stuck me
with a needle.
Ugh! Cursed objects were
created a long time ago.
We use them so we
don't get busted
by Marcel
for doing magic.
The one she used is called
the needle of sorrows.
It was cursed
in 1860, when...
Jump ahead
a few decades
and tell us
what it does, luv.
It has one purpose...
To kill a child in utero by
raising her blood temperature.
It's for
a miscarriage.
So how much time do
we have to fix this?
It'll do what it's meant to
by tonight's high tide,
and... believe me...
It will work.
I saw her use a similar object
on a kid who went mad
and killed a bunch
of priests.
I'd like to have a little
chat with this Agnes.
Where can I
find her?
You won't.
There are a thousand places she
could hole up to wait it out.
That's precisely why
we need to unlink you
from Hayley,
no more danger
towards her
or the child.
No. What?
If I am not linked
to Hayley,
I lose my
leverage on you.
We got a deal.
We are not on the same side,
Sophie Deveraux.
Our deal
no longer stands.
Does this mean
you're pardoning me?
Aw, you know
I can't do that.
You broke my
number-one rule.
You killed
a vampire, T.
I let that go, it'll
make me look weak.
I warned you
about Klaus.
Yeah. I should've
listened.
This guy has been
in my town for months
but hiding where
he lays his head at night.
What else is he hiding
is what I want to know.
I didn't listen
to you before,
but I sure as hell
am now.
Tell me about the night
that got you put in here,
and you might find yourself
out by Mardi Gras.
The night of the
masquerade party,
you sent us rousting
in the cauldron
to mess with
the witches.
So when Max
came in rousting,
he went right
for Katie's throat.
Now, you said to roust.
You didn't say to kill.
Now, he's a nightwalker.
I'm a daywalker.
I told him to stop,
and he wouldn't.
So I stopped him.
That night is on an
endless loop in my head.
I think Max
was compelled.
No. All my guys
are on vervain.
Not if Klaus
drained them.
Max went missing
for a couple of days
before the
rousting, right?
T., they found stuff
you and your girl
stole from me
in her shop.
Have you ever been
to the Jardin Gris?
You can't find
your own hand
in front of
your face in there,
and yet somehow
someone went in there,
and after a couple
of minutes,
they found
some stolen goods?
Go there,
see for yourself,
but I'm telling you,
besides Max,
somebody else
in the crew
had to be compelled.
Watch your back.
So a few tourists
go missing, ok.
We can spin it,
no problem,
but do you know
how rd it is to sell
a gas-leak story to
the city council
when a bunch
of church windows
magically explode?
Come on, Mr. mayor.
What is this,
an electoral debate?
Marcel overstepped.
I will handle it.
Easier
said than done.
Marcel is quite
the little warrior.
Uh-uh.
Aah!
Who
the hell are you?
My name is Klaus,
and you lot
are the faction...
Pillars of the community
who maintain
the city's
supernatural balance.
I should know.
I created this group,
only in my day,
it was a bunch of pirates
and corrupt politicians.
Looks like
nothing has changed.
One thing has.
It's exclusively
human now...
No vampires allowed,
especially no originals.
I haven't come
to join.
I've come to ask
this group to utilize
its considerable
resources
to find a witch elder
named Agnes.
All I need
is an address.
And why would we
want to help you?
What if I told you
that Agnes
was the answer
to a question
you've been asking since
you ran screaming
from this town,
that she is
the witch who hexed
your nephew Sean?
We'd need some time
to discuss...
I don't have time...
Nor do I like being
asked to wait.
You may have
all the vampires
in this town
cowering in fear,
but right now, you are
dealing with the humans,
and unless you plan
on killing all of us,
I politely suggest
you do as I say
and give us time
to discuss it.
You know, what I like
about you, father,
is, you're aware
of my reputation
and yet still
you stand tall
against me.
It's admirable.
You have one hour.
Track down that witch...
Cell phone records,
our guys in the 9th.
For the vampire?
No, for me.
Phesmatos, omnio ligor
coldate sangorium.
Stop fussing, will you?
Elijah will be here
any minute.
I feel like I've
been microwaved.
Hey, just because
you're carrying a baby
doesn't mean you get
to act like one.
I'm sure my little niece
is healing you up as we speak.
What the hell
is she doing here?
I'm trying to help.
Help?
You're the reason we're
in this bloody mess.
Why aren't we unlinked
with this witch
already, Elijah?
Rebekah, let her
do what she can.
I may know a way
to slow the fever down,
but I'm gonna need
some special herbs.
I'll text you
a list.
Fine. Happy to play
the fetch girl.
Isn't this
Katie's shop?
She leave you the
keys in her will,
or maybe it's just
help yourself Tuesday?
What are you
doing here?
You know, I read that
if you mix mugwort with sage,
you've got quite
the vampire repellant,
wards off even
the most resilient pest.
Why are you here?
Just keeping
my city safe
from thieves
and vandals,
but every time
I turn around,
I catch an original
with their hand
in the cookie jar.
Well, luckily for you,
your cookies
are the last thing
on my mind.
Oh, I can see that,
though I remember
a time when things
were different.
Maybe once.
Not anymore.
Camphor. Find it.
Going somewhere?
You're early.
Well, it's
a good thing I am.
You seem hell-bent
on enacting vengeance
all on your
lonesome.
The trouble is,
I need something
from Agnes before
you send her off
to meet her maker.
So I propose
we strike a deal.
Bring her here.
In exchange,
I'll even ensure
your niece Cami
remains safe.
Mm. I would
so hate for her
to get caught up
in all this.
This is outrageous.
What's the charge?
Please, Agnes.
You know that Marcel runs
the vampires in this town.
Who do you think
runs everything else?
I believe this is what
you're looking for.
Hello, Agnes.
You made a deal
with him?
After what you
did to Sean,
I'd deal with
the devil himself
just to see you
suffer.
You can't hurt me.
The entire witch
community
will turn
against you.
Enough!
Please. Enough.
I don't care
about witch politics.
I don't care about
your ridiculous,
little harvest ritual.
What I care about
is this trinket.
Undo its curse, or I'll show you
things worst than death.
Dark objects don't come
with an off switch.
The curse took root
in Sophie.
She's linked
to your devil child.
It's just
a matter of time.
She's burning up.
We need to do this now.
Get her
in the water.
I don't see how
a midnight swim
is supposed
to help.
Her temperature
is sky high,
and the water, with
the help of the herbs,
should cool us down.
Drink this.
You're gonna have to get
her heart rate down.
And how do you
suggest I do that?
Hold her.
It's a natural human remedy to slow the heart beating
and reduce
blood pressure.
This is never gonna work.
Davina will
break that link.
We just need time.
Phesmatos,
omnio ligata soluto.
Oh, I can't breathe.
Ok.
Take long,
deep breaths.
Hayley, look at me.
Long, deep breaths.
Just focus on the
sound of my voice.
You'll be ok.
Phesmatos, omnio ligata soluto.
Vingulia cordit...
Aah! Aah aah!
Agh!
I just felt it lift.
Oh...
Elijah.
Let's go.
Elijah...
As soon as your
brother finds out
that the link
is broken,
he'll kill Agnes.
I know you don't
owe me anything,
but please don't
let him kill her.
Elijah,
she's our only access
to the power
we need to survive.
Promise me that
you'll stop him.
It's me.
Where are you?
Don't hurt her.
I'll be there shortly.
I'll make you
one last promise.
I won't let my brother
kill Agnes.
I know you were just
using me to save your people,
but try it again,
I'll kill you.
The unlinking worked.
Maybe now we
can make plans...
Not now, Rebekah.
Can we discuss this
when I return?
I won't be here
when you return.
That sounds like
a good-bye.
I guess it is.
I only came
to New Orleans
to make sure you
were safe.
You are.
I thought that
I might be able
to convince you
to come with me,
but here you are,
rushing off
into whatever
Klaus and Marcel
and the witches
have cooked up,
and I finally
get it.
You'll never
leave this city.
leave Klaus.
Then you should stay.
This thing that you and
Klaus and Marcel have,
I want no part of it.
I just want to be free.
Well, then go.
You are free.
Rebekah...
Twice in one night.
To what do I owe
the pleasure?
Call me old-fashioned,
but I believe
farewells are best
in-person.
Got Elijah back,
and now you're both
gonna tuck tail
and run.
Smart girl.
Have a nice life.
He's staying,
and I'm not running.
I'm disembarking
a sinking ship.
People been saying
the city has been
sinking since
I was a boy.
It ain't
going anywhere,
but, hey, how about
one for the road?
Why, so you can
liquor me up
and convince me
to stay?
Why else did you
come here?
I came to say
good-bye.
Then say it.
Good riddance.
You're a piece
of work, Agnes,
but guess what.
I'm quite a piece
of work myself.
You know, I contemplated
leaving bits of you
artfully arranged
outside your family's tomb.
I thought it would leave
a fitting message.
Don't touch
my family.
Leave her.
I gave my word.
You tend to give
your word
at the most inopportune
times, brother.
We've been doing things
your way all day.
Come on.
Just one little snap,
and it's toodle-loo, Agnes.
She deserves it.
Niklaus, do not
make another move.
You have asked
for my forgiveness.
I will Grant you
that forgiveness,
but do not make me
break my word.
My noble brother.
How's that for
personal growth, eh?
Still, it is just like you
to spoil my fun.
Oh, not necessarily.
Agh!
Aah!
I swore you
would not die
by my brother's hand.
I said nothing
of my own.
No one hurts
my family and lives.
No one.
Mm.
I've been away from this
home almost 100 years,
and you haven't changed
a thing in my bedroom.
I guess I was holding out
hope that you'd come back to it,
although I imagine it's
not quite as comfortable
as those beds
at the palace royale.
It's plenty
comfortable.
I'm famished.
Nah. Apples
aren't my thing.
They were your favorite
once upon a time.
Yeah. They were.
Get my ass beat
if I ever ate them
working
on that plantation,
even spoiled ones.
Now they just
remind me of a time
when I couldn't
have things.
Well, now you can have
whatever you want.
Come with me.
And go where,
Rebekah?
Ever we want to.
We can build
a home together.
We can leave behind
Klaus and this city
and those orphan
Annie vampires.
Whoa, those orphan Annie
vampires are my family,
and this city
is my home.
It was my home,
too, once. I left.
You ran. I stayed.
This empire, it thrives
because of me,
and you want me
to run.
A man does not
run from his home.
I have lived
a lot longer
than you, marcellus.
I have seen kings
rise and fall.
If there is one thing
I know to be true,
it is that no matter how
big your empire becomes,
it is nothing
if you have no one
to share it with.
You want New Orleans,
have it.
I won't be here
to stop you.
Where is he?
I've been trying
to find him all day.
Marcel knows that
Niklaus lied
about where
he lives.
I'm not his damn
keeper, Josh.
Fine. Just tell him
to call me, please.
Ok.
Uh!
Oh! Ooh!
Oh, what the hell,
Josh?
Hi there.
I'm Marcel.
I don't think
we've met.
What are you
doing here?
Do you remember
the promise I made you?
Promise? No.
Yes.
You promised you'd find out
what happened to Sean.
And I kept my word.
Your twin brother's
behavior
was not born
of natural causes.
A witch hexed him to
commit those murders
and to kill himself.
I knew it.
I knew
he wasn't crazy.
Who is this witch?
Oh, you needn't trouble
yourself over her.
She has already paid for
her actions in blood.
What? Wait.
You killed somebody?
Well, I had a hand
in the matter, yeah.
Forgive me if I'm
a little surprised
by your reaction.
How the hell am I
supposed to react?
You just made me culpable
in a revenge murder
I never asked for.
I've been alive for
a thousand years,
and, I can assure you,
many people have died
for far less.
Besides, now you
can find comfort
in the truth.
The truth?
You compel me.
You make me at peace
with something
that should be
tearing me up inside.
I don't know how,
but I will undo
whatever the hell it is
you've done to me,
and when I do,
you're gonna wish
you never
laid eyes on me.
Hey...
Where you been?
Not still mad about our tiff
the other night, are you?
Water under the bridge.
Cami is all yours
if you're interested.
I'm feeling like now
is not the right time
for me to pursue
a relationship.
Life is all about
timing, you know?
Speaking of, I swung
by your place earlier
to commiserate
over a drink,
but I must've
just missed you.
Oh, the palace royale
didn't suit me.
I moved on
weeks ago.
No. I mean
your other place.
Hayley.
Interesting location
to put down your roots,
same plantation
where I was a slave.
I guess that's why you
never invited me over.
Well, how rude of me.
I'll speak to Elijah.
I'm sure he'll be
pleased to host
you and Davina
for the evening,
especially
after you were
so hospitable
to him.
Good.
I look forward to it.
Od-bye means
good-bye, Elijah.
Is she with you?
What the hell are
you talking about?
Hayley is gone.
Where is she?
What?
Marcel was here.