♪ We face the music together ♪
♪ And throw our hats
in the ring ♪
♪ Facing all kinds of weather ♪
♪ And not afraid of anything ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When the sun comes up,
we'll be on our way ♪
♪ And we don't care
where we land ♪
♪ And the waves are high,
but we won't turn round ♪
♪ 'Cause your hand
is in my hand ♪
♪ And, oh-oh ♪
♪ You make me feel invincible ♪
♪ 'Cause it's you and me ♪
♪ Through the wind and hail ♪
♪ Setting sail into the world ♪♪
[emcee] Welcome to the stage
Lil Parker!
[cheering and applause]
- [woman] Yeah!
- [barking]
- [whooping]
- Yeah!
How many of you saw my name
on the marquee outside
and thought I was a rapper?
- [laughter]
- It's okay. I forgive you.
But, anyway, tonight is
a real special night,
and it's for my ladies...
[cheering]
[whoops]
Shout-out to the ladies!
Yeah, so tonight
is not gonna be about
those relationships
with the fuckboys
who ruined us and, you know,
left us on the side of the road
for dead
and then threw that bitch back
in reverse
- and went over us again.
It's not...
- [laughter, gasping]
It's not about them tonight.
It's not about how we love
or-or don't love someone else.
It's about how we love
ourselves.
[cheering and applause]
[whistling]
And then how we fuck that shit
up, too. [chuckles]
[laughter]
[cheering and applause]
♪ ♪
[♪ A Tribe Called Quest:
"Find a Way"]
[Lil] Once upon a time,
when I was 12 years old,
my family moved to Brooklyn
from Cleveland, Ohio.
Sure, for most kids,
it would've definitely been
a culture shock.
Liliane, wait a sec.
[Lil] Which it was.
But in my fairy tale,
Brooklyn was so...
Cool.
Liliane, wait a second!
[screaming]
- [laughing]
- ♪ Got a leash and I wish ♪
- ♪ Just to rock you, miss,
make a militant move ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Peep my strategy,
end of the day, you're not ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
- ♪ Mad at me, not dealing
with nobody, now, that's what ♪
- ♪ Ugh ♪
- ♪ You told me, I said,
"Hey, yo, it's cool ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
- ♪ We can just be friendly,"
'cause, yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
♪ Picture me messing it up ♪
♪ Her mind not corrupt,
with the ill C-cups...
[Arturo] You were gonna say it.
Fact, you know what,
- I'm the man. I'll say it.
- Yeah. Yo.
[Arturo] 'Ey,
you a lesbian or somethin'?
[Moose] We ain't judgin'.
[Arturo] Nah, we ain't judgin'.
My favorite auntie a lesbian.
Yeah, she mad cool, dawg.
Mad cool.
So, lesbian or no lesbian?
No. I'm not a lesbian.
Why you always wearing pants
and ties and stuff then?
'Cause I like them.
And I look good in them.
Look, our bad.
You know, we kinda just assumed
- you was...
- See?
That's the thing
about assumptions.
When you assume,
you make a ass out of you.
- [gasping, chuckling]
- Damn. My bad.
Yo, look, we ain't mean to...
So neither one of you
need to be sweatin' what I wear.
- Okay?
- [gasping]
Or maybe y'all just jealous.
- What?
- Jealous?
My Jordans are fire.
And you need
to stop telling girls
how they can and cannot dress.
We're a little too young
to be dippin' our toes
- in misogyny, don't you think?
- [gasping, laughter]
- [Vince] Yo!
Sit your punk asses down.
[Arturo] She's the one
name-calling.
And your shoes
ain't even that fire, yo.
- They need a good cleaning.
- [Moose chuckling]
Damn. Let's get out of here.
[Moose] Goodbye, Queen.
Liliane, right?
Wrong. Lil.
Hi. I'm Vince.
Student council president.
I should've introduced myself
a week ago.
I'm Lil. [chuckles softly]
I can fight my own battles,
you know.
I can see that.
- ♪ ♪
- [Lil sighs]
And that was the moment
I fell in love
with Vincent D. Naravaez.
Our kids are going to be
so beautiful.
Mrs. Liliane Naravaez.
Liliane Parker-Naravaez.
I ain't want to just give up
my last name.
♪ ♪
- [♪ Nas: "I Know I Can"]
- ♪ Boys and girls, listen up ♪
♪ You can be anything
in the world ♪
♪ In God we trust,
an architect, doctor ♪
- ♪ Maybe an actress...
- Hey.
They think you're still mad
at them from earlier.
We're cool!
- We "F" with you, Ohio!
What are you listening to?
♪ Do drugs
and you came to sing ♪
♪ So if you gonna be the best ♪
♪ I'm-a tell you how,
put your hands...
- Old-school. I like it.
- ♪ I know I can ♪
♪ I know I can ♪
- Oh, no. [chuckles]
- ♪ Be what I wanna be ♪
Why are you so loud?
- ♪ If I work hard at it ♪
- ♪ I'll be where ♪
- ♪ I wanna be ♪
- ♪ I'll be where I wanna be ♪
- ♪ I know I can, I know I can ♪
- Nice.
♪ Be what I wanna be ♪
♪ Be what I wanna be ♪♪
You play?
Point guard. You?
Playa, let's go.
You ain't got it like that.
And, more importantly,
I'm trying to get
that pastrami sub
like yesterday.
Yeah, for real. We hungry, man!
[Arturo] Corny ass.
Maybe we can play
a pickup game sometime.
Maybe.
[indistinct chatter]
Ohio!
Where you at, Ohio?!
Ohio, where are you?!
Hey!
Hey. [chuckles]
- Meet me at the park in ten.
- [♪ Santigold: "Creator"]
♪ All the attention
that it brings ♪
♪ Tell me no, I say yes,
I was chosen ♪
♪ And I will deliver
the explosion ♪
♪ Can't say
it's gonna get me far ♪
♪ Do no good
to say what you are ♪
♪ I run the streets
and I break up houses ♪
♪ River runs deep
and the flame devours it ♪
♪ Me, I'm a creator ♪
♪ Thrill is to make it up ♪
♪ The rules I break got me ♪
♪ A place up on the radar ♪
♪ Me, I'm a taker ♪
♪ Know what the stakes are ♪
♪ Can't roll it back,
it's understood ♪
♪ Got to play our cards ♪
♪ Me, I'm a creator ♪
♪ Thrill is to make it up ♪
♪ The rules I break got me
a place up on the radar ♪
♪ Me, I'm a taker ♪
♪ Know what the stakes are,
can't roll it back ♪
♪ It's understood,
got to play our cards ♪
♪ Sit tight,
I know what you are ♪
♪ Mad bright
but you ain't no star ♪
♪ Polish up
till you make it gleam ♪
♪ Your M.O.,
I know what you mean ♪
♪ I know what you here for now,
words out ♪
- No!
- ♪ You're an idea whore
though ♪
- ♪ Now, don't you crush on me ♪
- [chuckles]
♪ I'll see you
in your pipe dreams ♪
- Hey!
- ♪ Whether or not you know ♪
♪ It's true,
you're who they dictate to ♪
♪ That shit must hurt real bad ♪
♪ Fakin' what you wish you had ♪
♪ Me, I'm a creator,
thrill is to make it up ♪
- ♪ The rules I break
got me a place...
- You want to eat?
My mom can make us
some banana PB&Js.
♪ Know what the stakes are...
You're a Brooklyn kid now.
You got to eat like one.
And how do Brooklyn kids eat?
Let's go.
Race you.
[siren wailing in distance]
Here we are.
Wow.
[horns honking in distance]
And you're gonna want
one of these.
[chuckles]
I told you.
I call it sriracha surprise.
How'd you know I like sriracha?
I know a sriracha lover
when I see one.
[horns honking]
[chuckles]
[laughing]
You know what I want to be
when I grow up?
[Vince] What?
- A comedian.
- Definitely.
My mom loves Wanda... Skies?
[chuckles] Yeah. Wanda Sykes.
Want to hear a joke?
Always.
Why do rappers need umbrellas?
Why?
Fo' drizzle.
[chuckling]
That was a good one.
You're way funnier
than all the guys in our class.
[beep]
Oh. Hold on.
It's probably for my tía.
How y'all doin' tonight?
I said, how y'all doin' tonight?
[beep]
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
Jessica Peña just told Arturo
she likes me.
She wants to know
if I like her back.
Do you like her?
Yeah. Duh.
It's Jessica Peña.
Everybody likes Jessica Peña.
What should I do?
[sighs]
You should definitely tell her.
It's Jessica Peña.
Thanks, Lil. You're the best.
[click]
Jessica Peña.
How long was Sleeping Beauty out
before she got that kiss?
Hey, Lil, good job.
- Way to go, Lil.
- Great game, Lil.
What's up?
[girl] Go, Panthers!
♪ ♪
Hey.
Wow, it is getting long.
Long enough?
- Yes.
- Where you been hiding?
I'm getting ready
for next year, fool.
I mean, not everybody got
a full ride to Harvard.
Please. A scholarship
to Fordham's not nothing.
Plus, Mom and Dad
get to keep you close.
- Yeah.
- [bell ringing]
So...
- Prom. You going?
- No. No.
- Yes. Oh, no.
- I don't like... I hate dances.
- Come on, dance with me. Hey!
- What? No.
- [singing in Italian]
- Oh, my gosh.
- Ah!
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
Hey!
[continues singing in Italian]
♪ Da, la, la, la, la ♪♪
- Yeah.
- Come on, Ohio, it's our
last year together.
- You gotta go.
- [Arturo] Ayyo!
My mans, my mans!
Am I your A-1
since day one or what?
- What happened?
- First, answer the question.
Am I your A-1
since day one or what?
Come on, you're doing a lot.
It better be piping hot.
It's lukewarm, but this moment
is beautiful, though.
- Let me hear it, Vince.
- Bro,
you are my A-1 since day one.
You're damn right.
You want to know why?
- Why?
- [Moose] Love is the answer.
- Delfia and Ernesto,
they broke up.
- Mm-hmm.
- And?
- And word on the street is
it's because of Vince.
Yeah.
We kind of hooked up
over the weekend.
- [Arturo] Hoo, hoo!
- I was about to tell you.
[Moose] Ha, ha!
Damn, son!
Nah, nah, he's stealthy.
- [laughter]
- Told you.
- [bell ringing]
- Yo, man,
I told you. I knew it.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
I really was about to tell you.
What? Daffodil pop your cherry?
Listen, not all of us
are saving it for the one.
Yeah. But, you know,
not all of us is giving it away
to just anyone, either.
Ouch.
Let me get that.
Come on.
[Vince gasps]
[♪ Frank Ocean: "Pink + White"]
Why we never talk
about who you like at school?
- Mm, 'cause.
- 'Cause why?
- 'Cause.
- Don't say you don't like
anybody at school,
- either, 'cause I'll know
your ass is lying.
- 'Cause.
[chuckles]
"'Cause."
- Yellow?
- Thank you.
All right.
- Take a look.
- [gasps]
- I'm finished.
- Oh, shit.
- Good luck to you.
- [chuckles]
♪ Halfway on a slow move...
- I look dumb as fuck.
- Terrible is what it is.
Embarrassing.
I mean, I just hope
nobody see me with you tonight.
So, like, you don't think you
could be any more embarrassed
- than you are right now?
- Highly doubt it.
- Highly doubt it, do you?
- Mm-hmm.
Because...
- I'd really hate to do anything
to embarrass you even more!
- Hey!
- Vince!
- Everybody!
Everybody, listen up!
I have to let you know...
- Shut up!
- ...that the very last thing
- I want to do right now...
- Stop it!
- You are being...
- ...is be an embarrassment
- to my best friend, Lil.
- Shut...
- Liliane Elizabeth Parker!
- Vincent!
- She did this to me!
- No, I did not.
- I would never!
I would never!
[chuckles]
♪ It's all downhill from here ♪
♪ Remember life...
- She lives right here.
Right here.
- I would never do that.
You'll be...
[laughs]
♪ It all ends here ♪
♪ Say "what up" to Matthew ♪
♪ To Shoob ♪
♪ Say "what up" to Danny ♪
♪ Say "what up"
to life immortality ♪
[phone chimes]
♪ Bending up my Nikes ♪
♪ Running out the Melpomene,
nicotine ♪
- ♪ Stealing granny cigs ♪
- ♪ Take it easy ♪
♪ Gimme something sweet ♪
♪ Bitch,
I might like immortality ♪
♪ This is life,
life immortality ♪
♪ Bending up my Nikes,
running out the Melpomene...
[Vince] Hey.
There she is.
- ♪ Take it easy ♪
- ♪ Gimme something sweet ♪♪
[chuckling]
[Vince chuckles]
- Wow.
- Yeah?
[chuckles]
[laughs]
See, since you
skipped out on prom,
I thought you were gonna try
to skip out on this, too.
[exhales]
Come here.
Oh.
There you go.
Cheers.
Mmm.
Yeah. I already told you.
I don't like dances.
But...
[clears throat]
[♪ Aaliyah: "At Your Best
(You are Love)"]
You are gonna dance with me
on our last night together
as seniors, right?
♪ Let me know ♪
[laughs]
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Let me know ♪
♪ Let me
know ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ Let me know ♪
♪ When I feel ♪
♪ What I feel ♪
♪ Sometimes it's hard
to tell you so ♪
[Lil chuckles]
♪ You may not be in the mood ♪
[both] ♪ To learn ♪
♪ What you think you know ♪
[Lil laughs]
- Hey.
- Oh...
- ♪ There are times ♪
- [Lil] Yes.
♪ When I find ♪
♪ You want to keep
yourself from me ♪
♪ When I don't have
the strength ♪
♪ I'm just a mirror...
- What?
- This is really nice.
Yeah.
And I just...
I've been wanting to tell you...
- [clamoring]
- What's good?!
Senior class 2014!
- [Moose] Yeah!
- [whooping]
- [laughing]
- Yes!
Oh...
[laughs] Yeah.
- Oh, damn.
- Mmm.
[Vince] What's up?
[Arturo] Mm-hmm.
- Yo, you better hurry up,
my guy.
- Watch out.
The car for the after-party
waiting for your punk ass
downstairs.
Oh, shit.
We gotta go.
♪ La, ha-ha...
[Lil] I have the dress,
I have the slippers,
but where is my
happily ever after?
You coming?
All right, I'm coming.
- Ha-ha!
- [whooping]
[laughter]
[Lil] My plan
would have to wait.
- [passionate moaning]
- [♪ Jasmine Villegas:
"Judgment"]
♪ Contrary to what
you think of me ♪
♪ I value my privacy ♪
♪ I ain't gonna reveal
everything ♪
- [breathing heavily]
- ♪ To satisfy your
thirsty needs ♪
♪ Ooh, you can keep
your rumors...
Thank you.
Ah, thank you.
♪ Think you know
but you don't know ♪
♪ You don't know ♪
♪ Just passing judgment, yeah...
Thank you.
That was great.
The pleasure was mine.
♪ Check your assumptions ♪
- ♪ You got me
on your timeline ♪
- [phone chimes]
- ♪ You think you know
what I'm like ♪♪
- Oh, shit.
We gotta go.
You still want to
go up tonight, right?
First time, you should probably
be there early, right?
Right.
I'm-I'm nervous.
I mean, I'm excited,
but I'm nervous.
[phone chimes]
Who is it?
It's no one.
[clears throat]
[phone chimes]
Ignore it.
[chuckles]
You're not gonna tell him?
He's having a tough time.
Let me know when
you know what you want.
[door opens]
- [phone chimes]
- [door slams]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[knocks on door]
Hey. Looking for Brooklyn?
He's in the shower.
What's up?
- [shower running]
- [Vince] Hey,
I'll be right out.
Mm.
[shower stops]
[shower curtain slides]
You're here.
- Hi. No. Ah-ha-ha!
- [cackling]
- Oh, my God.
- Oh!
- Vince, you old...
- You're here!
Oh, I'm here, I'm here.
- I thought we were studying.
- Look at you.
Brooklyn? Are they
calling you Brooklyn now?
- Are you wearing makeup?
- A little bit.
- Ah, you clean up nice.
- Shut up.
Oh, come here.
I missed you, Liliane.
Five more minutes.
[Lil chuckles]
So, what, all you need
is five minutes?
Oh, word?
[Vince laughs softly]
♪ ♪
Have you ever...
Not yet.
♪ ♪
[Lil chuckles]
[zipper opens]
[both laugh]
[laughs]
♪ ♪
[drawer closes]
- Ow.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
[both laughing]
[hip-hop music playing faintly
over headphones]
[laughs]
Mm, you're awake.
How long have you
been sitting there
biting your nails?
Uh, I got you peppermint tea.
- [clears throat]
- Okay.
Your member has certainly grown
since I pantsed you
in eighth grade.
- Do you remember that?
- [scoffs]
Mrs. Liverpool hated me.
I got detention for that.
[music continues
over headphones]
Okay, so last night wasn't
that great, but, you know,
not everybody can be
busting it open like Nicki Minaj
on your first go, right?
- Oh...
- What's wrong with you?
Huh?
Well, should I leave?
[sighs]
Oh, shit.
- I fucked up.
- Oh, my God.
Lil, look,
I don't want anything
to change between us.
I-I shouldn't have done that.
I messed up.
I got my wires crossed
and I-I didn't mean to do that.
- Got your wires crossed...
- You know what I mean,
all right?
I just meant that
you're special to me, Lil.
- You're my friend. Y-You...
- Friend? That's not what
I would call this, Vince.
This is exactly why I never
said anything about...
About what?
About how you feel
about me, Lil.
So, what, y-you just left me
hanging for eight years?
No. Lil, you're my best friend.
That's bullshit, Vince!
[whispers] That's bullshit.
Because I know you have
feelings for me.
Lil, I just don't feel...
Vince.
You are my best friend.
- Lil, wait, uh, that's...
- [roommate] How's it going?
- [Vince] That's not the...
- Hey, Vince. Lover boy.
- [door closes]
- Uh, yeah.
- Can we, can we talk?
For a minute? Please?
- [Lil] Move.
- I want you to move. Move!
- Okay.
And you know what?
Maybe I'm not Nicki Minaj,
but you no Magic Mike, neither.
Lil, wait. Stop. Lil.
Please? Lil, wait.
♪ ♪
[cheering over TV]
[Loni Love] And I'm-a
tell y'all something.
You know, women,
we're brainwashed.
We're brainwashed really early.
Why? Because of fairy tales.
Fairy tales. "Find your prince."
You're a princess,
find your prince.
But your prince is never
gonna be perfect,
but he'll change, maybe."
You don't believe me?
Beauty and the Beast.
- [laughter]
- Fall in love with that Beast.
"So what, he got a hump in his
back and his breath smell and...
he got one tooth.
He might turn into something."
- [laughs]
- Time for me to do
my own thing,
and not get caught up
in this fairy tale bullshit.
- Ladies, are you with me?
- [cheering over TV]
♪ ♪
Oh, excuse me. Sorry.
[distant laughter]
[♪ Yseult: "Corps,"
lyrics in French]
♪ ♪
Ah, fuck it.
[heart beating]
♪ ♪
Hi, my name is Lil Parker.
And I just, uh...
[exhales] Okay.
- Fuck it.
- [microphone feedback]
"Fuck it" is just-just literally
what I said to myself,
like, ten minutes ago...
[laughs softly]
...outside before I,
before I came in here.
Because I've never
done this before.
[people murmuring]
Sorry to anyone here
on a first date.
There won't be a second.
- [laughter]
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you for the drink.
[chuckles]
Can you get 'em a refill
on the house?
[whoops] So, show of hands,
how many of you have ever
had your heart ripped out
through your
motherfucking asshole...
...by the one true friend
you ever had?
Directly after
sexual intercourse?
- [audience groaning]
- And it was the first time,
too.
Yes.
I am about to fuck up
your night.
[laughter]
So why you not laughing?
My date was supposed to be here
but she ain't show up.
So what are you doing
after this?
- Uh, you?
- [laughter]
[applause]
♪ This time, this time,
this time ♪
♪ This time...
[squeals]
Ah!
Yeah! Yes!
♪ This time...
[cheering, applause]
[Lil] Brooklyn in the house!
How many of you saw my name
on the marquee outside
and thought I was a rapper?
It's the "Lil" part.
You know, "Lil Parker."
Uh, I could be a rapper, though.
I feel that.
♪ You want to,
with the ugh-ugh ♪
♪ You want to rub it
with the ugh, get, ugh ♪♪
You know?
[tongue clicks]
Man, fuck y'all. Y'all sexist.
- [laughter]
- No, for real,
'cause if I was a dude,
I'd be up here talking about:
♪ Uh, in the pussy ♪
♪ In the, in the, ugh, ugh ♪♪
Y'all would've been like,
"Yeah!"
Y'all would've been standing up
out of y'all seats.
Don't play with me.
I know what it is.
[cheering, applause]
And I was like, "I'm going
to the Upper East Side,
because, like,
my vagina's depressed.
And I had my leg up in the air.
- Gary, hold the leg.
- [audience cheering]
Uh, and give me that.
- And hold another leg.
- [whooping, applause]
Don't worry,
I'll return to sender.
So I'm in this office,
and the mist is not going
directly at the labia.
Liby... La... The liby, labia?
W-What is it, Gary?
- Labia... Labia.
- [laughter]
Gary, if you make me fall,
I'm-a have to sue you.
Yes.
Let's give it up for Gary!
[cheering, applause]
[laughs]
♪ You got the juice,
I'm in the zone...
- Holy shit. Hi.
- Holy shit. You.
- Oh, my God.
- Thank you, thank you. Hi.
Wow, you were
fucking incredible, Lil.
- Wasn't she?
- She is incredible.
Always has been, Vince.
♪ I got to know some things...
Lil, I'm going to get myself
a drink.
♪ Pop the, oh, champagne,
shorty, watch it flow...
Big sis is watching.
- Awkward.
- Thanks so much.
That was so fun.
Oh, thank you, thank you. Bye.
♪ Party then, harder,
got to get the Cristal...
[chuckles] Well, this is,
this is a surprise.
For sure. Yeah.
Well, I-I've been, um,
doing this for about
a year or so.
Yeah. Feel-Feels
really good, so...
I'm-I'm just sort of seeing
what happens with it.
What's there to see?
I mean, you're fucking doing it.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
- I'm so proud of you.
Well, what-what about you?
Like, it-it's been forever.
- Yeah, it has.
- [woman] Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's okay.
I get it, though.
Yeah, I'm back for, uh,
a-a couple weeks
and then I, I actually head
overseas for a little bit.
- R-Really?
- Yeah. Prague.
- Prague?
- Yeah. It's this...
like, fancy study abroad thing.
I get to, like, teach kids
and travel Europe and shit.
Well, congratu-fucking-lations,
Vince. That's nice.
- Hey, nice job. That was great.
- Oh. Thank you. Bye.
♪ All night,
be gone till we get back ♪
♪ Yeah, you and me, girl,
we get it...
I miss you, Ohio.
♪ I get the bag,
you got the juice...
I miss us.
♪ I got it on,
tell me who's who...
Should we...
Do you want to...?
♪ Gone till we get back,
yeah, you and me, girl...
- [laughs]
- But you know
the coldest part, though?
- What?
- You had your sister
block me, too?
- I sure did. And she still
hates your ass, too.
- Damn.
- Yeah, she really does.
- [laughs]
Hey, Lil?
- You know I never meant to...
- Vince.
I know. I'm okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
[exhales]
It seem like it was good
for both of us.
- Yeah?
- Not seeing each other.
Yeah.
I had a chance
to grow up a little.
And find my own way for once.
I hated it, though.
[chuckles]
God...
It's so crazy I finally
get to be around you again,
and I have to leave
in three weeks.
Well, then, I guess we got three
weeks to be best friends again.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hey. You down?
Yeah, I'm down.
What's this?
Who did this to you?
What you mean,
who did this to me?
Yeah. I mean, come on.
- Right? The kicks...
- Who did all of this to you?
I mean, look.
Look, it's called
the glow-up, okay?
- Yeah.
- Check me out.
- I'm not kidding,
you look really good.
- Thanks.
- You look really good.
- Thank you.
When I was little, I dreamed
of spending my whole life
with Vincent D. Naravaez,
and now that I think about it,
the plan kind of worked.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
♪ Oh, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, yeah ♪♪