Previously on "The Originals."
This town was my home once.
I want it back.
You are free. Go far away
and never come back.
Every werewolf will be a bundle of fur
and sharp teeth tonight whilst your
cursed crescent clan will be...
Human but only for a few hours
and won't be again
until the next full moon.
I'm Jackson.
You're the wolf who's been watching me.
You were supposed to be my wife.
It's herbs ground into paste.
On the next full moon when your
people become human, feed it to them.
The curse will be broken.
Kieran, voice-over: I've been hexed,
and I don't know how long I have.
The ancestors said
they'd do horrible things
to me if I misused my magic again.
Marcellus, you are here by exiled.
If I so much as find a trace of
you, it will not end well for you.
Nicely done, brother.
You're beginning to sound like me.
Klaus, voice-over:
They say the passage of time
will heal all wounds...
But the greater the loss,
the deeper the cut...
[Rustling]
And the more difficult the
process to become whole again.
The pain may fade, but scars serve
as a reminder of our suffering
and make the bearer all the more
resolved never to be wounded again.
So as time moves along,
we get lost in distractions,
act out in frustration...
React with aggression...
Give in to anger.
All the while, we plot and plan
as we wait to grow stronger.
Then before we even realize
that so much time has passed...
We are healed, ready
to begin anew.
Spoken like a man who's
made peace with his demons.
My demons are dead
or chased off.
Yes, apart from the one lingering
monster with whom you share a bed.
I trust you can find your
clothing and the door.
You do recall that... woman
tortured our sister?
She also revealed the truth
about our sister's treachery.
And as a consequence,
Rebekah is gone forever.
A desire which she apparently
harbored for quite some time!
Niklaus, it has been a month.
Now I feel our sister's
loss as deeply as you,
but you must stop distracting yourself
with this ridiculous
behavior and channel it
into some kind of action.
Why must I exactly?
Because over the course
of Marcel's tenure,
the city grew accustomed
to having a King.
You wanted this throne.
Now you must accept the
responsibility that accompanies that.
Apologies, but I'm rather
ensconced in other pursuits.
If you can so easily neglect your home,
I wonder what will become
of your daughter.
Have you forgotten what it was like
to live beneath the threat of violence?
We must work together, Niklaus.
Let's make this city whole again.
Perhaps it is too broken to mend.
If you won't do anything, I will.
Kieran: St. Anne's has
long been neutral ground
in our city, so it's only fitting
that we gather in this chamber
at the behest of Elijah Mikaelson
to bring harmony
to this place we call home.
Thank you all for coming.
Elijah: Yes, thank
you, and welcome.
These are the rules of the city
according to Marcel Gerard...
Which of course no longer
apply because I am in charge.
You said if we came along that
we would get to run things by ourselves.
Never mentioned anything
about making yourself King.
While you were each
selected to represent
your own communities,
and I'll honor that.
However, issues which arise between
factions, they will come to me.
Now we are all
to some extent responsible
for the current chaos in the city.
However, you have one very, very
simple choice ahead of you here.
You can all play nicely
together, or you can leave.
Bay lavi à cette fleur.
Maintenent.
See, Davina?
It's easy.
All you have to do is try.
I am trying.
Trying and failing ever
since you came back.
When are you gonna stop being
such a bitch to me, Monique?
When you stop being weak.
You're supposed to be a harvest girl,
but maybe you don't belong here.
Maybe you never did.
[Shouting]
[Music playing]
Shouldn't you be out there
playing fight club
with the rest of the frat boys?
Nah. That's just for pecking order.
They already know who's the Alpha.
Ohh!
Next up!
[Cheering]
You got to try Tucker's ribs.
Then what? Then we're
gonna go play horseshoes?
Hey. Don't mock country living, darling.
Sorry. This is just
a lot more family fun
than I'm used to.
Well, maybe I can
help you get used to it.
Then all we got to do is just forget
that she spent half her life with humans
and the other half with vampires.
Ollie, back off.
It's ok. If the runt of the
litter has got something to say,
he should say it.
You know, word from the quarter is
your boy Elijah's holding
some kind of power summit.
Guess who wasn't invited.
Where did you hear this?
It doesn't matter.
The point is is that
we're stuck here living
in the swamp while
your vampire boyfriend's
deciding who gets what in the city,
but I guess that shows
how much respect he's got
for the werewolves, huh?
This is our city, too.
We should be able to go
wherever the hell we want.
We would consider it an act of war.
We're getting nowhere.
You vile creatures
cannot agree...
Elijah: Father, calm yourself, please.
Thank you.
Now returning
to the issue of boundaries,
you will all heed to the following.
Hayley: Are you serious?
You're dividing up the city, and the
werewolves don't even get a say?
What the hell is she doing here?
Diego, sit.
We are not dividing the city.
We're establishing boundaries...
No, Elijah!
There is not gonna be a peace
if the werewolves are excluded.
They want a seat at the table...
And if they don't get one,
I can guarantee that
you will all regret it.
[All talking at once]
Do you have any idea what it took
just to get those people
in one room together?
No, actually, I don't because I
didn't even know what you were doing
out here until someone else told me.
Tell me something, Elijah.
Did you leave the werewolves
out because of me?
I excluded them because they no
longer reside in the french quarter.
My immediate concern is to end
the mounting conflict here.
Now I can assure you once
this treaty is solidified
it will expand to include your people.
And until then, I should tell them what?
Sit, stay, roll over?
I would prefer that you remove
yourself from the process altogether.
Hayley, are you absolutely certain
that you shouldn't
return to the compound?
You think the baby belongs there?
You think that's where she'll be safe?
Is the bayou any better?
The wolves deserve a voice.
Give them one.
You know it's the right thing to do.
Genevieve: You should have
seen your brother's face
when Hayley walked in.
Crescent curse is broken then?
Do you believe this will actually work,
that we can finally have some
semblance of peace in this city?
Cami: I saw the light from the
courtyard and took a chance that...
You weren't with
a half-naked psychowitch.
Seems I gambled and lost.
10 minutes ago, I was fully naked.
Oh. Then you served your purpose.
Don't let me hold you up.
You O'Connells sure do
love to piss off witches.
Really? The woman tried to blackmail me
into stabbing you with the mystical
knife of excruciating pain.
Well, New Orleans breeds nothing
if not strange bedfellows,
but I assume you're not here to
question me on my leisure activities.
He's... deteriorating.
The pills, the meditation,
they're not working.
His lucidity's shrinking by the day.
A witch did this, a witch can undo it.
You seem supertight with Genevieve.
Maybe you could persuade her to help.
It won't do any good.
These hexes, they start with magic,
but as they take root, they alter
the very chemistry of the brain.
I'm sorry, Cami.
The damage is done.
I refuse to accept that, and
you would, too, if you had
any concept of family.
Josh.
Davina, what are you doing out here?
I would have met you
anywhere you wanted.
I mean, not anywhere Klaus or Marcel
would be, which could be pretty
much, you know, anywhere,
but you know what I mean.
Hey. You ok?
It's Monique.
She has no idea what I went
through when I was dead.
The ancestors hated me
for what I did with my magic.
I can't just start practicing again.
I knew I shouldn't have trusted
Marcel when he told me to go back.
I don't know how much
more of it I can take.
Thierry: On the outs
with the witch again?
I got it covered.
What was so important you dragged
me all the way out here?
I have a proposal.
I want you and all
the guys who walked out
on Klaus with you to join me.
Rounding up an army?
Can't take back the city without one.
You have nothing.
You have no weapons, no allies.
You go even close to the quarter,
and Elijah will kill you.
That's if Klaus doesn't get you first.
So, what, maybe I should hide
out in bucktown like you?
I think you're here because you
don't want to leave your home.
I sure as hell don't want to leave mine.
A battle is brewing, T, and while
everyone's busy choosing sides,
I'm gonna find a way to
take back our city, so...
You with me?
You were always great
with words, Marcel,
but it's gonna take more
than a big speech this time.
Is that really necessary?
The sickness, it's... It's overtaking
my inclination to forgive,
replacing it with one
thought that I could
barely contain at the summit...
"Kill every last one of them."
We'll figure it out.
I tried to figure it out with Sean,
but I was focused too much on that
instead of trying to stop him,
and I'm not...
I'm not gonna let
that happen to me.
You're an O'Connell.
They are going to ask you to
take my place at the table.
Don't. Just leave.
Just start over.
I'm not going anywhere as
long as there's still a chance.
How many times do I have to
tell you I can't be fixed?
And how many times do I have to
tell you I will not stop trying?
That is just stubbornness like...
like when you were a little girl.
You always had to be right.
You... you... you never listened.
Just that thick head of yours.
I prayed for you.
And I got no answer.
There is only blackness.
There is only death.
There's mine...
And yours.
Aah! Aah!
No, no, no!
Unh!
[Panting]
[Music playing]
Mr. Mikaelson.
Ms. Correa.
Please call me Francesca.
We can dispense with any
formalities, Ms. Correa.
I know exactly who you are.
You own the palace royale casino,
you're one of the city's
leading philanthropists,
and according to my sources,
you're the matriarch
to a rather sizeable
drug trafficking empire.
So why am I here?
Whatever you may think
of me, my family's been
a part of the human faction for years,
which makes me uniquely qualified
to take father Kieran's place.
You'll deal with me from now on.
Are you giving me a mandate?
No. Heh heh heh.
I'm giving you an ally.
I want peace just as much as you do.
My lifestyle, which I enjoy
very much, depends on it.
Yes, I can see you're highly motivated.
You know, I should mention,
I've already spoken
to the city's new mayor
and the chief of police and other...
Interested parties,
and I have their blessing.
I think you'll find it beneficial
to have me on your side,
even if it's just to prevent my less
civil brethren from lashing out in ways
that could prove painful to you.
Have a good night.
Not a fan of cerulean blue?
Not a fan of your
continued indifference.
Well, it's difficult trying to unite
a community that has a history
of mutual loathing.
Spare me the platitudes, Niklaus.
A perspective then.
If you want peace, you must
begin with the werewolves.
100 years ago, they had a
run at ruling this city.
As of late, all they've had is time
to watch their enemies
tear down that legacy.
All the more reason why their enemies
are reluctant to bring
them to the table.
Take a page from Bienville, brother.
If the table's the
obstacle, remove it.
Do you recall in 1720 the Governor's
desperation to secure our help
to build the cities first levees?
We sat with him and refused his offer,
and so he plied us with wine,
with corseted women, and
with raucous camaraderie
until he had his yes.
Are you suggesting that I throw a party?
[Music playing]
Woman: Laissez les bon temps roulez!
I'm impressed, brother.
Yes. Now if I can just keep them
from tearing one another to shreds.
Well, then for your sake, here's
to a spectacularly boring evening.
What's up, little man?
He's not even worth it.
Since you're preoccupied, I'll
intuit your flattering compliment.
Thank you. I think I look stunning, too.
I trust you've spent as much time
fortifying alliances as you clearly
have selecting that dress.
So you do notice me.
And, yes, I've already
settled the dispute
over the docks, I pacified the witches
with an increased share
in cemetery tours,
and I've given the crescents
a welcome back
to humanity gift in the form
of $100 chips to my casino.
So I think I deserve
some champagne, don't you?
Ahh.
You know, in light of Kieran's
deteriorating condition, the others
have acquiesced to your proposal.
You will represent the human faction
until he's ready to resume.
Then I suggest we make the most
of our limited time together.
[Gasps]
God.
Look. If you expect me to beg for
my life, that's not me anymore.
You think I'm here to kill you?
I'm here about Davina.
You heard about the summit.
If it falls apart,
each faction's gonna look
for leverage against the other ones.
Davina has to be able to defend herself,
even from her own people if need be.
She has to start doing magic again.
Why are you telling me?
Because someone has to tell her,
and she won't listen to me.
So, what, I tell her,
and you try to get her
back on your side, right,
go back to using her
as your personal weapon?
I don't care whose side she ends
up on, just that she's safe
because we both know
right now she isn't.
[Music playing]
Elijah: Diego.
You will be polite and welcoming.
Yeah. See, his people
killed my whole family.
My sister bled out on the
floor right next to me.
The only reason I'm standing here
is because Marcel came along and
turned me before I bled out, too.
So I'm telling you right now
I cannot be polite
and welcoming to that.
Diego, I understand your anger.
However, there are certain overtures
that need to be made if we are
to find a degree of peace.
Welcome to my home.
I wouldn't be here if Hayley
hadn't forced the issue.
Yes. It's rather unlikely
that you'll experience
an outpouring of kind sentiment here.
The vampires in particular
view you as...
Well, barbaric.
Hayley tells me that this peace
treaty is important to you.
Yes, it certainly is.
So much so, in fact,
that if anyone threatened
to dismantle what I'm building here,
I'd destroy everything they hold dear.
Have a wonderful evening.
Looking for your shrink?
Don't tell me you're
jealous of Cami, luv.
Just curious why you'd seek her company.
She seems so... ordinary.
Well, sometimes, ordinary
is a welcome respite.
I thought I was your respite.
Well, you are.
You are.
Promise me not another
thought about Cami.
Heh.
I'm so glad you accepted my invitation.
So is this where
the great Klaus Mikaelson
says something poignant
and snaps my neck?
I'm not here to kill you.
I'm here to offer you a gift.
Out of the kindness
of your vampire heart?
Our hearts are more similar
than you might realize.
You see, long before I evolved,
mine beat as a werewolf.
I know your power.
I know your burden.
I'm here to take the latter away.
You want to make me a hybrid.
I put my pack first, and I'm not
gonna let anything compromise
my family line, especially becoming
some bloodthirsty vampire parasite.
That pride...
That sense of loyalty,
well, that's exactly why I
haven't snapped your neck yet.
Well, if you're not gonna kill me,
then what the hell do you want?
Only to give you back the
city that was taken from you.
How was that for poignant?
Why would I trust someone
who's conspiring behind
his own brother's back?
I'm not trying to
undermine Elijah's venture.
I'm supporting his vision.
Vampires destroy life to survive,
witches are only as powerful
as their dead,
but the werewolves have thrived
because their strength
comes from family unity.
The safety of that unity is what
I want for my unborn child.
The painful truth is
vampires are the antithesis
of unity.
So, what, after a thousand years,
you're finally ready to embrace
the other half of your family tree?
Maybe the other half doesn't want you.
Oh, they will once they
return to the quarter.
You got a plan to back that up?
My mother was a very powerful witch.
I watched her craft all
manner of magical items,
but her most prized
possession was this ring.
I hadn't seen it for 1,000 years,
and then it turned up hanging
around the neck of a werewolf,
a direct descendant
of my biological father.
I believe she gave him this ring
as a way of freeing him.
How so?
Daylight rings shield
vampires from the sun,
so why not a moonlight ring to
protect werewolves from the curse?
Think about it...
No more breaking bones,
no more losing control
to the beast within.
What do I have to do?
[Music playing]
Hey.
You look, um...
Nervous, out of place,
short in this dress?
I was gonna say pretty.
I'm Oliver.
So what's the name of the girl
I'm about to ask to dance?
Her name is Monique.
[Sighs]
Would you care to dance?
You outdid yourself.
You even got Klaus to come out and play.
Yes. It seems that only
a sizeable soiree
is enough to tear my brother away
from his efforts at the easel.
That's never a good sign.
Klaus once told me that his painting
was a metaphor for control,
for achieving his vision
through sheer force of will.
Well, trustfully, I'd be shocked if he
didn't have at least a dozen or so
of those visions swarming around
in that insidious skull of his.
I do hope your daughter
inherits her mother's...
Everything.
It is weird being back here.
Not unpleasant I hope.
Not entirely.
Are you entirely sure you
shouldn't be here with us?
Why, Elijah?
Because you don't think it's
safe in big, bad wolf country?
I'm not gonna sit in a rocking chair
and knit booties, or haven't
you figured that out yet?
Can I have a minute, Hayley?
You can have it later.
Actually, he can have this dance.
Everything all right?
Yeah. Fine.
We were just discussing
the future of the city.
How can you be thinking
about the city right now?
I should have told you how
beautiful you look tonight.
Easy. Easy.
Julep minus the sugar and mint?
Hey.
I just saw Kieran.
He's not gonna hurt you again.
In fact, he won't
leave the attic at all.
I arranged for a little boundary spell.
You got a witch to help you?
I thought they hated you.
For you, I found one who doesn't.
Hey. What's wrong?
Nothing.
You're the first person
to help me in a month.
Kieran's the only family I have left.
Without him, I'm alone.
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm a little short
on family myself these days.
Hey. If there's anything I can do,
Cami, just... just let me know.
There is one thing.
We're out of bourbon.
[Music playing]
Hey, wolf boy.
Should have had them
put it in a bowl for you.
Well, yeah, if you want
me to crush your skull with it.
Please, boys. At least fight
over something interesting...
Me perhaps?
Naw. You don't want to get
involved with his kind.
See, they got this nasty little
habit of going berserk and ripping
innocent people to shreds.
No, no, no.
Ok. Look.
If my people wronged you in any
way, you have my condolences, ok?
Though I'd be surprised my kin
could choke them down,
being half as ugly as him.
This ends now.
I won't ask again.
Jackson: Oh, we'll end it all right.
Hayley: What's stopping you?
Kill him.
Go ahead, Elijah.
Do it.
I mean, it's not like
he doesn't deserve to die.
Shouldn't you intervene or something?
Why would I? This party
just got interesting.
I mean, it was Oliver
who handed Rebekah over
to the witches so
they could torture her,
but then again, wasn't it Diego who led
a werewolf massacre last month?
And the witches cursed the wolves,
while the humans stood back
and let it all happen,
so when you think about it,
everyone here deserves to die.
Are approaching a point?
My point, Elijah, is this.
If we can't all learn to get along,
if our families can't create some sort
of community, then what's the point?
Kill each other
and get it all over with.
Josh: You know, I've only
gotten roses once in my life.
Didn't even get to keep them.
Why not?
My first boyfriend,
my only boyfriend really,
gave them to me
for Valentine's Day senior year.
Tried to hide them in my bedroom,
but my parents found them.
You may not know it, but roses will
jam even the best paper shredders.
You know, I don't have
a home to go home to
or a family to go home to.
I used to hate myself for
that, but the thing is,
I don't really care
what they think anymore.
If your family doesn't like you
the way you are, screw them.
You got me and Cami,
even Marcel if you want.
Marcel used me.
He used you to fight the people
who were trying to kill you,
and, you know, he also saved
you from those people, so...
You don't have to trust the guy,
but he does love you.
And P.S., so do I.
Even if I don't have any magic?
All the power I had
was from the other harvest girls.
I don't even know
what I have without it.
Don't you owe it
to yourself to find out?
You're a witch, Davina.
You can't change your DNA
any more than I can,
so you might as well embrace it.
Bay lavi à cette fleur.
Maintenent.
Ohh.
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha! Ow! Oh!
Oh, oh, oh. Ha ha!
You ok?
Yeah. Just some bruises.
I'm still bruised.
Oh! "Bruise" is such a funny word.
It sounds like "booze."
Do we have any more booze?
Uh, no. I think we drank it all.
Oh.
You're a good friend, Marcel.
You should lie down.
I'm tired of being alone.
I am, too.
Not that that wasn't totally worth
it, but it can never happen again.
What if one of us craves another julep?
For whatever reason, Klaus trusts me,
and you're the person
he probably hates most right now.
He'd see it as a betrayal.
That wouldn't be good for either of us.
Marcel... It really
was totally worth it.
Yeah, it was.
[Music playing]
You said I had nothing.
You were wrong.
I have the same thing
I had when I rebuilt
this city from the ashes
the first time...
Everything to gain and nothing to lose.
I'm making inroads, allies, not
the least of which is Davina,
and I'm not leaving this roof
until I can count you in, too.
Besides, let's be honest, T,
I'm all you got.
I know those vampires, they
didn't just leave the compound.
They left New Orleans.
So us against the world?
We'll get a third and a fourth,
and pretty soon, we're
gonna have that army.
Klaus, voice-over: All change
begins with a plan...
The success of which
depends upon several things...
Depth of commitment...
Passion for one's cause...
Hey! To Hayley!
To Hayley!
Willingness to embrace a new path...
Determination to overcome
any obstacle...
And in some cases,
even making unnatural alliances.
You made a deal with Klaus Mikaelson?
I'd rather turn every full moon.
If Klaus is right,
this magic could do more
than just stop us from turning.
We could finally control what we are.
We could draw on all the strength,
all the speed, the raw power
of our werewolf form.
Our bite would be
lethal to vampires 24/7.
The humans who hunt us,
the witches who curse us,
the vampires who hate us, we
wouldn't just be their equals.
We'd be their superiors.
Sign it.
Why?
You've already done so on our behalf.
Brother, I'm not a fool.
It's clear to me you're
not as disinterested
as you'd like me to believe.
Sign, please.
If there is no peace between us,
then how can you expect
others to follow suit?
Fine.
If it will make you happy...
But I assure you this city's inhabitants
will not adhere to this agreement.
Well, you are welcome
to wager against me.
You will lose.
We'll see.