Sorry I'm Iate.
Did I miss anything?
Joey stuffing fifteen Oreos
in his mouth.
Fifteen?
Your personaI best!
Where were you?
On a date.
I met this girI on a train
going to a museum upstate.
-Which museum?
-How'd you meet her?
No. Answer his.
We were at the back of the train.
I sat near the door
so she'd have to pass by me. . .
. . .if she wanted to switch cars.
She was totaIIy at my mercy.
Were you so Iate because
you were burying this woman?
I'm Iate because
she Iives in Poughkeepsie.
She seems great,
but she's two and a haIf hours away.
How can she be great
if she's from Poughkeepsie?
That joke wouId have kiIIed
in AIbany.
Done! I did it.
Who's stupid now?
The One with the
GirI From Poughkeepsie
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Look! They're Iighting
the big Christmas tree tonight.
That paper is two weeks oId.
Who keeps Ieaving oId newspapers
in the trash?
I reaIIy wanted
to take Kathy to this.
At Ieast you have somebody
to miss stuff with.
I hate being aIone
this time of year.
Next it's VaIentine's Day. . .
. . .then my birthday, then bang!
Then they're Iighting
that damn tree again.
I want somebody!
You know, I want a man!
It doesn't even have to be
a big reIationship. Just a fIing!
I didn't think girIs ever
just wanted a fIing.
Let me teII you, it's been
a Iong time since I've been fIung.
I know what I'm giving you
for Christmas.
There are nice guys in my office.
Want me to set you up?
I've been singIe a Iong time.
Why haven't you offered before?
I have a girIfriend.
I'm happy.
I no Ionger go out of my way
to stop others from being happy.
No accountants.
And no one from " IegaI. "
I don't Iike boring jobs.
And Ross was what?
A Iion tamer?
What's wrong, Mon?
Everybody at work stiII hates me.
I was making headway.
Everyone was smiIing at me,
and then I get off work. . .
. . .and find out they wrote this
on my chef's hat.
Maybe they meant to write
"Quiet, Bitch. "
What's the matter?
Fine! Just trying to be nice.
I haven't been picked on this much
since kindergarten.
And they brought in someone from
junior high to do the see-saw with me.
They're trying to make me quit.
If it were any other job, I wouId.
But I've waited for this
my whoIe Iife.
Wait, you're the boss.
YeII at them. Or fire them!
I wouId Iove to, but I can't.
I'm not good at confrontation.
You know what you can do?
I read about this director,
Orson WeIIes. . .
. . .who, at the beginning, wouId
hire somebody just to fire them.
Then they wouId aII know who was boss.
I'm not doing anything.
Why not fire me?
It's a good idea.
Can you waiter?
Good enough to get fired.
AII right. You're hired!
That's why I got fired Iast week!
Does Orson WeIIes direct commerciaIs?
I say, Drew?
Are you seeing anybody right now?
I'm not asking for me.
I'm not gay.
I'm not asking you out.
I didn't think you were gay.
I do now.
My friend, RacheI,
wants to be set up.
I just got out of
a big reIationship.
I'm not Iooking to get serious.
That's okay. A fIing
might be aII right with her.
Is this " Hot RacheI" that
you took to the Christmas Party?
By the way, that is her fuII name.
Wow! I'm free for her.
Wait, I didn't say I wasn't free.
Let's taIk it over
at the Ranger game.
HoId on.
I just got a box of Cubans.
I'II bring them
by your office at five.
That's a IittIe Iater
than I usuaIIy stay, but sure.
Before the game, we couId enjoy
some eight-year-oId BasiI Haydens.
I don't know what that is,
but Iet's!
I'm writing a hoIiday song for everyone.
Do you want to hear it?
Happy Hanukkah, Monica
May your Christmas be snowy, Joey
Happy New Year, Chandler and Ross
Spin the dreidel, Rachel
Pheebs, that's great!
But you know,
RacheI doesn't rhyme with dreideI.
I know, but it's so hard.
Nothing rhymes with your stupid name!
What are you taIking about?
Lots of things rhyme with RacheI:
BageI, maiI, jaiI, baiI, cabIe.
MaypoIe.
AII good. Thanks.
Do you, maybe, have a nickname
that's easier to rhyme?
Didn't your dad used to caII you
"Pumpkin" ?
But did he ever caII you
"BudoIph" ?
HeIIo, chiIdren.
Have I got the 50 guys for you!
I showed them your picture.
Guys are throwing themseIves at me
and giving me stuff.
-Knicks tonight?
-Where are the seats?
Wherever! I've got 20.
WiII I Iike any of these guys?
You know, I'm going to. . .
. . .pIay the fieId a IittIe bit more.
Guys are signing over
their 401 Ks to me.
You work with robots?
One guy, Patrick, you'II Iike him.
He's nice, funny and a swimmer.
I Iike swimmers' bodies.
His dad made the magnetic strip
on credit cards.
I Iike credit cards!
I'm not bad at this!
-What does he do?
-He works in fine foods.
-You have a fine foods division?
-It's a big company. . . .
Now, wait a second.
You make food and robots?
No, the robots just work for them.
AII right, I'm going to work.
Does anybody have
a probIem with that?
Yeah, Iady. I do!
I got a probIem!
I'II give you a probIem!
What wiII you do?
Fire me?
You bet your ass I'II fire you!
See you Iater.
I shouId go.
I've got a date.
With who?
You know the girI
who Iives in Poughkeepsie?
Not her.
This is someone eIse.
I can't decide between the two.
The one from Poughkeepsie, though
two hours away, is pretty. . .
. . .reaIIy smart and a Iot of fun.
But this other girI,
she Iives right uptown.
She's just as pretty.
I guess she's smart.
She's not fun.
If she's no fun,
why date her at aII?
I want to give her a chance.
She Iives so cIose.
And, at the end of the date,
she said something that. . .
. . .if she was kidding,
was very funny.
If she wasn't kidding, she's not fun.
She's stupid and racist.
How was your first day
at the restaurant?
Damn!
What happened to your fancy jacket?
They baked it.
I can't take this anymore.
-I'm going to fire you tonight.
-You got it.
What are you doing?
You're stiII on fire there.
I think you got it!
ChandIer, you have
the best taste in men.
Like father, Iike son.
Patrick and I had such
a great time Iast night!
This couId, maybe, get serious.
I thought you weren't Iooking
for serious. Just a fIing?
WeII, you know, possibIy.
You didn't teII him that,
though, right?
You toId this guy that
I was Iooking for a fIing?
-You don't teII him that!
-Why not?
I'd be thriIIed if some hot girI--
I see.
You teIIing him I want a fIing
and me putting out. . .
. . .he's so going to get
the wrong idea!
Joey, couId you pass the cheese?
I'd prefer you didn't caII me Joey.
I thought it might be fun
to try out a cooI nickname.
Hey, Dragon!
Here's your tips
from Monday and Tuesday.
There's $300 in this one.
PeopIe get generous
around the hoIidays.
And it never hurts
to wear tight trousers.
CouId the waiters Iisten
to the speciaIs?
There's ChiIean sea bass
with a mango reIish--
Why is nobody writing these?
We can remember them.
Because you'II make up fake speciaIs
and make me cook them?
Sure, that too.
Forget the speciaIs for a minute.
Here's the thing. . . .
For the Iast two weeks I have. . .
. . .tried hard to create
a positive atmosphere.
Can't hear you!
Positive atmosphere.
But I've had it up to here.
From now on,
it is going to be my way. . .
. . .or the highway. AII right?
Does anybody have
a probIem with that?
Hey, new guy.
I said, does anybody
have a probIem with that?
No, ma'am.
He has a name. It's Dragon.
You want to know your name?
Check your hat.
We did the hat, right?
-What the heII just happened?
-I am so sorry.
I was going to do it.
But I was standing there
with $327 in one hand. . .
. . .and $238 in the other.
And I was thinking. . .
. . .it's been a Iong time since I had. . .
. . . $327 pIus $238!
We had a deaI! It's why you're here.
I've got to fire you!
And I got to pay rent!
How about you don't fire me.
Instead, I stay.
I gain their trust.
They'II Iisten to the nice things
I say about you.
What nice things?
Nothing yet. They hate you,
and I want to fit in.
Happy Hannukah, Chandler and Monica
Merry, merry--
You know what, Pheebs?
I'm not Jewish so. . . .
Ross doesn't decorate his tree
with fIoss. . .
. . .but he's not compIaining.
Bad dream?
I wasn't sIeeping.
What was Phoebe's song about?
It's the one with the cat.
I got to go.
I've got another date.
Did you pick one yet?
It turns out the one
from uptown was making a joke.
It was a different joke.
It wasn't that funny.
So I'm stiII torn.
You don't Iike the one from uptown.
And you're exhausted
from dating Poughkeepsie.
Just end them both!
Go to Poughkeepsie
and break up with her.
Then break up with uptown.
By the time you get home,
you're done!
You're right. Thank you.
I had a simiIar probIem
when I Iived in Prague.
-Prague?
-So much you don't know.
Patrick just ended things with me.
Did you or didn't you teII him
I wanted a serious reIationship?
I did! I absoIuteIy did!
You idiot!
I'm sure you're right.
But why?
You don't teII a guy that
you want a serious reIationship.
Now you scared him away!
I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
You shouId never be aIIowed
to taIk to peopIe!
I know, I know!
Now I'm right back where I started.
This sucks!
Being aIone sucks!
You'II meet somebody.
You're a great catch!
When I toId those guys about you,
I didn't have to Iie once.
ReaIIy?
You graduated magna cum Iaude, right?
It doesn't matter.
I got tickets to the Ranger game.
You want to come with me?
Cute guys in IittIe shorts?
Sure.
ActuaIIy, it's a hockey team.
Angry Canadians with no teeth.
That sounds fun too.
Thank you.
Have you ever been with a woman?
What is the matter with you?
There is no good time
to ask that question.
The station is Poughkeepsie.
Poughkeepsie!
Ross?
Wake up!
I need more swordfish.
-Can you get me more swordfish?
-I don't speak EngIish.
You just did.
I don't know what to teII you.
Fine.
Very funny.
Let me out, pIease.
Come on, I'm coId!
And covered in marinara sauce!
Let me out!
You found that handIe, did you?
-It's not funny.
-WeII, that's not true.
I'm a good person.
And I'm a good chef.
And I don't deserve to have
marinara sauce aII over me!
If you want me
to quit this bad then--
Chef GeIIer?
You know that speech you made?
I got a probIem with it!
-You do?
-You bet I do!
I just wasn't Iistening then,
that's aII.
If you want a probIem,
I'II give you a probIem!
What are you going to do?
Fire me?
You bet I'II fire you!
Get out of my kitchen!
Get out!
AII right.
Anybody eIse got a probIem?
How about you, chuckIes?
You think this is funny now?
What if I dance covered in sauce?
You think it's funny?
No, it's reaIIy good.
Take those saIads to tabIe four.
And you, get the swordfish!
And you!
Get a haircut!
Last stop, MontreaI.
The stop is MontreaI!
What?
I bet myseIf
that you had beautifuI eyes.
Now that I see them, I win!
We're at my stop.
WouId you Iike to have coffee?
Are we reaIIy in MontreaI?
Yes, we are.
So coffee?
Coffee sounds great.
Wait.
So you Iive in MontreaI?
No, but it's onIy a two-hour
ferry ride to Nova Scotia.
I shouId have thought
about my wife and kids. . .
. . .before I taIked back
to Chef GeIIer.
It wiII be a Iean Christmas
at the Dragon house this year.
Enough!
Lean, Iean, Iean!
Went to the store
Sat on Santa 's lap
Asked him to bring my friends
All kinds of crap
Said all you need is
To write them a song
Now you haven 't heard it yet
So don 't try to sing along
No, don 't sing along
Monica, Monica
Have a happy Hannukah
Saw Santa Claus
He said hello to Ross
And please tell Joey
Christmas will be snowy
And Rachel and Chandler
Happy hoIidays, everybody!