Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I am not impressed
with the talent in here tonight.
And the more I drink,
the less attractive they get.
I'm one scotch and soda away
from the Cantina scene in Star Wars.
What about those girls over there?
They're hot.
- They're not hot.
- Are you kidding?
I hated their guts
the second I saw them.
Which means they're hot.
In fact, I hated them almost
as much as I hated Robin
when I first met her.
- You hated me?
- A lot.
Barney, they're hot.
There is so much to teach you all.
You have just become victims of...
"the Cheerleader Effect".
Glad you asked.
The Cheerleader Effect is
when group of women seems hot
but only as a group.
Just like with cheerleaders.
They seem hot,
but take each one
of them individually?
Sled dogs.
That's insane.
Take a good,
hard look at each one of those girls.
Individually.
I don't know.
The one on the end is kind of cute.
Yeah, she really is.
And that, my friends,
is "The Cheerleader Effect".
Also known
as the Bridesmaid Paradox,
Sorority Girl Syndrome,
and for a brief window
in the mid-'90s,
the Spice Girls Conspiracy.
Scary Spice indeed.
Barney Stinson.
Okay. Got it.
Great, we'll be in touch.
What?
Apparently, I'm gonna be a dad.
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Arrow
You're gonna be a dad?
How did this happen?
It was just some girl I hook up
with a few weeks back.
She's not sure. She's gonna go
to the doctor in the morning.
Maybe it's a false alarm.
Maybe she's not pregnant.
No part of Barney Stinson does
anything less than 110%.
If one of my little Michael Phelpses
got loose, he's swimming for the gold.
Oh, this is a nightmare.
I don't want kids.
Who in their right mind
would ever want kids?
Now, when you turn 30
and you're in a couple,
a strange thing happens.
You start to see babies everywhere.
Oh, come on.
Yes, Marshall and Lily
were coming down with baby fever.
Their new neighbor weren't helping.
Did you lose a sock there,
little dude?
That is without a doubt
the cutest little thing
I've ever seen.
There's my little peanut.
That night they sat down
to have a serious
practical discussion
about having kids.
So, if we have a baby,
do you think you could
work fewer hours?
Doesn't matter, he's gonna be so cute,
I'm gonna eat him up on the first day.
Okay. But what about money?
We're still in a ton of debt.
We'll count our overdue bills
on his teenie tiny fingers.
Let's have a baby.
Oh, oh, right now? Oh, okay.
There was just one thing
in their way.
Scooch over. I TiVo'd The View.
And that thing happened to be unemployed
and sleeping on their couch.
So, Robin,
how's the job and
apartment search going?
You didn't hear?
I'm the lead anchor on CNN.
And I got a penthouse
overlooking Central Park made of gold.
Get your head out
of your ass, Marshall.
They realized if they were
going to start a family.
They had to plan ahead.
So, Robin, would you mind crashing
at Ted's tomorrow night?
I'm... cooking Marshall
a special dinner.
Just dinner. That's it.
Nothing else.
Fine. But you'd better not be
as uptight as these idiots
about me shooting beer cans
on the roof.
"It hurt my ears.
"The neighbors called the cops.
You almost hit me."
Enjoy her, Ted.
She's in a real good place right now.
God? It's me. Barney.
What up?
I know we don't talk much,
though a lot of girls call out
your name because of me.
Awesome.
But, God...
If you could get me out of this,
I swear I will never ever,
ever, ever, ever, ever, ever...
Oh, hang on, bro.
Go for Barney.
Really?
Great news! I'm not a father!
Congratulations, buddy.
This is the happiest moment
of my life, Marshall.
The way I feel
about not having kids?
I never knew I could love
something this much.
That's why I'm creating a holiday.
From now on, today will be known
as "Not a Father's Day."
- You're creating a holiday?
- Why not?
Everyone else gets a day:
mothers, fathers, bastilles.
Why can't there be a day for people
who are single and like it that way?
Now you just sound like
the chubby girl on Valentine's Day.
- Hello, Stinson.
- Hey, Nolan. How are the kids?
You ready for tonight, Eriksen?
Big merger.
That's between me and my wife, sir.
The meeting with Mr. Li. Tonight.
I thought
that was a breakfast meeting.
It is. Breakfast in China.
We're teleconferencing with the Chinese.
I'm counting on you, kid.
- Marshall?
- Hey, babe.
- It's breakfast time in China.
- Yeah, it is.
Not a euphemism. Look, I...
- Wait, what would that even mean?
- I don't know, hot buns, spicy pork?
There's something there.
You're not coming home tonight,
are you?
Are you shaking your head "no"?
I thought so.
Thank you, guys,
for coming over so fast.
Are you all right?
You sounded upset on the phone.
Marshall and I made
this big decision to have...
dinner. And I thought
I was ready to have... dinner.
But then he called and canceled,
and it got me thinking.
Is it too early for us to have...
dinner?
I had an early lunch,
so I'm ready for dinner.
- Dinner is a baby!
- Lily, that's horrible!
No, no, I need you guys to figure
something out for me.
What?
Are Marshall and I ready
to have a baby?
So, are Marshall and I ready
to have a baby or not?
Lily, we can't make this
decision for you. It's huge.
You know what else is huge?
Marshall's head.
That thing's the size
of a late August watermelon.
Marshall's baby coming
through there?
- What does Marshall think?
- Probably a lot
in that 1950s space helmet
of a head he's walking around with.
Marshall really excited.
But I think he only sees what's
cute about having a baby,
not what's hard about it.
Like the other day, while
Marshall was playing with baby Jeremy,
I was talking to Jeremy's mom.
Thanks so much for inviting us over.
I have not talked to another adult in,
like, weeks. Besides my husband.
But "It's your turn to change him"
and "Make him shut up"
really doesn't count
as conversation.
Sorry, I'm rambling.
I haven't gotten laid in seven months.
I just did it again!
Sleep deprivation!
Oh, wait, I'm not crying, am I?
I usually am.
I don't mean to complain.
Now I feel bad!
There's my little peanut!
Oh, I love you so much!
I'm going to be as strung out
as Charlotte.
Worse actually.
At least her husband works
from home.
I mean, he's a pot dealer,
but he's a very involved parent.
- Marshall will be a great dad.
- Marshall's always at the office,
and I'm afraid that
if we have a baby now,
all the work will fall on me.
You're just panicking
and focusing on the downside.
I think Lily's just being realistic.
See, this is good. This is why
I called you guys both over here.
Ted, you're pro kids.
Robin, you're against.
Counselors, opening statements.
Okay, I know you're afraid
that you're not ready.
But no one ever thinks
they're ready.
You just have to take the leap.
Parenthood will come naturally.
Of course you think
it comes naturally.
- You're basically a dad already.
- You're a total dad.
- What are you talking about?
- Ted, think about it.
You tell super corny dad jokes.
Shredded tweet!
You lecture us. Like when we broke
your stupid ship in a bottle.
I'm not angry.
I'm just disappointed.
- She did it!
- Shut up!
And you do that thing all dads
do with waitresses.
Hi, I'm Lori.
I'll be your waitress this evening.
Hi, Lori, I'm Ted.
I'll be your customer this evening.
Hey, Lori, before you go, tell me,
what do you get when you cross
a canary with a lawn mower? No hints.
She's right.
You maybe single and childless,
but you're totally a dorky dad.
I don't think I like your tone,
young lady.
Not a Father's Day is a hit!
Laraby and Finklestein are helping me
celebrate. Check it.
"World's Greatest Not A Dad" mugs.
There's...
"Who's Not Your Daddy?" t-shirts.
Both available
at Not-A-Father's-Day.com.
Check out the greeting cards.
"For everything you do for yourself,
For all the scotch upon your shelf,
"Your Porsche Carrera rules the freeway,
Here's wishing you
"an all night three-way.
Happy Not a Father's Day."
Check out the illustration.
It appears to be some sort
of Asian hooker.
Because on Not a Father's Day,
you get a Thai you'd actually wear.
Wordplay five!
She's really kicking your ass here.
Your only hope is to go negative.
Okay.
I'll tell you
why my opponent is saying all this.
Three words:
scared of...
- babies.
- What?
That is crazy.
- I am not.
- Yeah?
Remember that time you met
my cousin and her kid?
She is so cute!
Do you want to hold her?
Or the baby shower Lily threw
for her friend Erika?
- Are you letting that baby sniff you?
- I don't want to get bitten.
And don't forget about...
- Talking baby commercial?
- Talking baby commercial.
But you're not like that.
You love kids and they love you.
Yes, I'm loveable, pretty and wise,
but is it enough?
Look, it all comes down
to one word: "you".
Are you ready to put
your own dreams on the back burner?
Grad school,
teaching art at the college level?
Look, you need to focus on Project Lily
before you can start Project Baby.
If you don't,
you'll always regret it.
And that wouldn't be fair to you
or the baby.
What's that?
It's Jeremy's sock.
I'm having a baby.
But what about all the things
I just said?
But, but sock.
But what about Marshall
working all the time?
- But sock.
- But,
but Project Lily!
Little fishies on it.
We made all of these arguments,
and a sock is what makes
your decision for you?
I guess that was the sock-out punch,
huh, Robin?
Shut up, Dad.
You shut up, baby hater.
Babies are scary, okay?
They have giant eyes.
And then, come on, the soft spot?
If there's gonna be
a self-destruct button,
at least hide it somewhere it
won't accidentally get pressed.
Where's Lily?
- Did you drink any of this?
- Not a drop.
Me, neither.
Meeting in five minutes. You'd better
bring your A-game for Mr. Li.
That guy haunts my nightmares.
Anyway, have fun out there, kid.
Put a baby in me, Marshall.
I'm ready.
- Lily, what are you doing here?
- I'm ready. Tonight's the night.
Put your melon-headed spawn
in my belly.
What?
Come on, right now.
Baby me. I'm ready.
Oh, hey, look.
The guys in the next building
are waving at me.
Hello, gentlemen!
We're going to make a baby!
I can't believe we lost her.
This is exactly
why I'm never having kids.
You can't let them out of your sight
for even a second.
I can't find my file.
I pulled out "A" through "G."
They just sit there
with their stupid bottles.
They cry.
They spit up.
And that's why kids suck.
It is a good thing we broke up.
I forgot how totally psycho you are
- on the kids thing.
- I'm psycho?
Any time you even hear
the word "kids,"
you get two little lactation stains
on your shirt.
Thank God you're not a mom.
You are such an ice queen.
Any baby nursing from you
would get brain freeze.
Don't paint me as some sort of a freak
for wanting to remain independent.
There are normal people out there
who don't want to have kids.
Brother, lay your hand on this box
of condoms and repeat after me.
I, state the fake name
you give to women.
I, Johnny Banana.
Vow to always choose
wet T-shirts over wet diapers.
- Vow to always...
- Yeah, you're in great company there.
I'm gonna look for Lily
in the bathroom.
While I'm in there,
I'll grab you a tampon.
Great. When you're done shaking off
at the urinal,
maybe you could ask the wizard
to give you a heart.
You know what?
Maybe I should find somewhere else
- to stay this weekend.
- No argument here.
- Fine.
- Great.
Welcome
to our fraternity of non-paternity.
He is one of us.
Gentlemen, Mr. Li,
if you would all please open to page 5
of your merger documents.
I think the...
- What is it, Eriksen?
- Nothing.
I just think that you look...
very nice today.
What are you looking at?
I am looking at the future...
of our two companies,
and it looks very...
naked.
Would you excuse me just
for a brief second?
Did anyone else see the drunk chick?
You guys didn't have to...
It's a picture of me with no kids.
And there's macaroni glued
on the frame.
Guys, I love it.
Lily's not in there.
Your phone rang. I answered it.
I hope you don't mind.
Marshall's got Lily.
She's fine.
Oh, thank God.
What?
When I was putting your phone back,
and I found something in your bag.
I have a permit for that.
And the other thing was a gift.
This.
You stole Jeremy's sock.
No, I didn't.
I don't know how that got in there.
It must've fallen in. Weird!
- "Fallen in"?
- Or Lily put it in there as a joke.
That bitch be drunk.
I took it.
It's just...
so cute.
Sock.
Robin Scherbatsky, are you warming
to the idea of having children?
I don't know.
Maybe someday.
When I'm, like, 70.
Science will catch up.
Look, I'm just...
I'm confused lately. I'm unemployed.
I'm living on a couch.
It's been a rough couple of months
for both of us.
I have a spare bedroom. Why don't you
stay with me while you look for a place?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Thanks, Ted.
I already have some leads,
so it'll be one week,
two weeks tops.
And that's how your Aunt Robin
moved in with me.
I'm bored.
Let's go dancing.
Let's rob a liquor store!
We're not going anywhere. Whenever
we go somewhere when you're drunk,
you always fall asleep
as soon as we get in the...
We're going dancing!
We're gonna party all night long!
Can you circle the block a couple times
just to make sure she's really down?
Sure thing.
Latest Not A Father's Day
brainstorm:
a pregnancy test,
but instead of a little, blue line,
there's a little blue Barney
going like this.
Barney, Not A Father's Day is lame.
It's a holiday for losers.
What are you... talking about?
That's a great group of bros.
- It's the Cheerleader Effect.
- No, Ted.
That only works for chicks.
Take a good look at each one
of those guys individually.
These geniuses are not
childless by choice, my friend.
- Good night, Barney.
- Good night.
Sock.
- Do I smell chocolate chip pancakes?
- No, you smell "Chocolate chip
I'm sorry I was such
a drunk idiot" pancakes.
Is there any "Wish I hadn't puked
on your shirt" bacon?
There sure is.
Baby...
I'm so sorry about last night.
I know I was a mess.
I just started freaking out
about whether we're ready to be parents.
But you took such good care of me.
I know you're gonna be
- a great dad.
- I don't want to be a dad right now.
What?
Last night, it was just...
between balancing work
and drunk Baby Lily,
it was too much.
I'm just getting started at this job,
I'm working such long hours, I mean...
Look, I love you.
And I absolutely want
to have kids someday. I just...
I want to be ready for it.
Me, too.
Whenever we are ready,
I know you're going to be amazing.
You, too.
Do you want to go have
completely protected sex right now?
I do.
Do you want to finish
your bacon first?
You are the perfect woman.
"And the cat's in the cradle
and the silver spoon
"Little Boy Blue
and the Man on the Moon
"When you comin' home, Dad?
I don't know when
"We'll get together then, son
"I'll know we'll have
a good time then."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org