♪ Ah, push it ♪
[Colin clears throat]
[Colin groans]
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Talk to me.
♪ Oooh, baby, baby ♪
Hello.
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ Oooh, baby, baby ♪
Tell me what you're doing to me.
Um, we're gonna... We're having sex,
we're having intercourse.
And, uh...
Have I been bad?
I don't know, have you?
Oh, for God's sake, Colin!
Just call me a dirty bitch.
- I don't know if I want to. Uh...
- Say it.
Uh...
- Say it!
- Uh...
Okay! Uh, you're... you're...
you're a lovely little female dog.
You're lovely.
["Push It" by Salt-N-Pepa playing]
[chuckles]
♪ Ah, push it ♪
♪ P-p-p-push it ♪
♪ Push it ♪
[Morris] Parade, shun!
Slope arms!
General salute.
Present arms!
Slope arms!
Not my fault, sir. The rifle's broken.
We don't deal with excuses
in this establishment, Groff.
Keep practicing,
and try asking
some of your peers to help you.
I don't need help, sir.
We all need help sometimes, son.
Parade will turn to the left.
Left turn.
To your duties.
Fall out!
[Morris] Everyone inside.
Get your breakfast.
- Come on, man, give it...
- What's wrong?
This isn't funny,
just give me back the hat.
- What's wrong with him?
- [boy] Hey!
[Luke] Give me the hat.
- Give me the hat.
- Don't be a pussy, Luke. Oi, Groff!
[boys jeering]
[boy 2] Nice one, muppet!
Sorry.
Bad luck, new kid.
- War. [laughs]
- [Luke] Yeah, all right.
[alarm beeping]
[sighs]
[clears throat]
[Jakob singing indistinctly in the shower]
[knocking on door]
Um, I'm late for school.
[singing continues]
Yeah...
How long are you going to be?
[singing continues]
- [Jean] Morning.
- Has Jakob moved in?
No. Why?
Bathroom is free.
Darling, I've been looking through
your SRE textbook.
There is no mention
of female pleasure at all.
I was thinking of talking about it today
in assembly, what do you think?
[sighs] I don't know.
[Jean] Otis.
I'd like your opinion, please.
- Why?
- I've never worked with teenagers before,
and you are a teenager.
Yep, I'm a teenager who...
doesn't want their mother
talking about sex at his school.
There has been a sexual health crisis,
and it's my duty to help.
You know, he is right.
It is a bit strange.
[Otis] Mmm, I mean,
my mum's a sexual health expert
so it's not that strange, actually.
Which doesn't mean
you should have said yes.
Would you prefer to call me Mum
or Dr. Milburn at school?
Neither.
I'll be pretending you don't exist.
Otis.
[sighs] Okay. Just try and...
[blender whirring loudly]
Try and be a bit...
Try and be less intense.
It freaks people out.
And it's embarrassing.
I don't know, Mum, just be normal.
Try and be more relatable.
Whatever, just don't humiliate me.
Bye, darling. I'll see you later.
- You want a smoothie?
- [door closes]
No.
["The Queen of Hearts"
by Ezra Furman playing]
♪ And I watch you with your purse
From the adjacent coffee table ♪
♪ At the Starbucks they built
Inside my heart ♪
♪ When your makeup starts to run
You can see you're getting older ♪
♪ You can see your life has been hard ♪
♪ Your face is worn
Like an old playing card ♪
♪ The Queen of Hearts ♪
[sighs]
[Otis] My mum is everywhere.
It's like it's her mission
to ruin my life.
- Were you up all night wanking again?
- No.
I've got a handle on that, actually.
I didn't sleep much
because I've been doing research.
- Research?
- Yeah.
So, Ola and I were kissing the other night
and she kept guiding my hand down
to her... area.
- So I've been looking up...
- Fingering!
Don't yell "fingering," please.
- [laughs]
- But, yes,
she's coming over later,
and I think I'm fully prepared.
Well, Otis, it's a vagina.
It's not an exam.
Actually, it's very complicated.
- Okay.
- I've been learning about something
- called the clock technique.
- Oh, my God.
Otis,
I think you might be overthinking this.
She knows I'm a sex therapist now.
I need to get this right.
[indistinct chatter]
Why is Angel Man staring at me
like he's plotting my death?
I don't know. French people are intense.
[laughs]
- Morning, dickhead.
- Oh, hey.
- I've got an 8:30 and an 8:45.
- Okay.
Why... why do you look so clean?
- What does that mean?
- It's just an observation.
Your aptitude scheme, of course.
Very professional, Maeve.
Shut up.
Can you do a session after school today,
by the way?
Uh, I can't. I'm going to the fair.
I thought you hated rides.
Yeah, but Ola loves them, so...
Are you going to be there?
Funfairs are simply a distraction
from the inevitability of death.
Oh, I guess they are.
- Hmm.
- Have fun with the smart kids.
You look great.
- Oh, hey! How you doing?
- Hey. I'm good.
[Otis] This is nice. Shall we, uh...
Oh, hi, Jackson.
[clears throat]
Hey, I'm sorry about your hand.
- At least you don't have to swim anymore.
- What are you talking about?
- You said you didn't want to swim.
- Listen, Maeve,
you're not my girlfriend anymore,
all right?
So you don't need to pretend
that you care.
Whatever it is you thought I said,
you're wrong.
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
Don't worry. You're gonna be fine.
- May I sit here?
- Uh...
Yes.
Yeah, we'll find other seats.
No. No, no. I mean next to you.
Okay, sure.
Rahim, you may sit with us.
These people are insignificant.
No, I'm fine here. Thank you.
[Mr. Groff clears throat]
Good morning, Moordale.
Today we shall be hearing from
a sexual health expert
who is here to review
the school's sex education curriculum.
Please give Ms. Milburn...
a very warm welcome.
Hello.
My name is Dr. Milburn,
and I'm here to start an open conversation
about S-E-X.
Uh, sex.
We adults know
that some of you are having sex
because when we were your age,
some of us were having sex.
- [pupils chuckling]
- In fact, many of us still have sex.
I'm sure even Headmaster Groff
sometimes has sex.
And so, I would like you to tell me
what you would like
on your sex education curriculum.
Take control.
[microphone feedback]
Perhaps you'd like to know about
the female orgasm...
[laughter]
...or mutual masturbation.
[Jean] Or maybe you've always wondered,
is my labia a normal length?
[laughing]
What I'm saying is...
- ♪ Let's talk about sex, baby ♪
- [audience groans]
♪ Let's talk about you and me ♪
Didn't you wank off a courgette?
[audience laughing]
[audience chanting] Courgette! Courgette!
Courgette! Courgette!
Anyway...
[laughing]
...there will be an empty box
at reception.
If you have any questions,
it is anonymous,
so put anything in there
that you would like to see
- in the curriculum.
- Courgette wanker!
[audience laughing]
[Mr. Groff] Thank you very much, Moordale.
I'm sure we would like
to say thank you to Ms., uh...
Forgive me, Dr. Milburn, for her...
I don't understand why
everyone is laughing at this nice lady.
Uh, uh...
Because it's high school. [laughs]
[Mr. Groff] ...happening this evening,
um, available at all prices.
- Please be careful...
- I'm Rahim.
...nut allergies...
Uh, I'm Eric.
...said issues...
Goodbye, Eric.
Bye.
...nice place to go. I highly recommend
you, uh, you sign up to that.
What was that?
- Ah. Emily, howdy.
- Good morning, Mr. Hendricks.
Now I see where you get
your terrible sex therapy skills from.
Fancy putting in a question? [chuckles]
[laughs]
No. Nay. Thank you.
Um... [chuckles]
I'm usually the person who answers
the awkward questions.
- I'm Colin Hendricks.
- Oh...
- You're the SRE teacher.
- Yes.
[Jean] Mr. Groff?
I'd really like to observe
one of Colin's SRE classes, please.
As I keep saying Ms. Milburn,
our curriculum is quite satisfactory.
Well, if it's as...
satisfactory as you keep saying,
then you won't mind
if I sit in on one of the classes.
Of course not. [clears throat]
But I'm sure that any questions
that appear in this box
will very easily be answered
by Mr. Hendricks, isn't that right, Colin?
Uh...
Absolutely.
Yes. Yes.
I am, um, I'm-I'm a master of sex.
Very good.
Good day.
[door closes]
[Mr. Groff]
The school is right behind you, Jackson.
We will do everything in our power
to support your speedy recovery.
Thank you, sir.
However, your parents and I feel
it would be in your best interest
to be paired with an academic tutor
for the rest of term.
A peer.
But my... my grades are fine.
Well, you can get by on fine
when you're a star in the pool,
but when you're not... you have to work
as hard as everybody else.
Good morning, brains of the future.
I'm very happy to welcome Maeve Wiley
to the program.
Make her feel at home, please.
All right.
Let's read out our ten-years'-time essays.
[whispers] We have to read them out loud?
[Emily] Who wants to go first?
I strive for excellence
in everything I do.
The points I gain
from my extracurricular activities
will earn me a place in Oxbridge
where I will...
Compete in the IFBB
Bodybuilding Championships whilst...
Keeping me on track to become
the Prime Minister of the United Kingdom
by the age of 30, which will...
Land me an Erasmus scholarship
to NYU Film and Television School
and then I'll make
investigative documentaries using my...
Purple penis hands.
The Chronicles of Glenoxi
is an epic alien love comic book series
that will be made into
a global movie franchise
and eventually be screened in space.
Right, last but not least.
Maeve, you're up.
[clears throat] I left my essay at home,
Miss Sands. Sorry.
Maeve, this class is for people
who want to plan for their future
and optimize their opportunities.
Organizational skills are key.
Don't let it happen again.
All right, uh, thanks to Maeve,
you can all...
head off to lunch early.
Oh... eh, um, uh...
On a side note,
since Nigel moved back to Australia,
the Moordale Quiz Heads
are looking for a new member
to join the team and compete
at the National Student Quiz Championships
this year.
So, who's interested in joining
Viv, Dex and Steve
in representing their school?
Oh, right, all of you then?
Okay, well, I'll make my decision
by tomorrow. Off you go.
Man, I just don't get why
Maeve Wiley is in this class.
Are you Vivienne Odesanya?
Yeah, that's me, why?
- Jackson Marchetti.
- I know who you are.
Okay.
So, Headmaster Groff said
you'd tutor me this term?
[exhales]
Did he now?
Apparently, you're the smartest kid
in the school.
That's true, but I'm also busy.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Headmaster Groff said he'd give you
extra credit if you'd help me out.
And we don't actually have to do any work.
I've just got to keep Groff happy
until I'm back in the pool.
- Okay. Your first session's tonight.
- Yeah?
Yeah, but it's the fair tonight.
Listen, my schedule's organized
for optimum time management.
Take it or leave it.
Picnic tables, six o'clock.
Bring your maths homework,
and don't be late.
Should have seen this smug look
Ola gave me earlier.
I don't like her.
Why? She seems nice.
She's still hung up on Otis.
It's got nothing to do with Otis.
I'm over him.
- How you getting on with your form?
- [Aimee] Everyone has a thing except me.
I'm hoping this form
is gonna tell me what my thing is.
- Your thing?
- Yes, my thing.
You have your feminine books.
- Feminist.
- Steve has his Quiz Brains thing.
Quiz Heads.
So great being part of the team.
What's so good about it?
Well, facts are fun,
and if we get through to the final,
it's going to be a very big deal.
[Maeve] What's your form say?
It says I should be a baker.
Aims, I think it might be banker.
Baker's not on there.
[mouthing] Banker?
Hmm.
I think I'm going to stick with baker.
I do really like toast.
Wow.
Maeve thinks she's so scary
and revolutionary
just because she used to have pink hair.
Is it because she hangs out
with your boyfriend all the time?
No.
She's just not my kind of person.
Why? Do you think it's weird
that they run the sex clinic together?
Yes.
- So, how's it going with Otis?
- Good.
Yeah, well, kind of.
Yeah, we're taking things slow.
Which is fine.
I sometimes just wish
we'd move along a bit, you know.
Not overthink so much.
Has he touched your vagina?
Not yet.
He sort of hovers
and then loses his nerve.
It's... really frustrating.
- Just tell him what you want.
- I think it'll freak him out.
Human boys are so fragile.
[door opens]
- [man 1, laughing] Such an idiot.
- What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
Then what's so funny?
Luke spilled some water
and it looks like he's pissed himself.
You need to chill out, man.
Look...
grab it with your right...
and let your left slap it.
Took me ages to get it as well.
Is this okay?
- Yeah.
[exhales nervously]
[Otis] Okay.
[both chuckle]
[Otis] Yep.
Oh!
Oh. Ah.
[Otis, whispering] Twelve o'clock,
three o'clock, six o'clock, nine o'clock.
Did you say something?
No, sorry.
Are you enjoying it?
[Ola gasps]
- Then spread it. Back to 12 o'clock...
- [moans, chuckles]
...three o'clock, nine o'clock.
[Ola moaning]
[laughing]
- Ooh.
- Ooh?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
It was good?
It was... so nice.
Okay.
It was really, really bad.
He was moving his fingers
like he was dialing a 1920s telephone,
but really fast, with no rhythm.
And then he was kind of, like,
jabbing at the same time.
And then he kept looking at the clock
on his wall
like he was timing himself or something.
You need to tell him it was bad.
Uh-uh. It'll hurt his feelings.
Maybe it will be better next time?
I-I definitely have to tell him.
- [Eric] Did you do it?
- Uh-huh.
- [laughing]
- I know!
I knew you had
a freshly-fingered glow about you!
- Tell me everything.
- So...
I think I might have facilitated
a crescendo.
- The big O?
- Yeah.
- First time round?
I stuck to my clock technique,
and I don't know, bingo.
- My God.
- Orgasm town.
I feel like maybe fingering
is my sexual superpower or something.
Oh, dude, I'm so proud of you.
- Thanks, man.
- Let's go celebrate.
- What shall we do first?
- You don't think it was beginner's luck,
- do you?
- No.
No, no, no, no, no,
you're definitely Fingertron.
Oh, my God!
They have Crazy Jungle, come on.
[Otis grunts]
[Eric laughing]
Why am I here? I hate fairs.
You're here because
Steve is doing extra study
for your stupid altitude scheme.
You're my date.
- Aptitude scheme, Aimee.
- Yeah, that's what I said.
- Yeah.
- Can you win me a giant pig?
Hi.
Hey.
[exhales]
[man] And we have a winner.
I need to go find Otis.
That's the kind of competitive spirit
you should be bringing
to aptitude scheme, Maeve.
See you tomorrow in class.
I'll be right back.
Ms. Sands. Ms. Sands.
Um...
I did write the...
the ten-years'-time essay.
I didn't realize we had to read it out,
so I got embarrassed.
"In ten years' time, I want to live
in a house with big windows,"
I want the house to be large enough
to have a kitchen table with four chairs
but not too roomy
to ever feel the depth of my aloneness.
Because I'll probably be alone.
But I think aloneness won't feel
so all-consuming with windows
"that protect me from the world
but still let me watch it."
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I don't think I belong in the class.
You're a beautiful writer, Maeve.
You can have more expansive dreams
than four chairs and some windows.
Think about it.
[sighs]
[indistinct background chatter]
- What? What?
- You're really not good at this.
Have you got a problem with me
or something?
Look, uh, it's simple.
So this is hidden quadratics.
You need to substitute the Y...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...and then back substitute...
the X.
Oh. See, no one's ever explained it
to me like this before.
You dating Pythagoras, Jackson?
Nah, mate, we're just studying.
They were just being idiots.
It's fine.
Men who engage in sporting activities
at school
are statistically more likely
to work in menial jobs as adults.
Well, that's a bit harsh.
No, it's realistic.
Look, if your hand doesn't heal,
what is your backup plan?
And even if it does heal,
professional athletes
statistically peak at 21.
So it might be worth
acquiring some other skills.
Statistics are a real buzzkill,
you know that?
[Morris] Parade, shun!
Slope arms!
General salute!
Present arms!
Slope arms!
That...
is a real improvement, Groff.
To your duties.
Fall out!
- Well done, mate.
- [Luke] Good job, man.
- We're going on the Ferris wheel.
- Wind isn't good for my hair.
I don't think I was clear.
Rahim's going on the Ferris wheel,
so we're going on the Ferris wheel.
You can squeeze in with me and Anwar
for the next ride, Rahim.
No, thank you.
What do you mean why are we going on it?
It's fun.
It's the least safe
of any of the rides here.
- It's fun.
- How do you know it's fun?
Because I'm telling you that it's fun,
that's how I know.
[Otis] Oh, I am going to die.
- [Eric] Come on then.
- I'm coming, I'm coming.
- [ride rattling]
- [Otis] Ooh!
- What was that? That was really unsafe.
- Calm down.
- Eric. Ahh, I'm sorry. I feel vulnerable.
- Excuse me, Oatcake! Get back here!
[Otis] It'll be fine, you're fine.
- Hello.
- Hi. Hello.
[Ferris wheel music playing]
- Why won't he notice me?
- Do you think they do vegan hotdogs?
[Ruby exhales sharply]
Milburn, can I have a word, please?
Um...
It's about your... biology test.
What... What biology test, sir?
It's not really about a test.
There is no test. Listen...
I heard on the grapevine
that you deal with matters of the heart.
And I'm desperate for some advice.
Thing is, I have a friend
who speaks Spanish
and I can't understand her at all.
She says things like, "Hola...
[speaking broken Spanish]
...and... all I can hear is...
Shakira, Shakira.
I don't speak Spanish, sir.
I can't do dirty talk.
I find it mortifying.
Oh...
Well, uh...
sometimes when we learn new skills,
we can feel exposed.
Right? And you wouldn't go
to a foreign country
without some basic understanding
of the language.
So why don't you write a script
for yourself
and practice speaking the words
until they feel more comfortable?
It's about making an effort
to take little steps to meet her halfway.
Does that makes sense?
Yes.
Muchas gracias, maestro.
[chuckles]
- What shall we say, a pony?
- Ah... Uh...
- Or a monkey?
- Please don't pay me.
Let's not speak of this again.
You bet.
[ride hinges squeaking]
- So, what are the interesting landmarks...
- Um...
...around here?
There's nothing interesting
to see round here.
[laughs]
Very boring.
Sorry.
Only boring people get bored.
"As if you were on fire from within.
The moon lives
in the lining of your skin."
Uh, pardon?
- It's about finding beauty in the world.
- Oh.
- It's a poem by Pablo Neruda.
I don't know her.
[ride motor whirring]
- Goodbye.
- Uh, bye.
[Ola] I think you're jabbing the duck
too hard, Otis.
Maybe you should just try it
a bit softer...
a bit slower maybe.
Yes! See, I got... See.
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
Ta-da!
For you.
- There you go.
- [mouthing] Tell him.
Okay. Um, thank you.
I need to tell you something.
- Um...
- Sure.
Okay. Uh, I...
Uh, I really, really don't like...
goldfish.
Here you go.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah.
Okay, thanks.
Yeah.
Hey, do you wanna hang at mine?
- We could, you know...
- No.
I've got loads of homework
that I need to do.
- In fact, I need to go... now.
- Okay.
- But thank you so much for the bear. Dog.
- Thank you for the fish.
Okay, I'll see you. [clears throat]
[gasps]
My friend's boyfriend doesn't know
how to finger her properly.
I'm off duty, sorry.
He's really bad at it.
Tell your friend's boyfriend
to look up something called
the clock technique.
It looks a bit complicated at first,
granted,
but once you get it right,
the results are astounding.
It's you.
You're my friend's boyfriend.
You're bad at fingering.
Please don't tell Ola
I said anything, but...
sort it out?
[doorbell buzzing]
I'm ready to talk dirty.
[Colin gasps]
I'm gonna do nasty things to you.
- [Emily groans]
- Yeah.
I'm gonna get you so wet.
You're going to feel like
your water just broke.
- What?
- I'm gonna treat you so badly,
you'll be late for work tomorrow
and I'm gonna get you fired,
completely ruin your life.
[chuckles]
Wait that's not... Is that right?
Um...
[gasps]
[sighs]
Uh... this isn't working.
Isn't it?
[sighs]
[whispering]
Grab your stuff. Come with us.
[door opens]
[sniffs]
[Luke] Here you go. That'll keep you warm.
[Eli] Are you homesick yet?
I was proper homesick
when I first got here.
Yeah.
- He used to cry every night for his mummy.
- Did not.
[laughs]
I miss my mum a bit, but...
not my dad though. He's...
An arsehole?
Yep, my dad's a dick too.
My dad's a pussy.
A mean one.
[loudly]
Fuck all the mean dads.
Fuck 'em! [laughs]
Fuck all the dads.
- You got a girlfriend?
- Yep.
Her name's Aimee.
Big tits.
You a boob or an arse man?
I like elbows.
[laughing]
- I love you.
- [Sofia] Oh, hold on, darling.
I'm not training, Mum.
Got to keep on track.
You'll be swimming again
before you know it.
Well, what if I'm not?
You know, maybe I should get,
like, a new hobby or something.
But your hand is going to heal.
- Yeah.
- Yes?
- Okay.
Go on.
- Have a good day.
- Yeah, you too.
[indistinct chatter]
- Well, what do I do?
- [stammers]
You're kind of asking the wrong guy
about fingering, dude.
I don't know. Shit.
For you to read.
Thanks.
Thank you.
First, he looks at me
like he wants to kill me,
then he calls me boring,
and now he's giving me books.
- Maybe he wants to be your friend.
- Or maybe he's a teenage Ted Bundy.
This is serious, okay?
I need to find someone
who understands vaginas.
Your mum.
- I'm being serious.
- No, Otis, your mum is here.
Okay. All right.
Good luck, Fingertron.
[laughing]
[mutters to himself]
I'm branching out. You should audition.
[chuckles] That's not really my thing.
Thanks, though.
But you're acting all the time.
And you'll probably get a sword.
No hats.
Take it to your dorm.
Come on.
[Eli and Luke moaning]
I've still got your, uh, hat.
[moaning continues]
- We're not poofs or anything.
- Yeah, I was thinking about my girlfriend.
And I was thinking of your girlfriend,
you know... with the big tits.
I won't tell anyone.
I need your advice.
I'm pretty...
I'm bad at fingering. Really bad.
And my girlfriend is actively avoiding me.
Please help.
Okay.
But only because I pity you.
- Show me what you did then.
- I was about to eat that.
- You want me to...
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. Um...
Sorry.
Well, I...
I started at...
I started at 12 o'clock...
and went to three o'clock,
and then back down to six.
Oh, it's juicy. And then there was nine.
Congratulations, you can tell the time.
[stammers]
Then I carried on, clockwise,
then I flipped it anti-clockwise.
So you DJ-ed on her vag.
What's with the clock thing?
- It's a technique.
- It's weird.
Continue.
Well, I sort of continued that motion...
Oh, then I had a spread,
which was kind of like that. That's...
- And continued to apply pressure, and...
- Stop jabbing.
- It's not, I'm not really jabbing.
- I think I'd know, it's my orange.
- Actually, it's my orange.
- Shh.
Okay, um...
- This is ridiculous. I'm sorry.
- Look...
there's no magic technique that works
with all women.
Every orange is different,
but you shouldn't be asking me,
you should be asking your girlfriend.
Tune into her orange.
Yeah.
Okay, we're done now.
Thank you.
[Colin] Okay, everyone.
It's SRE question time.
Okay?
In the old box, and... Ah! [laughs]
It doesn't matter. [clears throat]
Okay.
"Can I get pregnant
from only giving hand jobs?"
[class laughing]
[Colin] Okay, um...
Well, fertilization only occurs
when Mr. Sperm enters Mrs. Egg.
So, no is the answer.
Okay...
Good.
[Colin] Um...
"My boyfriend
doesn't want to wear a condom.
What should I do?"
Uh... Hell.
Condoms protect the egg
from fertilization.
- Okay.
- Monsieur,
what about gay sex?
Well, you can't get pregnant
from, um, homosexual activity.
[Rahim] But what about pleasure?
People don't always have sex
to make a baby.
[Colin] Mm. Um...
Where was I? The, uh... The egg...
What type of lubricant would you recommend
for doing anal sex?
[Jean] Well, you should always use
a water-based lubricant.
Oil-based products will decompose
the latex in the condom.
And, sorry, just to answer
the previous question,
no matter how persistent
a sexual partner is
about not using contraception,
remember it is always your right
to say no.
Always.
Cool.
Uh, Ms. Milburn?
Has that given you enough information
for your report then?
Well, quite frankly, Mr. Groff,
I'm shocked by the ineptitude.
I'll be spending the next few weeks
getting to know the students
and their needs a bit better.
I'm not sure the board will agree
to anything that drastic.
I've already spoken to Maxine Tarrington,
and she approves.
I'm looking forward
to working with you, Mr. Groff.
Oh, for God's sake!
Did you know you need, like,
sugar and flour and an oven to bake?
And you don't just shove it all in,
you have to follow all these rules.
Yeah, it's called a recipe.
Hey, Maeve,
you're our new Quiz Head. High five.
Don't let me down.
Hey, have you guys...
Have you seen Ola anywhere?
- Maeve got on the quiz team.
- Oh, good job.
If you see Ola, I'm looking for her.
Are you happy, babes?
I don't think I'm over Otis.
That is what I keep saying.
Oh, my God! Your mum is everyting.
She talked about anal sex
in front of Mr. Groff.
- Jean actually gives me life.
- That's not good news, Eric.
Oh, and I think Rahim is gay.
- That actually makes a ton of sense.
- Mm-hmm.
Staring at you,
wanting to sit next to you all the time,
giving you books. He probably likes you.
Otis, I don't think so.
Read the signs, Eric. I have to go.
[exclaims]
Sir! I was wrong. I was wrong.
You have to tune into her orange.
Just listen to what she's actually saying.
That's how you learn Spanish, huh?
Good luck!
It's an apple.
[grunting]
- [bell ringing]
- [exhales]
- [door opens]
- [clears throat]
Hi.
I know I'm bad at fingering.
I was really busy trying to get it right,
and I wasn't listening to you.
We don't ever have to do it again.
Or...
I could show you what I like?
[knock at door]
Could you explain why you enjoy dirty talk
so that I can understand?
If not, I bought dips.
Loads of them.
I feel like a dowdy teacher all day, so...
when I'm at home,
I want to escape and to feel...
Like a female dog?
No. [laughs]
Colin, I don't care what you say.
I just...
want to feel sexy.
[scoffs]
So it's not about the words.
["Sexy Boy" by Air playing]
Spatula.
Pepper grinder.
Milk frother.
♪ Sexy boy ♪
Ice cream scoop.
[moaning]
Baba ghanoush! Oh!
Baba ghanoush!
Say it again! Baba... [moaning]
Ghanoush!
[both moaning]
[both laugh]
[both exhale]
♪ Sexy boy ♪
That's not mine.
They planted it.
And why would they do that?
Does this... belong...
to you?
[sergeant] Left, right, left, right,
left, right, left!
Left, right, left, right,
I lied.
I lied. It's not my weed.
They wanted to get me expelled
because they're... poofs.
Sir.
Yes.
Quite a lot of us are poofs
in this institution.
But some things
are better left unacknowledged.
So I don't have to...
go home?
You were found with drugs
in your possession, Adam.
I'm sorry.
["Bashed Out" by This Is The Kit playing]
♪ And so the outside, it bashes us in ♪
♪ Bashes us about a bit ♪
♪ Feel it tugging you
Ploughing you flat ♪
♪ Then feel it filling your sails
And warm on your back ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
[Mr. Groff] That was your last chance
at a formal education.
If you put one foot out of line,
you won't have a roof over your head.
Understood?
♪ And blessed are those
Who see and are silent ♪
♪ Blessed are those
♪ Blessed are those who see ♪
♪ So won't you hoist up
The bucket now, Charlie? ♪
♪ Hoosh it all over the deck ♪
♪ 'Cause we've been getting most
Mightily filthy ♪
♪ Mud marks up to our necks ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, oooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, oooh ♪
♪ And they did unfold
And the wind, it did feel them ♪
♪ And they did unfold and the wind ♪