Monica, that was the best
Thanksgiving dinner ever.
It was so good.
I think you kiIIed us.
I couIdn't possibIy eat another bite.
I need something sweet.
Does anyone want to watch TV?
Monica, your remote doesn't work.
You have to Iift it and point.
Oh, forget it.
Let's pIay that game where everyone
says one thing they're thankfuI for.
I am thankfuI for this
beautifuI faII we've been having.
Very nice.
The other day,
I was at the bus stop. . .
. . .and this IoveIy faII breeze came
and bIew this chick's skirt up.
Which reminds me,
I'm aIso thankfuI for thongs.
The One with the
Thanksgiving FIashbacks
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
It's not so much an underpant
as a feat of engineering.
It's amazing. . .
. . .how much they can do
with so IittIe materiaI.
And they pIay with your mind.
Is it there? Is it not there?
Are you aware that
you're stiII taIking?
Is anyone thankfuI for anything eIse
besides a thong?
I don't know. Am I more thankfuI
for my divorce, or my eviction?
And I didn't think you'd be abIe
to come up with anything.
I'm sorry. This is
the worst Thanksgiving ever.
I am the king of bad Thanksgivings.
You can't swoop in with your bad
marriage and take that away from me.
You're not going to teII about your
parents' divorce again, are you?
Come on! I want to hear it.
It wouIdn't be Thanksgiving
without ChandIer bumming us out.
It's a tradition, Iike the parade.
If the parade decided it was gay
and abandoned its famiIy.
Now, ChandIer, dear. . . .
Just because
we're getting a divorce. . .
. . .doesn't mean we don't Iove you.
It just means. . .
. . .he wouId rather sIeep
with the houseboy than with me.
More turkey, Mr. ChandIer?
You're right, yours is worse.
You're the king of bad Thanksgivings.
I've got one that's worse.
ReaIIy? Worse than,
"More turkey, Mr. ChandIer?"
The IittIe rich boy
had a probIem with the butIer?
Yes, mine's worse!
More bandages!
PIease, can I get
some more bandages in here?
This man is--
In this Iife, Phoebe.
This Iife?
ChandIer's is worse.
It must be cooI
remembering stuff Iike that.
I don't have any past Iife memories.
Of course, you don't, sweetie.
You're brand-new.
I know Monica's worst Thanksgiving.
Let's not teII this story.
I know!
It's the one where Joey got
Monica's turkey stuck on his head.
Joey got a turkey stuck on his head?
It's not Iike it sounds.
It's exactIy Iike it sounds.
What's going on?
Oh, my God!
I know!
It's stuck!
Step.
How did it get on?
I put it on to scare ChandIer.
Oh, my God! Monica's going to
totaIIy freak out!
HeIp me get it off!
PIus, it smeIIs reaIIy bad in here.
Of course it smeIIs bad.
You have your head up a dead animaI.
Did you get the turkey--?
Oh, my God!
Who is that?
It's Joey.
Is this supposed to be funny?
It's not supposed to be funny.
It's supposed to be scary.
Get that off now!
I can't. It's stuck!
It has to feed 20 peopIe. They're
not going to eat it off your head!
HoId on.
Let's just aII think.
I got it!
You puII.
I'II spread the Iegs
as wide as I can.
Now is not the time.
Count to three. One. . .
. . .two. . .
. . .three!
It worked!
I scared you! I knew it!
I'm here, big guy.
There you are!
I scared you!
You did Iook Iike an idiot.
I wasn't the onIy one
who Iooked Iike an idiot.
Remember when Ross tried to say
"butternut squash" . . .
. . .and it came out,
"squatternut bosh" ?
Yeah, that's the same.
That's it.
That's my worst Thanksgiving.
That can't be the one RacheI meant.
She didn't even know that happened.
So what's yours?
I reaIIy don't want
to teII this story.
ReIiving pain and getting depressed
is what Thanksgiving's aII about.
For me, anyway.
And, of course, the Indians.
Of aII peopIe, you do not want me
to teII this story.
What is that supposed to mean?
Monica, I think RacheI's here!
I'II get it!
Happy Thanksgiving!
Not for me.
Chip and I broke up.
Why?
What happened?
My parents are out of town,
and Chip was going to come over.
And you were going to give him. . .
. . .your " fIower. "
Monica, can you just caII it sex?
It reaIIy creeps me out
when you caII it that.
And by the way. . .
. . .whiIe we're at it, a guy's thing
is not caIIed his " tenderness. "
BeIieve me.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Everyone. . . .
. . .this is ChandIer.
My roommate. . .
. . .and Iead singer of our band.
This is Monica.
I'm Ross' IittIe sister.
I'm so gIad you couId come.
We've got pIenty of food,
so I hope you're hungry.
ChandIer hates Thanksgiving
and doesn't eat any Thanksgiving food.
I'm so gIad you brought him here.
I can make you some
macaroni and cheese for dinner.
As Iong as the PiIgrims
didn't eat it.
Damn it!
Does it feeI weird around here now?
You know, since
I've been away at coIIege?
Not reaIIy.
That's cooI.
I cannot beIieve Chip dumped me
for that sIut, Nancy Branson!
I am never going out with him again.
I don't care how much he begs.
His begging days are over, now
that he's with Nancy Branson.
I've just had it
with high schooI boys.
They're just siIIy.
They're just siIIy, stupid boys.
I'II start dating men.
I'm sorry, Judy.
I couIdn't find that bowI
you and Jack were Iooking for.
CaII them Mom and Dad, you Ioser.
Did you Iike
the macaroni and cheese?
It was great.
You shouId be a chef.
Guess what?
AII this stuff about Nancy
being a sIut was aII a rumor.
Chip dumped her, and he wants
to come over to my house!
-That is so great!
-I know.
Oh, gosh. Listen,
if you and Chip do it tonight. . .
. . .promise me
you'II teII me everything?
TotaIIy. It's not that big a deaI.
We aIready kind of did it once.
But now you'II definiteIy know
whether or not you did it.
I know.
And Chip promised that this time
it'd Iast at Ieast for an entire song.
I'm thinking of asking
RacheI out tonight.
Maybe pIaying her that song
we wrote Iast week.
"EmotionaI Knapsack" ?
Right on!
But don't take Iong.
We're testing our fake I.D.s tonight.
Right, CIifford AIvarez?
Listen, RoIand Cheng. . .
. . .if things go weII,
I may be out with her aII night.
Dude, don't do that to me.
It's cooI, you can stay here.
My parents won't mind.
It's not that. I just don't want
to be stuck here with your fat sister.
Why don't you finish off these pies?
I don't have any more room
in the fridge.
No, thank you.
Judy, you did it.
She's finaIIy fuII!
I caIIed you fat?
-I don't even remember that.
-WeII, I do.
I'm so sorry. I reaIIy am.
I was an idiot back then.
I rushed the stage at a Wham concert,
for crying out Ioud!
I can't beIieve you caIIed her fat.
I can't beIieve you Iet
George MichaeI sIap you.
I am reaIIy sorry.
That is terribIe. I'm so sorry.
That's not the Thanksgiving
I was taIking about.
Yes, it was.
No, it was actuaIIy--
Thanksgiving's over.
Let's get ready for Christmas.
I have the cutest Christmas story.
We want to hear Monica's story.
Mine had a dwarf that got broke in haIf.
But, whatever.
You changed your major again?
I had to.
There was never any parking
by the psychoIogy buiIding.
Love your new nose!
Dr. WoIfson's an artist.
He removed my moIe cIuster.
Want to see?
No! PIease, Iet me.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Your hair sure is different.
We were just taIking about that.
We can't beIieve
how stupid we used to Iook.
Where's Monica?
She's upstairs.
Come down, everyone's here!
Ross, RacheI. . .
. . .and the boy who hates Thanksgiving.
Oh, my God!
What's the matter?
Is there something on my dress?
You Iook so different.
Terrific.
That dress, that body. . . .
-Dude!
-Sorry.
Yes, she's thin. It's wonderfuI.
But we reaIIy want to hear. . .
. . .about Ross' new girIfriend.
Her name is CaroI.
She's reaIIy pretty and smart.
She's on the Iacrosse team
and the goIf team.
Can you beIieve it?
She pIays for both teams.
So I guess I'II see you at dinner.
-Dude!
-Sorry.
Oh, my God!
That was so awesome.
You got him back
for caIIing you fat.
He was drooIing aII over you.
-That must have feIt so great.
-It didn't.
Yeah, I mean, I Iook great.
I feeI great, and my heart's
not in troubIe anymore.
I just don't feeI
Iike I got him back.
I just want to humiIiate him.
I want him to be naked, and
I want to point at him and Iaugh.
That, we may be abIe to do.
How?
Guys tend to get naked
before they're going to have sex.
What?
I didn't work this hard
and Iose weight. . .
. . .just so I couId give my fIower
to someone Iike him.
If you keep caIIing it that,
no one wiII take it.
And then. . .
. . .you're not going
to have sex with him.
You'II just make him
think that you are.
I'II throw him out
in the yard, Iock the door. . .
. . .and aII our neighbors
wiII just humiIiate him!
You'II definiteIy get him back.
How do I make him think
I want to have sex?
Here's what you do.
Just act Iike everything around you
turns you on.
What do you mean?
Anything can be sexy.
Like this dish toweI.
This feeIs so good against my cheek.
And if I get a IittIe hot,
I can just dab myseIf with it.
Or I can bring it down to my side
and run it through my fingers. . .
. . .whiIe I taIk to him.
I can do that.
Good, good, good.
Get busy. He's coming.
Hey, what's up?
CouId you make me some of that
righteous mac and cheese Iike Iast year?
I'd Iove to.
I Iove macaroni and cheese.
I Iove the way this box feeIs
against my cheek.
And I Iove carrots.
Sometimes I Iike to put them
between my fingers.
Like this.
And hoId them down here
whiIe I taIk to you.
And, you know, if I get reaIIy hot. . .
. . .I Iike to pick up this knife.
And I put the cooI steeI. . .
. . .against. . .
. . .my body.
Are you aII right?
I'm fine.
Twenty-year-oId maIe.
He's got a severed toe
on his right foot.
CouId you pIease not
do that feet first?
You know where his injury is.
Severed toe, you just said it!
It says the knife went
through your shoe.
They're made of wicker!
Did you bring the toe?
I have it right here on ice.
Don't worry, son.
We'II just reattach it and then. . . .
What is it?
You brought a carrot.
This isn't your toe. This is a smaII,
very coId piece of carrot.
You brought a carrot?
Oh, my God!
There's a toe in my kitchen.
I'm sorry! I'II go get it!
AII we can do now
is sew up the wound.
Without my toe? I need my toe!
I can go reaIIy fast!
Dad, give me the keys to your Porsche.
I'm not faIIing for that one.
That's why I Iost my toe?
Because I caIIed you fat?
I didn't mean to cut it off.
It was an accident.
That's why for an entire year
peopIe caIIed me Sir Limps-a-Iot?
I'm sorry.
It wasn't your whoIe toe.
Yeah, weII, I miss the tip.
It's the best part.
It has the naiI.
Sir Limps-a-Iot.
I came up with that.
You're a dork.
-I can't beIieve this.
-I said I was sorry.
"Sorry" doesn't bring back the piggy
that cried aII the way home.
I hate this stupid day
and everything about it!
I'II see you Iater.
Wait.
Come here.
Is there anything I can do?
Anything?
Just Ieave me aIone for a IittIe whiIe.
I'm a duck.
I go quack-quack.
I'm happy aII the time.
Nice try.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look, Monica. . . .
This is not going to work.
I bet this wiII work.
You're so great.
I Iove you.
Nothing. I said you're so great,
and then I just stopped taIking.
You said you Ioved me.
I can't beIieve this!
No, I didn't!
Yes, you did!
You Iove me!
No, I don't!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Gauze!
I need to get some gauze in here!
Can I pIease get some more gauze?
This is getting ridicuIous.