You again?
You really wanna know
what happened last week
on Shameless?
The same old shit as last week.
When you work for a living,
the weeks just seem to blur together,
you know what I mean?
Don't judge me.
It's not like she wouldn't
be drinking by the third grade
growing up in this neighborhood.
Go.
Debbie needs her share of the utilities.
Want me to get some
shitty-ass minimum wage job
like you hauling boxes
around a warehouse?
Isn't marriage supposed
to be about communication,
compromise, agreed upon
mutual fuckin' goals?
How's that supposed to happen
when one person in the marriage
just goes off and does
whatever the hell he wants
without telling the other
person what he's doing?
Officer Tipping, I
believe I'm your partner.
Welcome to the Chicago police force.
Wait, you've never been shot?
Never been shot, never
shot at. You know why?
I don't leave the car.
I was bored shitless today.
I don't care 'cause I wanna be
the best partner that I can be.
So the least you can do
is buy me a damn drink.
One drink.
Really sorry again, sir,
that you had a heart attack.
You know, I somehow feel responsible.
We made $3,400.
It's been lovely doing
business with you.
Shall we do it again tomorrow?
I don't see why not. V?
Until our suppliers are
back up and running, sure.
"Wrongly convicted lesbian welder."
It's blowing up.
Everybody wants to hire you.
Just put on the dress, Franny!
No, no, no!
I need to take your picture
for Little Miss South Side.
Don't you want to be
Little Miss South Side?
No!
- Dress.
- Pants!
- Dress!
Can you at least brush your own teeth?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Your room is gonna be
swimming in constellations, little man.
Like Cassiopeia.
- Can you say...
- Cassiopeia.
Hey.
How's baby?
I was up all night with
Cami and Brad at the ER.
Baby's lost a lot of weight.
They ran a bunch of tests,
but they still can't figure
out why he's not eating.
He's gonna be okay, though, right?
They're meeting with the
doctor in a couple hours
so I'm gonna shower, head
back, hold Cami's hand.
Brad was hoping you
could open up at BornFree.
- Yeah, sure. I'll take Fred.
- Cool.
Hey, you wanna hit
that switch right there?
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Yeah, right?
Oh, Milton's coming by later.
Thought he was on an
aircraft carrier somewhere.
- He's on leave. He's getting married.
- Mm.
Coming by to look for his dress shoes
in those boxes left in the garage.
Take it, you dirty convict.
Thought you weren't gonna fuck me
until I got a real job, huh?
Oh, I got my eyes closed,
pretending you're a Jonas Brother.
- Which one?
- Uh, Joe.
Fuck you. I'm totally Nick.
What the...
Call me Nick, you Jonas-loving slut.
Whoa, hey. The fuck you doing?
I'm gonna get you pregnant. Come on.
This isn't how we do it.
Well, it's not how we normally do it.
Been watching a lot of prison porn.
Kinda feel like making you my bitch.
I'm not your bitch.
Well, when I bottom, I power bottom,
so even then, you're totally my bitch.
And we're done.
Oh, come on. Where you goin'?
To whack off in the shower.
Oh...
All right, well, you know, I guess
I'll just drill the
fuck outta my hand too.
Maybe color it orange, call it Ian.
How was your first day as a cop?
Pfft, seen more action
playing Minecraft on the shitter.
- This stuff is delicious.
- You high?
As the Willis Tower.
Fringe benefit of being
the Alibi's chief
quality control officer
and weed sommelier.
Gotta fuel up for a big
day of pot purchases.
- Franny, breakfast!
- No!
I'm gonna kill her.
I'm gonna choke her with her
cargo pants until she's dead.
Still won't put on the dress?
Won't put on her dress,
won't brush her hair,
won't brush her teeth,
won't pack her own backpack.
Why can't Little Miss
Sunshine wear pants?
'Cause it's not Little
Mr. Sunshine, Carl.
Sounds like gender conformity.
It's not my world,
Liam. I just live in it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Who you guys think is the
man in our relationship?
- You are.
- Ian.
Yeah, Neanderthal.
There's no man in our relationship.
But if there was, it'd be me.
Okay, well, who sticks it in who?
- I do.
- Irrelevant.
- And my dick's longer.
- Mine's wider,
which is the only metric that matters.
Look at him. He's too
pretty to be the man.
I'm pretty?
You have the hairless
body of a preteen girl.
Well, you like sticking
it up my shitter,
so what does that say about you?
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Baby on board. Christ.
Uh, Pop Tart or banana?
Uh, Pop Tart. Whoa, Debs.
You're looking especially, um...
Boobularly abundant.
Hot Lesbian Convict Handywoman.
Customers love it. More
work than I can handle.
Franny, let's go!
I gotta go poop!
No, Franny. No!
Huh.
If I'm late to work, I'm
gonna lose this client.
If I'm gonna drop
you off before the doctor,
- we have to go.
- Hey, can you guys drop me off
at the precinct on your
way to the warehouse?
Would one of you guys
take Franny to school, please?
- I'd really appreciate it.
- Yeah.
- Sure, whatever.
- Thank you.
Carl, you get shotgun.
"Ianna" here can ride bitch.
Fuck that.
- Bye, buddy.
- Hey, wait up.
Mommy?
Come on, Franny.
Everyone left. I'll
take you to school again.
Everyone? What am I, chopped liver?
You're Frank.
You don't think I can get
my granddaughter to school?
You just said you're
high as the Willis Tower.
I've been high, drunk, or both
for every major moment
in all of your lives.
I think I can handle
something as minor...
Okay.
- Okay what?
- Okay, see you.
Why the hell did I do that?
Fuck.
Smile, girls.
There are my little Miss South Sides.
V, I ordered a few things.
Better not be any more toilet paper...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You gonna go kill Bill?
Oh you like the drip? It's cool, right?
I got something for the
girls for their photo shoot.
Ahh, yeah!-
- No!
- Yes.
Little Miss South Side is about finding
the perfect representative
for the neighborhood.
What South Side girl
can afford a fur coat?
A girl whose parents are
getting rich selling pot.
I got us something too.
Oh!
- Versace?
- Versocky.
S-O-C-K-Y. Knockoffs.
But we're making baller money now.
We should dress like ballers.
People have been looking
down on me my entire life
for being foster-kid poor.
I just wanna walk the streets
wearing my Versocky tracksuit
with my head held high
looking down on everyone else for once.
We need to be saving that money.
Return it. All of it.
How about I return the stuff that I got
for you and the girls
but I keep my new stuff
because... I'm a grown-ass man
and I can wear whatever I want?
Can I wear it today at least?
I'll return it tomorrow.
Fine.
But not the girls.
Give it back, and let's go to school.
- Why, Mom?
- Mom.
Because Mommy hates joy. That's why.
Let's go, girls.
Grab these masks, grab these bags.
We gotta go. Come, come, come.
Kev, what have you done to our truck?
Nothing.
Just new rims and a bangin' stereo.
Bang.
You see how I went down?
It kinda hurt, though.
After you weld the leak under the sink,
can you fix the toilet?
It's doing one of those things
where the water keeps running.
Sure.
And also, the light bulb
in the fridge is out.
Can you change it?
You want to pay me to
change a light bulb?
Mm-hmm. Oh, and
the shower isn't draining.
Probably a hair clog. Sorry.
- Oh, a bunch of the doorknobs are loose.
- _
Can you go around and
tighten all of them?
- Shit.
- Oh, I have this squeaky...
You can just say no.
- Oh, no. I can do that.
- Oh, okay.
Also, there's some holes
in the wall in the master
bedroom that need patching up.
Oh, also, I have been
dying to mount the TV
in the living room, if you don't mind.
But the walls are thin, so
just... careful with the drill.
- Did you get all that?
- Yeah.
Great. All right, I gotta get to work.
Please wear your mask all day, please.
And when you're done,
you can just pull the
door closed behind you.
- It'll lock automatically.
- Great.
And, uh,
can I get a picture for Instagram?
My Ladies Who Lesbian group will flip.
Sure, yeah.
Do you have anything
sexy you can hold up?
Oh, my God, that is so
hot. All right, whoo!
Oh, wow.
All right, great.
Thank you. Have a great day.
Yeah, you too.
Come on, guys.
_
And that, Franny dear,
is how your mother
was conceived.
Okay, kiddo.
Thank you for your
intellectually challenging conversation.
Go get 'em in there.
And remember, always
throw the first punch.
This isn't my school.
Yeah, it is.
It's the school named
after the Black writer lady.
I go to Maya Angelou Elementary.
The poet, Maya...
I don't know where.
Uh, so it's boring, old prose for you.
Go on in.
Fuck.
Ah, what the hell.
Schools are all bullpucky anyway.
Let's get you some
real world experience.
Today is Take Your
Grandkid to the Work Day.
- You like that?
- Yeah.
I just made that up. Come on.
- Gallagher!
- Yes, sir.
How's Officer Tipping?
Life support. 60/40 chance of recovery.
Fuck.
Got you a new partner.
Try not to kill this one!
Sergeant James!
Yo, Billie!
Shit,
you really do look like Billie Eilish.
Huh. Well, what do you say, Billie?
Should we go get our dicks wet?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Mm-kay.
Open at last, open at last!
Thank the almighty mayor,
we are open at last.
Yo, drunks! Rise up.
Bars are officially open again?
Until there's another spike in cases.
I give it two weeks, tops.
All right, look. See?
My girls have Little Miss South Side
written all over their faces.
Well, that one, anyway.
She's something special.
Who, Gemma? Yeah, she is.
Kev, they are both special.
Gemma's just a little more special.
What's Little Miss South Side?
It's the South Side
Better Business Bureau's
annual contest to find a face
for all their advertising,
a face that shows hope and promise.
Makes you forget about
the looting and tear gas.
A face that makes you want to
spend money in the community.
I think Gayle King was
Little Miss South Side.
- And maybe Shelly Obama.
- Oh.
One case of expired brownie mix.
Take a Schlitz and my
payment, ple... hey.
Jesus Christ, Kev.
What is with the giant erection
and those fuckin' awful banana pants?
It's my money roll.
New thing I'm trying out.
Show people how rich I
am without saying anything
because V doesn't allow
me to announce it out loud.
She's the dom top in
your marriage, then.
Damn right.
You wanna thin out your money roll
for our brownie dealer, please?
And do not stretch those things out.
You're returning them tomorrow.
Hey, how much it cost
to use that shitty gym thing next door?
KevFit? $20 a session.
Lifetime membership for a Bitcoin.
Got a lot of takers on that, do you?
$10 a session for friends and family.
Well, there's ten boxes
in here at 2 bucks each
so... sign me up for two sessions.
Since when do you work out?
Since I married a body-shamer.
You know that Ian thinks he's
the man in the relationship
just 'cause he sticks it to me
and can do a few bicep curls?
I mean, clearly, I am the man.
But figure if I go pump
some iron, you know,
make it more clearly clear that...
More fucking clear.
Kev, where's the cash from
the pot sales last week?
It's not in the safe, and
the liquor guy's coming.
I didn't feel comfortable
leaving it in the safe
because it's the first
place robbers would look.
So...
it's like a piggy bank, but it's a keg.
It's a keggy bank.
You've been shoving our pot cash
in a keg under the bar?
Of course not.
Net profits are in the keg,
the money for Frank to do pickups
is in the bench cushion,
and the cash to pay off the liquor guy
is in an envelope taped
under the pool table.
You can't be hiding our
cash all around the bar.
You can't just put it in a bank?
The banks are licensed by the feds,
but pot isn't legal nationally,
so banks won't take pot money.
I thought money was money.
They'll take it if
you just launder it first.
Just cash it in for chips
at the Indian Casino,
down a few free cocktails
for a couple hours,
then cash chips back out.
Clean money.
All right. Time to go get swole.
Swole?
Swole. Like swole.
Eh, fuck you, Kermit.
Hey, how long you two been married?
- About 14...
- 15.
- 15 years.
- Uh-huh.
Would you guys consider yourselves
equals in the relationship?
- Yeah.
- No way.
What the fuck, Doris?
I do shit around the house.
What, throw a dish
in the dishwasher once a week?
Yeah, I take out the trash. I fix stuff.
- So I can re-fix what you fix?
- Oh...
A man thinks if
he brings home a paycheck
and, I don't know, mows the
lawn every once in a while
that he can throw his
feet up in front of the TV
and call it a day.
Meanwhile, his wife does the
same shit at work for less pay
and still has to pick up after
her husband when she goes home.
- That's bullshit.
- Really?
Yeah.
I went to take care of my mom in Ohio
when she caught the virus.
Came back.
George hadn't done the
laundry for a month.
Tell him what happened.
I got a rash under my balls.
- From reusing his underwear.
- Reusing my underwear.
Women performed $1 1/2 trillion
in unpaid housework last year.
So the answer is no, Red.
Two people are never
equal in a relationship.
The woman always does more.
Honey, he's gay. They're both men.
Gender's a social
construct, but thank you.
No. One of you is the woman.
Who does more cooking or
cleaning, you or your husband?
Neither of us.
Who provides
more emotional support?
Don't know what that is.
- Kids to take care of?
- Nope.
Ah, see? There. Equals.
You both have jobs?
Uh, Mickey? Ish.
Who makes more money?
He does.
You do more work for less money?
I got news for you, honey.
You're the woman.
Atrial septal...
Atrial septal defect.
A hole in your baby's heart.
Is it life-threatening?
Under normal circumstances,
not immediately,
but there are risks.
- Like what?
- Heart failure.
- Jesus.
- Oh, my God.
Will it close on its
own as he gets older?
Unfortunately, no.
There's an opening on the
surgical schedule Tuesday.
Let's get you squared
away with a payment plan.
- Payment plan?
- For your copay.
How much we talking about?
- It doesn't matter, Brad.
- How much?
Your insurance company
will need to give you a proper estimate.
Ballpark it for us.
Well, assuming no complications,
your baseline copay
could be around $65,000.
Oh, my God, what?
Wait, they need to come up with $65,000
before Tuesday?
Well, with the payment plan...
So they can save their kid on layaway.
Mask up, Tami.
Well, how is she supposed
to see how pissed I am
if she can't see my face?
I mean, their baby is dying.
He's not dying yet.
If he were, the hospital
would have to treat him
regardless of your ability to pay.
So it's 65 grand?
Or you can wait until he's almost dead.
Stop, Tami.
Upbeat music playing
My most important function at the Alibi
is to procure the finest
product at the lowest price
so Aunt Kev and Uncle V can
sell it at a massive markup.
_
Side note... learn a
few words of Armenian.
They run the underworld, and
they appreciate the effort.
Now, the key to any negotiation
is to set your target
and to stick to it.
- What's your favorite number?
- Seven.
Oof. It's low.
But it'll be a good
test of your aptitude.
Now when I ask you a
question, you say, "Seven."
Don't sound angry, but speak firmly.
_
Mm. What do you want, Frank?
Ten ounces of your best, madam.
Mm-hmm.
And who is this?
This? This is my granddaughter.
She can tell you the exact
per-gram wholesale worth
of any type of marijuana available.
Total savant.
What is your name, girl?
Uh, idiot savant. Severe
learning disabilities.
Doesn't know anything it has
to do with pot evaluation.
She's like Rain Man, only a girl.
She's Rain Girl.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
- Is that...
- Peruvian Mother Sativa.
Well, Peru had a wet spring,
but if that's what you've got.
Franny, what do you think?
Seven.-
You're kidding me.
Clients are paying 11 per gram.
Franny?
Seven.
Should we compromise? Maybe...
Seven, seven!
Looks like it's seven.
Or... we walk.
My philosophy
is no wrong is too small
for a cop to make right.
Like this motherfucker.
Arturro knows he's not
gonna make it across the road
before the light turns, but
he still begins his journey
after "don't walk" starts blinking.
Whole reasons he's in a
wheelchair to begin with
is because he started
crossing too late a decade ago.
Got hit by a streetsweeper.
Motherfucker never learns.
Yo, Arturro.
Let me help you, man.
Officers, I'm going as fast as I can.
Don't go faster, go sooner.
What? What?
All right, now you get your paraplegic
ass back to the side of the road
and you stay here
until the little, white
dude blinks at you.
What? This is...
I said stay, motherfucker. Just stay.
Yeah. Stay, motherfucker.
_
It's just snacks, guys.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Fuck these guys.
Yes.
Hey, where have you been?
Sorry, I've been busy. What's up?
Do you have food at your house?
I need you to run some
snacks to Franny's school.
Well, I'm not home.
I mean, I guess I
could run to the store.
Never mind. It'll be too late.
I'll just borrow some food
from my client's house.
Pick me up on the way.
I can help you relax.
No, I can't.
I gotta run these snacks to school,
and then I gotta go to the store
and replace what I took,
and then I gotta get back
here and finish all this work.
Dude, okay. We could...
fingerbang on the way.
It'll help, I promise.
No.
Fine. Where are you?
Yeah?
Uh...
Parker and Sandusky.
What the hell are you doing over there?
Damn. It'll lock.
Fuck it.
♪ I got a... I got a... ♪
♪ Baby, I got a whole lot of money ♪
♪ Whole... whole lot of money ♪
♪ Whole lot of money
whole... whole lot of money ♪
- K-Ball?
- What's up, what's up?
Yo, what'd you do to your truck?
Oh, what you talking about, man?
The wheels, the boomin' bass?
Making a little money now.
Okay.
I would stay and hoop wit' y'all
but I gotta take this
cash to the Indian Casino
and launder it.
Take it to the bank.
Those gold spinners I got coming in
ain't gonna pay for themselves,
you know what I'm saying?
This man.-
All right, y'all. Mad respect.
Nice. Stay up.
♪ I got a whole lot of money ♪
♪ Whole... whole lot of money ♪
Damn, man. Baller truck.
That's what good, old
fashioned bootstrap-pulling
will do for ya.
Started with a bar and a dream.
Now I own the bar and
a dispensary and a gym
all under one roof.
You should stop in some time. The Alibi.
Give you a discount from you
being from the neighborhood.
Ugh. Dude, he got a boner.
No. Oh, that? No, that's my money roll.
Oh, cool, cool.
- Can we have it?
- Hmm?
Oh, no.
Five bucks even.
What is this shit?
Oh, you know. Just
some powdered donuts...
No, no, no. Fuck coffee and donuts.
No, you gotta treat
your body like a temple.
Look.
Red Bull for sustained energy,
turkey jerky for protein,
gingko biloba to stay mentally sharp.
Listen, you got a perp with
an axe coming towards you
at the end of a long day,
you don't wanna be fighting to remember
what side of your body
you keep your gun on.
Now let's go. You can have some of mine.
Wait, uh...
What are you doing, Gallagher? Let's go!
We don't pay for shit.
What are they gonna
do, call the cops on us?
We have a 1080
on the north side of Lincoln Park.
All available officers on the scene.
1080. What is that, a car chase?
Yup. Let's go.
Hey, hey. Why you riding shotgun?
What? You want me to drive?
Well, you ain't gonna learn nothing
from the passenger seat.
Fuck yeah.
Seven.
- Franny?
- Seven!
No wonder Ian's always
in such a bad mood.
Forgot how much working
out fuckin' blows.
V, got any protein shakes?
I'm just kidding. Give me a Guinness.
Give me the bat! Give me the bat.
Give me the bat, V.
Holy... Kev, what happened?
I got robbed, V.
They took my bling, my money roll.
- Your pants.
- Dignity.
They got the JL 12-inch TW1 speakers
I installed in the truck.
- How did they get those?
- They took the truck.
Please tell me this is
after you laundered our money
and made the bank deposit.
I could tell you that...
- but I'd be lying.
- Kev.
Oh, hey, buddy. Oh!
Why don't we, uh, stick to the binky
instead of, you know, rusty metal, huh?
There you go.
Hey, it's your mama. Hey.
How soon can you sell that bike?
Huh?
- The Indian in the garage. How soon?
- Well, it's not done.
I know, but how much
could you get for it,
like, right now?
Slow down. What's going on?
He's got a hole in his heart.
The baby?
No, Brad. Yes, the baby.
They're gonna operate on Tuesday
if Brad and Cami can prove
they can cover the
- $65,000 copay before then.
- What?
Dad is trying to pull
together some cash,
but his business is in the crapper
since the COVID shutdown,
and I've got a few
thousand in savings, but...
Yeah, no, I mean I can
put the Indian on eBay,
but it probably
wouldn't sell by Tuesday.
Do you think Debbie
would sell her truck?
No, considering that's
how she makes a living.
What about the rest of the Gallaghers?
What do they got?
Uh, 50 bucks in the squirrel fund
and a cupboard of expired cereal.
Are you telling me the Gallaghers
can't do anything here?
Okay, Aunt Oopie is
gonna pawn some jewelry.
Uh, Cory's donating the money she made
posing nude at that art school.
Everyone is making sacrifices.
Yeah, well, the Tamiettis
have things they can sacrifice,
all right? Liam and Carl
still share underwear.
Look, um, I'm in this
with you, all right?
100%.
We'll help Brad and Cami figure it out.
Okay.
It's just...
yeah, I don't know
what they're gonna do,
so...
Um, I gotta get back upstairs,
but I'll check in with
you in a bit, okay?
All right. I'll
talk to you soon. Bye.
Bye.
My wrist is cramping.
I'm sorry. I'm just too stressed.
So what if she wouldn't
put on the damn dress?
I need to get a photo for
Little Miss South Side.
Girls wear pants, Debbie.
Whatever. Let's just drop it.
She's coming.
- Hi, Debbie.
- Hey.
Sorry I'm not 500 feet away, but...
That's okay. I won't tell if
you won't.
Uh, so I brought flax seed crackers,
organic split pea hummus,
and green juice pressed from vegetables.
You're kidding.
- I'm sure they'll... love it.
- Mm-hmm.
So good of you to stick to snack duty
with Franny not at school today.
Thanks again.
Wait, what? Franny's not at school?
What the fuck?
Okay, stick your nose in
that. Tell me what it needs.
That is exactly what I would've chosen.
We're gonna call this recipe
Little Half-Mexican Red
in your honor.
Here.
Stick your pinky in there
and pack it in nice and tight.
There you go. That's really good.
This reminds me of the time
your mother helped Grammy Monica and me
measure out some premium Columbian blow.
One of my favorite
memories of your mother.
You know, that might've
been your Aunt Fiona.
Hmm.
Okay.
Back when I was in college,
I would be embarrassed
to roll a joint like that.
Today, I'll take it.
_
- Not in there?
- No.
Did you ask them who
took Franny to school?
- Yeah, I just did.
- Well, what are they saying?
"Don't know," "Not sure,"
"Fuck if I know," "Don't know."
Well, who was supposed to know?
"Don't know," "Not
me," "Fuck if I know,"
- "Frank."
- Frank?
They left her with Frank?
Where is he now?
"Bar," "dumpster,"
"Hooker's vag," "Leave
me alone, Debbie."
- Huh.
- It's lunchtime,
so Frank's probably tanked
at the Alibi already.
I'm gonna fucking kill 'em all.
- This blows.
- I told you.
You take 41, you get pinned
to the lake with traffic.
Think I'ma get in trouble for
busting out that headlight?
Nah. German Shepherd
should've looked both ways
before crossing the street.
Check this out.
What you see?
Old lady screaming into her phone,
couple lookie-loos.
Okay, now that lookie-loo right there.
Tell me about him.
White guy. Mid-20s.
Looks like he wants to be Macklemore.
We should talk to him.
Lone white kid in the vicinity
where a Black man's getting arrested?
90% chance Black guy's his drug dealer.
- Ain't that racial profiling?
- Black is as Black does.
- But you're Black.
- Bitch, I'm blue.
Yo, can we talk?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, where you going?
None of your business, Lady Po-Po.
Oh. Gun, Billie.
Yes, Leesie... Kaleesie.
Bitch, this makes
everything my business.
Hands in the air, motherfucker.
Yeah. Hands in the air, motherfucker.
- Shoot him.
- Wait, really?
No... girl, no! Go get him.
Oh, right.
Got you now, motherfucker!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Where you think you're
going, Macklemore?
Oh, shit.
Oh, wait. No,
no. Come on, come on!
- Wait, no... stop, stop...
- Get up.
Hey. Cuff him, Gallagher.
Congratulations.
- You just popped your cherry.
- Fucking bitch.
What is that?
It's my kid brother.
He got his first arrest.
- Aww, yeah.
- Oh, big shot.
Yeah.
It's noon-thirty, boys and Doris.
Everyone take their lunch break.
Hey, Red.
Finish filling that order before you go.
You want me to work
through my lunch break?
Yes.
- You gonna pay me extra?
- No.
Then no.
You're behind.
You're not gonna finish
by the end of the day.
Okay, so I'll stay late.
I could use the overtime.
We don't pay overtime.
You working too slow isn't my problem.
You gave me a bigger
order than everybody else.
Everyone takes their turn
with the bigger orders.
Hike up your skirt and be a team player.
Yeah, how about no?
How about don't be a little bitch
and you get to keep your job?
I'm not anybody's bitch.
Think we should quit the pot business?
But we're making real money, V.
Doesn't matter if you're dead.
Dealing shouldn't be
dangerous now that it's legal.
Dealing isn't dangerous.
Being rich on the
South Side is dangerous.
We are not rich.
You saying that out loud is dangerous.
We need to arm ourselves.
- Guns.
- No guns.
Throwing stars, then.
Where are my throwing stars?
Okay, dumbasses, stop, stop, stop.
Look. First off...
Actually, first off,
Kev, put some pants on.
You're turning me on a little bit.
Second, you need to get rid
of these clothes, all right?
No more bling, no more
tricked-out trucks.
You need to go way under the radar here.
And finally, you two need
to pay someone security
for your daily cash runs.
I would say do it yourselves,
but clearly that's a
bit of a non-starter,
so pay me 25% of your gross profits,
I'll do it for you.
Security and armed transport
from the bar to the casino to the bank.
- I think we should do it.
- 25%?
Between him and Frank,
that's half of our profits.
15%.
23 and free KevFit membership.
Done.
Frank Gallagher!
- Jesus.
- Whoa.
He's not here. What happened?
My dumbass family left Franny with Frank
and he never took her to school.
Does anybody know where he is?
He's supposed to be
doing pot runs for us.
He took her to buy drugs?
- Where?
- I don't know.
He said something about
an Armenian dry cleaner in Chatham.
And his dealer friends by the park.
Hey! Eat shit, Ian!
What the fuck, Debbie?
Kev, can I get a shot of whiskey?
What are you doing here?
- Getting' man-swole.
- Oh, great.
Maybe when I fuck you, I won't
feel like such a pedophile.
Suck a dick, bitch.
Shouldn't you be taking it up the vag
at your shitty warehouse job?
Fuck 'em.
Tried to make me work for
free through my lunch break,
so I quit.
Really?
Oh, well, don't you worry
your pretty little head
about it, there, babyface.
'Cause between the expired food sales
and the new business
deal that I just got,
I got us covered.
Maybe you can be one of those
kept wife things they had in the '50s.
Nice, frilly aprons
and high heels and a...
bouffant.
"Buff-int"?
Okay, fuck it. I'm going home.
No, it's a good idea. Why
don't you kick back, relax?
Maybe watch some soaps
while you think about
what to cook me for dinner.
- You little bitch!
- You're the bitch!
Whoa. You gonna stop this?
I wanna see who wins.
Shit.
Uh-uh.
Hey! Hey!
No, sir!
No, sir. Not in Mama's house.
Hey. What are you doing here?
Eating my feelings.
Fuck it. I need a smoke.
Yeah, good idea.
We can probably afford lung surgery.
Yeah, okay.
You know, I, uh,
talked to everybody here
about pulling some money together,
but, uh, everybody's
still pretty underwater
from the recession and all.
Do you remember those
assholes in Tennessee
who bought up 18,000
bottles of hand sanitizer,
sold 'em for, like, 70 bucks a pop?
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
- What if we bought up
all of something like... like,
uh, all of the condoms in Chicago?
No, we'd just end up with
more pregnant 13-year-olds.
Hey, we could stab the baby.
That'll open that hole right up.
Then they'd have to operate.
Could've been Fred.
One of the most important
things a human can learn
is how to take advantage
of a vulnerable population.
Who are the most vulnerable
people in the world?
Puppies?
Close.
Millennials.
Vulnerable to their own inflated senses
of their self-worth.
Now, the vast percentage of our market
is made up of millennials
and every single one of
- 'em thinks that he or she...
- Or "they."
Or they is special.
So a plain old joint
isn't enough anymore.
We need a variety of
fancy rolling papers
so that each millennial
can choose one that says,
"This is me."
Will the dye in the
papers destroy their lungs?
- Yes.
- Do they care?
- No.
- Not at all.
Because in the moment, they
can say to their friends,
"I got something you don't got,"
and at the end of the day,
we all want that, I suppose.
So that's everything on our list.
Let's head home.
Vernon and Jackson.
Uh, where are we? What...
Why are we here?
Paper store?
Rolling papers, right.
Let's head to the paper store.
Grampy Frank.
I think...
I got a little, um...
well, I suppose we're done.
Hey.
You wanna make one more
stop before we head home
to commemorate this day?
Come on.
Ow.
My bad.
Nah, leave it, leave
it, leave it, leave it.
How do you know the perp in
that car chase back there?
I don't.
Fuck!
How do you know the
perp in that car chase?
Oh, come on, bitch. I ain't
answering shit without my lawyer...
Fuck!
How do you know...
Please! I don't, okay?
Fuck!
Fuck.
He's my dealer, okay?
Are you willing to
testify to that in court?
Please. Come on.
You know his people will kill me.
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
kay, kay, kay, fine, fine.
I'll testify.
Frank Gallagher!
No! What you...
He is not here. What do you...
Debbie, this park is
huge. Where do we start?
Over here? Maybe over there.
Frank Gallagher!
What's going on with you two?
He's been sitting on his ass
spending all our wedding money...
This lady just decides we're
not sharing our money...
And all of a sudden, he's
making bank doing all sorts...
And as soon as I start making
more than him, he turns...
- He's a fucking top now.
- Stop!
First of all, you need
to clean up your language.
Bitch this and vagina that is
incredibly offensive to women.
And just because you're gay
doesn't mean you get away
with turning women into
second-class citizens.
Second of all, there are no
men or women in a marriage,
there are only partners,
and I'd be very careful
about claiming the title of head partner
'cause you have no clue
what's gonna happen.
And you're fucking yourselves
if you think keeping
score is a good idea.
Finally, I don't care who's
the top and who's the bottom.
You fight in my bar again,
I'm cutting both of your dicks off.
Then ain't no one topping anyone.
Now, here. Eat some pot brownies.
Y'all need to chill the fuck out.
Bitch.
- Yo.
- Hey, thanks.
How you holdin' up?
As well as can be expected
for a parent that can't
afford to save his kid.
Tami and I, we're gonna figure out a way
to help you pay for the surgery.
Yeah?
You kiddin'?
You got your own kid to take care of.
Nah, this one's on me.
- I appreciate it, though.
- Yeah.
You got a plan?
Think I'm gonna let him die.
I told Tami that, uh, we should stab him
so they have to operate.
Nah, I'm gonna sign
up for a payment plan.
Sell BornFree.
No, man. I mean, you can't do that.
I don't think there's any other way.
You poured everything
you have into that place.
It saved you.
I got a wife and two kids.
They're my BornFree now.
I gotta choose between
my business and them,
it's them in a heartbeat.
Have fun today, Billie?
Beats whacking off to "Training Day."
Uh, hey. Was waffling
an admission of guilt
out of that guy without a lawyer present
legal, ethical, or whatever?
You're cute.
Listen, our job isn't law
or ethics; it's justice.
That guy was running away from the cops,
and he admitted guilt.
End of story.
And the second you start
thinking 'bout legal
and ethical is the second a
bad guy shoots you in the face.
You wanna get shot in the face?
No, I wanna shoot people in the face.
Ooh, that's the spirit.
Just make sure they shoot first.
Congratulations on a good day, Billie.
We'll get that blood
running icy blue in you yet.
Maybe one day I'll get one
for your baby cousin, Fred, too.
I don't know if I like him yet.
But you're pretty swell,
so you've earned a
place on my arm forever.
I've wanted to ask you since breakfast,
but we didn't have the
same relationship then
that we do now.
Why were you giving
your mom such a hard time
to put on that dress and
get your picture taken?
I know it was a butt-ugly dress,
and I get the sense you're less
a girly-girl and more of a...
A boy.
Sure.
Live your truth.
But you know, sometimes
it's nice to make other people happy.
My father used to get drunk
and make me put on a dress
when I was your age,
and I hated it,
but I did it because my father liked it.
It's called playing the long game.
Someday, you'll get
caught doing an eight-ball
or sleeping with a
not-too-distant cousin,
and you'll get off
with a slap on the wrist
'cause your mom will remember
that you put on a dress for her once.
- That's beautiful.
- Oh, thank you.
I had a really nice
day with you today, kid.
A really nice day.
If anything happens to Franny,
I'm gonna fuckin' kill them.
Who was supposed to
take Franny to school?
I don't know. Any of them?
So you left for work without making sure
an actual person took
your kid to school?
What? Do you think this is my fault?
Fuck!
Hi, Liz!
Debbie, the police are here.
Wait. Why?
Apparently, a neighbor saw you
crawling out of the window
with an armload of stuff
- so she called the police.
- Shit.
And I checked my security
camera, and it showed you
stealing food out of my pantry
and crawling out my window.
I'm so sorry! I...
I... but I can explain.
Did you steal anything else?
No, I didn't steal anything.
I... listen. I'll come back tomorrow
and I'll replace everything
that I borrowed, okay?
I'm not gonna press
charges because, clearly,
you are so white trash
that you need to take food
- for your family.
- I am not white trash!
But you are never coming
near my house again.
P.S., I'm leaving you a
really shitty review on Yelp.
Fuck!
Wait. Is that them?
You're nuts.
Oh, my God. Franny!
Franny, are you okay?
Where have you been? I
was so worried about you.
Why? She was with me all
day. We had a great time.
Look, we got tattoos.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You were supposed to
take Franny to school!
I actually did take her to school.
It just happened to be one
named after the wrong Black lady.
They all look the same!
- What?
- Wow.
Not Black ladies! Schools!
She missed a day of preschool.
It's not like she missed
What To Do If There's A
Hole In Your Spacesuit Day
at astronaut camp. What's the big deal?
The big deal is that I didn't know
where my kid was for six hours.
I know you didn't give a
shit where your kids were
most of our lives,
but I care about mine!
What happened to you?
I got married. That's what happened.
Well, I'd divorce you, but
you never signed a prenup.
- What happened to you guys?
- They got married.
Guess what. I just made my first arrest.
- Awesome.
- Way to go.
- All right, buddy.
- Fuck you, cop.
Hey, assholes. Who
left my kid with Frank?
- I didn't.
- Wasn't me.
Nope.
I did.
What the hell is wrong with you, Liam?
Hey. Ease up.
So Frank left her at
school. What's the big deal?
He didn't drop her off at school.
He took her to buy drugs!
All right, well, that's
not Liam's fault.
Why'd you leave her with Liam anyway?
Didn't leave her with Liam.
I left her with all of you guys.
No, you didn't.
I stood right there
and asked one of you
to take her to school
'cause I was running late for work.
I didn't hear you say that.
- Me, neither.
I mean, did anybody say, "Yes, Debbie,
I will take Franny to school"?
Great, take her side.
I'm not taking anybody's side.
I'm just saying take some
fuckin' responsibility.
I'm taking all of the responsibility.
I am running this entire
house, I'm holding down a job,
and I have to take
care of a kid in my...
Jesus Christ!
You're not the only one
with shit going on, Debs.
If you can't handle
it, lean the fuck out.
Don't blame us for being a shitty mom.
Debs.
I didn't mean that.
Ah, fuck.
That is good.
- Oh, you like that?
- Mm!
That's a little Half-Mexican Red.
Named after Franny.
Indica-forward, mellow and agreeable
with just enough sativa to give
it a little kick of rebellion.
Just like Franny.
Sounds
like your granddaughter
left quite an impression on you.
What do you mean?
Well, you never named anything
after any of your actual kids.
That's because they don't make pot
that's belligerent and ungrateful.
If your kids are
belligerent and ungrateful,
it's probably 'cause
you made 'em that way.
I...
Kids are tough.
They need things.
Grandkids are simpler.
You don't owe 'em anything.
They don't expect anything from you.
Pressure's off.
You can't disappoint anyone.
You two just murdered my high.
Sell that for seven a pop.
Little expensive, don't you think?
Seven's the price.
Where you goin'?
Gotta see a girl about a dress.
Yeah.
- What the...
- Fuck, it's Milton.
It's gonna disturb...
Hey, I got it, I got it, I got it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, shit. Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I wake the baby?
No, no, no, it's all
good, it's all good.
He's just settling down.
He's in the nursery with Tami.
Come in, come in.
So it, uh, feel good to be off the boat?
And to not have my CPO up my ass?
Yeah, it does.
- Hey, uh, when's the wedding?
- I just got tested.
- Oh, cool.
- The wedding is this weekend.
I just hope my dress shoes
are in the garage
where I left them, man.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, the...
The place looks fantastic.
Oh, yeah, well, the inside, at least.
The neighbors wanted to keep
the outside looking like shit.
So.
Did you do all this by yourself?
Uh, yeah. I mean, it's just some
plaster work and paint, mostly.
You put tile up in the kitchen too?
Um, backsplash, yeah.-
- Looks good, man. Damn good.
- Thanks.
How much did
all of this cost you?
Uh, I don't know.
I picked up most of this stuff for free
at condemned houses and work sites.
Hmm.
Um, I mean, I guess I bought
some stuff, too, though.
Uh, I put in some hours.
You should've told me.
Yeah, I would've thrown you some cash
or reduced your rent or something.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What do you think you spent?
Uh, five...
six grand, maybe?
I don't know.
Why don't I split it with you?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Did the work. Might as well.
- Great.
- All right, cool.
- Shoes.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just back there in the garage.
- Yeah, of course.
- Okay.
- Backsplash, huh?
- That's the backsplash, yeah.
Go away.
Mommy?
I'm ready for you to
take my picture now.
Franny.
Hang on. Let me get my phone.
Oh.
Okay, smile.
Oh, look how beautiful you are.
A little to the side.
Give it to me, dom top daddy!
Take it all, you uber-masculine slut!
Flip fuck?
Sure.
What's my name?
Nick.
I said what's my name?
Nick Jonas!