"Notwithstanding the provisions
of subsection 3, section A,
clause 214 of the Administrative
Procedures Scotland Act 1978,
insofaras the implementation of
the statutory provisions is concerned,
the resolution of anomalies
as between departments
shall fall within the purview of
the MinisterforAdministrative Affairs".
What does it mean?
- I'm sorry?
- What does it mean?
Oh, er, well, Minister,
it means "notwithstanding
the provisions of..."
I've just read it to you.
What does it mean?
What it says, Minister.
May I remind you,
you are seeing a deputation
from the TUC in 15 minutes,
from the CBI afterthat,
and from the NEB at 12 noon.
- What do they all want?
- They're all worried about machinery.
Yes, for inflation,
deflation and reflation.
What do they think I am,
a Ministerof the Crown
ora bicycle pump?
When am I going to do
all this correspondence?
You do realise
you don't actually have to.
- Don't I?
- We can draft an official reply.
What's that?
"The Ministerthanks you
forthe letter".
Then we say:
"The matter is underconsideration".
Oreven,
"underactive consideration".
What's the difference?
"Underconsideration"
means we've lost the file,
"Underactive consideration"
means we're trying to find it.
You just transferall the letters
to yourOut Tray,
put a note if you wish
to see the reply
and if you don't,
you neversee it again.
If I transfereverything from here
to here, without even reading it,
- that's all I have to do?
- Yes.
- Itwill be dealtwith?
- Precisely.
- Properly?
- Immaculately.
What's the Minister
here forthen?
Er... to make policy decisions,
Minister.
When you've decided the policy,
we can carry it out.
How often are
policy decisions needed?
From time to time.
Bernard, this government
is here to govern.
Not merely preside
like ourpredecessors did.
When a country is going
downhill, it's time forsomeone
to get into the driving seat,
put his foot on the accelerator.
I think you mean the brake.
- Ah, Humphrey.
- A moment of yourtime, Minister.
"The official visit to the UK
of the President of Buranda".
Where's Buranda?
- Africa.
- I've neverheard of it.
Yes, it's fairly new, Minister.
It used to be called
British Equatorial Africa.
It's the red bit on the left hand
side, below the Mediterranean.
Oh, there!
But why's this come to us?
- This is forthe Foreign Office.
- There are administrative problems.
Her Majesty's due
to be up at Balmoral,
so she'll have
to come to London.
State visits are arranged
years in advance.
This isn't a state visit,
it's a Head of Government visit.
The President of Buranda
is Head of State.
But he's also
Head of Government.
But ifhe's coming
as Head of Government,
why does the Queen
have to see him?
Because she's
the Head of State, Minister.
The Head of State
must greet a Head of State,
even ifhe's not here
as Head of State.
It's all a matterofhats.
- Hats?
- Yes.
He's coming wearing
his Head of Government hat.
He is the Head of State,
but he's notwearing
his Head of State hat,
but even though he's wearing
his Head of Government hat,
he must still be met by the Crown.
Why are we having
an official visit from
this tin pot little African country?
I beg of you not to referto it
as a tin pot little African country.
- It's an L. D. C.
- What?
Buranda is
an Under- developed Country.
However, this term
was regarded as offensive...
so they became known
as Developing Countries
and then as Less Developed
Countries or L. D. C.'s.
We are nowready to replace
the term L. D. C. With H. R. R. C.
What's that?
- Human Resource Rich Countries.
- Which means?
They're grossly overpopulated
and begging formoney.
And Buranda is an H. R. R. C?
No, Minister.
Is it one
of the "have not" nations?
We don't use that term
any longer.
But if we did, Buranda would be
a "will have" nation.
Will have a huge amount of oil
in a couple of years from now.
Oh, I see.
Why didn't you say so at first?
- It's not a T. P. L. A. C. At all.
- T. P. L. A. C?
Tin Pot Little African Country.
No, Minister.
Oil.
I've got a marvellous idea.
The Queen doesn't have
to come down from Balmoral.
Are you proposing
that they should exchange
official greetings
overthe telephone?
No. No. No. No.
You'd like them
to shout rather loudly?
No. The visit shall take place
in Scotland.
- At Holyrood Palace.
- Out of the question.
- Why?
- It's not ourdecision.
- It's a Foreign Office matter.
- I don't think so.
"Notwithstanding the provisions
of subsection 3 blah blah...
it is proposed blah...
the resolution of anomalies
shall fall within the purview
of the Minister
forAdministrative Affairs.
It's brilliant.
We save the Queen
a pointless journey,
and there are three Scottish
by-elecctions coming up soon.
We'll hold them afterthe visit.
We do not hold
Head of Government visits
forparty political reasons,
but forreasons of State.
My plan shows that Scotland
is an equal partner in the UK.
She is Queen of Scotland too.
And it is full of marginal constit...
depressed areas.
I hardly think thatwe can exploit
ourSovereign
by involving her
in what some might call
a squalid vote grubbing exercise.
- You want a betterreason, right?
- Indeed we do.
Then tell me why he's coming.
Forexchange of views
on matters of mutual interest.
- Now tell me why he's coming.
- Off shore drilling equipment.
We're hoping he's going to place
a huge orderwith us.
And where is he going to see
all this offshore equipment?
Aberdeen. Clydeside.
Howmany oil rigs
have you got in Haslemere?
- But the administrative problems
- That's why we are here.
- But Scotland's so remote...
- Not all that remote.
It's that pink bit about
two feet above Potter's Bar.
Very droll, Minister.
So, it's going to be Scotland.
That is my policy decision.
That's what I'm here for,
right Bernard?
Right Humphrey?
Good, thank you.
What's he got against the idea?
Sir Humphrey likes going
to Foreign Embassies,
with his white tie, tails, medals.
Itwill all be on a much smaller
scale in Scotland.
No room for Humphrey?
Onlyforthe Permanent
Secretary there.
Has Sir Humphrey got lots of um...?
Yes one ortwo, Minister.
And he's been recommended
forthe K. B. E.
How do you know?
I thought honours were
a closely guarded secret.
- More coffee, Jumbo?
- Thank you, Humpy.
Any luck with the Foreign Secretary
about this Scottish nonsense?
"Fraid not. Can't budge him.
Your Ministernobbled him first.
No chance of getting it
back to London?
No, I'm afraid the Cabinet
are utterly united.
All these marginal seats,
d'you see?
Shameful.
- Political.
- Typical.
Inevitable.
And so blatant.
Issuing writs forthree Scottish
by-elections to poll
on the day afterthe visit.
Can you imagine Harold MacMillan
doing a thing like that?
Yes.
Yes, so can I, actually.
Now, about the arrangements
forScotland.
The reception I mean.
Do we knowwho's going?
Yes. I'm afraid the Burandan
Consulate in Edinburgh
is rathera hutch.
I shall have to carry the flag
forthe Civil Service all by myself.
Oh really?
Well, you have my sympathy.
God knows what they'll be serving up
forthe Scots and Burandans.
Haggis in missionary sauce,
I shouldn'twonder.
Actually, between ourselves,
the visitwill probably neverhappen.
- Neverhappen? Why?
- Rumblings in the interior.
Oh dear...
Oh, I see what you mean.
- From ourman in Mungoville.
- Isn't that ratherserious?
Buranda's a friendly country
with a Commonwealth connection.
Our information is it's likely
to turn into a hostile L. D. C.
With a Cuban connection.
- Whatwill the Government do?
- The same as always...
Damn all!
We are just getting reports
of a coup d'etat in Buranda,
the West African State, formerly
British Equatorial Africa.
It is reported that
the Commander in Chief
Colonel Selim Mohammed
has been declared President.
It is not known what's happened
to President Alam,
who was due to pay an official visit
to Britain next week.
There is still no sign
of agreement...
Did you see that?
Get me the Foreign Secretary.
Shall we scramble?
No, it's not secret,
it's on the news.
Martin.
- What's all this about Buranda?
- What's all what?
There's been a coup d'etat.
How do you know?
Itwas on the news.
Didn't you see?
You're Foreign Secretary!
My TV set's on the blink.
YourTV set?
Don't you get telegrams?
No, they come in later.
I get all the foreign news from TV.
You're joking... aren't you?
No.
We've got to make sure
this official visit still happens.
How can we?
Who's the new President?
We must find out.
And make sure he comes.
- There are three by-elections.
- I know that.
Let me know if you hear...
No, you let me know.
You're the one with the telly.
- You've heard the sad news?
- Yes, disaster.
No. No. No.
No, just a slight inconvenience.
The wheels are in motion,
it's really simple
to cancel the arrangements
forthe visit.
- You'll do no such thing.
- We have no choice.
We are reissuing the invitation
forthe new President.
But, we haven't recognised
his government.
The wheels are in motion.
- But who is he?
- Mohammed something.
We knownothing about him.
What's he like?
We're not putting him up
forthe Athenaeum.
Minister.
Buranda is in total confusion.
We don't know
who is behind him.
Whetherhe's Soviet backed,
orjust a Burandan with an eye
forthe main chance.
We cannot take diplomatic risks.
- The Government has no choice.
- But Her Majesty...
Her Majesty will cope.
She always does.
But who is he?
He might not be
properly brought up.
He might be rude to her.
He might take liberties.
He will be photographed
with Her Majesty
and what ifhe turns out
to be anotherldi Amin.
The repercussions are
too hideous to contemplate.
- We'll find out about him.
- We can't.
All thatwe know
is that he's an enigma.
Humphrey,
I don't care forthatword.
Enigma?
And there are reasons of State
which make this visit essential.
Buranda is enormously rich.
It needs oil rigs and we have
idle shipyards on the Clyde.
Buranda is essential
to ourAfrican policy.
The Government doesn't have
African policy.
Well, it has now.
And ifhe is Marxist backed,
who betterto win him over
to ourside than her Majesty?
Moreover, it is an important
state occasion forScotland.
Not to mention
three marginal by-elections.
Not to mention...
It has nothing to do with it!
Of course not.
Yes?
It's the Foreign Secretary.
Martin? Yes? Yes?
The visit's on.
Oh, splendid.
The new President
of Buranda intends
to visit this country,
as previously agreed.
So, the Foreign Office
is getting the facts at last?
Well, not exactly.
Martin's driverheard
a newsflash on his carradio.
So, the visit's on.
That is my recommendation
to the PM.
Anotherpolicy decision,
Bernard.
Quite a lot of them afterall,
aren't they?
Burandan Airways!
They are doing well.
- Howmany planes do they have?
- None.
What about that one?
That one was chartered lastweek
and repainted specially.
Actually, there's one 747
that belonged to
9 different African airlines
in one month.
They called it the Mumbo Jumbo.
- When does my plane leave?
- I've booked you on the sleeper.
- You'll be at the House tonight.
- Oh, lord.
And nowwe are about to catch
ourfirst glimpse
of President Selim Mohammed
of Buranda.
I knowhim!
That's Charlie.
- Charlie?
- We were at L. S. E. Together.
He's not Selim Mohammed,
he's Charles Umtali.
Are you sure?
You don't forget a name
like Charlie Umtali.
- Have we anything on this?
- In the brief it stated
that Colonel Selim Mohammed
was converted to Islam.
We didn't knowhis previous name
norhis background.
He's a red hot
political economist.
Wiped the floorwith everyone.
- That's all right then.
- Why?
He'll knowhow to behave
ifhe went to an English University.
Even if itwas the L. S. E.
You said red hot,
were you speaking politically?
Partly.
You neverknowwith Charlie.
He follows you into a revolving
doorand comes out first.
No deep commitment?
- Only to Charlie.
- I see. A politician, Minister.
Very droll, Humphrey.
It'll be a couple of days.
Can't do much harm.
Always remember, Minister,
you wanted him here, not me.
It is afterhalf past, Minister.
When am I going to do
all this correspondence?
Well, Minister...
Well done, Minister.
Betterout than in.
22:30 Edinburgh train
will leave from Platform 7...
- Who is it?
- Bernard.
Come in.
Bernard, what's the matter?
- Will you read this, please?
- No, I will not.
- It's top priority...
- You always say that.
It is a copy of President Selim's
speech tomorrow.
I know these speeches:
Happy to be here,
bonds of shared experience,
- Ties between ourtwo countries.
- That is all in it, but...
- I'm not going to read it tonight.
- I think you should.
I've underlined
the important bits in red ink.
I'll just distribute some copies
around the train.
Around the train?
To Sir Humphrey, the Foreign
Secretary, the Press Officer...
"Burandans feel
a special affinity with the
Celtic peoples
in theirstruggle forfreedom.
We too had to fight
to break free
from the chains
of British colonialism".
Bristish colonialism?
"The people of Buranda
urge the Scots and the Irish
to end the English oppression,
cast off the imperialist yoke
and join the fellowship
of free nations".
Good God!
Yes.
We would appearto have been
caughtwith ourtrousers down.
He can't say this in front ofher.
I don't like to say I told you so.
- Egg all overourfaces.
- Not egg, just imperialist "yoke".
Three Scottish by-elections.
It is indeed a catastrophe.
A tragedy.
A cataclysmic, apocolyptic,
monumental calamity.
- And you did it.
- You're paid to advise me, advise me!
This is like trying to advise
the Captain of the Titanic
afterhe's struck the iceberg.
There must be
something we can do.
We could sing Abide with Me?
- Yes?
- Minister.
The Foreign Secretary
would like a word.
- Ah, Foreign Secretary.
- Have you read this...?
My Minister is concerned
thatwe will have egg
all overourface.
Scotch egg, presumably.
- Why is he doing it?
- Maybe it's forhome consumption.
Perhaps he's trying to persuade
the otherAfrican Leaders
that he's a pukka anticolonialist.
Yes? Yes, Bernard?
The Press Officer
would like a word.
Oh dear!
Room fora little 'un?
Do you think it's good idea
to issue a statement?
Well, Minister, in practical terms
we have the usual six options.
One, do nothing.
Two, issue a statement
deploring the speech.
Three, lodge an official protest.
Four, cut off aid.
Five, break off diplomatic relations.
- And six, declare war.
- Which should we do?
If we do nothing,
we implicity agree with the speech.
Two, if we issue a statement,
we just look foolish.
Three, if we lodge a protest,
itwill be ignored.
Four, we can't cut off aid
because we don't give them any.
Five, if we break off
diplomatic relations
we can't negotiate
the oil rig contracts.
And six, if we declare war it might
just look as if we were overreacting.
In the old days
we'd just send in a gun boat.
I suppose that is absolutely
out of the question?
- Yes?
- Minister...
The Permanent UnderSecretary
of the Foreign Office.
It'll be like
the Black Hole of Calcutta.
- May I come in, Minister.
- You can try.
This is all we needed.
Welcome
to the Standing Committee.
Sir Frederick, what are we going
to do about this?
Well, Minister,
Foreign Secretary...
I think...
I think we knowwhat's behind it,
don'twe, Humpy?
Humpy?
Sir Frederick is suggesting that
the offending paragraph may be
a bargaining counter.
- He wants something?
- Why send us an advance copy?
Why don't you find out
what it is he wants?
The Embassy staff are all new,
we've just seen the speech.
And no one knows anything
about this President.
Except me.
- Except you?
- They were at University together.
- The old boy network.
- Thatwas 25 years ago.
He may not even rememberme...
I don't really think I could...
You ought to see him.
I think you carry more weight.
Then the mountain
shall go to Mohammed?
No. No. No. Jim's going.
That's what I meant.
All right.
But you'll have to come with me.
Of course, Minister.
I'd hardly let you do it
on yourown.
Jim, come in.
- Hownice to see you again.
- Charlie... Long time no see.
You don't have to speak
pidgin English to me.
Sir Humphrey Appleby,
my Permanent UnderSecretary.
- Your Excellency.
- How do you do.
Do sit down.
Permanent UnderSecretary
is such a demeaning title.
I beg yourpardon?
Sounds like an Assistant Typist
orsomething,
whereas you're really
in charge of everything.
Well, not quite everything.
I should congratulate you
on becoming Head of State.
Oh, thanks.
Itwasn't difficult.
I didn't do boring things,
like fighting elections
orby-elections.
Jim, of course I'm delighted
to see you,
but is this purely a social visit,
or is there anything
you wanted to talk about?
I do have to finish my speech.
Ah... Well, yes... Actually,
we have seen an advanced copy...
You liked it?
Charlie, may I speak frankly?
- We're old friends.
- Of course.
You must realise that that bit
about colonialist oppression
was a bit...
well... um, very...
Well, actually
profoundly embarrassing.
That passage where you urged
the Scots and the Irish to er...
I wonder if you could um,
give it a miss?
- Give it a miss?
- Yes.
But, this is something I feel very,
very deeply to be true.
Surely the British don't believe
in suppressing the truth?
Good heavens no.
I wonder if there's anything
that might persuade you
to considerrecasting that sentence
and transfering the emphasis
from the specific instance
to the abstract concept
without in any way,
impairing the conceptual
integrity of the theme.
Yes...
May I change the subject?
Jim, while you're here may I sound
you out on a proposal
I was going to make
to the Prime Minister?
What proposal?
Our little change of Government
has quite unnecessarily alarmed
some of the investors
in ouroil industry.
Only temporarily,
but it does mean thatwe need
a little British investment
to tide us over.
To restore confidence, you know.
Howmuch?
Fifty million pounds.
Ask him on what terms.
On what terms?
Repayment of the capital
not to start before ten years.
And interest free.
Fifty million pounds...
it's a lot ot money.
I see, well in that case...
But that doesn't mean
we can't talk about it?
Interest free?
Ten years?
Assuming a 10 % interest,
he's asking fora free gift
of fifty million pounds.
Itwould appear
that you're asking for
a free gift
of about fifty million pounds.
But it's to youradvantage.
We would use the loan
to buy oil rigs built on the Clyde.
Ah, well.
He's asking us to give him
50 million pounds
so that he can buy
ouroil rigs with ourmoney.
Reasonable to me.
- Reasonable, Minister?
- Lots of jobs, Humphrey.
Supposing itwere possible
to do this deal,
would you find it possible
to make cuts in yourspeech?
Yes, but I'd have to knownow.
Blackmail!
Are you describing me,
ormy proposal?
Yourproposal, naturally.
No, no, not even yourproposal.
I think we can come
to agreement, don't you Humphrey?
Minister...
Could I have a word with you?
Yes?
Will you excuse us,
Your Excellency?
- Is anything wrong?
- Is anything right?
He's offering us a way out.
A gift of 50 million pounds
is a way out?
- It's a loan.
- We'll neverget it back.
You buy yourway out
of political involvement
with fifty million pounds
of public money?
- It's diplomacy.
- It's corruption, Minister.
K. B. E.
Humpy.
You mean...
Yes, I see.
I suppose we don'twant the Soviets
to invest in Buranda, do we?
And I suppose it could be argued
thatwe have a responsibility to the...
T. P. L. A. C.'s.
Yes, quite.
Oh, good.
Mr. President, I think we can
come to terms afterall.
- Well, you knowmy price.
- And you knowmine.
Everyone has his price.
Yes, Minister.