Come here, girl. Jess, Jess.
DOG BARKS
DOOR CHIMES
This way, Mrs Brompton.
Thank you.
To what do we owe the pleasure?
Well, it's that time of year.
Oh, the Daffodil Ball, I've been
counting the days.
And who's the lucky lass tonight?
Who can say at this point,
Mrs Brompton.
Ah, Jim, Jim, perfect timing.
Ah, wallet!
I'm sorry, what am I paying for now?
It's the Daffodil Ball tonight.
All proceeds go towards the
restoration of the steeple.
It's the highlight of the social
calendar.
There'll be music, dancing, the
frisson of a warm spring evening.
Mr Farnon not in?
He's yet to grace us
with his presence.
How about it, Mrs Hall, a ticket
for you?
Just four, please. Four?
Yeah, need one for my date
for the evening.
Your date?
The day is young.
Come on, Jim, no girl likes a
cheapskate.
Who's the extra one for?
Who do you think?
Time waits for no man, Jim lad, and
neither will Helen.
Morning, Mrs Brompton.
Diana - please.
How can we be of service?
Daffodil Ball.
If you're not too busy I wondered
if we might lure you on to the dance
floor.
Well, that depends what you're using
as bait.
SHE GIGGLES
Stop it.
It would be our pleasure to
support the cause.
Tristan, money? Yeah.
"Our pleasure" really?
And, uh, Mrs Hall, would you mind
showing Diana out?
Show her out?
We'll have to scrape her off him
first.
This way.
Swap. Thank you. Thank you,
bye-bye...
What?
What, is it?
I mean, if you can't see, then
there's really no hope for you,
brother.
If that woman were any more forward,
she'd be here yesterday.
Nonsense, Diana's happily married.
Isn't she?
Not any longer. Not for a year now.
Well, she was probably just
being friendly.
You know, I heard he ran off with
the housekeeper.
I heard the gardener.
How did you get on with Merrick last
night?
I thought you were going to tag
that on to the end of your list.
Oh, James, you really can't allow
yourself to be so forgetful.
The memory is a muscle that must be
exercised.
I'll get up there right away.
No, no, you've got a busy surgery
today.
Here.
Organised as ever.
Why doesn't Tristan stay
and help out?
With both examination rooms
in operation,
we'd get through them a lot quicker.
I'd like to keep Tristan under my
wing for a while.
He's still got a lot to learn.
Go on, go and get ready.
Mr Farnon - postcard from Dorothy.
Who's the old Siegfried?
And why does she hope he gets out
from time to time?
Sorry, I thought it were for me.
I didn't realise until it were too
late.
I'm sure.
HORN BLARES
All right, all right, I'm coming.
No Rover? Not today, it's leaking
oil everywhere.
Do your tie up, man, we must present
our very best self to our clients.
You know, you could do far worse
than Diana Brompton.
I see you got another postcard from
Dorothy.
How's Malta?
Hot and rocky.
She's looking forward to becoming a
grandmother.
Shame, I got the impression you were
rather fond of her.
Oh, hang on, hang on, slow down,
slow down.
Stop.
Morning, Helen.
All right, Triss, Siegfried.
What can I do for you?
Oh, it's not me, actually.
Um, I think James wanted to see
you about something.
He's at the house if you wanted to
pop in.
Right.
Thanks.
Bye. BOTH: Bye.
Helen. Hello.
Please, come in, come in.
Come on through.
There we are.
OK, then...
..how can I help?
I thought you wanted to see me.
You did? I mean, I do. Why wouldn't
I?
Of course I'd like to see you...
Right.
Only, I've got to get back and put
our carrots in, so, shall we?
Sorry, shall we what?
The reason you wanted to see me.
I'm not sure I understand -
you came here.
Because Tristan asked me to.
Ah.
He said you wanted to speak to me
about something.
I'm sure he did.
Well...
Triss and I are going to the
Daffodil Ball.
And I couldn't be happier for you.
Oh, no, no, he's not...
Not together.
I mean, well, we are but not...
James, it's fine...
..you have my blessings.
See, because of that...
..now I'm not inviting you.
I had a spare ticket but I'll just
have to give it to someone else.
Probably for the best.
I haven't really been out since...
..well...
No-one will care.
We'll go as a group, you, me,
Triss...
..whoever he manages to drag along.
I'm a terrible dancer,
so that amusement alone is a good
enough reason to come.
I don't know.
DOOR CHIMES
It's my dog.
He disappeared yesterday
evening on one of our walks.
I found him when I went back out
again this morning,
he must've been in this
trap all night.
Well, bring him through.
James!
DOG WHINES
I need you!
Don't worry, go.
We need to get him something for the
pain and sedated right away.
What's his name? It's Rock.
Mrs Hall, pass the cotton wool,
please.
You'll be able to save him,
won't you?
I can't tell.
I won't be able to tell you
until I've explored the wound.
Who would do such a thing?
It's monstrous.
Oh, it looks a mess.
I won't know until I'm right
inside how bad it is.
What I'd do for an X-ray machine
now.
Doesn't seem natural, being able to
see your insides on the outside like
that.
They're an incredible diagnostic
tool.
All right, he's asleep.
I don't think the leg's broken.
We better hope there's still some
circulation to the paw.
And if there's not?
I'm afraid he'll lose the foot.
Colonel, good morning.
Now, then, Farnon, what's all this
about?
We were expecting you last night.
Yeah, I'm afraid, there was
something
of an administrative balls up.
My colleague missed you off his
list.
Oh, and there I was believing I was
one of your most valued clients.
Oh, I'm almost hurt.
Rest assured, you have my undivided
attention now.
Bag please, Tristan.
Yes, err, unfortunately, I've
had to find another dance partner.
Sorry to say, too little, too late,
old chap.
Still, there's, there's nothing like
a bit of healthy
competition to keep you on your
toes, hey, Farnon?
Indeed.
George, what a qualified pleasure it
is to see you.
HE LAUGHS
Now, now, chaps, we mustn't
squabble.
I'd hate to be the bone between a
pair of scrapping dogs.
If you're finding yourself
unable to cope,
I could always take a few more
clients off your hands.
I'm perfectly capa... More than
capable, thank you.
Oh, there's no shame in admitting
you can't keep up.
The years are rolling on.
Ha-ha, the coup de grace.
Until next time, Hubert.
Rolling on? You're rolling on.
He's older than I am.
Still, since you've come all this
way,
there's no harm in you casting
an expert eye over her.
I imagine there wouldn't be a
charge - on account of all the
bother.
No, of course not, Hubert...
..anything for our most valued
customer.
I've asked this morning's clients to
come back this afternoon.
I don't understand why Siegfried
doesn't let Tristan run surgery.
If there were two of us, we wouldn't
have to send anyone away.
Mr Farnon has his ways...
..maddening as they might be.
It's best to let sleeping dogs lie.
Mm.
I'm not sure I'd describe Siegfried
as a sleeping dog.
Thanks.
How's he getting on?
I'd like to be able to give
Mr Hammond some good news.
I don't think the bone is broken.
We need to hope it's not infected.
Seems like a nice chap.
He does.
He is.
I better get a brew on before he
wears a hole in the floor.
I'll do the best I can.
102.5.
Stethoscope.
Thank you, Tristan.
Pandhi said her insides are blocked
up,
gave her some linseed oil to
grease the wheels.
Really?
Well, that's one way of doing it,
I suppose.
And that's not the treatment you'd
prescribe?
Well, we all have our different
approaches, Colonel.
And different degrees of success
that go with them.
COW MOOS
Yes, I thought so.
You're struggling, aren't you, old
girl?
Stomach powders. Coming right up.
I'm afraid there's definitely
a blockage.
It could be she's had too much
roughage and that's bunged
her up or there could be a wire or
something else caught up inside.
Well, it sounds serious.
More common than you'd think.
Did Pandhi not mention the
possibility?
I told my stock man to wait for you,
Farnon.
Lesson learned.
We'll start off with the powders to
help her work it through and
if that doesn't shift it, I'm afraid
we'll have to come back and operate.
COW MOOS
Mr Hammond?
Oh, noticed the timing's off.
Well, I put it forward every
morning.
Well, I could fix it for you, if you
like?
Oh, I've got used to it now.
Sometimes I put it forward more
than I should
to get them out the house sooner.
Well...
..there speaks a woman wise to the
world.
Wise to the lot I've been lumbered
with, certainly.
Sorry, I've never been good at
waiting for news,
I have to keep myself busy.
You and me both.
Mr Herriot is a wonderful vet.
If you want any more milk, you just
let me know.
I will.
I'm sorry, in the rush,
I didn't catch your name.
It's...
..Audrey.
Gerald.
Sugar, I forgot the sugar.
I'll just, um.
No, no, I can leave that.
And I'll come back with your, uh...
..with the, um... Sugar.
That's the chap.
What's this? It's the list.
The list, man. Don't look like that,
tell me what's next. Oh.
Mr Dinsdale.
Ah, yes, sow, aural haematoma.
See? All up here.
Why would you have Merrick
written twice?
Well, I wouldn't.
Unless this was left in your pocket
from last night.
Which would suggest you were
supposed
to go to Merrick's and not James?
What're you doing?
We must present our best self for
the clients, Siegfried.
Morning.
Oh, we thought it'd be a grand
adventure...
..too young to know any better.
You were in good company.
I should never have been there in
the first place,
I lied to the recruiting officer
about my age.
Oh, God, you were one of those...
..king, country.
The usual nonsense.
You know, funny thing is...
..I wouldn't change it for the
world.
Even though it left me hobbling
about.
The struggle makes everything all
the more worth it.
I'll keep telling myself that.
Mr Hammond, you can come through.
Thank you for the tea.
We've patched him up.
I'm worried there could be an
infection,
the wound must've been open for some
time.
If it spreads, it could poison the
blood stream.
And then what?
There's still a chance he could lose
the leg.
Hm, better that than his life.
Leave him with us for a few days.
Hey, you'll be all right, Rock, lad.
This nice gentleman and kind lady
are going to take care of you.
And Jess will keep him company.
Will we be seeing you at the dance
then?
God willing.
So long as you fulfil your
professional obligations first.
And, by God, I naturally mean my
brother.
Them eggs will not collect
themselves, you know.
Should have kept her locked in
the coal shed.
Our little Buttercup's in here.
Now, that boil on her noggin's even
bigger than last time you were up.
I didn't have the correct instrument
to complete the procedure.
Here's our little lass now.
Holy Mary, Mother of God.
Oh, yes ,I can see from here the
haematoma's even more engorged.
Ah, looks fit to burst.
I thought about going in and having
a go myself, like...
..not for very long, mind.
Yes, well, it's becoming apparent to
me
now why you might have left your
scalpel at home last time.
Thankfully, I believe we have it
here today. Mm.
I don't know why you're
handing that to me,
we learn by doing, little brother.
I imagine she's called Buttercup
because uh...
..well, despite appearances, she's
a tender and sweet soul at heart?
Not as it goes.
Nearly took me finger off once.
If she gets hold of you, my advice
is to play dead.
Unless you think she might actually
kill you,
in which case, don't...
..play dead, I mean.
Right.
Siegfried? Come now, Tristan.
It's alright to be frightened,
for without fear,
there cannot be courage.
Ha, without courage, there can't be
pain.
# I'm called Little Buttercup
# Dear Little Buttercup. #
Try not to startle it!
Forget the pig, you startled me!
Good Buttercup.
Good pig.
BUTTERCUP GRUNTS
Oh, God!
Oh, ah.
Mr Dinsdale, I fear we may have to
return with anaesthetic
to tame the beast before we operate.
Oh, aye, when would that be then?
Oh, not until this evening. What?
No, Siegfried, we can't come back.
Look, we're here now, I'll do it
now.
He's either very brave or very
stupid.
I believe it's a heady mixture of
both.
No courage without fear.
BUTTERCUP GRUNTS
Good God!
I admire your persistence
but sometimes discretion is
the better part of valour.
He's done it.
I'll be damned.
I did?
I mean, yes, I did.
Yes, well, you made a bit of meal of
it but you got there in the end.
Maybe I'll, uh, see you later.
Tristan, it's this way.
Frowning at it won't change it.
It's from a friend of my mum's.
He owns a vet's practice in Glasgow.
Hm.
They've offered me a job.
Well, I'm not surprised.
Who wouldn't want you working for
them?
Mum seems to have accepted it for
me.
Oh, dear.
The practice is run by a man
called Bill Weipers.
He's on the board at Glasgow
Veterinary College.
He employs modern methods
and equipment.
He has an immaculate practice,
sterile examination rooms, nurses,
X-ray machine.
And you got lumbered with us lot.
well, it's just a different...
..very different way of working.
If you ever have any ideas about how
you might improve this place,
I'm sure Mr Farnon would hear you
out.
If you catch him on a good day,
perhaps.
It's more complicated than
that, Dad's struggling to get work.
They're really struggling to
make ends meet.
Well, they'd want you to be happy.
As a parent, that's all you want for
your children.
It feels so selfish.
They spent their life savings
putting
me through college, I owe it to
them.
How long have you got to decide?
I've got a few months to work out
if there's something here worth
staying for.
Or someone?
Helen took the other one.
How many cases have we got to get
through this afternoon?
16.
We'll use both examination rooms.
While I'm treating an animal in
one...
I'll settle the next one into the
other room.
Once I've finished treatment, you
show them out, settle up the bill.
I'll go straight through to deal
with the next. Righto.
Hello, there.
Hello.
Good afternoon. Mr Herriot.
Afternoon. Hello.
Right, Mrs Kirkby, with a rabbit.
That's me.
Lovely.
Miss Fearnly? Yes, lovely.
Would you like to come through?
Thank you, Mrs Jackson.
Keep George warm by the fire,
that'll help speed up the waking
process.
Thank you, love.
It's Anne with Susie.
I'll be with you in a second.
And don't you look happy about it.
Sorry, I've been rushed off my feet.
Hello, Susie.
How're you getting on with those
pups of yours?
They're all grand.
First one you got out's
biggest of the lot.
We named him James.
I'll have to come up and visit him.
Don't worry, Susie. Hey, we just
need to check how you're getting on.
BELL RINGS
Excuse me. Come on through.
Hi, Helen. Hi.
You look...
It's good to see you.
Shall I come in?
Yes ,of course.
I'm just finishing up, I won't be
long, I swear.
She won't mind waiting.
Oh, hello.
Tea? I think so.
Oh, you've certainly put
the weight back on.
Sorry, Susie.
That's very rude of me, isn't it?
You know, if ever you're to get
beyond smiling at the girl...
..you might eventually have to do
something about it.
What happened to the other one?
What?
I thought we could chat.
Um..
..yeah, great, OK.
The other one, the barmaid,
Margaret?
Maggie? I suppose she got sick of
you.
Yeah, the thing about Maggie and me
is we're like ships in the night.
Travelling our own separate
courses...
..occasionally we...
..crash into one another during
stormy weather.
Meanwhile, you happily flit...
..courting one girl and then the
next.
First of all - no-one courts.
Then what are they doing?
They date.
We're not Americans.
The world's changing.
Not every evening spent in the
company of a woman
necessarily has to end in something
particularly meaningful.
In fact, most often it necessarily
doesn't.
Then what's the point of it all?
Fun.
I understand that's a very alien
concept to you.
I am fun, I'm perfectly bloody fun.
You certainly used to be.
Now I don't know what's happened.
What's that supposed to mean?
You didn't used to be like this.
Like what?
Allowing Merrick to get a free
ride...
..letting Pandhi rattle you and...
..don't even get me started on the
women.
Well, I imagine the problem's
getting you to stop.
There's no spirit, the fight's gone.
I assure you, it has not.
Really?
Cos in the not too distant past,
you would've tackled that sow
without a moment's hesitation,
just to show people that you could.
I'm not saying you're past it but...
You just did!
Stuck in a rut maybe, one that I
thought Dorothy
had got you out of it but...
I'm not in a rut, there is no bloody
rut!
Oh, I'll get that for you.
Bye. Bye.
Good evening, good evening, Mrs
Hall, Helen, a delight as ever.
What happened to you?
Fight with a pig.
Is it hard to believe
I actually won?
Bring your muddy things down,
don't leave them festering on the
floor.
It's been a long day.
You must barely recognise me.
Oh, I don't know Siegfried,
I think you've weathered rather
well.
You're very kind.
How've you been?
You know, one foot in front of the
other.
Glad to hear it.
There you are, James.
About bloody time, poor Helen's
being bored silly waiting.
I'm fine, Mrs Hall's been looking
after me.
I had an emergency case,
I've been playing catch up all day.
You should really learn to deal
with these cases.
No wonder we're struggling
to turn a profit.
I would say, Siegfried,
if Tristan were here today,
there would've been no need to
send anyone away.
I want him with me until he's served
some time under my supervision.
He's more than capable.
Oh, see how they shower me with
praise?
Perhaps this could wait for another
time?
No, if James has got something he
wants
to get off his chest, I'd like to
hear it.
If Tristan were able to practise on
his own, we could take on more work.
With the extra money, maybe we could
change a few things around here.
Change? Why on earth would
we want to change?
We could be working much more
efficiently,
half of our equipment
is from the last century.
So am I! Should we just toss me
out as well?
I don't think James means that.
Of course I don't.
Siegfried, I learned more from you
in a year
than I did in all the time I spent
at college.
You flatter to deceive.
It's true...
..he told me as much before.
I just want to be able to offer the
best care possible to our patients.
Of course, as do I.
You know I'm always open to new
ideas.
HE CHUCKLES
What?
I am.
Did you know we were the first
practice in whole of Yorkshire
to have our own centrifuge for TB
testing?
And I always put us forward
for the trial of new medications.
We are a forward looking practice.
And I am one who always looks ahead,
rather than behind - always.
Semper progrediens!
Always progressing. I know.
Good. Well, that all seems settled
then.
Now, shouldn't you be going before
something or other
turns into a pumpkin?
Semper progrediens!
I believe he's fighting the
inevitable march of time.
Oh, Lord help us.
Go on, get on with you, I've my book
to read.
James...
..good luck.
You sure you won't come?
Oh, it's not for me.
Listen to that, Jess.
Isn't that wonderful?
You'll be fine.
Dorothy happen to mention
when she'll be returning?
She has no plans at the moment.
Oh, and how do you feel about that?
How do I feel?
When you care about someone very
much, you...
People have these things,
feelings, emotions.
Dorothy's a good friend - nothing
more.
Understood.
Well, then...
..without fear...
There can be no courage.
Once more unto the breach.
Diana.
Good evening. Good evening to
you.
You're looking stunning. Thank you.
How many do you think he'll
dance with tonight?
I've a feeling that once she gets a
hold of him...
..she won't be letting go.
My mum used to make me
go to tea dances with her.
It used to be me and a room full of
old ladies.
Mum used to make me stand up in
front of all of them
and request songs from the singer.
She didn't? I had to dance with
her...
..and all her friends.
That's why I find it the most
embarrassing
thing in the world to do.
It's probably why I'm terrible at
it.
Oh, James, stop it.
You're just saying it to make me
feel better.
So, I apologise in advance for the
absolute shambles
this'll inevitably be
but would you like to dance?
I promise once people see me
out there,
no-one is going to be talking
about your wedding with Hugh.
You'd really do that?
You'd make a complete fool out of
yourself for me?
Every single day.
No Maggie tonight, then?
No, no, boyfriend. Her, not me.
That were very clever of you,
tricking that pig in to bursting its
own bubble.
There'd be some who'd mistake
it for you running away.
Yes, well, it often takes brains
as well
as brawn to solve these problems.
Hm, I'd settle for a pretty face.
How about it, then?
Oh, sadly, Anabel, I'm just not
one of life's dancers.
Oh, that's handy...
..because I'm not one for dancing
either.
Outstanding.
I've no idea what I'm doing.
Don't worry, you're doing fine.
Ooh. Sorry.
It's alright, I've got another one.
Look, try and loosen up, let
yourself go with it.
That's it, that's better.
Ooh!
That's a little too much.
I was sorry to hear about you
and your husband.
Which was it, the housekeeper or the
gardener?
Oh, I don't hold for such
tittle-tattle.
Both, actually.
I wouldn't blame him if it was the
gardener - he was quite the dish.
There's even one going round
where I've got old Len buried in the
basement.
That's why no-one's seen him
for so long.
I don't mind that one so much,
it keeps everybody on their toes.
Farnon, we've got ourselves a bit of
a problem.
Yes, Colonel, I believe we have.
I was in the middle of a charming
conversation with
this young lady and I've been rudely
interrupted.
I beg your pardon?
You can beg all you like,
you're not having it.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
You see, Colonel, what did I tell
you?
He's lost it.
I do apologise, Diana.
Oh, no need.
I love a bit of drama.
Now hear this, Farnon, that cow is
still unwell.
You told me it needed an operation.
If you're not willing to come up
and sort her...
..well, I can always take my custom
elsewhere.
Custom suggests a transfer of money
for services rendered.
I put a lot of work your way.
Because we're the finest in the
district.
We've three qualified vets and
enough work
to necessitate the expansion of our
practice.
We don't have to fight like jackals
over scraps left by others.
If you really want the best possible
care for your animals,
you can call during our normal
business hours.
Otherwise, go with the reserve team.
Good evening.
Good evening? I'll give you good
evening!
That was very impressive.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
No idea, I always like to sweep
out at the end of an argument.
But since we're on the move, might I
suggest somewhere more salubrious?
The Renniston, perhaps? Why not?
Sorry again about your toes.
Oh, it was great.
You were great.
It's been so long since...
I really needed that.
I'm glad.
I'll, er, I'll fetch our drinks.
Don't forget to come up for air.
Goodnight, Tristan.
Helen, been awhile. How've you been?
Yeah, not bad. You?
Oh, same as always...
What do you say then, lass,
Fancy a turn around the floor?
Oh, Fernley, this is... Hello.
I'm James Herriot.
Right, nice.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to... If you two are
together, then.
Us? Oh, no, we're not.
Are we? No, not at all.
Only, we were known to have the odd
dance in the past.
We even won a show together.
Go on, at least he won't stand on
your toes.
Right.
Really, no trouble.
Enjoy yourself.
Thanks, James.
Idiot.
Tea, Siegfried?
If you wouldn't mind, Tristan,
thank you, very kind.
When. Bless you.
Good evening? Oh, very much so.
How long's this going to go on for?
What?
The inane expressions...
..the smug sense of satisfaction.
Mrs Hall, I would've thought
you'd be glad
to hear we enjoyed ourselves last
night.
Oh, it's enough to put me off my
breakfast.
What about James?
Did he enjoy himself?
PHONE RINGS
Darrowby, two, two, nine, seven.
One moment.
Mr Farnon.
Colonel Merrick.
Yes, what, is it?
Oh, you do?
Yes, well, I'll have to consult our
appointment diary first.
Three o'clock?
Breakfast's on the table.
I'll be there in a minute.
SIEGFRIED: See you then.
How'd it go?
He's doing all right, temperature's
down.
The infection is starting
to clear up.
You can call Mr Hammond and tell him
to pick him up later.
That's not what I meant.
Oh, love.
It's alright.
There are a lot of people Helen
needs to catch up with.
SIEGFRIED: Herriot!
Tristan!
I'm literally three feet away from
you.
I don't understand why you
have to bellow.
Don't be such a sensitive Sidney.
Here.
I've been keeping these back, one
each.
And what are these for?
You said you wanted us to modernise,
James?
We're about to give the good Colonel
a show he'll never forget.
Morning, Colonel.
No Pandhi today?
You're our vet, Farnon, for now, at
any rate.
Well, I'm glad we managed to squeeze
you in.
Yes, prepare the patient
for the operation.
COW MOOS
Thank you.
Right. This is where we go in.
I hope you aren't squeamish,
it's not for the faint hearted.
I've seen blood before, you needn't
worry, I shan't faint.
Now, you see the rumen exposed,
the cow's first stomach,
you know they have four?
Hang on Farnon, that doesn't look
too clever.
Um, yes, it's probably just
a bit of ruminal gas.
Wouldn't you say?
Aye, probably.
James, could I borrow you for a
second?
Farnon, what was it you said,
the finest vet in the district?
You're putting on a right show, now.
Siegfried, do you not think
the good Colonel could
benefit from seeing some of your
handiwork up close?
You know, you really are full
of good ideas at the moment, James.
Yes, Colonel, come in.
Come in, that's it.
That's it, a little closer.
Scalpel, please.
There we are. Thank you.
Ready, Colonel?
Oh, get on with it, Farnon.
Oh, oh.
COLONEL MERRICK: Absolutely...
That's what the problem was. What do
you make of that?
Farnon, what the...
It's Mr Farnon...
..and my bill will be in the post.
Well, I thought that went rather
well. Mm.
Absolutely. Quite the show.
Text book.
COLONEL MERRICK: God, absolutely
covered in the stuff.
You'll have to keep him inside for a
few days
to keep the wound clean.
But I'm pleased with how the
infection is clearing up.
Well, we can't thank you enough,
Mr Herriot.
No trouble at all.
Mrs Hall will show you out.
Come on, then, Rock, here we go.
It looks like these two have
become firm friends.
Oh, we'll be sorry to see him go.
Won't we, Jess?
I'm sure they could see each other
again.
We could take them for a walk
together.
One of the men usually take Jess
out.
Ah, well, never mind.
Maybe we'll see you out
and about, hey, Jess.
When you grow tired of moving
your clock forward,
let me know and I'll come fix it.
Lost time is never found again.
Come on, Rock, let's go.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, Helen, love, good to see you.
Is James about?
In there.
Come in.
I'm just clearing up, won't be a
second.
Sorry we lost each other last night.
Oh, it's fine, don't worry.
It's been so long since I caught up
with everyone.
I've known most of them since we
were kids.
Oh, it's all right, I understand.
It was the same for me when I went
home, seeing everyone again.
It feels strange hearing you call
somewhere else home.
You belong here.
This is your home.
I looked for you last night,
couldn't find you?
I got dragged into a conversation
outside
with Gene Gilbert and
Mr Summers.
Once they get their teeth in,
they're hard to shake off.
I would've liked to have danced with
you again.
If your toes could take it.
Last night were the first time in a
long time
that I've felt like myself again...
..and I was only there because of
you.
Everything all right with
Miss Alderson?
Aye, grand.
Everything's grand.