My siblings and I
are the first vampires
in all of history,
the original family.
3 centuries ago, we helped build
a town called New Orleans.
Now a plot by witches
has lured me back,
hopping that I will
defeat a tyrant,
a vampire I created.
My brother hopes
I will find redemption
through the power of family,
a miracle child,
part werewolf,
part vampire, a hybrid.
My sister is doubtful.
She thinks I am
beyond redemption.
Despite my brother's
best efforts,
I have a plan of my own.
I will take back my home
and claim what was mine.
I will be King.
The city of New Orleans.
People of all stripes
and flavors
from all over the country come
here to party on our streets.
Some are just looking for fun,
some are looking for something
a little darker,
more dangerous.
So we invite them
into my home,
and we give it to them.
Then at the stroke of midnight,
everything changes,
and it's time to feed.
This is how I keep
my guys happy,
the occasional
all-you-can-eat buffet.
My nightwalkers love it.
Got them working hard
trying to earn
one of these
daylight rings.
They deserve to blow off
a little steam.
My daywalkers,
the trusted few,
they just like to party.
It's quite
an operation.
Tell me, what
about the victims?
Seems like a lot
of graves to dig.
Can't kill them all.
Too many folks go missing,
tourism drops,
so we heal them
with a little vamp blood,
erase their memory,
send them on their way,
no muss, no fuss.
I'm impressed.
Nothing I didn't learn
from you back in the day.
Marcel.
What's up, Thierry?
6 of our guys
were killed in a bar
outside of the quarter,
nightwalkers.
No one saw who.
Elijah, if not
answering your phone
was part of your clever plan
to get me back
to this godforsaken city,
then well done.
I'm here,
and I'm worried.
Now pick up before I kick in
your bloody door.
Who the hell
are you?
Ahh. You must be
the maid.
My bags are in the car.
Get them, will you?
Hello. Not the maid.
Right. You're that
werewolf girl
my brother Klaus
knocked up.
I was expecting
to see some kind
of supernatural
miracle baby bump.
Guess you're not
showing yet.
It's Hayley, isn't it?
You have your
brother's manners.
And his temper, too,
so watch it.
Where's Elijah?
Beats me.
He's long gone.
What do you mean
long gone?
Well, one minute
he was here
making epic promises
about protecting me
in this predicament
that a bottle of scotch
and some bad decisions got me into,
he was all poetic
about how we're family,
and then Klaus
told he me bailed.
Guess that's what I get
for trusting a vampire.
Elijah is not just
any vampire,
and he doesn't
break promises,
which means Niklaus has done
something dastardly and Klaus-like.
Klaus, get out here
and tell me what you've done
with our brother, you narcissistic,
back-stabbing wanker!
Enough with all
the shouting.
Little sister.
I should have known.
I assume the 6 dead
vampires were your doing.
They were very rude...
Aah!
Trying to victimize
a poor, innocent girl
just trying to find
her way to the quarter.
So sorry. Were they
friends of yours?
Oh, that's right.
You don't have any friends.
I do have friends.
I have Marcel.
You remember him,
don't you?
Yes, of course
you do.
He fancies himself.
The king of quarter now,
and he has these rules
about killing vampires.
It will be fun to see
what sort of punishment
he comes up with
for you.
I don't care
about Marcel or his rules.
Elijah doesn't welsh
on deals.
What did you
do to him?
Perhaps he's
on holiday
or taking a long
autumn nap upstairs.
Well, go on.
Take a look around.
You remember this house
as well as I.
I remember
everything.
I remember how the drunken fool
of a Governor hid away
all our vampire sins
in exchange for gold.
I remember the lavish parties
the Governor threw
as if to impress you.
I remember finding
a moment of affection
with the Governor's son Emil...
And I remember that
even Elijah was happy.
Your brother,
he's gone too far.
Niklaus, there is no hope for you,
is there?
Are we interrupting?
Yes.
No.
Dearest Elijah,
you've only ever wished
happiness for me.
Emil and I are
in love.
Please let me
turn him.
Heh heh heh!
Rebekah, the Governor
has graciously agreed
to hide a lot of our...
Indiscretions.
It would not do to turn
his only son into one of us.
Please for me.
It's not gonna happen,
sister.
If we turned every man you
dropped your knickers for,
then human beings
would cease to exist,
and we'd have
no bloody food.
How dare you, sir!
You would do well
to... aagh!
Drop him.
Klaus!
Klaus, drop him.
Wait!
No!
Get him out!
Well, he wasn't
good enough for you.
No one was ever good
enough for me, Nik.
You made sure
of that.
Now where's Elijah?
Where are you going?
It appears the night
is not quite over yet.
I'm off for another
drink with Marcel.
Elijah told me
your plan to take apart
Marcel's empire
piece by piece.
I don't remember it
involving you two drinking
New Orleans dry together.
I know you don't have
many friends, Rebekah,
but what some friends do when
they get together is they drink,
and when they drink,
they tell secrets.
Marcel has somehow
found a way to control
the entirety of witches
in the quarter,
and I aim
to uncover the how
so I might take it
for myself.
Finding Elijah didn't
make my to-do list today.
Oh. And welcome home,
little sister.
You, wolf girl.
I'm gonna search this
house inch by inch
until I find what my evil
brother has done to my good one.
You're helping.
The Governor had lots
of secret rooms.
I'll show you
his favorite.
You think Klaus
killed him.
We can't be killed,
silly girl,
but that doesn't stop Klaus
from finding ways
to torture us.
He has a set
of mystical silver daggers.
One in the heart sends
us into a deep slumber.
Klaus gets his jollies
from keeping us in a box
until he decides
to pull the dagger out.
That must be what he's done
to Elijah.
This one's mine.
He keeps your coffin
on standby?
He likes to be prepared
for when his family members
inevitably disappoint him.
Elijah's isn't here.
He must have stashed
him elsewhere.
I feel sick.
Welcome
to the family, love.
You should have run the second
your realized Elijah was gone.
Yeah. Well,
the witches have put
some sort of hex
on me.
As long as I'm
carrying this baby,
I can't leave
New Orleans.
If I do,
they kill me.
Well, knowing Klaus,
he's planning a box for you
the second you give birth to
whatever's cooking in your tum.
I'm leaving as soon
as I find Elijah.
Being daggered in a box
for decades sucks.
Trust me.
You best find a way
to break that hex and run.
Hello?
Seriously, Marcel?
Trying to scare me?
I had nothing to do
with the attack
on your guys last night.
Sophie Deveraux.
My brother Elijah
told me about you.
Know who I am?
Yeah, I know.
Then you know we
need to talk.
So if I had to guess,
knowing Klaus' history,
Elijah has a dagger
in his chest.
It's a magical object.
You're a witch.
Do a locator spell,
locate the dagger,
locate Elijah.
I can't use magic.
It's punishable
by death.
Marcel's rules.
Marcel? What do you think
I'm going to do to you
if you don't give me
what I want?
Not much.
I've been linked,
so anything you
do to me,
you do to Hayley.
Who?
Oh. Right.
The mumsy.
Well, luckily for you,
Elijah seems to care about her.
Otherwise, I'd break
your neck right here.
How did Marcel get
so bloody powerful anyway?
It wasn't like this
when I left 11 years ago.
Marcel has a way
to tell whenever
there's magic done
in the quarter.
The how isn't relevant.
I'll tell you what's
not bloody relevant.
A coven of witches
who can't do magic.
Here's an idea.
Move away.
We practice
ancestral magic.
This cemetery is
filled with the remains
of our witch ancestors.
Without access to them,
we're powerless.
If we run, we're leaving
our legacy behind,
our home, our family.
Well, family's overrated.
Look at me.
I'm back in a city that's
given me nothing but heartache,
looking for a brother
who's hell-bent
on protecting a baby
I don't care about.
I find that hard
to believe.
You're here,
aren't you?
I'm here for Elijah.
The instant I find him,
I'm gone.
He was the one who
idiotically believed
this baby would be
Niklaus' redemption,
and now he's missing, probably
at the hands of Klaus himself,
and you were foolish
enough to believe
that Elijah could convince
Klaus to go against Marcel
when everyone knows
that they have a history.
Klaus sired Marcel,
I'm aware.
You don't understand.
Marcel is not just
some guy
that Klaus turned
into a vampire.
Klaus loved him
like a son.
I was there the day
that they met.
We were burying Emil,
the Governor's only son.
Ow! Ow!
Turns out
the Governor had another son
from a mother that he owned.
Oww!
Owww!
What is your name?
Don't got one.
Mama wouldn't name
me till I turned 10
case the fever
took me.
Then it took her.
You're a survivor,
and survivors
need names.
How about Marcellus?
Marcellus?
It comes from Mars,
the God of war,
and it means
little warrior.
Perhaps there is hope for
our brother after all.
Klaus saw himself
in the boy.
He remembered how
our father used to beat him.
He, too, was
the bastard child
of a man who saw him
as nothing but a beast.
And that is why
your plan will fail.
All you've done is bring back
together two long lost souls.
Without Elijah
between them,
who knows
what they'll do?
Well, this is a far cry
from last night's party.
Ahh. In pursuit of the bartender
from Rousseau's, I see.
She's a work
in progress.
And yet here you are,
pining over her
when you should be
eating her for lunch.
Well, she must be special.
Business first.
The coroner called.
He's got my number in case
any dead tourists show up.
Let me guess. Dead tourists
with a stamp on their hand
and vampire blood
in their veins.
It happens.
Someone takes a drunken tumble
off a balcony or
into the Mississippi,
and today, I've got two
of them to deal with.
Excuse me, love.
What's that
you're studying?
Abnormal psychology.
Abnormal psychology. Well...
Perhaps you could help me
diagnose my friend over here.
He's been a little bit
depressed.
Can't keep his mind
off a girl.
He tells me she's a queen
fit for a King.
I think he should
cut his losses and move on.
What's your
professional opinion?
Be a nice guy,
and maybe the opportunity
will present itself
someday.
How about tonight,
9:00?
I'll meet you
right here.
I'll take it
under consideration.
Hmm. Harsh.
I daresay I've
lost my touch,
or you've lost yours.
Oh. Hey, hey, wait.
We're closed. Sorry.
I just need one teeny
tiny little herb.
Please.
Which herb?
Crushed aconite flower.
Wolfsbane?
That's a poison.
Looking to kill a wolf?
Just a little one.
Give me a minute.
Cut it with jimson weed,
a few drops in some hot tea.
That should do it.
Here.
It's an ugly town
for wolves.
You're doing
the right thing.
Hey. Want to gain points?
Tell Marcel there's
a werewolf in the quarter.
You take me
to the nicest places.
Welcome to the land
of the newly dead.
I won't waste your time.
I trust you filled
them in.
To be honest, not much in
the way of potential here.
Yeah? Well, I just lost
6 nightwalkers.
I got wholes to fill.
I'll keep this quick.
That itch you feel,
that's the need to feed
coming on strong,
a hunger for human blood.
Drink it,
you're a vampire.
Don't, you die again,
this time for good
right here in a body bag.
Hey. What are you thinking,
cute, dorky girl
or gay best friend?
Dealer's choice.
Dealer's choice. Ok.
Whoever picks up this coin
gets to live forever.
The other one dies.
Damn, girl!
I said damn!
How could you?
Get over it, Josh!
It's not like I had a choice.
You would have done
the same thing
but you're such
a little, measly...
let her die
in cold storage.
Got a thing about people
who betray their own friends.
Come on. Let's go
for a ride.
Go.
Attaque au fer.
Now counter-parry.
A hit! Palpable hit.
I'm gonna marry you
someday.
I would never marry someone
who couldn't best me in a duel.
Another lesson?
Huh!
Hyah!
Rebekah Mikaelson.
Come to teach me
another lesson?
Last time I saw you,
royal street was burning,
and you all
were fleeing the city
from your daddy.
Thought you
were dead.
You never looked back
to find out.
Why are you here?
Elijah. I think Klaus has
done something to him.
Stop. Stop right there.
If there's one thing
I've learned about you Mikaelsons,
it's don't get in the middle
of family feuding.
Doesn't end well.
There's nothing
going on between us.
I swear it on my life.
Your life means
something to me.
Give me the privilege
of honesty,
or that will cease
to be the case.
I like her,
and I think it's mutual,
but I haven't done anything
about it, and I wouldn't, not...
and you won't.
I love my sister,
but she lacks fortune
when it comes to men.
They come and go for her,
but I am the constant.
She's my family.
You said
I was family.
I have begged you to
turn me into a vampire.
And I told you I will turn
you when you're ready.
You go near Rebekah again,
and you never will be.
Even after
all you've achieved,
you're still scared
of him.
I'm not scared
of anyone.
If I find out you know
where Elijah is,
you needn't fear Klaus.
I'll kill you myself.
Nostalgia's
a blast and all,
but I can't help you.
It's nice seeing
you, though.
Good luck finding
what you're looking for.
I know that face.
Woman trouble.
You're a dick,
you know that.
Why didn't you tell me
your sister's back in town?
I thought it would be more amusing
for you to find out for yourself.
Is there anything else
that I need to know?
Only that she's grown
considerably more insane
in the last century.
Or maybe that it was her
who killed my guys.
Doubtful.
Unless that biker bar
is frequented by small-town
high-school quarterbacks,
I can't imagine
she'd be interested.
Yeah?
Just got a tip someone
saw a werewolf in Bienville Park.
Get a couple nightwalkers
to run it down.
Bring me back
its head.
Well, I guess that
solves the mystery
of the murdered
riffraff.
At least my sister's
in the clear.
About that.
I don't have time
for Mikaelson
family drama.
You're my guest.
Keep your sister in line.
I have a greater chance
of draining
the Mississippi
with a straw!
Come on, Hayley.
One upset stomach,
and all this stupid drama
is ancient history.
Dumb moving coming
into the quarter.
You're coming
with me, wolf.
I have had it
to here with vampires
telling me what to do!
Aah! Ugh!
Unh!
Now that is no way
to treat a pregnant lady.
I do hate bad manners.
This is why I told you
never to leave the house.
Werewolves are banned
in the quarter.
I had a plan,
and your little nighttime stroll
put it all in peril.
Leave him!
You've done enough,
don't you think,
leaving a trail
of bodies like
a roadmap
to my door?
If I hadn't overheard this lot
bragging about werewolf heads,
everyone here
would be screwed,
and don't give me
that crap about having a plan.
You've had all the time
in the world
to execute a plan,
and no one's seen you
do a damn thing!
Elijah made a deal
to protect your child
so that he could save you from
your selfish, rotten self.
You obviously don't
give a damn
about the child
or Elijah
because what have you
done to honor it?
I have done
everything.
Let me spell it out
for you, shall I?
From the day I arrived,
Marcel hasn't trusted me.
From day one, he's
had his vampires
ingest
toxic vervain,
which as you know,
little sister,
protects them from
my mind control.
I needed a spy,
someone on the inside
with me
who Marcel
would never suspect,
so I created a day zero
and got there first.
Unh!
Hey.
Marcel had just lost
6 vampires
thanks to your
little murder spree,
and he needed
new recruits,
so I made
the new one mine
before he'd had
even a drop of vervain.
Now let's have
a little chat
about what you can
do for me.
But we all know
the real way to a man
is through
his heart, so...
So my mate Marcel...
nice bloke,
don't you think?
No.
He's charming,
sexy, confident,
incredibly hot,
but let's be honest,
he's a bad boy, right, like you,
and right now,
I only need good in my life,
not someone who's...
tragically wounded
and damaged
by demons
he can't escape.
The damaged ones, they're not good,
at least not for me.
I understand, I do.
However, give him
one chance.
Then I need you to
tell me where he goes
and who he sees.
Compel him to believe
his mates found religion
and moved to Utah
so that he can
explain to Marcel
why he lost 3 more
vampires tonight.
Does anyone have
any more questions?
No. Good because
I have a question, Hayley.
What were you doing
in the bloody French quarter
in the first place?
Answer me!
Nik, leave her be.
You want to know
what I was doing?
I was buying poison
so I could put
your little baby
out of its misery.
Nik!
Keep your hands
off her.
She is pregnant
for God's sake!
All of this bluster
about not wanting the child,
and then the second she tells you
she's ready to get rid of it...
It's ok to care.
It's ok
to want something.
That's all Elijah
was trying to do,
all he's ever
wanted for you,
all we've ever wanted.
I gave Elijah
to Marcel.
What?
Marcel was nervous.
It was bad enough one
original returned to town,
but two?
His crew was
getting antsy.
He wanted
Elijah gone,
so I gave him
a peace offering.
You bartered our brother.
I have a plan.
Gain Marcel's trust,
dismantle
his empire,
honor Elijah's wish
that that baby be born.
I am executing that plan
the only way I know how.
If you don't
like it,
there's the door.
See if I care.
I know you don't know me very well,
but thanks.
I appreciate what
you did in there.
Us girls have got to
look out for each other.
What is it
with you two?
I mean, you say
you hate him,
but the way you deal
with him, it's so clear.
Even when you hate him,
you still love him.
I guess when you spend
a thousand years with someone,
deciding to
quit them is like
losing a part
of yourself,
but sometimes,
the hate is just so powerful.
Emil wasn't
the only boyfriend
of mine that
Klaus killed.
He did it again
and again
every time I found
someone to care about.
He just kept
doing it
until finally I stopped
falling in love.
He said he was protecting
me from my mistakes,
that no one was ever good
enough for his little sister
until one day
someone was.
How was the river?
It's cool, sweet.
I should go inside.
My brother will kill you.
Then I'll
die smiling.
Did I not warn you?
Klaus, I beg of you!
He is not like any other.
You saw it in him
from the very first day.
You saved him,
protected him.
You raised him.
You cannot kill him.
You are right.
I cannot.
Ohh!
But you,
dear sister,
need a lesson
in what you can
and cannot take
from me.
If you know Marcel
has Elijah,
why don't you just
get him back yourself?
Because if I cross
my brother,
then there's still a coffin
downstairs with my name on it.
Oh, my God.
I found them
under your coffin,
so if a couple
of antique steak knives
were the only thing stopping
you from getting Elijah back,
then here you go.
I sent everyone
home for the night.
I am your
humble host.
Well, ok.
Extra points for flair.
And the night's
just started.
What made you
decide to come?
Everyone deserves
a chance.
You lied to me.
Where's my brother?
Hello to you, too.
Cami, Rebekah,
Rebekah, Cami.
I see you still have
a thing for blonds.
Hey!
Tell me where
Elijah is.
What the hell
is going on?
Tell me where he is,
or I will kill you!
No, you won't.
Perhaps you're right.
But I will kill her.
Let her go.
You won. I'll take
you to see Elijah?
Ohh! What the hell
are you people?
Shh. It's ok.
Go home, forget all this,
and just know that
I will make it up to you,
I promise.
You want to
see Elijah?
Fine. Follow me.
Invite me in.
Got to ask the lady
of the house!
Davina, come on out,
sweetheart.
Invite her in.
Come in.
I wouldn't do that.
Who the hell
are you?
Davina.
She's an old one,
isn't she?
Yeah. Rebekah is
an original,
which means she
can't be killed.
She doesn't seem
very nice.
She can be,
but she hasn't been
very nice to me tonight.
Then I'm afraid it's time
for you to leave.
Aah!
Well, it's about time.
I was bored waiting,
but I did so want
to see your face,
and it is
indeed priceless.
You bastard.
What day is it?
Sunday.
I have been daggered
for a whole week?
Marcel... what have
you done to him?
It's 1887, Rebekah.
You've been daggered
for 52 years.
What?
And don't worry
about Marcel.
I presented him
with a choice.
He could choose
to undagger you
and live out the rest
of his human days with you,
or I could turn him
instead,
as he's always wanted,
in exchange
for giving you up.
No. He wouldn't
do that to me.
Oh, but he did.
Welcome back,
Rebekah.
You were out
for quite a while.
Where am I?
How did I get here?
You upset Davina.
I'm glad you two
finally got to meet.
Now you know what
you're dealing with.
Is this my old room?
Oh, it's mine now
just like this town is
mine, Davina's mine,
and Elijah's mine
until I feel like giving him back.
What was once yours,
what was once your brother's
it's now mine.
And don't ever touch
Cami again.
I didn't use it.
You're awake.
I could barely
sleep all night.
This house is like
a freaking swamp sauna.
What stopped you?
You could have been free
of all of this,
of me.
Yeah. Well, when I was
fighting off those vampires,
I realized I wasn't
just protecting myself.
Maybe it has to do
with the fact that
my birth parents
gave me up
and my adoptive parent
kicked me out.
All I know is
push came to shove,
and I realized I wouldn't
let anyone hurt it.
I'm beginning to think
we're a lot a like,
you and I.
We're both castoffs
who've learnt to fight
when we're backed
into a corner.
Well, we're backed
into a corner now.
Ah. That we are.
It's time to fight...
Little wolf.
This whole thing
with Marcel,
the deal you have
with the witches,
trying to take him down,
take what's his,
Rebekah told me that you two once
loved each other like family.
What happened?
I made Marcel
everything that he is,
I treated him like a son,
and when my father chased
me and my family
from New Orleans
a hundred years ago,
we believed Marcel
was killed.
We each mourned him
in our own way.
Yet when I returned,
I found not only had he survived,
he had thrived.
Instead of seeking us out,
instead of sticking
together as one,
he made a choice
to take everything
my family had built
and make it his own.
Now he is living
in our home,
he is sleeping in our beds.
The letter "M"
he stamps everywhere,
it's not for "Marcel,"
it's for Mikaelson.
I want it all back,
and if I have to push
him out to get it,
then that's exactly
what I'll do.
I'll have somebody see
to the air conditioning.
You're right.
The girl Cami, she's the key.
Marcel likes her,
and because of that,
I got to see
the secret weapon
of his that you've
been going on about.
Well, don't stand
on ceremony.
What is it?
It's not a what.
It's a who,
a girl, Davina.
She can't be
more than 16,
and I have never
felt power like that.
A witch.
She's not just
any witch.
She's something I've
never seen before,
something
beyond powerful,
and now because of you,
she has Elijah.
Who knows what she
could do to him.
Where is she?
That clever bitch.
I don't know.
What's wrong?
She wiped my memory
of the location.
Marcel possesses
a weapon
bigger and more powerful
than an original,
and you handed our
brother to him!
How many times will
Elijah forgive you?
How long until his hope
for your redemption
finally dies?
I did what I had to do!
Marcel took our home.
And our home
is worthless
without family.
I am finding Elijah,
whatever it takes.
Are you going
to help me?
Whatever it takes.
I'm sorry
about that unpleasantness.
She doesn't scare me.
None of them do.
I didn't think
they would, honey,
but the thing is,
it seems like they're
here to stay.
They don't belong here.
Might be kind of tough
to convince them of that...
Which is why I need to
ask you for a favor.
I'm gonna need you
to figure out
how we kill an original.