Oh,look, Saturn 3is on.
I don't want to watch Saturn
3. Deep Space Nine is better.
How isDeep Space
Ninebetter thanSaturn 3?
Simple subtraction will
tell you it's six better.
Compromise. WatchBabylon 5.
In what sense is that a compromise?
Well,five is partway between three...
Never mind.
I'll tell you what. How about
we go rock-paper-scissors?
Ooh,I don't think so.
Anecdotal evidence suggests that
in the game of rock-paper-scissors,
players familiar with each other will tie 75 to 80%
of the time due to the limited number of outcomes.
I suggest rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock.
What?
It's very simple.
Scissors cuts paper.
Paper covers rock.
Rock crushes lizard.
Lizard poisons Spock.
Spock smashes scissors.
Scissors decapitates lizard.
Lizard eats paper.
Paper disproves Spock.
Spock vaporizes rock.
And as it always has,
rock crushes scissors.
Okay,I think I got it.
Rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock!
Hello,boys.
Ahoy,matey.
Noticed the eye patch,did you?
It's all part of a technique I've
been studying for picking up women.
You employ a visual display designed to
make yourself distinctive and memorable.
Oh,yes,like the male peacock with brilliant plumage
or the rutting baboon with engorged hindquarters.
Or in this case,the bar
mitzvah boy with pinkeye.
Mock me if you will, but it works.
You show up at a club in something distinctive,
scope out your target and toss out some negs.
What are negs?
A neg is a negative compliment that
throws a pretty woman off her game,
like "Normally,I'm not turned on
by big teeth, but on you,they work."
I got a whole list of 'em.
Who wants to be my wingman?
You're not gonna need a wingman.
You're gonna need a paramedic.
Howard,your scooter's blocking my car.
Aw,did you get pinkeye again?
Step one: she notices the eye patch.
May I say,Penny, not a lot of women could
look as hot as you do with such greasy hair?
Yeah,just move your stupid scooter before
I pick it up and throw it in the dumpster.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ßÇÈâÈâ
The Big Bang
Theory Season02 Episode08
I'm sorry,but I'm not going to watchThe Clone
WarsTV series until I've seen The Clone Warsmovie.
I prefer to let George Lucas
disappoint me in the order he intended.
Well,I want to watch it now.
Then I believe we've arrived at another quintessential
rock-paper-scissors- lizard-Spock moment.
Watch whatever you want.
I saw what you did there.
What'd I do?
Hello. Hey,Howard. What's wrong?
Okay. Okay, we'll be right there.
What happened?
Howard's at the Mars Rover
lab. He says he's in trouble.
- Defcon 5.
- Defcon 5?
Well,there's no need to rush.
What?
Defcon 5 means "no danger."
Defcon 1 is a cris.
How can 5 not be worse than 1?
Yeah,Star Trek V worse thanI.
Okay,first of all, that's a
comparison of quality, not intensity.
Secondly,Star Trek I is
orders-of-magnitude worse thanStar Trek V.
Are you joking?
Star Trek Vis the standard against
which all badness is measured.
No,no.
Star Trek V has specific
failures in writing and direction,
whileStar Trek Ifails across the board: art
direction,costuming, music,sound editing.
Can we just forget I said Defcon and go?
Star Trek V.
All right,will you at least stipulate thatStar
Trek IV: The Voyage Homeis inarguably the best?
I have three words
for you: Wrath of Khan.
- Oh,thank God, you're here.
- What's the emergency?
I got the Mars Rover stuck in a ditch.
Where?
On a dusty highway just
outside Bakersfield.
Where do you think? On Mars!
Howard, is everything okay?
Yeah,baby,I'll be right in.
You brought a girl to the
Mars Rover control room?
Yeah,I picked her up in
the bar. She's a doctor.
One free barium enema, and my
mother won't care she's not Jewish.
Wait a minute. So the eye
patch and the insults worked?
No,there were three other
guys with eye patches.
It was a fiasco.
What did work was, "How'd you like to
visit a secret government facility?"
So what exactly do you want us to do?
I need you and Raj to help me
get the Rover out of the ditch
and I need you to get Stephanie out
before somebody notices she's here.
She doesn't exactly have clearance.
Really? They don't let
strange women from honky-tonks
come in and play with $200 million
government projects on distant planets?
Yes,I was bad.
Maybe she'll spank me.
Can we please move on?
Hey,Howard,you know, it's getting late,
so do I get to drive this thing or what?
Yeah. No. I'm sorry,
but something's come up.
Kind of a Mars Rover...
Mars Rover can Howard come over...
situation.
So my friend Leonard
is gonna take you home.
- Oh,okay. Let's go, friend Leonard.
- Okay.
- I'll call ya.
- Yeah.
So are you a scientist like Howard?
No one's a scientist like Howard.
My mother is so gonna love her.
How nice. Maybe they can carpool
when they visit you in federal prison.
I'm sorry. I totally interrupted you.
What,what, what were you saying?
Just said Howard's a terrific guy.
He's got a great sense of humor.
He loves his mother... a lot.
People say "too much."
I really like that you're
such a loyal friend.
Yeah,I am loyal.
You know,if you look at the big picture.
Out of curiosity, did he
ever have a shot with you?
Are you insane? The guy
was wearing an eye patch.
Then why did you...
He said that I could
drive a car on Mars.
Got it.
So,can I see you again?
You're not gonna see me now.
Cool.
Anything?
Actually,I was just checking my e-mail.
But,uh,no,the Rover is not responding.
I believe the appropriate metaphor
here involves a river of excrement
and a Native American water vessel
without any means of propulsion.
Hang on. There's got
to be other options.
You could try calling Triple-A.
But based on NASA's latest timetable,
they won't get there for 35 years.
Plus I understand you have to be standing next
to the vehicle with your card when they arrive.
Oh,snap.
Snap what?
Okay,I guess we have to turn to Plan B.
What's Plan B?
Erase all the hard drives,
scrap the surveillance tapes,
wipe our fingerprints
off every surface and run.
Why wasn't that Plan A?
A NASA spokesman states
that due to the loss of data,
they will most likely be unable to determine
the cause of the Mars Rover's malfunction.
This is not the first time an exploratory
mission to Mars has ended in disappointment.
Thank God for Plan B.
Howard,didn't you say you
worked on the Mars Rover?
No,you're mistaken.
Yeah,when we first met, you said that if I
went out with you, I could drive a car on Mars.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Will you all excuse me?
Leonard is subtly signaling that
he'd like to talk to me in private.
No. Yeah,I remember specifically.
You started by asking if I was from Mars
because my ass was out of this world.
Well,that does sound like me, but no.
- Is there some problem?
- Yeah.
Listen,I have to kinda
sneak out for a while.
All right,good-bye.
No,wait!
If anyone asks you where
I went, you don't know.
Whereareyou going?
I can't tell you that.
Who would ask me?
I can't tell you that,either.
So you brought me in here to
inform me that you can't tell me
where you're going and you
can't tell me who might ask?
Yeah,I really didn't think this through.
- Leonard,a moment.
- What?
If someone-- and of course,we
don't know who this would be--
does ask where you've
gone, what should I say?
I don't know. Just tell
'em I went to the office.
- Are you going to the office?
- No.
Then how can I say it convincingly?
Just say,"Leonard went totheoffice."
All right. Leonard went tothe office.
What is... No,not like that!
Just,"Leonard went to the office."
This would have worked out a lot better if
you'd just told me you were going to the office.
I'm going to the office.
See? Why don't I believe you?
I'm going out for a while.
Okay.
Doesn't anyone want to
know where he's going?
Okay,where is he going?
Leonard is going tothe office.
So how was work today?
Busy.
I removed an appendix, a gall bladder
and about a foot and a half of bowel.
I'm hoping that's three different guys.
No,just the one.
He didn't make it.
So,how was your day?
Oh,you know,I'm a physicist,so...
I thought about stuff.
That's it?
Well,I wrote some of it down.
Are you done eating?
- Uh,yeah.
- Oh,good.
If I knew you were waiting, I
would've swallowed that lasagna whole.
You've reached Dr. Stephanie
Barnett. Leave a message.
Hey,Steph, it's me again,Howard.
Listen,if you're free Friday, maybe we could
have a little something to eat at my place.
My mom cooks a hell of a brisket.
Let me know. It's Howard.
I've had her brisket.
Melts in your mouth.
Maybe we should think
about going to the bedroom.
That's a good idea.
There's a bed in there, and
I'm very... very,very pro-bed.
You've reached Dr. Stephanie
Barnett. Leave a message.
Hey,it's me again.
Just want to let you know the head
count for dinner Friday has gone up.
My Aunt Betty and Uncle Elliot
are coming in from Palm Springs.
Oh,and if anybody should ask, you're
half-Jewish on your mother's side.
Okay,call me. It's Howard.
Don't you think we should
tell him you're not interested?
Do you want me to stop and
call him back right now?
Dear God,no!
Oh,Leonard...
You've reached Dr. Stephanie
Barnett. Leave a message.
Hey,it's me again. Howard.
Listen,my cousins from Fort
Lauderdale are flying in to meet you
so that means we're gonna have to
move the dinner to a restaurant.
Tell her we're going
to the Olive Garden!
I have a coupon from the paper.
We're not going to the Olive Garden,Mom!
Oh,Mr. Bigshot with his Red Lobster.
I'll call you back when
we firm up the details.
It's Howard.
- New shirts?
- Yeah,a couple.
- Nice.
- Thank you.
So,who's the girl?
I'm sorry?
Well,last time you bought a new
shirt was when we were dating.
So what we did was in fact dating?
Well,yeah,we did have a date.
Exactly. Thank you.
Do me a favor. Tell Koothrappali
that next time you see him.
So,who is she?
Oh,she's a doctor.
Oh,nice.
A doctor doctor, or
a you kind of doctor?
Doctor doctor. Surgical
resident. Smart,pretty.
Let me ask you something.
If your friend thinks he's dating
someone, but he's not because,in fact,
you're dating her, does
that make you a bad person?
- Well,that depends.
- On what?
Is that friend Wolowitz?
- Yeah.
- Screw him. You're fine.
Are you sure?
Well,have you slept with her yet?
You dog!
Good for you.
- Does that change things?
- No.
So why'd you ask?
I'm nosy. See ya.
Howard,get the door!
Really? Is that what
you dohen someone knocks?
Thank you. I had no idea!
Hey,buddy. What brings you
to my little slice of hell?
Who is it?
It's Leonard!
You're gonna have to play outside!
I'm not dressed to receive!
No one cares,Ma! So,what's up?
Listen,I need to talk
to you about something.
Momentito. Yello.
Oh,Stephanie, thanks for
calling me back. I was worried...
No,I understand. Sure,we
can be friends. Absolutely.
Thanks for calling.
Yeah,you have a nice day,too.
You are dead to me.
Okay,who gets the extra dumpling?
Rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock.
Okay,one of us is going to
have to stop putting up Spock.
*******
Rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock.
- Oh,hey,guys.
- Hello.
Hi,Howard.
- Howard?
- Sheldon.
Howard is employing a schoolyard
paradigm in which you are,
for all intents and purposes,deceased.
He intends to act on this
by not speaking to you,
feigning an inability to
hear you when you speak
and otherwise refusing to
acknowledge your existence.
That's just ridiculous.
Why are you cooperating with him?
I don't make the rules, Leonard.
Howard,come on. I didn't plan on
this. These things just happen.
Usually not to me, but they do happen.
Did someone just feel a cold breeze?
I believe this is an extension
of the death metaphor.
The cold breeze is the so-called ectoplasmic
issue of a disembodied soul passing by.
You know,screw it. I'm
just gonna eat the dumpling.
Oh,hi,Steph. Come on in.
Is this a bad time?
Yeah,but I don't see a better
one on the horizon,so...
Oh,if it isn't Mrs. Dead to Me.
- Hello,Howard.
- Sheldon?
I'm sorry,you violated the terms of your
metaphor by acknowledging her existence.
I'm out.
He just won't listen to me.
Okay,I guess it'll just
be the three of us then.
- Lisa's gonna be disappointed.
- Yeah.
Lisa?
Yeah,my roommate. She just went
through a really bad breakup
and I thought she might like
to meet somebody fun like you.
Leonard,Stephanie, you're
alive! It's a miracle!
So,anyway,Lisa, I just wanted to tell you
again how much I enjoyed the other night,
and again, I'm sorry for how it ended.
But again,if you could
let me know about Friday.
My mother needs a head count so she
can know how big a brisket to get.
Howard,Howard, look at this.
- Anyway,call me.It's Howard.
- The possibility of life on Mars has long fascinated scientists and laypersons alike.
It's unclear how the Mars Rover got into
the crevice, but one thing's certain:
The data which it has sent back
contain the first clear indications
that there may have been life on Mars.
It's a scientific discovery that has
staggering implications for all mankind.
Unfortunately,we'll never
know who's responsible.
Son of a bitch.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ßÇÈâÈâ