(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KEYS JINGLE)
(KEYS CLATTER)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(READING NUMBERS INDISTINCTLY)
(SCREWDRIVER CLICKING)
OFFICER ON RADIO: Black
Ford Mustang on sidewalk...
(OFFICER
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
...juveniles with spray cans,
uh, took off on foot.
Asian male, no visual...
DISPATCHER: 10-4.
OFFICER 2:
Noise complaint, 6165...
(SILVERWARE CLANKING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(CHUCK GLASER'S MUSIC AIN'T
A BAD LIFE PLAYING)
French toast
didn't work out, huh?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Oh, yeah.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
It's fine.
I can
warm it up for you.
It's... It's okay.
I can get you
something else.
We're serving lunch now.
I'm good. Really.
Can I at least
freshen that for you?
Yeah. Um...
Thanks.
(COINS CLINKING)
Hi, Molly.
It's, uh, me... Gene.
Is this your cell number?
I'm sorry about that.
Yeah, I... I'm fine.
It was a false alarm.
You know, um, turns out
I was just dehydrated, so...
(CHUCKLES)
Can you believe it?
Yeah, I definitely will.
Um, hey, uh...
I won't be back for...
Uh, well, till Thursday.
Can you and Frederica open?
Oh. Good. And, um...
Also, I think you're gonna have
to sign for a delivery this afternoon.
Oh, you did already?
Great. Thank you.
Um, oh, and...
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Has anybody
been asking about me?
You know,
I mean, like any customers
come to the store looking for me,
somebody hanging around?
No, no, nothing wrong.
I just...
I got some calls
from an insurance salesman,
you know,
the pushy type, so...
(CHUCKLES)
So, nobody at all?
Ah.
Well, that's it then. Um...
Yeah. Sure. I will.
And, uh, I will see you
in a few days.
Thanks, Molly. Yeah.
(COIN CLINKS)
(SIGHS)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
OFFICER ON RADIO: 953 down
at the warehouse on Bonner and 4th,
report of a civilian
two blocks...
DISPATCHER ON RADIO:
District is 1094 Aurora Drive.
OFFICER 2: 10-23.
(KEYS JINGLE)
(LOCK DISENGAGES)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
OFFICER ON RADIO: Vehicle
blocking... (SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
...van blocking driveway.
10-23.
OFFICER 2: There's
a juvenile white male,
about 4'8",
70 pounds...
DISPATCHER: 10-28 on hold.
That'd be 0700.
OFFICER 3: 10-23.
OFFICER 4: ...at restaurant
on 6th and 5th at 70th.
(SCANNER BEEPS)
(INDISTINCT
POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(JIM REEVES'
WELCOME TO MY WORLD PLAYS)
(ENGINE HUMMING)
♪ Welcome to my world
♪ Won't you come on in?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
♪ Miracles, I guess
(BLENDER WHIRRING)
♪ Still happen now and then
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
♪ Step into my heart
♪ Leave your cares behind
♪ Welcome to my world
♪ Welcome to my world ♪
MAN: Hey.
Hey!
It is you.
I thought it was you.
I wasn't all the way sure,
but now that I'm seeing you up close...
Sure. It's you.
(CHUCKLING)
come on, man.
I just want to say hi. I'm a big
fan. Y'know, back in the day,
when I lived in Albuquerque
with my ex,
I used to
see you everywhere.
You were on the billboards,
on the TV.
I used to have
one of your matchbox.
You got me mixed up with someone. Uh,
my name is Takavic.
Gene Takavic.
Sorry. I'm... I'm gonna...
I got to get back to work.
Come on, man.
That's not cool.
I know who you are.
You know who you are.
Let's just
get past that.
Don't worry about him.
He's cool. (CHUCKLES)
He just wanted
to come along.
Hey, you know who I had
in my cab once?
Sammy Hagar!
(CHUCKLES)
He's even more famous
than you.
What do you...
What do you want?
I just want you
to admit it.
I... I don't know
what you're...
Sure you do.
Just say it.
I... I really
don't know what...
Come on.
Come on, man.
Say... It.
"Better call Saul."
What?
I... I can't even
hear that.
"Better call Saul."
Once again.
And... And do the point.
"Better call Saul."
(CHUCKLES)
There we go.
A little rusty,
but you'll do better next time.
(CHUCKLES)
You didn't ask,
but the name's Jeff.
(EXHALES)
Anytime you need me,
you just call up Omaha United Cabs.
You ask for me. They'll find me,
no matter where I'm at.
Never more
than five minutes away.
Oh, man.
It's great to meet you.
It's an honor.
I... I'll see ya.
Gene.
(CHUCKLES)
(DOOR OPENING)
(COINS CLINKING)
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE:
Please deposit an additional 50 cents.
(COINS CLINKING)
(LINE RINGING)
ED: (ON PHONE) Best Quality
Vacuum. How may I help you?
Yeah. I need an adapter
for a Hoover Max Extract
Pressure-Pro, model 60.
Aha.
ED: We've delivered to you before,
haven't we?
Yeah.
I'm in Omaha, Nebraska.
Mr. Takavic.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
That will be a very
difficult part to obtain.
And I want to warn you it's gonna
be more expensive than the original.
How expensive?
Double the price.
And we are still in
a cash-on-delivery situation.
Uh, will that
be a problem?
JIMMY: No. No. It's fine.
How hot are you?
(SIGHS) I got made.
You got made.
All right.
Any official involvement?
No. Not yet.
Pick-up is going to be
in the same place
you were dropped off.
Do you remember
where that is?
Yeah, I do.
All right, Mr. Takavic.
Thursday.
7:00 a.m. Same spot.
You know the rest.
Am I right?
Mr. Takavic?
Still there?
I've changed my mind.
Changed your mind?
Yeah.
To be clear, you are
not going forward with this?
I'm gonna fix it myself.
(RECEIVER SLAMS)
(COIN CLINKS)
(OPENING THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Jimmy, what...
Kim.
What are you...
Listen.
I know
this seems fast.
It is fast,
but I can see it.
You're changing
your name?
No! I... Well, yes,
but it's for my clients.
You're gonna call yourself
"Saul Goodman"?
I'm already calling myself
Saul Goodman.
We've talked about this.
The skells who've been
buying my phones...
Sure as shooting,
sooner or later,
every last one of them
is gonna find themselves
in the back
of a squad car.
How do I get them
to call Jimmy McGill?
I don't!
I stay Saul Goodman.
They call the guy
they already know.
I thought I was wasting
a year of my life.
It wasn't a waste!
It was for this!
This is it!
When did you decide to...
Just now, just back there! It just...
Poom! It just hit me! This is the way.
Kim, it's gonna work.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I...
I know. I know.
All of a sudden,
I've got it all figured out, but I... I do.
This is right.
So, let me just...
I'll get this done,
and then we can
talk about it, okay?
(SIGHS)
I mean...
Uh... Unless there's...
Is there some angle
that I'm not seeing here?
Uh, if you want me
to slow my roll,
I can come back
and do this another day.
(SIGHS)
If this is how
you're really feeling...
It is.
...I say sure.
Great.
Five minutes, max.
JIMMY: Okay,
where were we?
WOMAN: Just that
you need to sign documents
with your legal name.
You got it.
Then all that's left
is the Notice of Entry.
Jimmy "Saul Goodman" McGill.
Thank you, honey.
Mmm-hmm.
(XOCOYOTZIN HERRERA'S
EL CONTRABANDISTA PLAYING)
Werner Ziegler.
Werner Ziegler. Ziegler. (MAN
SINGING IN SPANISH ON RADIO)
You know how many Werner
Zieglers there are in Germany?
27.
26 now,
according to Mrs. Ziegler.
(SCOFFS) I told you
I never heard of the guy.
What about "Michael"?
Like I said,
I only know the names
of two guys over there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Victor and Tyrus.
You.
Yeah? Werner Ziegler.
You ever heard of that guy?
Werner Ziegler.
MAN: Uh... No.
What about Michael?
He's a bald gringo.
He's in the game.
Okay.
(TRILLS LIPS)
You're good.
MAN: Okay.
South wall,
pouring concrete.
What's he up to, man?
What's he doing?
So, there's nothing new
going on, huh,
nothing different?
Like what?
Like anything.
Mmm-mmm.
What?
It's nothing.
It's nothing, man.
A couple of skells
on 4th
been complaining
that the stuff is stepped on.
Stepped on?
MAN 2: Mmm-hmm.
You hear that, too?
They say
it's different.
Different how?
MAN 2: Skells complain.
It's what they do.
Okay. Show me.
(DSCHINN'S
LET'S GO TOGETHER PLAYING)
Arlo!
My man!
Three.
Let's see what you got.
ARLO: Hey!
Wait! Whoa, whoa!
Yo! Vato! Yo!
Yo! Vato!
Where you going?
You're not
going in there.
Yo!
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
MAN: Mouse, it's okay.
(DOOR HANDLE CLANGS)
So, where's the stuff?
It's in the chair.
What, this chair?
(CHAIR SCRAPING)
ARLO: This about
the count?
'Cause the count
is good.
You holding cash?
Yeah. Got it
all right here.
If you're holding
my cash...
What're you doing up here
with my stuff? (BAG THUDS)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
No one's stepping
on it, man.
We pick the stuff
from the chicken farm.
We cut it, split it,
and it lands here.
I'm with it
all the way.
At his chicken farm.
(SIGHS)
You pick it up how?
He puts out ten keys.
I pick six.
How do you pick 'em?
I just pick different
ones each time.
They're all the same.
(SIGHS)
Okay, so, these...
These are okay.
But these...
(BAG CRINKLING)
(SNIFFS, COUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
This shit's
not ours, man.
(CHUCKLING) Whoa.
This is old-school
beautiful.
Yeah.
You deserve it.
But, uh...
"JMM."
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
I didn't know.
I got it for
Jimmy McGill.
Yeah, well,
Jimmy loves it.
And don't worry.
I'm using it.
If, uh, anybody
says anything,
I'll just say
JMM is my motto.
Your motto?
Yeah.
"Justice...
Matters Most."
Mm, nice.
(CHUCKLES)
There's also this.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
(CHUCKLES) "World's
2nd Best Lawyer. Again."
Oh, that's the real mistake,
world's second best lawyer,
because Saul Goodman
is gonna give you
a run for your money.
I bet he will.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Thank you.
For everything.
Really.
You know what?
The real trick is gonna be
to get my clients to know
that the cellphone guy
is now a lawyer,
their lawyer.
Yep.
That'll be a trick.
(WATER RUNNING)
(WATER SHUTS OFF)
What I'm thinking
is, see,
I've still got almost a full
pallet of cellphones left,
so why not run
a promotion?
I... I'll make a real
event out of it.
I'll... I'll give
'em away, okay?
And, uh, for
added sweetener,
limited time only,
um, non-violent
felonies, 50% off.
(DRAWER CLOSES)
You know, it's like, uh,
commit four felonies,
you get the
fifth one free.
And there'll be friends
and family, too,
so you can share
'em around.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean, it's just,
get people in the door.
Once they're hooked,
I will up-sell them.
Doesn't that
sound like
you're encouraging these
people to commit crimes?
(CHUCKLES) They don't
need encouragement.
Believe me.
One scoop or two?
One.
Kim, you don't know
these assholes like I do.
Rain or shine,
these morons will be out there
doing stupid shit and
getting arrested for it.
Little discount won't make
a bit of difference.
Do you want sprinkles?
'Cause I'm having sprinkles.
Uh, sure.
I'm just worried about
how this reflects on you.
(SIGHS)
You know what? When you're right,
you're right.
What am I doing
cutting prices?
Discount is
a desperation move.
(SILVERWARE CLINKING)
(SIGHS) See?
This is why
this works.
I go too far.
(REFRIGERATOR DOOR OPENS)
and you pull me back.
Don't you think you're
selling yourself short?
You worked...
(BOWL THUDS)
So hard to get your
license back. We worked.
(FOR HE'S A JOLLY GOOD
FELLOW PLAYING)
We worked.
So, why be...
(STAMMERS)
Why... Why this?
(CHUCKLING)
It's perfect.
They already know me.
I know them.
What's not to love?
(REMOTE CLICKS, MUSIC STOPS)
Kim, I can't go back
to being Jimmy McGill.
(SIGHS)
Jimmy McGill the lawyer
is always gonna be Chuck
McGill's loser brother.
I'm done with that.
That name is burned.
(SIGHS)
This is a fresh start.
This is how
I move forward.
And I like it.
(EXHALING HEAVILY)
(CHUCKLES) Sorry.
It's...
I just can't see it.
It's okay. You will.
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF,
CAR DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(ELECTRICITY HUMMING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
GUS: It'll be
most discreet.
That I can guarantee.
Did I keep you waiting?
I was admiring
Gustavo's establishment.
It's tremendous.
(CHUCKLES)
So many trucks.
Uh...
Are all those buildings
really full of chickens?
(CHUCKLES)
DON JUAN: Please sit.
There's a serious
matter to discuss.
Of course,
Don Juan.
You may have noticed that
some of the product is...
Altered.
Gustavo will explain.
I have a confession
to make.
A man was
working for me.
On the legitimate side
of my business.
He was supervising
a construction project.
A German engineer.
I think you know his name.
Werner Ziegler.
Through an oversight,
Ziegler became aware
of our other activities.
The temptation was
too great for him to resist,
and he stole
two keys of product.
I believe you know
the rest of the story.
You know of
Ziegler's escape.
You know that my man
tracked him down.
My shame...
Is not simply that I
allowed this to happen.
It's that I hid
the truth.
When I discovered
what Ziegler had done,
I replaced
the stolen product
with methamphetamine
I purchased locally.
Some of this inferior product
went to your organization.
And for that...
I must apologize.
Sincerely.
What construction project?
I mean,
you said the German was building something.
What?
Ah.
(CHAIR LEGS SCRAPE)
It would be simpler
for me to show you.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING,
TOOLS WHIRRING)
When finished,
this will be
the most advanced
in-line chilling system
in the Southwest.
A chicken freezer?
Chiller.
Our product is
never frozen.
These are Ziegler's men,
working from his plans.
As far as they're
concerned,
their leader
has gone home.
(TOOL WHIRS)
Nothing was keeping you
from sharing all this.
A lot of trouble could
have been avoided.
GUS: Yes. There were any
number of misunderstandings.
My man didn't know
who was following him.
And as a result,
he went to great lengths
to conceal his activities.
Your man... Michael,
is that right?
Yes.
That's not him, is it?
It is.
Well, I'd love to say hello,
if that's permitted.
Well, certainly.
(TOOL WHIRRING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Michael.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Michael, please meet
my associate, Eduardo.
(HANDS CLASP)
What a pleasure.
I've heard
so much about you.
That right?
Oh, yes.
I'm gonna
get back to it.
Thank you, Michael.
Well...
That explains
everything.
I am glad
you are satisfied.
DON JUAN: Listen to me.
There must be
no more trouble.
You two must co-exist.
This is non-negotiable.
Gustavo, there can be
no more secrets.
Yes.
Don Eladio
is not happy.
Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
I do.
Then we are done.
(TOOLS WHIRRING,
ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
You know, it's gonna be
a very nice chiller.
The south wall's
gonna look beautiful.
(DOOR OPENS)
(VEHICLE DEPARTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CONVERSING IN SPANISH)
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(HORN HONKS)
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT RAPPING)
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Or if I'm looking maybe... ♪
♪ Hair pulled up ♪
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on, let's just go.
(INDISTINCT SINGING)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT RAPPING)
♪ Let's take it easy ♪
MAN: Let's do it right here!
Whoa. Whoa.
Back off.
(CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE)
There are plenty of phones.
Plenty of phones.
Sorry. Can't
help you, ladies.
Everybody got
to wait their turn.
(BELL DINGS)
Here you go, buddy.
Next! (LEE MORGAN'S
THE SIDEWINDER PLAYS)
Welcome, welcome.
Take a load off.
Before we talk phones,
let's talk you.
I'm guessing, from
our brief acquaintance,
that you're a fellow
who occasionally,
through no fault
of your own, uh,
finds yourself in
a donnybrook or two.
Yeah, a, um,
knuckle duster.
A fistfight.
I'm thinking
you might be someone
who partakes of the
herb of the Earth.
I'm guessing
that you ladies
are popular
with the fellas.
And this could lead
to a misunderstanding
with the boys in blue.
Say hello to
my little friend.
See right there,
circled in red?
It's preprogrammed,
ready to go.
Number 1 on the speed dial
goes directly to me.
You press that,
and, poof! I'm there.
(BELL DINGS)
Next!
Why call the cellphone guy?
'Cause I'm not just
a cellphone guy.
I'm the lawyer
who's gonna fight for you.
You might find yourself
in possession
of a few pieces of military
ordinance, you know,
RPGs, maybe couple claymore
mines in the trunk. (CHUCKLES)
Before you know it,
the other guy is bleeding
out on the pavement
and the cops are
giving you the evil eye.
It's just that
people are always
looking over
each other's shoulder.
And you're not
hurting anyone.
You know, who doesn't
want to be...
(BELL DINGS)
Next!
Big fella outside?
His name's Huell Babineaux.
Go ask Huell about me.
He was facing three years.
He was facing six years.
Eight years down
in Guadalupe.
He was facing 25 years.
Didn't do a single day.
That's why he calls me
the "magic man."
I asked him not to call me that,
but he insists. (CHUCKLES)
(BELL DINGS)
Next!
Number 1 on the speed dial,
that's your lifeline.
Cops pick you up. They threaten
you. They look at you sideways.
You press that button,
and I'm there.
It's not just...
Press number 1.
Zip your lip
and press the button.
And keep your mouth shut.
Press number 1.
Keep it charged.
Poof!
Poof! I'm there.
(BELL DINGS) At number
1 on the speed dial...
It is your lifeline. It's your panic
button. Just press number 1.
Press 1 on the speed dial. Goes straight
to me. Ask him about the "magic man."
Press the button...
Speedy justice.
...and, boom,
your friend Saul is there.
I got your back
24 hours a day,
seven days a week,
365 days a year.
(BELL DINGS)
Press number 1.
Speedy justice for you.
Just press 1.
If and when that happens...
Here's your lifeline.
(BELL DINGS)
Press number 1.
Use it in good health.
Number 1 on the speed dial...
Goes straight to me...
...trouble with the law...
Number 1...
Ask him about the "magic man."
Press number 1.
And, poof!
Saul Goodman is there.
(BELL DINGS)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
Folks, folks, ladies and gents,
boys and girls,
uh, due to popular demand,
I'm very sorry to say
We've given out our last
phone. (CROWD MURMURING)
However, I'm still here
for legal consultations,
free legal consultations.
You know what?
At least take a card.
You meet the law,
you want the law to meet me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, you know what?
Uh, since none of you
are getting phones tonight,
how about a
special discount?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yeah, um,
for the next,
uh, two weeks,
um, non-violent
felonies, 50% off.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah? That's for you.
I'll take one.
JIMMY: 50% off.
Yeah. All right.
Now we got some takers.
There you are.
50% off.
Remember, 50% off.
All right.
For real?
(CHUCKLES) Very good.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Very good.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Well-done, magic man.
(SIGHS)
We're just
getting started.
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(LOCK DISENGAGES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
If you were gonna die,
you'd be dead already.
Now step out of the truck.
We got things to do.
All right.
The job may only be half done,
but you're being paid in full.
Does it need to be said
that your cooperation
is expected to continue...
Permanently?
Not a word,
not today,
not tomorrow,
not next week, not ever.
You let your end down,
there will be consequences.
Is that understood
by all?
All right.
Udo and Renke,
you're in the Cherokee.
Keys are inside.
You're driving
to Denver.
Flight for Zurich
leaves at midnight.
You hang a right,
you'll hit the main
highway in four miles.
Passport and
some tickets.
Kai, you're traveling
solo in the red Pontiac.
You're flying
out of Dallas.
It is a long drive.
Flight leaves at 9:40,
direct to Berlin.
I will never
say anything.
Ever.
It had to be done.
He was a good man,
but...
In truth, he was soft.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS) Casper, Toyota.
You're headed
to Phoenix.
10:15 to Vancouver and
then Vancouver to Budapest.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(PAPER RUSTLES)
Yeah?
He was worth
50 of you.
(VEHICLE DEPARTING)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
Sebastian, Adrian.
The Civic.
You're driving
to El Paso.
You're on the 7:25
to Chicago,
then Chicago to Vienna.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Well?
Last of them got on a plane
for Zurich an hour ago.
No problem.
Will do they as
they've been told?
You're asking
my opinion?
I am.
They know
the consequences.
And the laundry?
Entrances to the site
have been sealed.
Nobody's gonna
stumble on it.
As long as Lalo Salamanca
is on this side of the border,
we cannot continue
as we were.
So this is it.
No. This is not it.
Once Salamanca
is dealt with,
and he will be
dealt with,
construction will resume.
Until then, you will
continue to be paid.
Mm.
So, you're gonna pay me
to do nothing.
Call it a retainer.
Even after Ziegler?
Yes.
What happened
in Frankfurt?
The attorneys spent
a full day with his wife.
She accepted the facts
as presented.
As per your suggestion,
a construction accident.
The funeral
was yesterday.
And, of course,
she has been compensated.
"Compensated."
I would choose
my next words
very carefully
if I were you.
Mm.
You keep your
God damn retainer.
(COINS CLINKING)
(KEYPAD CLICKING)
(VENDING MACHINE WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STUTTERS, STOPS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(BAG THUDS)
WOMAN: Mr. Oakley!
Mr. Oakley!
Would you care to comment
on the Carl Gravenhorst case?
Oh, I'm... I... As you know,
the D.A.'s office
has been accused of misconduct
in the Gravenhorst case.
Would you comment on
the latest development?
Uh, the Graven what?
People are saying you're
prosecuting an innocent man.
Does the D.A.'s office
have something to hide?
Well, what,
um... JIMMY: Excuse me. Excuse me.
Please let me through.
Uh, that's my client
you're talking about.
And you are?
I'm Saul Goodman,
and Carl Gravenhorst
is 100% innocent.
The Albuquerque
D.A.'s office
is perpetrating an outrageous
miscarriage of justice.
You're who?
I'm Saul Goodman.
And we are
countersuing you
and the entire
Albuquerque D.A.'s office
for malicious persecution,
unlawful detention,
and abuse of process.
Seriously?
Yeah.
We'll take this all the way
to the Supreme Court.
By the time
we're through,
Carl Gravenhorst's name
will be cleared,
and we'll receive a settlement,
a cash settlement.
All right. Enough.
I've got to be in court.
You...
Go if you must,
but know this,
we will meet again!
I'm sorry. What'd you
say your name was?
I'm Saul Goodman,
and I make it my business
to defend the citizens
of Albuquerque
against injustices of
every kind. (CHUCKLES)
Wow, you must be really expensive,
though.
Not at all. I believe every man,
woman, and child
deserves speedy justice
at a price they can afford.
MAN: Do you have a card?
Not for me,
for a friend. JIMMY: Yes.
Uh, and please tell
your friend
that, uh, I make
no judgments
and I'm available
24 hours a day.
Uh, can I get
one of those?
Oh, yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
What about me?
Oh, sure.
Okay. Wow.
Yeah, uh...
I just...
I just don't know.
Five months.
With overcrowding,
you'll probably do less than two.
Yeah. Yeah.
Considering your priors,
sentencing guidelines
would have you looking at
two to four years
in custody.
So...
Five months is
really good, Bobby.
Are you worried about being
there when Lois delivers?
Delivers?
Oh, right.
Yeah, yeah, so, um...
So, if I go to trial,
you'll be my lawyer, right?
Bobby, you do not
want to go to trial.
But you'll be
my lawyer.
Yes, but going to trial
would be a mistake.
Trials are always
unpredictable.
At trial, the D.A. will
throw everything at us.
You'd just be rolling the
dice. Yeah. Roll the dice.
Yeah. I mean, I don't mean to
tell you your business, Miss Wexler,
but you put me
up there,
I give the people
the big eyes,
they see Lois here
and the kid,
y'know,
they gonna believe me. I'd believe you.
Bobby, there are a million
reasons not to go to trial.
But it's up
to me, right?
Yes, it is, but I'm
advising you not to.
Odds are you would end up
going away for more time,
not less.
And I am talking about
years of your life.
But I might not, right?
You don't want
to take that risk.
Maybe I do.
Lois...
Whatever Bobby says.
(DOOR OPENS)
Excuse me a moment.
Please...
Think this over
carefully.
Both of you.
You ready
for lunch?
There's a new sandwich
vending machine
down by family court.
I've heard good things.
Sorry,
I'm stuck here.
Really? What's up?
He's not
taking the deal.
Who? That guy?
(SIGHS)
Isn't he the punk
who tried to sell
a flatbed of hot mini-fridges
to an undercover cop?
What'd you get him?
Five months.
Five months?
With his priors?
Well,
he should be on his knees thanking you.
I'm trying to talk him
out of going to trial.
No! Seriously?
Seriously.
(SCOFFS) You know what?
(SIGHS)
No.
No. We can fix this.
I'm from the D.A.'s
office, okay?
I'm giving you what for.
You're giving me what for.
We'll be loud.
We will go over there.
We will make
a scene, okay?
Uh...
New evidence
has come to light,
and I'm pulling his deal
with extreme prejudice.
I... I'm pissed.
I wanna put him
away permanently.
(VIDEO GAME BEEPING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
JIMMY: ...third-degree
felony...
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
But you fight me,
I will push back hard.
We'll have that punk
on his knees
begging for the
five months.
(SIGHS)
I don't think so.
Yeah, come on, Kim.
We can do this.
Lead-pipe cinch.
He's the client.
It's his decision.
What good
is it gonna do
to put that dweeb away
in Los Lunas, huh?
You think he's
a jackass now?
Wait till he gets back
from that clown college.
Jimmy, it... No. Yeah,
but what about his wife and kid?
That's them, right?
What about them?
If this isn't using our powers for good,
I don't know what is.
We're not doing that.
But, Kim, we can do it.
It'll work. I am not
scamming my client.
But it worked
for Mesa Verde...
Jimmy, back off.
Well, y...
(CHUCKLING) Okay.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Um...
Yeah, I'll see
you at home.
(FOOTSTEPS DEPART)
So, who was that?
Is everything
all right?
(SIGHS)
He's from the district
attorney's office.
They're taking the deal
off the table.
Uh, so what?
I mean, we weren't gonna
take it anyway, so...
Miss Wexler, why are they
taking it off the table?
I... don't know
for sure.
It's possible they
have new evidence.
Like... Like...
Like.. Like what?
Like cameras or...
Or witnesses or...
I really couldn't say.
We'll find out
soon enough.
Bobby, I'm sorry.
It looks like they want to
make an example out of you.
Uh...
All right, well,
we better go tell the judge
that we're taking
this to trial.
Yeah, yeah,
you know what? Um...
Are you sure we still
can't get the five months?
The D.A. took that
off the table.
You mean if you... Even
if you asked real nice?
I could try.
Are you sure that's
what you want?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I thought about it,
just like you said, and...
I could do
the five months.
Miss Wexler, please?
(SIGHS)
Wait here.
I can't promise
anything, but...
I'll look into it.
Sure, sure.
You do that.
We'll...
We'll be right here.
(DOOR OPENS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(INHALES SHARPLY)