Leonard, what time does
your mom's plane get in?
I don't know--
some time tomorrow morning.
Don't you want
to know for sure?
No need to. As soon as she flies
into California airspace,
I'll feel a disturbance
in the Force.
It's so nice
both of your moms are coming in
to see you guys get an award.
Well, my mother's been there
for every honor I've won
since I beat out my twin sister
for the "did it
on the potty" trophy.
How does this look?
Aw, it's so nice.
She's gonna love it.
Sure, his mom gets roses.
When I want them,
they're a "bouquet of
severed plant genitals."
You act like I didn't get you
that mushroom log
on Valentine's Day.
He's right.
Roses die, but a moist rotting
log will pump out mushrooms
for two or three magical years.
You know,
your mom's never been
too thrilled
with our relationship.
Maybe I should get her something
so she warms up to me.
If you could run
out and get a PhD,
that might make
her like you.
Really?
It didn't work for you.
Do you think
the moms will get along?
Uh, I don't know.
They're pretty different.
Maybe they'll be best friends.
One of them is brilliant,
one is sweet and simple.
Sound familiar?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
Shelly, I'm so proud of you and
Leonard for getting this award.
Oh, thank you, Mother.
I tried to read your paper,
but it was very hard
for me to understand.
Oh, it's quite
straightforward, actually.
It describes a new model
of the universe
that conceptualizes it
as the surface
of an n-dimensional
superfluid.
Interesting.
You can believe that,
but God filling an ark with
animals two-by-two is nonsense.
What did they feed
the lions, Mother?
The floating bodies of
drowned sinners, of course.
Listen, Leonard's mom is
a renowned psychiatrist
and woman of science.
Can you please keep
the Bible babble to yourself
while she's here?
Are you ashamed of me?
Of course not.
I love you.
I'm just embarrassed by the
things you believe, do and say.
Well, I love you, too.
My little bowl
of lion chow.
So, have you and Penny
set a wedding date?
No, we're kind of
taking it slow.
I see.
What does that mean?
You've been on and off with
this woman for seven years
and engaged for one year.
One has to wonder
if there's a problem.
Are you having
satisfactory intercourse?
Yes, Mother.
Only satisfactory.
I see.
I change my answer.
It-it's amazing.
It's hot.
We can barely keep our
hands off each other.
Seems odd to try
and impress your mother
with your
sexual prowess.
But then, you always did have
that unresolved Oedipal complex.
See, this right here,
what you're doing,
can you please not do that
around Sheldon's mom?
Why? Are you attracted
to her, too?
Of course not.
She's-she's just a very
sweet and God-fearing lady,
and you have to be
respectful of her beliefs.
Leonard, I'm an adult.
I know how to conduct myself
around people
from different
walks of life.
Thank you.
Where is she from again?
East Texas.
Ugh.
Hey, look who's here.
Oh, Dr. Hofstadter,
it's so good to see you again.
Likewise.
I read your paper;
it was very impressive.
Oh, thank you.
We just spent
two hours in traffic.
Did you think to mention to me
that you liked our paper?
Of course I did, but
it's a mother's job
to make sure her child's
self-esteem is not dependent
on anyone's approval.
That's so sweet,
you think I have self-esteem.
Dr. Hofstadter, I want you
to meet my mother, Mary.
So nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
How was your flight?
Very pleasant. And yours?
Lovely. Almost
as if someone--
not saying who-- was
watching over the plane.
You're kidding, right?
Subtle, Mom,
real subtle.
Stuart.
Morning.
We talked about this.
I don't mind you
still living here,
but we got to have
some rules.
And rule number one is pants.
Hey, hey.
(clears throat)
You must be very
proud of your son.
Oh, yes.
He recently argued a case
before the Supreme Court.
He did?
Oh, you mean this son.
Uh, sure,
he's terrific.
Uh, Beverly, would you like
to see the math I worked out
to support our hypothesis?
Uh, you mean,
my hypothesis.
I hypothesized it
all by myself.
Calm down, dear.
Mary, I'm curious.
When did you
first realize
that your son had such
a remarkable mind?
Ooh, good question.
Everyone loves stories about
Sheldon Cooper, boy genius.
Well, I would have to say
when he was 13
and tried to build a nuclear
reactor in the tool shed.
Ooh, this is a good one.
Now, the first thing you have
to know about Shelly is
ever since he was a little boy,
he was always concerned
with the well-being of others.
And he didn't think
that it was fair
for people to pay
for electricity,
so he was gonna power
the entire town for free.
(stammers)
Tell her about the uranium!
Tell her about
the uranium.
Oh, well!
Oh, this is adorable.
When he arranged to get
some yellowcake from Chad,
I thought he was talking
about Twinkies
from one of his friends.
Yeah.
But I wasn't.
'Cause I didn't
have any friends.
(laughs):
No.
It turns out that this
little scallywag was trying
to use my Visa card
to buy uranium
from an African warlord
in the country of Chad!
Sounds like Sheldon
was a handful.
Oh, he was a handful.
I was a handful.
You still are.
Uh, Mom, hey,
tell Mary the story
about how I made
a Van de Graaff generator
out of our vacuum cleaner.
All right.
He broke the
vacuum cleaner.
(video game sound effects
playing)
I mean, for a while,
everything was vampires.
Now it's all zombies.
I wonder what the next
monster fad will be.
We haven't had a good
invisible man in a while.
Clearly, you've never seen me
try to talk to a woman.
Guys.
In the time you've been sitting
here playing video games,
I got the car washed,
picked up cleaning supplies
and went to the bank.
I put on pants.
Kiss-ass.
Okay, I don't know when
I became the mother
to three lazy teenagers,
but it stops today.
You guys are cleaning
the kitchen, top to bottom.
Hey, I don't even live here.
Yes or no, do you have clothes
in my laundry right now?
I do.
And some of it's wool,
so dry flat if possible.
Oh, and here's a picture
of me receiving
my bachelor of science degree.
You don't look
very happy.
Well, I had just begun puberty.
(sighs)
It was figuratively
and literally
one of the hairiest moments
of my life.
Shelly does not like change.
Oh, true.
But all the clenching
in the world will not keep
testicles in your abdomen.
Hey, sorry,
got caught up at work.
Hi, Beverly!
Hello.
(giggles)
Oh, okay.
(chuckles)
Sorry, I forgot.
You remember my mother.
Oh, yes. Hi, Mary!
Good to see you
again, dear.
Ah, yeah, now that's
what I'm talking about.
So, Mom, you haven't seen Penny
since we got engaged.
Oh, yeah, let me
show you the ring.
Oh, lovely.
Must have been
very expensive.
Oh, no, not at all.
No, we, uh, found
a place online
that, uh, repurposes
diamond drill bits.
We did not. That's not true.
Can I speak to you alone
for a second?
Oh, sure.
It came from Tiffany's.
(chuckles)
You mean the box, right?
Keep walking!
Really doesn't matter to me
how much he spent on the ring.
I think.
Did I misspeak
about the ring?
Yes, and we'll get
back to that.
But, uh, even with
your mother here,
you are deliberately hogging
all the attention from my mom.
You're like one of those
elephant seal pups
that steals the milk
from two mothers!
Do you mean
what marine biologists
refer to as "super weaning"?
Yes, you are a super weaner!
Well, now I have to correct you.
A-As a bit
of an elephant seal buff,
the more accurate
comparison
would be when two mother seals
actively seek
to nourish the same pup.
So I believe the term
you're looking for
is a double mother suckler.
Yeah, you're right.
That is the term
I'm looking for.
You are a dirty double
mother suckler!
Okay, well, now that we have the
terminology straightened out.
How dare you!
We're not in a rush.
We'll set a date when
the time is right.
It doesn't matter, sweetie.
The moment a man lays
with a woman,
they are married
in the eyes of the Lord.
Uch.
"Uch"?
The bible is "uch" to you?
No, I'm sorry.
That was inappropriate.
As a psychiatrist,
I know how important
people's superstitions
can be to them.
You want to talk
about superstitions?
Sheldon sent me
the books you wrote--
all that nonsense
about superegos and ids.
What bull dropped that
on the barn floor?
His name is Sigmund Freud.
Hey, look at that!
You both believe in
Jewish bearded guys.
Stay out of this.
Mm-hmm.
At least the bearded man
that I believe in
preaches love and compassion.
All yours
talks about is
why you hold in your poop
and want to crawl back
inside your mama.
It's fascinating.
How can someone
as enlightened as Sheldon
come from someone like you?
I know the answer.
You're not gonna like it.
Try me.
When I was pregnant with Shelly,
I was driving to church,
and I was praying
to the Lord
to give me a son smarter
than his dumb-ass daddy.
And I looked over
and I saw a Jesus bobblehead
in the Subaru next to me
nodding yes.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means... I can't believe
we're having this conversation.
Well, do it some more.
Maybe you can knock
some sense into yourself.
Why don't we all stops
hitting ourselves
and talk about something
safe, you know,
like shoes or how cute
little Chinese babies are.
It is not my fault
that your mother likes me
better than she likes you!
Oh, don't flatter yourself!
She likes everybody
better than she likes me!
How old is this Jell-O?
Well, it's carrots,
so gonna say very.
Sorry we have to do this.
Bernadette's not wrong.
She does work hard around here.
Yeah, maybe it's a good thing
if she stops
babying you so much.
She doesn't baby me.
I saw her pull you home
in a wagon.
For your information,
I twisted my ankle
chasing the ice cream truck.
Face it, dude, Bernadette
treats you the same way
your mother used to, and that
was not a healthy relationship.
You're right.
(chuckles)
It's time for me
to act like an adult
in this marriage.
Starting with my husbandly duty
of taking out the trash.
Bernie, I made a mess!
I'm terribly sorry
that I upset your mother.
Oh, it's all right.
She'll forgive you.
She has to or
she goes to hell.
I can't help but notice
how her unconditional
love for you
is diametrically opposed
to my own parenting strategies.
Well, you doled
out affection
as a reward for
achievement--
a proven way to
raise a child.
Or train a rat.
But look how well
you turned out.
I'd feign modesty at this point,
but who would believe me?
Still, you need
to consider
how successful Leonard's
brother and sister are.
I suppose.
While my brother and sister
are mouth-breathing idiots.
Do you suppose
you would've flourished more
in a reward-based environment?
Perhaps.
But my mom made me spaghetti
with chopped-up hot dogs
whenever I wanted,
so who cares?
Not once did my mother ever
give me any love or affection
for just being myself;
I always had to earn it.
Oh, Leonard,
I'm sure she loves you
very much.
In her own cold godless way.
Yeah, and you certainly don't
have to earn my love.
Thank you.
Of course,
you already knew that
when you bought me
this princess-cut drill bit.
That's not what it is.
I know, I know.
(imitates drill buzzing)
When your mom gets back,
I'm gonna need
to apologize for the way
I spoke to her.
Well, come on now,
she did kind of start it.
Doesn't matter; a good Christian
would've turned the other cheek.
On the other hand,
a good Texan
would've shot her, so...
I just kind of
split the difference.
Hey, who's in the mood
for spaghetti and hot dogs?
Oh, me!
Yeah, me, too!
Coming up.
I don't really
feel I deserve it.
That was a big
sticky mess,
but... I think I got it.
Looks good.
Yeah.
Look at that.
You cleaned it up
all by yourself.
Yes, I cleaned it up
all by myself.
Honestly, I don't know
why you complain so...
Okay, maybe I missed one spot.
Just leave.
I'm so glad
that you and I were able
to bury the hatchet.
Me, too.
And I respect your right
to your beliefs.
And I will
pray for you.
Okay, Mom, let's get you
back to your hotel
before anyone says
anything else.
BEVERLY:
One moment.
There's something
I need to say to you.
Oh, really? That's too bad.
Leonard, I always
made you earn my affection,
but today I realize
that there's more than one way
to raise a child.
I taught her that!
BEVERLY:
Therefore, I would like
to initiate a new protocol
wherein I...
shower you
with unconditional love.
Wow.
When does that start?
So needy.
Come to Mommy.
It's okay, go ahead.
Oh, my son.
Oh, my mother.
Oh, my God.
(whistling
"It's a Hard-Knock Life")
(humming along)
♪ It's a hard-knock life ♪
♪ It's the hard-knock life
for us ♪
♪ It's the hard-knock
life for us ♪
♪ 'Stead of treated,
we get tricked ♪
♪ 'Stead of kisses,
we get kicked ♪
♪ It's the hard-knock life ♪
♪ Got no folks to speak of so ♪
♪ It's the hard-knock row
we hoe ♪
♪ Cotton blankets...
'stead of wool ♪
♪ Empty bellies...
'stead of full ♪
♪ It's a hard-knock life. ♪