Previously on "the originals"...
Klaus: I assume
i have the misfortune
Of speaking
to my mother.
I have come to heal
our family.
I will undo everything
that has been done,
Thereby giving you
a new life.
You should
get out of here.
My brother is not
the forgiving kind.
I'm not afraid
of him.
I'm about to get even
with klaus,
And you're
gonna help me.
You're the alpha.
Our people are not
meant to be slaves.
You can free them.
[coughs]
ollie?
I want you to
rejoin our family,
Take the body
of a mortal,
And we can all
be happy again.
Niklaus...
you're not real.
I am flesh and blood,
your flesh and blood.
You are my son.
I brought him here to be
the father you never had.
You said you wanted elijah.
He's sleeping.
When he wakes, he'll
make his own decision.
You cannot
catch me, elijah.
You're getting
faster, klaus,
But you're not
yet fast enough.
Ha ha!
Klaus? Niklaus?
Elijah:
There you are.
[thunder]
Do you understand?
One day, only a monster
shall remain.
[elijah panting]
Klaus: I know you
are locked in battle.
Klaus, voice-over:
However deep in your mind
Our mother has set the stage,
hear my voice.
Our mother thinks she will win
because she has left you alone,
But you are not alone.
Let me in.
Let me help end whatever torment
she has forced upon you.
Uh! Ah!
Uh!
Oh!
What are you doing?
[panting]
I'm trying to enter elijah's
thoughts to wake him.
Esther has
locked me out.
Is this rash
a side effect
Of the witchy
acid trip he's on?
I haven't seen this
since i was a child.
Mikael would return
home from battle
More blindly
temperamental than usual,
And our mother
would use the petals
Of a rare marelok orchid
to put him to sleep.
She would mend his mind
with a spell
And then wake him with
the roots of the same plant.
If she has
access to it now,
Then maybe it also
grows in the bayou.
You stay here
with your wolves
And mind the fort.
I'd rather rip
your mother's head off.
Steer clear
of her.
I mean it, hayley.
She already
got to you once.
What would happen if
elijah were to wake
And find you a victim
of her madness?
I won't
go after her.
I promise.
I've learned a few things
from your mother.
I won't go after her.
I'll go after
everything that she loves.
[music playing]
[footsteps]
I'm so sorry, jack.
This is bull,
hayley.
Crescent tradition
says you have a funeral
At dawn,
and no one is here.
That loyalty...
Loyalty is gone.
We're standing around
moping over ollie's body
When there's a war
to be fought.
I understand that
you have to grieve, jack.
You waited for me.
So i'll do
the same for you,
But our people
need their alpha.
[sniffles]
Marcel:
Where's your alpha?
Unavailable.
So you brought
junior varsity?
I'm getting a little
tired of you
Using my place as a den
for wayward wolves.
Oh, it's just that we
were going to take down
Finn mikaelson today,
and considering
How he treated your vampires,
i assumed that you
Would want in
on the bloodbath.
I'm listening.
Well, it's not
gonna be easy.
He's surrounded by a pack
of juiced-up wolves.
He doesn't have
a weakness.
He does, actually,
And i have her
on speed dial.
He's got a thing
for cami.
Klaus would go ballistic if
we get cami involved in this.
Klaus ain't here,
and cami, well,
She's got this thing
about people telling her
What she can
and can't do.
Trust you, of all
people, understand.
He hasn't called.
He thinks he's
protecting me,
But i don't think
i want to be protected.
Truth be told,
i don't think
I want to be around him
anymore at all.
Well, that's a nice
piece of progress.
What's on your mind?
I was wondering. I...
I know this is, like,
horribly unprofessional,
But i was hoping i could
get a new advisor.
You aren't finding our
sessions productive?
No. No.
That's not it.
They've been great.
You're really getting
to know me.
I just...
I want to get
to know you, too.
Uh...
Right. Yes. Heh.
Mortifyingly unprofessional.
I'm gonna go.
Uh, camile...
Do you enjoy jazz?
[chanting]
[glass cracking]
Still at it?
[glass shatters]
I'm trying to repair
the damage that you did
To my delinking spell.
Oh.
The only reason i'm still
shacked up in this dump motel
With you is for your freaky
witch encyclopedia brain.
Ok. Well, here's
a magical secret
From the ancient legends
of the romani psychics...
Sleep, davina.
You've been awake
for days.
Kind of hard to rest
With a 1,000-year-old
psycho in the next bed.
When you say that,
i sound
Like a bit
of a creeper.
Can you just stop?
Stop what, darling.
Calling me darling
and trying to be funny
And... All of that.
Oh, well, most girls
like this, but then
You're not like most
girls, are you?
What i'd like is for you
to just stop messing around.
Ok, davina.
All right.
I have been trying
to charm you,
And your resistance
is as impressive
As it is baffling,
but there are things
That we can do,
big things.
I can't share
my secrets with you
Unless we trust
each other.
I don't care about
your secrets, kaleb...
Kol. I don't even
know what to call you.
Kol mikaelson,
And if you want
to take down klaus
Without your
friends dying, well,
Then you'd be a fool
not to listen to me.
Uh! Ooh...
Uh...
What's happening?
That's mother dearest
calling me home.
[panting]
Well, you always
did know how
To leave a message,
mother.
If only all my sons were
as respectful as you are.
Kol will return
home soon.
Elijah will wake from
his slumber believing
The only way to salvage
his humanity
Is to rejoin our family,
which is why
It is time you
bring camile in.
Here. I've spelled this
to subdue her
Without causing
bodily harm.
I thought we had
more time.
We don't.
Once klaus has been
duly influenced
By his father, we will
need to act quickly.
No. There's no need
for this.
I can bring her in
without it.
Stop following me.
I have no intention of
taking esther's bargain
And no desire to be
remade a mortal being.
Now kindly piss off.
I'm in a hurry to help
my real family.
You seek
the marelok orchid.
How did you
know that?
I saw you carry elijah
home last night.
Who do you think used
to find the orchid
For your mother to put
mikael to sleep?
Without my help, you
could search forever.
My mother brought you
back from the dead.
My sense of strategy
tells me it wasn't
To play a father-son
game of hide-and-seek.
You can storm off
in a fit
Of stubbornness
if you like,
But i suggest you do
so toward the west.
[classical music playing]
[blues music playing]
[music stops]
Ha ha!
You have any fun
with magic, or is it all
Just angst and child
sacrifice with you lot?
You were a witch
before you were
A vampire, right?
Yeah.
None of my siblings have
tapped into their power,
Little bit of
a child prodigy.
I loved it.
I loved the power.
I loved
the rush,
And then when we turned,
i lost it all,
Went through a bit
of a dark period.
1,000 years?
Yeah.
Well, i'm
a thrill seeker.
Couldn't get that
from magic anymore,
So i looked elsewhere.
Murder, mayhem.
Youthful misadventures.
I actually spent quite
a lot of time with witches,
Learning from them,
teaching them,
Trying to get back what
my mother stole from me.
Is that why she brought
you back as a witch?
She felt like
this body
Would be the best
for the task at hand...
Spying on the
prettiest witch in town.
Can't believe your
mom sent you here
To flirt with me.
No, no. She sent me
to follow you.
The flirting bit
was me.
[classical music playing]
Cami said vincent wants to
meet at preservation hall,
But he won't be
unprotected.
There'll be wolves
positioned here and here.
Can we keep
this alley open?
Great.
We'll wait there
And rip vincent's
head off.
Nah. He'll body jump.
His head stays on.
He'll have a hard time
answering our questions
Without it.
Sweet. It's a big box
of dusty, old junk. We're saved.
They're dark objects
my uncle left for me.
I've been cataloging them
according to kieran's notes.
As far as i can tell,
these can be used
Against witches
specifically.
Kinky.
I remember these.
What?
100 years ago,
the human faction
Waged a war
against the voodoo queens.
They had a trader
spell these manacles.
You slap them
on a witch,
They can't do magic
as long as they're on.
All right.
Well, we're not gonna get
the handcuffs of doom on him
While he's surrounded
by a werewolf entourage.
We just lure him away.
I can do that.
Cami, if we do this,
you're the bait.
Are you sure you're
ok with that?
Make it look
convincing.
The guy
is really smart.
Ansel: 1,000 years
estranged,
And you choose
to walk in silence.
Surely, you have
questions for me.
Just one.
Is there a way
to cure elijah
Without having to listen
to the pointless
Ramblings of
an old man?
I'm afraid the price
of my expertise
Is conversation.
You know, i used
to tell myself that
My real father must have
had no idea i existed.
Otherwise, he'd never leave
me to suffer under mikael.
Esther forbade me
from seeing you.
So i waited, knowing
that one day,
You would trigger
your curse
And need
your real father...
But when that happened,
mikael found me first.
I fought him for you.
Yes.
Well, your grand declaration
is just a few years too late.
Now, you joke,
but i know you've
Always felt a void
in your life.
I've watched you from
beyond for centuries.
You've traveled all
corners of the world,
Seen monuments erected,
feasted on the blood
Of history's most
extraordinary men,
But you've never
found true peace.
The only moments of joy
in your life,
However fleeting, have
been simple pleasures...
As you climbed
the himalayas,
As you tended
to your horses,
Quiet days teaching
that boy shakespeare.
Stop.
I watched you paint.
I watched you feel your
unborn daughter's kick.
I said stop.
A millennium
of observing me,
Were your eyes closed as
i slaughtered whole villages,
Fed my way through
thousands of innocents?
Because...
let's face it...
I have a tendency
to play with my food.
Have i made you
proud, father?
Remind me to teach you
how to send a text message.
You were told to get the
white oak stake days ago.
We need it now,
Seeing as your
father has risen.
Mikael?
Back from the dead?
Enough.
You kept it from me.
Why, because of
davina claire?
To protect your plan.
She's never gonna trust me
if she thinks i'm just
A flying monkey
to the wicked witch.
I've got it
handled, mother.
I want that stake,
and i don't care
What you have to do
to get it.
Vervain.
It's everywhere.
My relentless mother
has set a trap.
I'll retrieve
the marelok for you.
At what cost?
Why don't you use
your vampire abilities
To end your doubts?
Search my mind.
You'll see i'm not
allied with your mother.
I have absolutely
no interest
In the inner workings
of your brain.
I'm surprised
at your cowardice.
While you stand here
in fear of me,
Your brother
suffers further.
Gather the orchids.
What'd your mother
want from you?
She wants me
to take that stake
Out of your bag,
give it to her
So that you
can't kill klaus
Before she gets her
big, happy family.
Is that why
you called me here?
I'm not
my mother's puppet.
I want something
different entirely.
I want your blood.
Relax, luv.
I'm not gonna take it.
I'm asking you nicely.
Sure. I'll just
bleed for you
Without any
explanation at all.
About 100 years ago,
This tomb used to be
my playhouse.
The witches i used
to run with,
They used to make all
kinds of magic in here,
That is, until i pissed
the prettiest one off,
As i tend to do, and,
well, she locked me out.
So why do you
need my blood?
Her name was
mary-alice claire.
Only a claire witch
can open this tomb.
Where'd you get
all this stuff?
Well, i was a vampire.
I could get anything
i wanted,
But i couldn't
practice witchcraft.
So i charmed some witches,
and i taught them
A new kind of magic that
i learned in arabia
Called kemiya.
We made items that
allowed me to use magic
Without doing magic.
You taught them how
to make dark objects.
Yeah, and for a time,
They were scattered
all around the city.
I can't for the life
of me find out
Where they are now,
but...
I've got the one
that matters.
What is it?
It's not about
what it is.
It's about what
it could be.
You want to take
down klaus, right?
I've wanted one
thing for years...
To drive a dagger
into his heart
Like he's done to me
so many times.
Those daggers
don't work on klaus.
Smart girl.
With a little practice
and some trust,
We'll fix it
so this one will.
We'll put him
in a box.
Seeing as he won't
be entirely dead,
Your friends
will be safe.
So what do you say?
[dixieland jazz music playing]
[bell rings]
Thank you.
This is amazing.
I developed
an appreciation
For the music
when i moved here.
I never had a taste
for it before.
I see you're
still developing
Your taste for beer.
My mom said beer
wasn't ladylike.
So i learned to love it
as an act of rebellion.
What about you?
Snobby mom, distant dad?
Let's go.
Well, my mother and
i are quite close.
She made so many
sacrifices for us,
Now anything she asks seem
negligible in comparison.
[cell phone rings]
Oh. Hold on. So sorry.
Can you hold this?
Oh, i have
to take this.
A friend is
covering my shift.
I'll be right back.
I'm so sorry.
Cami: Aah! Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Hey!
[hayley whistles]
Klaus: I've always seen a blade
to have a very different use.
Mikael taught you
to kill, klaus,
But you were born
to create.
Power lies in embracing
your true nature.
You think i should accept
my mother's offer,
Sacrifice my vampirism.
Then what,
become a florist?
[chuckles]
You wouldn't be
sacrificing anything.
As a wolf,
you could be king
To an entire
species.
You would feel
true peace.
You would be
a better father.
I am no longer
a father.
In our animal form,
We feel everything
more acutely.
When you were a boy,
after each full moon,
I would wake closer
to your village,
Having been drawn
to you in the night.
Since i've been back,
each month when i turn,
I wake further
from new orleans.
I know the call of
my own blood, klaus.
I know your child
is still alive.
It was a wolf bite.
Who broke rank?
I'll knock some heads
together and find out.
I'll know where
camile is shortly.
You'll
meet me there.
Come alone
Because your wolves
can't be trusted.
[beep]
Well, he bought it.
His locator spell
will bring him here
Without
the bodyguards.
I always thought
having a woman's mouth
On my neck would be
more erotic.
You'll heal fast.
Let's get all these
lights off. Here.
We're so going
to hell for this.
Ha ha! Yeah.
You get used to it.
Hey, i know this probably
isn't your ideal friday night.
I'm sure you'd rather be,
like, doing pushups
Or drinking beers with
your bros or whatever.
Eh, it's not so bad.
Cami: Ok. Tell me
the plan one more time.
Aiden is gonna get
vincent to the altar,
And then i'm
gonna jump him.
He's powerful, though,
so we only have
A few seconds to get
the shackles on him.
Where's marcel?
He's looking
for davina.
He heard she
was back in town.
Overprotective
dad stuff.
If you want to call
ripping kol mikaelson
Into 1,000 little pieces
protective dad stuff,
Then, yeah,
that's it.
[chuckles]
[snap]
[music playing]
Kaleb: The hunters who forged
the originals daggers
To take out my family
didn't know that klaus
Was part werewolf
and vulnerable to silver.
Now, it's impossible
to replicate
The spell cast
on the dagger...
Trust me, i've tried...
but it's not impossible
To change
the dagger itself.
Now, kemiya allows
witches to destroy
One element
to create another,
Say, changing silver
to gold, for example.
So you've been hanging out
with me this whole time
Because you don't have
enough power on your own.
Oh, kemiya
is about chemistry.
It's about connection,
and after what happened
With the white oak
stake,
I don't think you could
deny what we have.
So, here,
hold my hand.
That's
a giant diamond.
It's a paragon
diamond.
They use them
to conduct power.
Is the hand holding
really necessary?
I mean, we could
make out,
But would that not be
entirely distracting?
[sighs]
All right.
Follow my lead.
Close your eyes.
[chanting]
[both chanting]
Heh.
[gasps]
To replace
the one i broke.
We changed it.
Oh, davina claire,
We're gonna
change everything.
This will help
elijah.
Ansel...
I'd be lying if i said
your offer wasn't appealing.
I've never known a parent
to be a benevolent force.
I think i would have liked
to have been your son,
But a different path
was chosen for me,
And i have for
the past 1,000 years
Been son of mikael...
paranoid, vengeful...
And powerful enough
to protect my daughter.
I want to help you
defend her.
I believe you,
But love is
what esther twists.
She will take the best
of your intentions,
And she will use them
to get to my little girl.
You waited too long
Before you came
to rescue me.
I won't make the same
mistake with hope.
No.
No, klaus.
I know you.
You are not
capable of this.
That's the first lie
you've told me.
Uh!
Oh...
It's late.
I should get going.
Suppose you'll
be wanting
To get back
to marcel's.
I lied to him
about you.
Probably go back
to the attic.
Voluntarily returning
to the jail cell
Where they
locked you up.
You must have been
lonely all that time.
A witch needs a coven,
even if it is just two.
When can we work
on the dagger?
Soon. We got some
more work to do
With each other
first.
You're gonna like me,
davina claire,
And i'm gonna let you
pretend a while
That you don't
already.
Well, i staked
it out.
Looks like a couple
of oliver's friends
Wanting to avenge
his death.
Where's cami?
She's tied up
near the altar.
Hey, you know what?
You beeline for her.
I'll handle the rest
of them, all right?
Aiden, your brother
Was among the recruits
that oliver rescued.
Was he not?
[thunder]
Oh, no.
[crack]
Camile! Camile!
First, i'm gonna
kick your ass,
And then i'm gonna
take my pack back.
Your pack?
Last i checked,
your pack
Was blindly
following me.
Want to talk
about following?
How do your mother's
boots taste, huh?
Ha! What have you
done with cami?
Oh!
Hybrids die by
losing their head
Or their heart.
Given the choice,
i'm gonna take the organ
That got you into this
mess in the first place.
[chanting]
[gagging]
Aagh!
Huh!
[clank clank]
[sobs]
You would've done the
same thing to me, finn.
[chains rattle]
Hey, are you ok?
I'm so sorry
i made you wait.
Your timing was
pretty awesome, actually.
Ha ha!
[elijah panting]
We were innocent
once, elijah.
[panting]
[thunder]
This bloodlust was
forced upon us
By our parents,
Turning us from prey
to predator.
[thunder]
We are the demons
lurking in shadow.
We are the
savage villains
In fairy tales
told to children,
But not for my child,
not for hope.
In her story,
We are the knights
in shining armor.
Without you by my side,
i don't think i can
Survive my own love
for my daughter.
I need you.
I need you,
brother.
The monster in me
can only be checked
By the monster
in you,
in you.
Only together can we
defeat our demons
And save our family.
[thunder]
Hraagh!
[panting]
[door opens and closes]
We put vincent in
the back of josh's car.
Is aiden
all right?
Mm, some ice and
bourbon, he'll be fine.
How'd you know
where to find us?
I spent a lot of time
tracking you when i was a wolf.
Call it
animal instinct.
What do you mean?
Oh, ollie used to
give me so much hell
For waiting on you.
Oh, girls came and went,
but i always knew
Someday you'd come.
See, our parents
had been so sure
That you and i could
change things for the better.
Jack, i think the girl
that you were waiting on
Was andrea labonair,
mythic revolutionary.
You got
hayley marshall,
A knocked-up tomboy
with a bad attitude.
You got dealt
a crappy hand.
[chuckles]
No. You're right.
You're not the girl
i waited for.
You're better.
What is it?
I spent the day
with my father,
My real father.
Esther brought him
back from the dead
Believing he
could convince me
To renounce
vampirism,
And the thought
of what i could be
Had i been
raised by him...
I'd have been
nurtured.
This was his.
He knew
about hope...
And i wanted
to trust him.
More than anything in
the world, i wanted to,
But...
Uh... I couldn't
be sure,
And i would never
forgive myself
If something
happened to her
Because of my selfish
desire for a father.
So i killed him.
Without hesitation,
i killed him.
[music playing]
You killed him
for hope.
Whatever innocence
remains
We must protect
at any cost.
[sobs]
[sobbing]
Yaah! Oh...
Sorry.
We're closed.
That's too bad.
I hear you serve the best
sazerac in town.
Camile, isn't it?
My sons have taken
quite the liking to you.
[chanting]
How do you feel?
The worst has passed...
Though i suspect
the nightmares
Are far from over.
Well, gather
your strength.
After the message
i sent mother tonight,
I expect hellfire to rain
down upon us imminently.
We need to make a move
before she strikes.
Marcel: Actually, moves were
made while you were sleeping.
It's good
to see you vertical.
Marcel and i each left
a gift for you in the ballroom.
You're welcome.
Kaleb: Kidnapping.
It's a rather unpleasant way
to begin a family reunion.
Well, wait until you see
how we end it.