♪ We face the music together ♪
♪ And throw our hats
in the ring ♪
♪ Facing all kinds of weather ♪
♪ And not afraid of anything ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When the sun comes up,
we'll be on our way ♪
♪ And we don't care
where we land ♪
♪ And the waves are high,
but we won't turn round ♪
♪ 'Cause your hand
is in my hand ♪
♪ And, oh-oh ♪
♪ You make me feel invincible ♪
♪ 'Cause it's you and me ♪
♪ Through the wind and hail ♪
♪ Setting sail into the world ♪♪
[man] One, two, three, four.
♪ ♪
[man speaking indistinctly
on radio]
- Mum?
- Mm?
[Flynn] I just want it plain.
- No ketchup or butter.
- Right.
- [Betty] And I want
the bagel toasted,
so it's hot.
Well, it's toasted.
It's hot now.
Where's the regular milk?
This is almond milk.
You forgot to get milk.
I can't drink that.
Aren't you all supposed
to be vegans by now?
- That's when you're 13.
- Ooh.
Well, don't you want to be ahead
of the curve? Hmm?
Don't forget,
your dad's picking you up today.
[Flynn] Don't bother
with lunches then, Mum.
- [Elizabeth] Why?
- Dad does his Fajita Fridays.
Mm. For lunch?
As soon as we get in.
- Gets takeaway?
- No.
He makes them,
- from scratch.
- They're the best.
Bet they're delicious.
Piping hot.
- [Flynn] Yeah.
- "Piping hot."
- [sighs deeply]
- Yeah, okay.
Enough with the sighing.
I get it.
It's not your bag.
You know, it's not...
- highbrow enough.
- Highbrow?
[stammers]
What's with this...
spitting and choking?
- [chuckles]
- They're supposed
to love each other?
Oh. You poor sheltered child.
[chuckles]
Everyone's doing it these days.
Really? Is that based on actual
scientific fact or something
you're regurgitating
from trashy magazines?
I-Is Chat trashy?
You need to buy me lunch.
Exactly. Well, I can buy you
a very nice lunch.
Do you think it'll sell?
Sadly, I do.
- Do you? Hmm.
- Yeah.
Super interesting guy.
- Ooh, really?
- Mm. Good-looking, too.
I mean, not that shallow things
like looks matter to you.
Lily, Lily. I'm actually all
right where I'm at right now.
Sure.
My marriage just didn't work.
- It ended. You know.
- Mm.
That's because you chose
a besotted boy
when you needed a man.
It wasn't Van's fault.
I had big plans
for married life,
constant expectations
leading to disappointment.
- I know.
- It was as much my fault
- as it was his.
- But it was never gonna work.
No.
I'm not closed off to it.
If it, if it happens,
it happens. Wonderful.
I'm just not gonna peddle myself
like some used car on a website.
But you're
a vibrant young woman.
You know,
you should be with somebody.
'Cause you are?
How is that working out for you?
Yeah.
I could wring his neck.
And not in a good way.
There is no good way.
Oh, you'd be surprised.
[chuckles]
You are such a prude. [laughs]
[doorbell buzzes]
[knocking]
Mm. Okay.
Come on, guys.
I don't think your mum's here.
Think she might have had
an early morning.
Or a late night.
- Yeah.
- I have keys.
Oh, no. We'll...
- we'll-we'll come back.
- Wait, she's...
- Oh. Um...
- Oh!
[Van] I'm really sorry
about this.
Uh, I-I tried texting.
Uh, Boo needs her ukulele.
- [Betty] Mm-hmm.
- [Elizabeth] Saturday morning.
Why aren't you glued to screens
like regular kids?
That's because I have
my talent competition.
- You're coming, right?
- Yeah.
- Wild horses wouldn't stop me.
- Boo.
[whispers] Sorry.
What's that?
Oh. It's her flask.
- Dad made yummy soup.
- Mmm.
- And it keeps it piping hot.
How'd you get so good at this?
- Yeah.
At what? It's just soup.
It's, uh, mixed vegetable,
a little bit of basil,
- maybe some garlic...
- Not the soup, dummy.
The whole...
- Super Dad thing.
- Uh...
I don't know. I guess, uh,
when you're on your own,
you have to do the stuff that
the other person used to do.
You just got better at
everything and I just got worse.
I think I had more room
for improvement, didn't I?
- You have a point.
- That's true, yeah.
- What time?
- Oh, I guess, like,
after the rehearsals.
2:30 in the Calder Hall,
isn't it?
- [Betty] Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
[chuckles] Okay. Come on.
- Okay. Bye-bye.
- [Flynn] Bye, Mum! Bye.
- Bye.
[cheering and applause]
I don't really like
the competition aspect
of these things,
but that was bad.
Yeah, that was.
And now we have Betty Cannon
on the ukulele.
- [whooping]
- [cheering and applause]
♪ When you were young ♪
♪ And on ♪
♪ Your own ♪
♪ How did it feel ♪
♪ To be ♪
♪ Alone? ♪
♪ I was always thinking of ♪
♪ Games ♪
♪ That I was playing ♪
♪ Trying to make ♪
♪ The best of my time ♪
♪ But only love ♪
♪ Can break your heart ♪
♪ What if your world ♪
♪ Should fall ♪
♪ Apart? ♪♪
[cheering and applause]
Yay!
Whoa. [chuckling]
I know. Look at her.
Come to dinner. Tonight.
If you fancy. Celebrate.
You were saying earlier your
cooking's disimproved, so...
So, I've got an idea. Ooh! Why
don't we order in and celebrate?
Why don't we have that banana
bread you made at school?
- There's loads of that left.
- No, no, um...
- No, that expired.
- No? I'd, um...
- Yeah, and, also,
- the-the bananas weren't...
- I'd love to.
If you're busy,
I didn't mean to...
Uh, no. I can, uh...
I can, I can rearrange.
What, uh... what time?
- Seven?
- Great.
Okay, kiddies. I'll, uh...
I will see you later. [grunts]
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye.
- Bye-bye, Dad.
- Wait, don't forget
chocolate cake.
- Yeah, and...
- What about
Flynn's banana bread then?
- No...
- It expired, remember?
- Wine! Wine.
- Okay, wine,
Flynn's banana bread...
- [Flynn] I think
it went a little wrong
whilst I was cooking it.
- [Betty] Yeah.
- [Elizabeth] Come on.
- See you later.
- [Flynn] Yeah! Okay, bye!
[Elizabeth] Come on.
No, I mean, I was immature.
I loved... I loved the idea
of being grown-ups, but I...
I didn't really have any
of the tools, you know?
So weird talking to a guy
whose emotional baggage
about his controlling ex-wife
is something
- I can completely relate to.
- [chuckles]
Well, my kids seem lovely.
- It's...
- Perfect date.
Perfect.
Do you remember
that flat in Bow?
[sputters]
How did we survive
a winter there?
Ha! You wore a ski suit to bed.
- I remember that.
- I did. [laughing]
I finally found a woman
to move in with me,
and... you were genuinely
putting more clothes on
to go to bed
than you wore during the day.
I mean... [stammers]
Can you imagine
how disastrous that was
for my...
my young male psyche?
It had zips.
I'd never skied. It was tricky.
- [laughs]
-Do you remember,
do you remember that night
where we... we, um...
we broke up the chairs
- and burned them on the fire
'cause it was so...
- You broke up the chairs.
And then when my parents
came round, there was nowhere
- for them to sit.
That was a red flag right there.
- Oh, come on.
- It was romantic.
- It wasn't romantic.
Eating tuna out of tins.
No television, no... phone.
No computers.
What the hell did we do all day?
We kissed.
We sat on the sofa for hours,
just...
just kissing to pass the time.
[inhales]
Did we?
Must've been...
That must've been fun.
- [inhales, exhales]
- You remember.
You don't remember?
[siren wailing in distance]
I remember the tuna.
[inhales, exhales]
♪ ♪
Ooh.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Come to bed.
Okay.
You sure?
No.
You still got the ski suit?
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
[door creaks]
[floor creaking]
- [quietly] Come on.
- [Van chuckles]
Shh. Don't make a peep.
[chuckles softly]
[whispers] Okay. Bye.
Mmm.
Hmm? That was fun.
It was. Yeah.
They've got drama on Tuesdays,
6:00 till 8:00.
Right. Okay. And?
[laughs]
Shh.
[♪ Gary Clark and Gregor Philip:
"Home Again"]
It's a date.
♪ Little cars
and small apartments ♪
♪ Boulevards
before my heart went wrong ♪
♪ You were
all my missing persons ♪
♪ And I've been missing you
for much too long ♪
♪ The day was only waiting
for the sun ♪
[panting]
♪ You took me home...
Need a lift?
I really thought
I'd make it home.
Then I remembered I'm... [pants]
- I'm 48.
- What gives you the right to be
so cheerful
this time in the morning?
[chuckles] Well,
I just spent the night
with the woman of my dreams.
Good for you.
Where'd you meet?
Well, that's the tricky bit.
- [starts engine]
- I, uh...
I used to be married to her.
Oh, do fuck off.
♪ ♪
Shut up.
- Van?
- [shushing softly]
We weren't very good
at being married, but...
everything else works.
That's twisted. [stammers]
I'm shocked.
- I'm sure you are.
- [chuckles]
Trapped
in your orthodox marriage.
I don't want to put a dampener
on it, Liz.
Aren't you just taking
the path of least resistance?
You know, just falling back
into something familiar.
I'm not marrying him.
Be very careful, Elizabeth.
It's fun.
No expectations on either side.
- [knocking]
- [doorbell buzzes]
[chuckles]
Hey. Wow.
You look amazing.
Sorry. I was just, um...
I've just come from work.
Do-do you mind
if I lift the bike in?
- Bring her in.
- [chuckles]
Okay.
Thanks.
Ah...
I was, um...
I was gonna pick up
some wine on the way,
- and then I was like,
"Is this..."
- No, no. Don't be silly.
- Don't be silly.
- [inhales]
Hey.
Maybe I should've got some wine.
- Shall I go and get some?
- No, no, no, no.
I was just... No, it's too sad.
- Okay.
- And we haven't got time.
There's an Irish dance class
after drama class.
Could sign the girls up
for that.
That would give us some time.
Do we need that long?
Well, it's funny
you should say that.
I did a-a tantric yoga class
last week.
Mm...
Yeah. I picked up a few tricks.
- Sh...
- Oh, you're interested now?
- I'm just...
- [laughs]
I might be interested.
Well, I was at the back
of the class,
- so, um... No, no.
- Oh, right. Here we go.
- But, from what I could see...
- Were you, now?
No. From what I could see...
Can I show you?
So...
[inhales] Yeah, uh, use...
If you give me your hand
and you sort of put that
there...
- [sucks air] Saucy.
- ...and then...
Yeah, it's very saucy.
And then this one under there.
- Yeah? You paying attention?
- Wow, I've never seen that
before.
[laughs] Just round here.
- Okay.
- Yeah. Concentrate.
[Elizabeth] Bog-standard
so far.
[Van] Okay, and this is
where it gets...
this is where it gets
pretty complicated.
- [Elizabeth] Okay.
- You ready?
Okay.
Gonna keep this fun, right?
Yeah. Yeah. No, of course.
No. You're the boss.
♪ ♪
[chatter in distance]
[line ringing]
No.
I'm going to have
to call your mum.
Your dad's phone is still going
to answering machine,
and... I have to leave soon.
Can you call him once more?
My mum said she had something
important on this afternoon.
Well, I was explaining
to your colleague
that I don't have the receipt.
It was, it was 12 years ago.
Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly.
Oh, I actually don't...
I don't remember.
It was, um...
Um...
It was... The name?
The name is Cannon.
Ivan Cannon.
Yeah.
I'm looking for the size,
the-the ring size, exactly.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll hold.
Okay. Thank you.
- Nice.
- Oh.
- Thanks.
- So...
when the lady orders
the baklava,
I return with one baklava
and the ring on another plate.
Or two baklava.
And no ring?
Oh, no, no. Definitely the ring.
What if she orders
something else?
Oh, well, just, um,
put it beside
whatever she orders.
Gotcha.
Okay. [inhales]
Um, great.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
What?
I found out today.
Why didn't you...
why didn't you tell me?
I just... I only just...
[clears throat]
I only just found out,
and, um...
Yeah, I've got breast cancer,
and it's quite advanced.
Why didn't you tell me? What...
It's not your problem.
Well, what have you...
Did you tell the girls?
I haven't said anything.
Haven't...
I haven't told anybody.
Listen, I'll...
I'll move back in.
I'll move back in. It's, um...
Liz, let-let's get...
let's get married again.
Let's just...
let's just...
Why the fuck
would I want to get married?
I don't know. I just...
The last few months
have been great, and...
this doesn't change anything.
This is just a diagnosis.
This is not the end
of your life.
And I want to be with you.
Liz, I...
I want to be with you, and...
[scoffs]
I can't... really...
deal with this right now.
Uh, s...
Uh, n... [exhales]
Enjoy.
Liz, look, I'm-I'm just...
No, no, no, no.
Please, I just...
I need some space.
♪ ♪
[female voice] You have
one new message
received at 10:15 p.m.
[Van] Hey. I'm sorry
my timing is so shitty.
And of course I'm here for you
in whatever c...
♪ ♪
[Flynn] Why is this
happening now?
I'm afraid
you can't plan your life out.
Not like chess, is it?
You can't work out
20 moves ahead.
Things just happen
that you can't...
that you can't foresee.
And sometimes
they're really good things,
like...
falling in love.
Like having two beautiful girls.
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
And sometimes
they're rubbish things.
- Yeah.
- Like being here.
Yeah.
Is that an invitation for a hug?
- Yes. Mm.
- I'll have that, please.
- I'll take it. Thank you.
- Mm.
Oh.
I feel much better.
- Mm. Same.
- Yeah. [chuckles]
That's good.
- Me, too.
- [chuckles softly]
[♪ Gavin Clark: "Painted Glass"]
...chop these up.
[speaking indistinctly]
♪ We were walking
through the old town ♪
♪ Coming in over the pass ♪
♪ You were checking
your reflection ♪
♪ There in the shopfront
smearing glass ♪
[speaking indistinctly]
♪ I saw the glory
of a new love ♪
♪ Oh, this pain ♪
♪ This restlessness ♪
♪ Some days, I feel better ♪
♪ Some days, I feel blessed ♪
♪ Oh, there's only
a few of us left...
[nurse] I appreciate that,
but only next of kin
or immediate relatives
are allowed
in the recovery ward.
And next of kin is given here
as a Mrs. Lily De Courcy.
Okay, all right, this is...
this is ridiculous.
I'm their father,
for God's sake.
I understand that,
but there's nothing I can do.
I can only go
by the patient's declaration.
Mrs. De Courcy is in there
at the moment.
Do you want me
to ask her to come out
and perhaps she can take
the children in briefly?
It's okay, Boo. It's okay.
Okay. Yeah.
If you could do that. Thank you.
Hey, girls.
Yeah, your mum is doing
really well.
Okay, I'm gonna take you in
in a minute, okay?
- I'm sorry. You know,
they couldn't be happier.
- Yeah.
Surgery's gone really well.
They think
they've got everything.
- They're really pleased.
- Okay.
And Liz is doing great.
- Uh, thank you. That's great.
- Yeah.
She's, uh, booked in
for radiation on Tuesday.
- Okay.
- So they've given me
a schedule.
- But I'll just forward it on
to you?
- Sure.
Yeah. Um...
Okay. Uh, girls,
um, go in with Lily,
- and I'll-I'll wait
for you here, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay. Bye, Dad.
- Okay?
- We're gonna be
- quiet as mice, okay?
- Yeah, okay.
Because it's a recovery ward,
not really her room.
[siren wailing in distance]
Yeah. Let's try and be quiet.
[indistinct P.A. announcement]
♪ ♪
- ♪ ♪
- [speaking indistinctly]
[female voice] You have
one old voice mail
received at 10:15 p.m.
[Van] Hey. I'm sorry
my timing is so shitty.
And of course I'm here for you
in whatever capacity you need.
But the truth is
that I love you.
The reason that I'm free
on Saturday nights, every night,
is because I stopped dating.
I felt stupid sitting opposite
some woman who wasn't you.
And that has nothing to do
with the girls
or our marriage
or even your diagnosis.
I want to be with you,
and I want you to be sure
about that.
I'm actually still
at the restaurant.
I kind of thought
you might come back.
That's all
I've ever really wanted.
I know you didn't want things
to get too complicated,
but that's kind of unreasonable
in itself
because I can't control
how you make me feel.
I know now
that I never stopped loving you.
So I'm-I'm running around
like a-a crazed teenager
every time you text me.
I don't know what else to do
in the face of everything
but to tell you that.
Because...
it's not going to change.
My feelings for you
aren't going to change.
I have loved you
since I met you,
and I will always love you.
End of.
Um, as the...
as the girls would say.
[engine idling]
Hey, if you want anything,
we can stop.
- I can run in.
- I should be good.
- You sure?
- Thanks.
- Okay.
You've done more than enough,
Lily.
Just go home. I'll be fine.
Don't be crazy.
I wouldn't hear of it.
- [Betty] [whispers] One...
- [popping]
- Surprise!
- [laughing]
- I nearly had...
I nearly... Oh! [giggling]
[Elizabeth] That,
that is a real surprise.
- So lovely.
What a lovely surprise.
- [Van] Hello. Say hello.
Give me a little kissy.
Careful of my arm.
[kissing] I see...
- Did you miss... You missed
my cooking, didn't you?
- Ooh.
Yeah, we miss
everything about you.
- I miss everything about you.
- Yeah, we sure did.
- Whee!
- Sit down.
- Sit down, Mum.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Can you stay for a bit?
- I want to...
- Yeah, yeah, of course.
...let her go. Madam,
- you are free to go.
- Balloons and...
I'll call you tomorrow.
- See ya, Van. Hey, girls.
- Thanks, Lily. See ya.
- [smooching]
- Bye! [giggles]
- [chuckles]
- Well, let's get my coat.
- Shut this up.
- I'm gonna take your coat.
- You're gonna take my coat
for me.
[Van] Do you want
to have a race,
- you two? Yeah?
- [Betty/Flynn] Yeah.
Ready? Steady? Go.
Ready, steady, go.
Crocodiles and sharks. Okay.
- [yelps]
- Oh, Boo's really quick.
[Flynn] [laughs] Oh!
[laughs]
- [Elizabeth] Come on.
- Oh!
[Elizabeth] What did you
just say?
I said if they both do it,
- um, without touching
the ground...
- [Betty] Oh! Oh, my God.
...I'm gonna get them lunch
at Alfred's.
- [girls chattering]
- What a sap.
I thought you were supposed
to be toughening them up.
Okay, you'll take the gravel.
- I would've been
over here already.
- No!
Toughening them up?
Have you seen them?
I think... I think they'd both
kill us without missing a beat.
- [chuckles]
- [Flynn] I got Captain Maloney!
- Okay, now I need
to go save him.
- [Van] Yay!
[indistinct chatter]
- Oh, my God.
Did you see these gems?
- They're amazing.
Scuse me. How much is this?
[vendor] Like,
for all the crystals?
[indistinct chatter]
- [Van] Show her your crystals.
- [Betty] Ooh.
- [Flynn] Ooh.
- [gasps] Oh, my God.
- This one's, like,
a crystal tree.
- It's a dreamcatcher, Mum.
- [Betty] Mummy, look.
- Is this, like,
a crystal solar system?
- [Betty] What are these?
- A bit small.
- What's the heart?
- Well, you...
well, you need to bring
your pocket money with you.
[girls chattering in distance]
- Just one.
- Okay.
I should put it. Go to bed.
- I am.
- [Betty] Daddy!
I'll be five minutes, honey!
- I can do it by myself.
- Okay?
I can do it by myself.
No. Uh... [grunts]
It's okay. Uh...
If... [clears throat]
if it, if it's okay with you,
I, uh...
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
Nothing to hide.
- Literally.
- [chuckles softly]
- [exhales]
- Okay. It's all right.
[exhales]
All right, then.
Okay.
Stuck.
- [shudders]
- [bandage peeling]
Okay.
- There's that.
- Okay.
- Can I take this off?
- Take the other piece.
- It's fine.
- Yeah, okay.
[inhales]
[peeling bandage]
[grunting softly]
Don't want to touch there.
Okay.
[sniffles]
Help put my dressing gown
on me, please?
Oi.
[grunts]
It was the biggest crocodile
- she'd ever seen. It...
- [Betty] Uh, what was the...
[Van] The crocodile's mouth
was this big.
- [Betty] Um, are you sure
it was a crocodile?
- It had 100 teeth in it.
- [Betty] That's an alligator.
- [Flynn] Like this?
- The-the crocodile...
- A bit like that. Exactly.
- Are you sure it's a crocodile
- and not an alligator?
- And the crocodile
looked at her... Hey.
Would you mind staying?
Yeah. Of course.
Okay.
And the crocodile's mouth had...
Guess how many teeth
it had in it.
- A hundred, a thousand.
- Fifty.
A thousand teeth.
[birds chirping]
Van's been great.
With the girls, with me.
Patient, reliable.
Wow.
Capable.
Ah.
Just gets on with it, really.
No fuss.
Do you love him?
I don't know what I feel.
I'm beginning to think
that maybe I never stopped
- loving him.
- [exhales]
That doesn't mean
we're meant to live together.
I'm not well.
Everything feels...
uncertain.
When next do you see Dr. Wyman?
Tomorrow.
What?
You don't think it's good news?
[Wyman] Although
we haven't beaten it yet,
it's important to stay positive,
Elizabeth.
What I'd like us to do
is to change our approach
and join a clinical trial
a colleague of mine, Dr. Kang,
is running here,
using an immunotherapy drug.
Okay.
Obviously,
there's no track record,
so I can't provide you
with much data,
but initial indications
are very promising.
Would I have to be admitted?
Only for a couple of days.
And if your tolerance is okay,
you could continue at home.
Sign me up.
Excellent.
You're making the right choice.
I'll get all the paperwork.
Um...
could you bring
my original admissions form?
I'd like to change
my next of kin.
What?
I'm bumped?
Yep.
[groans]
[indistinct P.A. announcement]
[Betty] It's Italian roast,
- Dad's favorite.
- Hmm.
[sucks air] Let's see.
[swallows] Delicious.
Told you.
But...
tomato-y?
You didn't wash it out,
you idiot.
- [laughing]
- I'll tell you what,
you and Betty
can buy something
in the vending machine.
And then I'll come and get you.
Okay?
- [Flynn] Okay.
- [departing footsteps]
♪ ♪
[Elizabeth] How many times
has one of them done that
and I haven't even noticed?
I can't bear the thought
of them growing up without me.
[Van] Hey, you're gonna get
through this, huh?
I mean, please?
[chuckles softly]
You have to. They're, uh...
they're already sick of me.
They're not sick of you.
Can't get enough of you.
You're actually amazing.
On that note.
[humming softly] Da-dum.
Don't worry.
It's not a proposal. [laughs]
It's a... That was, um...
Open it.
I just, I noticed you,
uh, looking at that ring
at the market.
That...
Wow. [laughing]
Moonstone. [inhales]
Well, it was too small, but...
You had it altered.
Yeah.
[laughing]
So annoying.
[sniffling]
Why? Am I driving you nuts?
- [chuckles softly]
- Yeah.
Sorry.
I mean, sorry, not sorry.
[whispers] I would have
said yes.
Really?
Mm. [chuckles]
- [sniffling]
- It's not... Are you sure
it's not just the drugs talking?
I haven't started them yet.
Okay. [exhales]
Okay.
That's-that's good to know.
Yeah, for-for future reference.
[shudders]
Yeah, there'll be...
there'll be more proposals.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
- So-so be warned.
[sniffles]
[♪ Neil Young: "Only Love
Can Break Your Heart"]
You probably, um...
Yeah, I bet you know this,
but...
the, uh... the moonstone
is, uh, renowned
for its healing properties.
- ♪ When you were young ♪
- [inhales]
- ♪ And on your own ♪
- [exhales]
♪ How did it feel ♪
Here's to healing.
♪ To be alone? ♪
In all its forms.
♪ ♪
♪ I was always thinking ♪
- Yeah.
- ♪ Of games ♪
♪ That I was playing ♪
♪ Trying to make the best ♪
- ♪ Of my time ♪
- Yeah.
♪ But only love ♪
♪ Can break your heart ♪
♪ Try to be sure ♪
♪ Right from the start ♪
♪ Yes, only love ♪
♪ Can break your heart ♪
♪ What if your world ♪
♪ Should fall apart? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I have a friend ♪
♪ I've never seen ♪
♪ He hides his head ♪
♪ Inside a dream ♪♪