Previously on Why Women Kill..
You can cheat on your wife
all you want,
but you're not
touching mine.
I am in love with you.
ROB: You knew the rules.
I will never...
leave my wife.
(sighs)
So I can tell Rob is still mad
about the other night.
He hasn't called in days.
Why would he even be with me
if he was so happy with her?
BETH ANN: Maybe she did
something to hurt him
and he needs time
to forgive her.
This project
I've been involved with,
it's almost over.
I'll be home in time for dinner.
Every night.
SIMONE:
It's Hector.
He was the best hairdresser
I ever had.
I've known for some time
about Karl's indiscretions.
I saw his car parked
at some seedy motel.
(gasps)
What in God's name?
We haven't seen each
other in years.
Hector was the only person
who ever saw me
for the man I truly am.
Stop romanticizing
your grubby little fling.
Do you love him?
I do.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
You fell asleep.
- Take this.
- Uh...
I don't think I should.
TAYLOR:
While I was away,
did you two fuck?
- (chuckles nervously)
- We absolutely fucked.
TAYLOR:
Okay.
This was bound to happen, right?
Since we're
all together now.
All right, let's talk
about my script.
I'm expecting offers in
the high six-figure range.
(exhales)
Be good to Jade.
She's your muse.
His muse?
I am the one who spent
the last two years cleaning up
the mess he made of our lives.
- What did he do?
- What didn't he do?
Speed, cocaine.
He's an addict.
One of the producers
wants a rewrite.
And if I can get it to them
on time, then... I'm back.
And the money that will follow,
Jade, I can take care of you.
("L-O-V-E" by Michael Feinstein
playing)
♪ "L" is for the way you look ♪
♪ At me ♪
♪ "O" is for the only one ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ "V" is very, very ♪
♪ Extraordinary ♪
♪ "E" is even more ♪
♪ Than anyone
that you adore can ♪
♪ Love is all ♪
♪ That I can give to you ♪
♪ Love is more ♪
♪ Than just a game for two ♪
♪ Two in love can make it ♪
♪ Take my heart
and please don't break it ♪
♪ Love was made ♪
♪ For me and you... ♪
♪ The moon was all aglow ♪
♪ But heaven was in your eyes ♪
♪ The night that you told me ♪
♪ All those little white lies ♪
♪ The stars all seemed to know ♪
♪ You didn't mean
all those sighs ♪
♪ The day that you told me... ♪
That girl April
is on line one.
(sighs) Tell her
I'm in a meeting.
♪ All those little white lies ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Who wouldn't believe
those lips? ♪
those eyes? ♪
♪ The night that you told me ♪
(door opens)
You were out late last night.
Who were you with?
Just some of the guys
from the track team.
(door closes)
♪ All those little white lies ♪
♪ The devil was in your heart ♪
♪ But heaven was in your eyes ♪
♪ The time that you told me ♪
Eli, what are you doing out
so early?
Oh, just going for a jog.
♪ All those little white lies ♪
♪ All those ♪
♪ Little white ♪
♪ Lies... ♪
- You're it!
- No, you're it!
So, can you ring me up
for that, ma'am?
- Bethany.
- Oh.
Thank you
for meeting me.
Yeah. I was... I was
a little surprised
to get your text.
It's, um, it's
been a minute.
Yeah, yeah,
I'm sorry about that.
I know I kind of
disappeared there.
Yeah. Thought maybe you had,
uh, found someone else.
No, no, nothing like that.
I just, you know...
Took a different path
for a while.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah.
All right, Tanya,
listen to me.
You're gonna go play
with your friends while Mommy
talks to her friend, okay?
- Okay.
- Oh, big girl.
I see them on
the playground.
You better go.
(whispers):
Oh, my God.
She's so big.
- I know.
- In my head, I still think of her
- as a baby.
- Yeah, well,
24 months is like a
lifetime in kid-years.
- Yeah.
- (chuckles)
♪ ♪
Okay, so I got this
shit from Mexico.
It's stepped on a little
bit, but it's good.
Just, like,
15% baby laxatives.
It'll definitely
get you high.
But this shit
just fell off the back of a
fucking boat from Colombia.
Okay, all I did was
chop it up and bag it,
and I swear to God, Eli,
the second you open it,
your entire face goes numb.
Okay, how much?
Give you an eight
ball for 300?
Or I can do two for five.
That's the best
I can do, though.
I'm trying to save for
Tanya's college fund.
Well, you're a good mom.
Mm.
All right, I'll take two.
Okay.
Nice to have you back.
(door opens)
SIMONE:
Karl.
We need to talk.
Bloody hell,
it's 7:00 in the morning.
I was so angry
with you last night.
The way you spoke to me.
Look, Simone...
I was up all night
thinking to myself,
"I wish I'd never
married that man.
He's stolen the last
ten years of my life."
All right, I'm sorry.
Here, put that on.
Why?
Just do it.
All right.
Then I started thinking
about our time together.
You taught me how to ski...
...how to tango.
(chuckles)
Hmm. How to speak French.
Asking for more chardonnay
is not really speaking French.
(laughs)
Most importantly,
you taught me how
to laugh at myself.
The truth is, you haven't
stolen anything from me.
If anything,
you've given me more
than I deserved.
I'm sorry, the suspense is
slightly killing me now.
Where is this going?
Follow me.
Just to be clear, I still think
we should get a divorce.
Uh, yes, I assumed as much.
But just because I can't
have you as a husband
doesn't mean I can't
have you as a friend.
And I do like to
keep my friends happy.
Hector.
Hello, Karl.
I have never loved you more
than I do in this moment.
Please, Karl, not in front
of the boyfriend.
(Hector laughing)
Hello.
Sheila.
Your apartment manager told me
you were down here.
- I was hoping we could get lunch.
- Ugh.
Sorry, I just got
called into work.
Two waitresses are sick.
I have to clean my uniform
and get over to Glendale.
It's fine.
We can catch up another time.
Well, there's certainly
a lot to catch up on.
- Has something happened?
- (groans)
Mrs. Persky...
I need you to leave.
Why?
I need to talk
to my friend.
What about?
It's private.
So sex, huh?
Just go!
You seem irritable.
(quietly):
Rob dumped me.
He did?
Yeah, he sent roses
with a note
saying, "I can't keep seeing
you, please forgive me."
Oh, well, you knew
this day was coming.
Yeah. I just thought
he would be man enough
to tell me to my face.
You know, I phoned him at his
work yesterday ten times.
His secretary, Claire,
won't put me through.
Well, honey,
it is time to move on.
- You don't want to embarrass yourself.
- Well...
Yeah.
(sighs)
What are you doing back here?
I brought my husband.
I want him to see
how you talk to me.
I should go.
I'll call you later.
- Thanks.
- Sorry...
Aw, why the long face?
Did your fella dump you?
Your wife is a horrible person.
Do you know that?
Yeah, I'm aware.
I thought we were excited
about the offer.
(sniffs)
No, no.
Look, of-of course I trust you.
Yeah. I mean,
do your thing. Okay.
All right, bye.
(sniffs)
Oh, shit.
(sniffs, clears throat)
Is everything all right?
Hey. Uh, yes.
Yeah, there's-there's an offer
on the table for the script.
But Lamar wants to hold out
for more money,
which, you know,
makes me kind of nervous.
(sniffing)
What are you on right now?
What? Nothing.
Oh, yeah? Then
what's this, then?
(sniffing)
Hmm?
It-it...
it's a heavy pollen year.
Dude...
It's been on the news.
We are on the same team.
I cannot cover for you if you're
gonna be stupid about it.
All right, I'm sorry.
The addy wasn't cutting it
for me anymore,
so I just... I needed something
a little bit stronger.
Why? The script is done.
TAYLOR:
Guys?
(sniffs)
Yeah, we're in here.
(quietly): Get your hand
out of your face.
- All right.
- Sorry.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I need to talk to you both.
- Yeah, what's on your mind?
- Look,
I know I said I was okay with
what went on with you two,
but clearly, I wasn't.
I felt like I went away
for the night, and you two
had suddenly become
this little team without me.
And it's not fair
to blame you,
because I'm the reason
we're all together
in the first place.
I just feel like
I talked you into this
with absolutely no idea of
how we would make it work.
Well, that's okay.
- Yeah. I mean, we will figure it out.
- We will.
But we're gonna need some help,
and I think I found
just the place to start.
JADE: "Amour the Merrier
Events, Limited"?
ELI:
Events?
You want us to
go to an orgy?
Oh, it's not an orgy.
It's a polyamory retreat.
Isn't that just a fancy
way of saying "orgy"?
Stop saying orgy.
- All right.
- This is a three-day event
at a hotel in San Diego.
- (sniffs)
- They have workshops, lectures, all designed
to help people who are new
to the polyamorous lifestyle.
- (sniffs)
- The whole thing is designed
by experts who know how to
make a relationship
- like ours work.
- (sniffs)
Oh, look, so here's
one of the seminars.
"Negotiating Boundaries
and Polyamorous
Relationship Agreements."
- Doesn't that sound helpful?
- Yeah, it really does.
- Um, let me... let me see.
- See?
So, I'll go make
the reservations.
- We'll leave tomorrow.
- All right.
- Yeah, wonderful. - Yeah.
- Yep.
(sniffling)
You okay, babe?
Yeah, yeah, just,
you know, allergies. Oof.
It is a heavy pollen year.
It was on the news.
Huh.
- (yelps, laughs)
- (laughing)
Here comes the bubbly.
Pour like there's
no tomorrow.
You are getting
your husband back.
I'm so happy.
Of course,
I feel bad for April.
Why? She should've known
what was coming.
This is how the movie
always ends: the man
slinks back to his wife,
and the whore ends up drunk
and alone.
Actually,
now that I got four kids,
it doesn't sound so bad.
(chuckles softly)
I was thinking of taking April
to a restaurant next week.
You know, to cheer her up.
Beth Ann, the war is over.
You won. Let the enemy
limp away in defeat.
April and I grew very close
these last few weeks.
It's a true friendship.
She thinks your name is Sheila.
- I admit, it's a complicated...
- (car door closes)
Honey! What's wrong?
April is in my driveway.
(gasps)
Shit.
(quietly):
What is she doing here?
Why the fuck
should I know?
We can't open the door.
I think we're
gonna have to.
I think she saw me.
You have to be me.
Are you crazy?
Please. I'm begging.
- Fine.
- (exhales)
Christ on a cracker.
Don't swear.
And be nice.
(doorbell rings)
(neutral accent):
May I help you?
Are you Mrs. Robert Stanton?
Yes.
And who might you be,
pray tell?
I'm April.
I'm... a-a waitress at
Jansen's Diner in Glendale.
Your husband is one
of my regulars.
Is he?
Yes.
Um...
I don't mean to rush you, dear,
but I have curtains to hem
and croutons in the oven.
APRIL:
Yes, I just wanted
to come by to say that I think
your husband might have left
his coat at the diner.
Well, mercy me.
APRIL: (chuckles)
I-I'm not even sure
if it's his, but...
if you wouldn't mind just
telling him that I stopped by
and asking him to call me.
(Brooklyn accent):
He knows your number...
(neutral accent):
number?
At the diner.
He could just give me
a call at the diner.
I'll tell him.
- Bye now.
- Goodbye.
I have never said "mercy me."
But you do bake
your own croutons.
I can't believe April
actually came to the house.
Got to say,
I'm impressed.
That tramp, she ain't going down
without a fight.
Well, this tramp isn't either.
You know what I mean.
I have to leave in ten minutes,
and I have got
absolutely no idea
what to wear.
You're so cute,
all aflutter
over your dinner
with your new beau.
Is this pastel too gay?
Have you ever seen
a straight pastel?
(scoffs) Will you please put
the paper down and help me?
I'm trying to find a nice
place for you to live.
Oh, what about a condo
at Sanford Palms?
Sanford Palms?
That's only about five blocks
away from here.
Well, I still want us
to have our movie nights.
You wouldn't have to drive home
after cocktails.
Our friends are going
to despise us.
Why?
When people split up,
they prefer venom
and fireworks,
tears and accusations.
So childish
and petty.
- Besides, we did that last week.
- Right.
I've narrowed it down
to these two.
Which do you prefer?
The linen.
Are you sure?
Why do you care
which suit?
How long is it gonna be on,
really?
(Cockney accent):
Oi! I'm a good girl, I am.
I don't let
no gentleman touch me
what ain't
bought me lobster first.
- (doorbell rings)
- (laughs) Oh, that's Tommy.
Don't do Eliza for him.
He won't understand
the reference,
and he'll think
you're having a stroke.
Yes. Much humor is lost
on the younger generation.
Trousers!
Tommy. Come in.
Where's Mr. Grove?
He has a date
tonight.
With a guy?
Yes.
I've lost a husband, but
I've gained a gay sidekick.
I'm glad.
Because now...
we don't have to hide
when we do this.
Mmm.
(hisses) I'm feeling
something interesting.
Can you blame me?
Not down there... up here.
Oh! Is this for me?
I was saving that
for after dinner.
Do you think you can wait?
What a question.
Of course not.
(gasps)
It's stunning.
Your taste is improving.
Mm.
A woman like you
deserves the best.
And I-I want you to see
that I can give that to you.
KARL:
Tommy!
He hasn't left yet?
Thank God
I caught you.
I need fresh eyes
on an outfit.
Uh, Simone
prefers the linen,
but I think the navy's
more slimming.
Thoughts?
Y-You're not fat.
Yes. As a straight man,
I am boyishly slim.
However, as a homo, I could
afford to lose a few. So...
See what Tommy
gave me.
Ooh.
Hark at you.
Diamond Jim Brady Bunch.
Anyway,
which one?
Just pick one.
Navy.
Navy it is.
Thank you.
(exhales) I'm terribly sorry
to interrupt,
but, as you know,
it's very important
to get the costume right
when you're coming out.
We don't care if you come out,
just as long as you get out.
I can always take a subtle hint,
Simone.
Perhaps, one day,
you'll give me one.
Oh, tell Hector you
won't sleep with him
unless he does my hair
for the wedding!
You got it! Goodbye!
You have
a very interesting marriage.
Sheila.
Um, what are you doing here?
Our visit was cut short
yesterday, so I just...
Now's not really a good time;
I'm feeling under the weather.
Do you want me to run
to the drugstore for you?
Oh, no, no. I just...
need a couple of aspirin.
Sit. I'll get them for you.
Oh, you don't
have to do that.
It's no trouble.
Besides,
I have some good news.
Oh. That's nice.
I could use some.
I've found you a man.
His name's Eldon Ratzinger.
Eldon Ratzinger.
He's my butcher. Very nice.
On the short side,
but you wouldn't notice
if you're wearing flats.
Thanks, but...
I can't meet anyone for a while.
You won't forget about Rob
if you sit around pouting.
Trust me, I won't be forgetting
about Rob anytime soon.
- (water running)
- You've got to get over this obsession
- with another woman's husband.
- (water stops)
You're going to end up
angry and sad.
You are right
about that.
You know,
flowers aren't the only thing
that Rob left me with.
What are you
talking about?
I'm pregnant.
(gasping)
Sheila,
are you hurt?
Yes.
- Yes, I am.
- Let me get you a bandage.
♪ ♪
(door closes)
(chuckling)
- (sighs)
- Oh.
Let me get that for you,
my lady.
Oh.
And my other lady.
How chivalrous of you.
Thank you.
All right.
♪ ♪
(car door closes)
You want me
to drive for a bit?
Hmm?
Sorry.
(exhales)
I think I'm just nervous
about the script, you know?
Actually, do you guys mind if
we pull off so I can call Lamar?
Will that stop you
from playing the steering wheel
like a bongo drum?
Almost definitely.
Then by all means.
Okay, great.
Here we go.
♪ ♪
JADE:
Oh, great.
(grunting softly)
I wonder if they
have a bathroom.
Uh, we can ask
inside the mini-mart.
Do you want anything?
Uh, potato chips.
And chocolate milk.
And gummy worms,
if they have 'em.
What are you, 12?
- I know you are, but what am I?
- (gasps)
The polyamorists
will hear about this.
(chuckling)
♪ ♪
(sniffing)
(horn blaring)
Fuck!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit.
JADE:
Bad news, Eli!
They were out of worms.
No.
So I got you bears.
Oh.
Thank you.
What are you doing in the trunk?
Uh, looking for my baseball cap.
Ah. So, where is it?
Forgot to pack it.
Fuckin' Eli.
- (chuckles)
- All right.
Let's hit the road.
Darling, is there any chance
you can watch the gallery
for me this morning?
Where will you be?
Uh, I have an
appointment.
Oh.
And would this appointment
involve
your new boyfriend Hector?
He may tag along, yes.
(gasps)
Look at you, proud gay man.
You know I'd do anything
to support you.
Short of canceling
my training session at the gym.
Are you sure
you're not a gay man?
(gasps)
Naomi.
I thought we were meeting
at the club.
You never know
who's eavesdropping there.
And what I have to say
is for your ears only.
Mm. Hello, Naomi.
My ears and I
were just leaving.
Thank you.
You seem upset.
Remember when I told you
that Tommy was hiding something?
I know his secret.
You do?
He's on drugs.
Oh, thank God.
That you finally figured it out.
It's the only thing that
makes sense... the secrecy,
the long hours, the lock
on his bedroom door.
Not to mention
the missing money.
What money?
He cashed in
his savings bond.
They became his
when he turned 18.
And I'm not supposed
to know,
but my friend
at the bank tipped me off.
I ask you, Simone,
what else could he have bought
that cost $10,000?
He spent $10,000?
(gasps)
I knew you'd understand.
Oh.
You're such a good friend.
I know we've had
our squabbles.
But in a crisis like this,
there is no one else
I can turn to.
No one?
What do you think
he's doing?
- Heroin?
- (scoffs)
This is Tommy
we're talking about.
I seriously doubt
he's on heroin.
What? That's a beautiful brooch.
Is it new?
Then again, it could be heroin.
All right.
- Oh, look at this place. It's cute.
- Yeah.
Here we go, come on.
- TAYLOR: Oh...
- ELI: Oh, man.
JADE: Why are they
stopping everyone?
Who knows?
(laughs softly)
Look at all these cars.
Who knew polyamory
was so popular?
(both laugh)
Oh, my God.
Vice President Pence
is speaking here tonight.
- At a polyamory seminar?
- (laughs)
- That's surprising.
- Odd choice.
No.
(chuckles)
He's in a different ballroom.
He's talking
to "local Republicans."
- Oh...
- Ugh. Well, that's the reason for the holdup.
It's extra security.
Oh, security...
(exhales)
They're opening
people's trunks.
That's gonna take forever.
(indistinct chatter)
Um...
- (Taylor sighs)
- You know what, guys?
- Uh, we-we, we need to turn around. Yeah.
- What?
- Why?
- Uh... I-I got to, I got to pee, guys. I'm so sorry.
- I just...
- No, honey, I was kidding.
The hotel is just
up the street.
- We'll be there in, like...
- Nope.
(straining): Can't do it. Dam's
gonna burst. Here-here we go...
TAYLOR: No, honey, wait,
what are you doing? What are you doing?
- Oh!
- I'm flipping a bitch.
TAYLOR:
Wait... Eli, what...
You can't make a U-turn here.
Yeah, well, now it's turning
into a bit more
of a three-point thing.
- TAYLOR: Eli...
- JADE: Eli, no!
- Or four.
- Oh, my God!
JADE:
Eli! Stop!
Oh, my God.
JADE:
Eli, what are you doing?
They're gonna think that
we're terrorists or something.
- (thumping)
- Five.
See that? Smooth sailing.
- Have you lost your fucking mind? Jesus...
- Smooth sailing.
(horn honking)
Eli, slow down!
You're gonna get us all killed.
ELI: Oh, wha... everyone,
just calm down, okay?
There's a Taco Bell
a couple miles down the road.
Right? We'll stop there,
it's gonna be fine.
All right?
Everything is gonna be fine.
(sniffles)
What?
Stop the car. Now.
(groans softly)
All right.
(beeps)
What... Why are you
opening the trunk?
Because I want to know
what's in there.
- Taylor!
- (door closes)
Shit.
Eli, your nose.
Oh...
Fuck.
Wait.
(chuckles softly)
Oh, my God. Eli.
I-I know that it looks bad.
Get in the car.
We're going home.
W-What about the retreat?
Oh, fuck the retreat.
(sighs, mutters)
(door closes)
SHEILA:
Pregnant? Jesus.
She's not only a tramp,
she's a stupid tramp.
- I don't want to drink right now.
- Oh, honey.
This is all for me.
I find your life very stressful.
At least we know why April was
so desperate to speak to Rob.
How do you think he'll react?
I think he will be thrilled.
Really?
Rob loved being a father.
When we lost Emily...
that was our daughter's name...
That's a beautiful name.
When we lost Emily,
he couldn't accept it.
Rob begged me
to have another child.
Why didn't you?
We tried and tried, but...
Did you ever think
about adoption?
Rob said he didn't want
to raise another man's baby.
He wanted a child
of his own.
(inhales)
And now he's going to get one.
God, I hate this guy.
Ugh, please,
he's still my husband.
What do I do now?
Come clean.
Tell him you know about
the affair, and the baby.
- No.
- It's time to put it all on the table.
But how will that help?
It will force him
to make a choice.
You or her.
What if... he doesn't choose me?
Well, then you'll finally hate
the fucking bastard
just as much as I do.
No, I won't. That's the problem.
Look, I don't know
what he's gonna do.
Maybe he'll choose you.
But whatever happens,
aren't you done
with all the lies?
Oh...
COACH:
Okay, team, let's go. Heads up!
Defense, north side
of the field.
Offense, south side.
Let's go...
Hey. What are you doing here?
Why didn't you tell me
these diamonds were real?
Yea... of course they're real.
I thought you knew that.
Well, I didn't. Take this back.
No. Why would I do that?
The bank told your mother
you sold a bond.
She now thinks you're on drugs,
and knowing
what you spent on this,
I'm wondering if she's right.
- I'm not taking it back.
- Tommy.
I should be able to buy diamonds
for the woman I love.
Relax. I don't expect you
to say it back.
I gave you that so you'd see
that I'm not just some kid
who can't play in your league.
The diamonds are real
because my feelings are.
You know I adore you,
but I just don't see how we can
have that kind of relationship.
Because of what people
would say?
- They'd be brutal.
- So, you're not embarrassed
that Karl dates men,
but you are embarrassed by me?
I am not embarrassed at all.
- (footsteps approaching)
- (gasps) Oh, dear God.
Hey, Tommy!
Who's your girlfriend?
I-I can't stay here.
- Here, take this, please.
- TOMMY: No.
It's yours.
I'm not ashamed to love you.
- Taylor...
- Don't.
I need for no one
to speak right now.
How long?
Sorry?
How long have you
been using again?
Not that long.
- I mean, it started...
- Don't tell me.
I don't want to know how long
I missed the signs.
How long this has been happening
right in front
of my own stupid face.
Babe, please, you...
You... shut up.
I was distracted before.
You'd better believe my eyes
are wide fucking open now.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Tommy's dealing drugs.
What?
Kay Randall's son Bradley
saw him today with a customer.
A customer?
He saw him making a deal
in the middle of P.E.
with some seedy,
middle-aged woman
- in dark glasses.
- Middle-aged?
Anyway,
do you have a screwdriver?
I want to break
into Tommy's room.
Why? I'm sure he doesn't keep
drugs in there.
Maybe not, but at least
I could read his journal.
His journal?
I think I found one.
W-Well, what do you mean,
he keeps a journal?
I-I have to go.
- Naomi. Uh...
- (dial tone)
(tires screeching)
- Naomi?
- NAOMI: Up here!
(grunts)
Naomi.
I'm so glad you're here.
You can help me look.
I am only here to stop you
from making an awful mistake.
If Tommy finds out
you read his journal,
you could lose him forever.
He won't find out.
He's at track until 6:00.
You trashed his room. You won't
have time to clean it up.
And the journal
may not even be here.
- Found it.
- (gasps)
Simone.
When Amy was ten,
I read her diary.
She didn't speak to me
for a year.
- Hand it over.
- If she had been Tommy's age,
she'd have moved out.
Do you really want to risk that,
just to get an intrusive look
at Tommy's most
private thoughts and...
- Jesus Christ. Nothing!
- What?
- Give me that.
- (gasps)
As your friend, I am
begging you, don't read that.
Why are you so emotional?
Karl is gay.
- What?
- He sleeps with men.
Uh... can we just focus
on my problems for a moment?
No wonder you're so distraught.
I mean,
I wanted to tell you,
but then I thought,
"No, Naomi has her own problems.
She doesn't want to hear
my tawdry tale."
Oh, but I do.
NAOMI:
You mean to tell me
that when I saw Karl's
car at the motel,
he was there with a man?
I can't talk about this
without a drink.
Maybe we could
go downstairs and,
you know,
open up a bottle?
Of course.
But how did you find out?
Did you catch him with
one of his lovers?
SIMONE: No, it was Wanda.
You were right.
She despises me.
- She found out...
- What are you doing in my room?
Is that my journal?
Uh, she just found it,
but she hasn't read it yet.
I'm so sorry, Tommy.
I just wanted to make sure
that you weren't doing drugs.
So you broke into my room?
Well, you've been
so distant lately.
Mrs. Grove,
if you wouldn't mind...
Yes, I should go, as this
doesn't involve me at all.
Jesus. Mom...
(scoffs)
You looking for these?
Oh, good, you found them.
Thank you.
How'd it go in there?
Eh, just told Mom
that I'm gonna
cash in another bond so I can
hike through Europe this summer.
She felt so guilty
about breaking
into my room that she agreed.
You turned the situation
to your advantage.
Good for you.
I, uh, leave for Paris
two days after graduation.
Care to join me?
Are you crazy?
We don't have to leave
at the same time.
I'll go first,
then you take a vacation
and meet me there.
No one's gonna know
that we're together.
Your mother's watching.
That is why we
need to do this.
Someone is always
watching us here.
We will never know who we can be
as a couple until we get away
from my mom, your friends,
and everyone else whose
opinions you're scared of.
Can I think about it?
Sure.
(exhales)
Wow.
Look at this.
Someone went to
a lot of trouble.
Oh, not so much.
I just put out a few flowers,
and the good silver,
and the candlesticks
your mother bought us.
Would you like a mai tai
before dinner?
You made mai tais?
(chuckles)
Hold it.
Did you wreck the car?
Why would you think that?
You only make mai tais
before giving me bad news.
- That's silly.
- Huh.
Now drink your mai tai.
(exhales)
♪ ♪
Where do you think you're going?
Upstairs.
Not alone, you're not.
In fact, this is what's
gonna happen right now.
You and I are gonna
take a tour of this house,
and you're gonna show me where
you've been hiding your stash.
- There's no stash. I just...
- And you know what, Eli,
put all that shit down,
because you have absolutely
no reason to unpack.
You're going to rehab
first thing in the morning.
Are you kidding? Rehab?
Come on.
I want your wallet.
And your phone.
You are cut off.
No cash, no cards,
no PayPal, no Venmo.
Do you understand?
You know, I understand
why you're upset,
but you don't have to
humiliate me
- in front of Jade, too.
- Wrong.
You should be humiliated.
After what we went through
last time,
the idea that you would even
put us through this again...
(phone ringing)
- Eli, give it to me.
- It's Lamar.
- He'll leave a message.
- Just... It could be
about the script.
Just...
please let me
take the call.
- (ringing continues)
- Fine.
Stay where I can see you.
Hey.
- Yeah...
- Tay...
I want to help.
Just tell me what I can do.
ELI:
How much?
- Just... be with me.
- ELI: Yeah.
Back me up. This is
gonna be really hard.
But it's the only way.
Hey, you got it. Of course.
ELI:
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
(phone beeps)
What did Lamar say?
He-he was able to start
a bidding war...
...and he sold it for a lot more
than we expected.
How much more?
One-point-two.
- One-point-two?
- Million.
(chuckling):
1.2 million.
- Holy shit.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
JADE:
Oh, my God!
- (chuckling)
- Are you serious? Oh, my God.
- Eli, congratulations.
- Oh, my God, thank you. Thank you.
- Oh, my God.
- Yes!
Honey, this is
such great news, okay?
Your career
is back again.
This is all the more reason
to get you to rehab.
(chuckling):
You-you know what?
I-I don't, I don't think
it's the best time for me,
right now.
Buddy... you don't really
have a choice here.
I just sold a script
for $1.2 million.
You know? I think
I got a lot of fucking choices.
Eli... I am not gonna stand by
and watch you kill yourself.
Oh, God.
Come on.
This is not like
last time, all right?
- I'm in a completely better place now.
- Eli!
This is nonnegotiable.
- Taylor...
- Do you know what...?
You're so fucking desperate
to control me, aren't you?
- I mean, it's fucking pathetic!
- Okay. No, Eli,
- this is the drugs talking. You know that, right?
- No. No. No, it's not.
This is me, okay? I am clear
as a fucking bell right now.
And from now on...
I make my own decisions.
Okay, Eli.
Well, here's one for you:
either you go to rehab,
or I walk out that fucking door!
- Whoa. Hold on. Hold on.
- Really?
- Yeah. Oh, yeah.
- Really? You just walk on out?
- If you push me, yeah.
- Okay. Well, Taylor,
you know, I really
wish you wouldn't go.
But if you want to,
that's your choice.
See? I would never force
you to do anything.
Come on, Jade.
Jade...
I... I think maybe
we shouldn't go.
- You what?
- Eli needs help.
I think maybe the best way
to help him is to
stay here and-and,
you know,
just keep
an eye on him.
You're choosing him.
I'm choosing us.
I'm choosing all of us.
Fuck you.
Fuck you both.
ROB:
Mmm.
(chuckles)
I can't believe
you made peach cobbler.
- I know it's your favorite.
- Mmm.
You must've been
cooking since noon.
I didn't start
all that early.
Well, thanks for this.
It was a beautiful night.
You're welcome.
Aw, geez.
I knew it.
Something's going on.
(exhales)
Robert?
And you're calling me Robert?
Ah, this is gonna be bad, huh?
We definitely need
to have a talk.
Ah, boy.
First...
I just want to say...
...I love you so much.
- Mm.
- And more importantly,
I love us.
And the life we've had.
You're starting to scare me.
I'm scared, too.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Just tell me.
Once I tell you...
...everything is going
to be different.
Oh, my God.
Are you sick?
Yes.
I'm sick.
Baby, what's wrong?
I have cancer.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
Oh... oh, my God.
(sobbing)
♪ ♪
(sets glass down)
Oh, nice flowers.
Are they from Hector?
How many men
do you think I'm juggling?
Oh, glad one of us
is having a good day.
(sighs) Oh, God,
I look like a raccoon.
I cannot tell you what
I've been through today.
I'm guessing you'll try.
You know the pin
Tommy gave me?
Well, it turns out
the diamonds were real.
Naomi was
furious, because
he cashed in one of his
savings bonds to buy it.
Anyway, she decided
he was on drugs.
(fading): And that she had
to read his journal...
DOCTOR:
Mr. Grove. How can I help you?
KARL:
Well, I was with my friend,
and he-he spotted
this thing on my back.
I mean, it's probably nothing,
but he-he suggested
I see a doctor.
DOCTOR:
You were right to come see me.
I am just relieved that
Naomi didn't find out.
Anyway...
(sighs)
before I left, Tommy ran out,
and said something
that I definitely need
to talk to you about.
Oh, dear.
Am I going to need
more wine... Oh!
Damn it!
(gasps)
- Oh, is it bad? Let me see...
- No!
No, no. No, no, sorry.
Um, uh, it-it's not deep.
Um... Can you just
get me a Band-Aid?
Of course.
Uh, uh, so, uh,
what did Tommy say?
Well, he's going to
Europe for the summer,
and he wants me
to join him.
Oh.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I thought it might be nice
to spend time with him...
and not have to sneak around.
What do you think?
You should go.
Really? I mean, it's a hectic
time, with Amy's wedding,
- and the gallery...
- Listen,
listen.
I have spent my entire life
putting off things
that I thought there'd be
time for later.
Open doors
don't stay open forever.
So please... go.
You'll be okay?
I'll be delightful.
(chuckles)
I'll bet.
Judging from those flowers,
Hector must be smitten.
- Yes.
- (chuckles)
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ I try ♪
♪ But there's no forgetting ♪
♪ When evening appears ♪
♪ I sigh ♪
♪ But there's no regretting ♪
♪ In spite of my tears ♪
- ♪ The devil was in your heart ♪
- (sniffing)
♪ But heaven was in your eyes ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ The night that you told me ♪
♪ All those little white lies ♪
♪ All those little white ♪
♪ Lies. ♪