Previously
on "The Originals"...
This town was my home once.
I want it back.
Our community
is under attack.
Resurrected witches
with vast power?
It's the harvest.
Four girls were
meant to die
and be reborn.
Someone jacked
that power.
I believe that when
you love someone
and that person
loves you in return,
you're uniquely
vulnerable.
Celeste, she died
because of me.
I'd appreciate it if you'd
call me by my real name...
Celeste.
What about Hayley?
None of my treachery
will harm this family
as much as your
feelings for her.
This blade contains
all the power I harvested
from the vampires.
It will do
things worse than death.
And are you ready
for the final offering?
Someone help me.
Thank you all for coming.
It means more
than I can tell you.
We gather today
for the first public service
of our newly reopened
church.
St. Anne's can finally
once again be the heart
of our community,
where we can congregate
as a people united.
Here, this hour, we come
together to praise God
and give thanks.
The events that took place
at our church were tragic.
Problem?
No.
Then pay attention.
We're meant to seem
like devoted parishioners.
...And it is
that hope in our hearts
and with the help of many
benefactors that allows us
to be here today.
So we gather
with renewed spirit
made stronger, committed
to the ideals of peace
and love. Amen.
Amen.
Each tomb
is well cared for.
Families honor their dead
with displays of affection
and respect...
Is someone there?
This tomb belongs to
the Deveraux family,
known throughout the quarter
for their strong connection
to witchcraft.
Please help me!
And if you look close,
these fresh bricks
tell us someone
in the family
has recently fallen.
Let me out!
Hello, Monique.
Welcome back to
the land of the living.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/
What is it?
What's going on?
It's a miracle.
Monique?
Ohh!
Lovely sermon
this morning, father.
Quite inspirational.
I wasn't
expecting you to join us.
Oh, we were hoping for some
word from your human sources
on the recent Haitian
invasion.
My guys have their
ears to the ground.
And no one has seen
or heard any sign
of whatever
his name is.
He's called Papa Tunde.
And right now, he's
wandering the corridor
with the power
he absorbed
from every soul I had
buried in the garden.
So you might want
to put your ear
a little closer
to the ground.
Or I could
steer clear
of whatever war
is brewing
between your kind
and his
before I
find myself in...
I wanted to congratulate you
on getting the church
up and running.
I can see this is
a bad time.
Nice to see you, Marcel.
Cami.
Well, don't look at me.
I tried to send her away.
Yes, Diego, what
do you have for me?
Uh, we got
a special delivery.
Would you
care to elaborate?
Either our witch
problems are over
or they're just
getting started.
Marcel.
Father.
God be with you.
Thank you.
God be with y...
Oh, I doubt that, but I
do appreciate the thought.
Bastiana.
Toursion fou,
mort de l'espirit.
Give your nephew Sean
my regards
when you see him in hell.
Can I get you
anything, brother?
A magnifying glass,
a pipe perhaps?
You have a theory
that you'd like
to share with us,
Niklaus?
Back in the day,
the witches wanted
to send a threat, they'd
just kill a chicken
and leave it
on your doorstep.
It's rather a large
and ominous chicken,
wouldn't you say?
Papa Tunde defeated
Rebekah with ease,
almost got the two of us
as well.
If he was supposed to be
their prize fighter,
why leave him for dead
in our front yard?
Well, don't you all
look cheery.
Listen to this...
A girl
literally exploded
from a grave today
as Sabine was giving
her tour of the city
of the dead.
It was Monique Deveraux.
What?
The tourists thought it
was part of the show,
but the witches are
celebrating
like it's some kind of
bloody miracle.
Maybe it is. They
think that all hope is lost,
but now suddenly a harvest
girl is resurrected.
This is how we're gonna
get Davina back...
Kill the witch who took
her place.
I have a theory about
who one of them could be...
Celeste. I mean,
it's got to be.
Davina was trying to tell us.
She was drawing
pictures of Celeste.
She was warning us that
a great evil was coming.
First Papa Tunde
returns to settle old scores.
Now your murdered
lover is back.
This isn't witches
attacking vampires.
They're declaring
war on us.
It's not too early
for scotch, is it,
with all the witches'
shenanigans
and subterfuge afoot.
It is entirely too
early if one intends
to drive, yes.
Funny. I don't have
any plans to go anywhere.
She's not safe here.
You have to take Hayley
to the plantation house
until this is over.
Are you worried about Hayley
or whether or not
you can trust me?
It's precisely
because I trust you
that I'm asking you
to do this.
Here's a novel idea...
Why don't you let Hayley
decide for herself?
Why are you
dictating her fate?
You know why.
Then perhaps you should
take her yourself.
Well, then that would
make me the very
hypocrite that you've
accused me of being.
Rebekah, I cannot
legislate my feelings.
My actions, however...
So would you kindly
do this for me?
You know the mama wolf
loves to be told
what to do.
She's not gonna like it,
but I will do it for you...
If only to end
this silly quarrel
between the two of us.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
Listen, everybody's
running off, looking
for resurrected witches.
Meanwhile, I think I saw
one at the church...
Genevieve.
What?
I can't be sure.
I only caught her out of
the corner of my eye.
Been with Klaus since.
But it looked like her.
And you and I both know
she would have a reason
to want to be back.
A lot of unfinished
business,
a lot of secrets that you
and I don't want getting out.
I have to take Hayley
to the plantation.
You need to find
Genevieve and end this.
End it like we did
the last time.
Tea, please.
I'm busy.
Cami, just hear me out.
You know, I came to your
reopening because I
wanted to try
and make amends.
And then I see you
talking with Klaus
out in the open, like
it's business as usual
in the quarter.
It is business as usual.
For the past 3 centuries,
the O'Connells have always
tried to keep the peace.
Save me
the family history.
It's all lies
on top of lies.
Cami, p... pour me a drink.
I have to tell you
something.
Uncle Kieran,
what's wrong?
I'm in trouble.
What happened to your
brother Sean is
about to start
happening to me.
What?
Look, uh...
Look, uh,
I've been hexed.
And I don't know
how long I have.
Wait.
I know some people.
There has to be some
sort of... I don't know...
Antidote or...
Cami, I need you
to promise me one thing,
that when it gets bad,
I need you to be as far
away from me as possible.
No. No.
There has to be
some sort of way.
Of course there is.
If you want to save
your Uncle's life,
all you have to do
is take this...
And make sure it ends up
in Klaus Mikaelson's heart.
I thought I was
gonna have to drag you
to the plantation
kicking and screaming.
Yeah. Well, we all just want
to protect me and the baby,
right?
Hey. I'm on your side,
remember?
So what gives?
Tonight's a full moon,
Rebekah.
So what? You're preggers.
You can't turn.
Yes. But I wanted
to invite
a few people over.
Of course.
Every red-blooded
American werewolf
will be a bundle of fur
and sharp teeth tonight
whilst your cursed
crescent clan will be...
Human but only for
a few hours
and won't be again until
the next full moon.
So I asked Josh to get
a message out to Eve
in the bayou.
Josh isn't dead yet?
Well, good on him.
I love a nice
survival story.
Who the bloody hell is that?
Kegs out back,
right? Ahem.
Right.
It appears you weren't
going to wait for me
to grant you permission
to throw a kegger.
Listen, you all want me
safe, fine.
I'll do as I'm told.
I'll play damsel
in the glass tower.
But tonight's
the one night a month
that I can meet
my family.
Now, you could rat me
out, send me to my room,
or you
could help me throw
one hell of a party.
Elijah.
To what do I owe
the pleasure?
My family needs
an ally
among the witches,
and you've helped us
in the past.
Perhaps together we
can avoid
an unnecessary
conflict.
They may be willing
to make a deal
if it were with
the noble Elijah.
But there will never be
any peace as long as it
involves Klaus.
Is that what all this
is about?
You want my brother
out of town?
I'm just telling you
how they feel.
My people are scared.
They're desperate,
but they're not dumb.
You have a niece
on the way.
It stands to reason you'd
be willing to discuss
how to run him out
of the city.
Let's walk together.
You can take me
on one of your famous tours.
You should eat
after everything you've
been through.
I was dead.
But you're here now.
Aunt Sophie, what
happened to mom?
Your mother loved you
so much.
She had faith that she
could use magic
to complete the harvest
and get you back.
In the end, she sacrificed
herself for the cause,
for the witches, for you.
And do you have
her faith?
I lost my faith.
Then I realized
that if I didn't believe,
I would be letting
you down.
I tried to get it back.
I tried.
Monique Deveraux.
Everyone in the
quarter's been talking
about you.
Classy.
You kill her mother
and now you've come
to threaten her?
I'm not here
to threaten anyone.
What do you want, Marcel?
There were 3 more
girls sacrificed
during the harvest.
I want to bring
them back.
Who are you kidding?
You don't care
about those girls.
You just want Davina back so
you can use her power again.
I just
want her alive.
He's telling the truth.
How do you know that?
I can feel it.
He's loyal to her.
He's here to help.
I got your message.
Where's Kieran now?
In the attic resting,
praying.
He's gonna go crazy
and die, isn't he...
Just like Sean.
And we'll still be
in this stupid fight
because he lied to
me about the witches
and vampires...
And you.
Camille...
I can see why you hate me.
Truth be told, I have done
some dreadful things.
But the lies your Uncle
told were meant
to protect you.
He is a good man...
With a loyal heart.
And he is your family.
As for these witches,
their attack on Kieran
should be proof enough
they're the enemy.
In that we are united.
Klaus...
This is
Papa Tunde's blade.
A witch gave it
to me.
Said it would
cause untold pain
and torment,
even to an original.
She said if I stuck
it in your heart,
she would heal
Kieran.
And yet you chose
to reject their offer.
Maybe if I were more
like you, I could do it.
But I'm not...
A monster.
I'm not stupid.
If there's a war
going on,
I want to be on
the winning side.
Let's see what we can do
about saving your Uncle,
shall we?
Hello again.
I'm looking forward
to meeting you soon.
You've got to be
kidding me.
A vampire is
trying to reverse
a witch's hex
placed on you,
and it's the cup you
find sacrilegious.
Are you sure this is
going to work?
Not remotely.
But I can't attempt
to use my compulsion
to counter Bastiana's
curse if the good father
has vervain in his
system. Thus...
We bleed him out.
I never said this
would be pleasant.
Just do what you have to do.
So help me God, Marcel,
if you don't call me
back with an update,
I will kill you myself.
Oh.
I beg...
Your pardon.
I was expecting
someone furrier.
You're one of them,
aren't you?
An original.
Yes. You might want to say
that with some more respect.
I suppose you'll be
wanting Hayley.
Or I could just
talk to you.
I'm Oliver.
I didn't catch
your name.
I'm Rebekah.
Hayley, the party's here!
You got enough power left
to find these witches?
I know the harvest
was an epic fail,
but I can still do
a locator spell.
Before I do that,
we need to make
a deal.
What deal?
If I betray these
witches, they're
gonna come looking
for me.
And if I'm caught,
I'm dead.
I said I'd protect you.
If you
could do that,
you wouldn't need my
help in the first place.
The quarter isn't safe.
Vampires on one side,
witches on the other.
No way am I
letting Monique get
in the middle of that.
In order to get her out,
I'm gonna need money.
Do we have a deal?
Find the witches,
I'll give you anything
you could ever need.
Well, come on! You can
do better than that.
Sorry. I've got
a burdened brain tonight.
No, no, no, no.
Tonight is not
a night for burdens.
It's to celebrate.
It's to enjoy life for
the few hours that we get
to live it.
It's to hug our friends,
our family,
and to dance our asses off.
I seriously doubt
you invited us here
to wait on us.
You're Hayley.
I'm Jackson.
It's nice to see
you again.
You're the wolf who's
been watching me.
I got to keep
my eye on you,
precious cargo
and all.
Right.
Got to protect
the miracle baby.
No. That's not
what I meant.
I don't care
about the baby.
Sorry.
That came out wrong.
I mean, of course
I care.
You're a labonair.
A baby,
it's a big deal.
But personally, my
interest is in you.
You don't even know me.
Our parents knew
each other.
They were of
the same people
but not the same
bloodline.
Now, you know how pack
hierarchy works, right?
Everybody has their
part to play,
and we had
our part, too.
What part was that?
You were supposed to
be my wife.
So this next
part of town is
one of the few areas
where any of
the original French
architecture remains.
Most of the buildings
were destroyed
in the 1700s,
when the city burned
for the first time.
Am I putting you
to sleep?
As surprising
as you might find this,
it's not every day
that someone asks you
to betray your own brother...
Celeste.
How did you know?
As Davina was drawing
your likeness...
I dared to imagine
that your presence
was near.
And when Sophie
discovered
that there was no magic
in your remains,
I wondered...
Could you have possibly
cheated death by using
your power to place
your essence
into the body
of another?
And if so, then who?
And then I recalled
the lovely Sabine.
Are you gonna continue
following me, Elijah?
Or do you want to talk?
You know who I am.
Original vampire,
always wears a suit?
Your visions of my
brother's child
precipitated the death
of the last elder
within your coven...
Tell them what you saw.
Ensuring that
the harvest ritual
could not
be completed...
Unless you
were to control it.
You're playing a very
long game indeed...
To what end?
Oh, Elijah...
My lost love...
After
all this time...
Don't you understand?
I died because of Klaus.
And even after all his
vindictive lies
about witches led to my
death, you stood by him
all because of your vow,
"always and forever."
What have you done to me?
It's a simple
enchantment.
You needn't worry.
I'm not here
to kill you, Elijah.
I'm here
to teach you
the error of your
ways.
"Always and forever" was
the greatest mistake
of your life.
Drink up.
It will heal your wound.
I think you've
suffered enough.
You will overcome
what the witches
did to you.
You will resist the dark
urges of their hex.
Did it work?
Ohh. How do I know
if it worked?
All I know is
that the vervain is out
and I'm at the mercy of
this murderous bastard.
I bet you find that
really funny, don't you,
Cami, you little...
I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't know
why I said that.
Well, I guess
that's our answer.
Wait. Klaus,
where are you going?
What are we going
to do?
I'm going to find
the witch who did this.
And then I'm going to
do what I do best.
I'm weaker than
I thought.
You want the deal, Soph,
you got to hold up your end.
I'm on a clock.
Ok.
It's working.
That's one. I need all 3.
I'm giving you
whatever I can pick up.
Keep trying.
Or don't.
Who needs a locator spell
when I have all the leverage
I need right here?
No! Monique!
You've poisoned me
with a kiss.
Uh! At least you haven't
lost your sense of irony.
We may have time
for more.
But first, I'm going
to cure you
of your greatest flaw...
This absurd devotion
to your lunatic family.
Celeste, your anger
is with me.
Now, if you have come
here seeking revenge...
Oh, I'll have
my revenge,
starting with Klaus.
He is gonna know
pain and torment
like he's never
felt before...
Unless you choose
to save him,
of course.
But then that leaves
Rebekah,
your tragic sister.
She's about to find
herself
in quite
the predicament.
You could save her.
But then that leaves
Hayley in jeopardy.
No. No, no...
Ah, this poor girl.
She has no idea
how dangerous it is
to be loved by you.
Oh, well.
With your body weakened
by my spell,
you won't be
able to save them all.
You'll recover
with just enough time
to choose one.
Who will it be?
I can't wait
to find out.
Witches of
the French quarter,
I have with me
Monique Deveraux.
What a shame it would be
were I forced to send her
back to the death
she's just escaped.
Should you wish
to prevent this...
Bring me
the witch Bastiana.
What the hell do
you think you're doing?
I'm opening negotiations.
You know my rules.
We do not hurt kids.
Spare me the hypocrisy
of your moral code.
It didn't stop you from
killing Monique's mother.
Bastiana!
I know you're close.
The stench of witches
hangs in the air.
Mark my words.
I will end this girl
with the very blade
you meant for me.
I'm not saying it
again.
We do not kill kids.
I decide who lives
and dies here, Marcellus.
Aah!
I'll take it from here.
I know it's a lot
to take in.
You think?
I just wanted
to meet my family.
I never imagined
I'd meet my husband
from some weird-ass
arranged marriage.
I guess you don't know
about any of this
because there was never
anyone around to teach you.
The crescents aren't just
any pack of wolves.
Ok? The bloodline goes
back to the very beginning...
two families...
Yours and mine.
I guess that makes us
kind of like royalty.
This is a joke,
right? I mean,
if you're royalty,
where's the throne?
New Orleans used
to be our town.
And we lost it all because
of some infighting.
The vampires came after us.
And if our
families were united,
we could have taken them.
So our parents
decided to bring
the two lines back together.
And you and I
were betrothed.
I'm sorry.
This is ridiculous.
Look, obviously things
didn't work out
the way anyone thought
they would.
Our pack made a huge
misstep with the vampires
when we refused
to back down.
And Marcel had us cursed
by a witch.
You are the last one of
your bloodline, Andrea.
Or, Hayley, whatever
you call yourself.
These people
will follow you.
You can help them... you
and what you represent.
And what is that
exactly?
A time when
things were different,
when our people fought back.
And after everything you
went through to find us...
You're the one who's
gonna break our curse.
What are you talking
about?
Your witch friend.
She told Eve she was
coming here tonight
to set us free.
Wait. What witch friend?
I'm sorry.
I really do like you, but
this is the deal we made.
What deal?
With whom?
Hayley.
Elijah, something's going
on with the witches.
Listen to me. You were right.
Celeste is back.
Niklaus, Rebekah.
You're all in danger.
What's going on?
It's a trap. I didn't
make a deal with any witch.
What?
Hayley, you
have to find Rebekah.
And you stay with her
until I get there.
Elijah, it's a spell.
They're trapping us inside.
You know what to do.
We have to get
out of here.
Here. Breathe
through this.
Where's Rebekah?
I don't know.
She went off
with one of them.
Elijah, my friend is
still in there.
On your feet.
Help me.
It's been such a long
time, Rebekah.
I'm going to enjoy this.
Missing something?
You won't hurt me.
I'm the only one alive
who can break
the curse on Hayley's
family.
And Genevieve knows
where your sister is.
Bastiana has Klaus
tucked away
someplace safe.
He's suffering horribly,
I might add,
and all because you
chose to save
the little wolf instead
of your own blood.
What a horrific
ending...
To your pathetic,
diseased family.
I guess "always" isn't
forever after all.
I have to go. The moon.
Listen, Jackson,
I want to thank you
for protecting me,
not just tonight.
I've been dreaming to thank you
about meeting you,
since I was a kid.
I never thought
it would go like this.
Hey...
I won't stop
until I find a way
to break this curse.
I promise.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Klaus, where are you?
Mr. Mikaelson
is currently indisposed.
What happened?
What did you do?
I did nothing.
Someone completed
your task for you.
If you got what you
wanted, then my Uncle...
Will die soon
and in great anguish.
You see, dear, you failed
to hold up your end
of our bargain.
You chose instead to side
with evil as your Uncle
has done many times
before you.
But take heart.
His punishment will atone
for his attempts
to prevent the harvest.
His suffering
will purify him.
You'd do well to heed
his lesson, girl.
To oppose us is to oppose
the natural order.
By choice or by force,
the witches
of the French quarter
will rise again.
We looked everywhere
for him.
Tore apart the cauldron,
the city of the dead.
Wherever they got him,
he ain't in the quarter.
Marcel!
Where is my brother?
I got guys out
looking for him right now.
Elijah!
Klaus threw one of his
classic temper tantrums,
snapped my neck,
tried to take on a coven
of witches by himself.
He got dropped.
I don't know where he is
or how to find him.
They also have Rebekah.
Every one of you
will help me
to find them.
I'm going to kill
them all.
Come on. We have to go.
I don't want to go.
Monique, this isn't
a debate.
I just stabbed
an original.
He's gonna kill me
as soon as he's
recovered.
Look...
I'm sorry
for everything.
I should have
come and got you
before that stupid
harvest.
But you can still
have a normal life,
one without all this
crazy witch nonsense.
But I am a witch.
And I don't want to go.
Monique?
The ancestors said you
didn't have enough faith.
I was
hoping they were wrong.
I should
have known better.
Monique...
You tried to stop
the harvest.
Please don't do this.
Now you want to run
when we need to stay
and fight.
Please. I'm begging
you, don't... don't...
The four of us,
when we return,
we'll have enough power
to rid the city
of vampires, and we'll
kill anyone...
Who doesn't keep
the faith.
Monique...
Please...
You should have
believed.
Stop. Please.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/