Previously on "The Originals"...
Our community is under attack.
They're
declaring war on us.
All his life,
there's only ever been
one man he has
truly feared...
My father Mikael.
All we need is a witch
who could help us
find him.
- Celeste.
- How did you know?
If you have come here
seeking revenge...
Oh, I'll have
my revenge,
starting with Klaus.
He is gonna know
pain and torment
like he's never
felt before.
Then that leaves Rebekah,
your tragic sister.
She's about
to find herself
in quite
the predicament.
Genevieve knows
where your sister is,
Bastiana has Klaus
tucked away
someplace safe.
I guess always isn't
forever after all.
Who's there?
How the hell did I get here?
Genevieve.
Rebekah.
Tell me you're not
leaving already.
I thought we
might reminisce.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/
Aah!
My siblings have been taken.
Where are they?
You're interrupting
my aunt Sophie's consecration.
How did this happen?
Aunt Sophie was
a casualty of war.
Monique, I recommend
you give me
what I want,
unless, of course,
you'd like me
to level this place
and everything in it.
That won't
be necessary.
I have a message
for you...
From Celeste.
To find what
you're looking for,
follow the path
she left behind.
What the hell are you
doing, you ruthless bitch?
Poor Rebekah.
You should rest.
You're looking
a little peaked.
Uhh! Ow!
Of course, that's
to be expected,
given the rather
impressive amount of
werewolf venom
in your system.
How did you like that wolf-boy,
by the way?
I thought he seemed
like your type...
Trashy and willing.
If I weren't
so bloody sick,
I'd rip
your head off.
But you are sick.
And comforting
the sick always was
a talent of mine.
I take care
of my friends.
We were friends,
weren't we?
Of course we were.
There, there.
Unidentified
sick man.
That can't be good.
You. Red.
Here. Try to take
a sip of this.
Hmm. Just like magic.
But then again,
what would you expect
from a practicing
witch?
It's a simple
herbal remedy.
Won't stop the inevitable,
but it should
ease his pain
and quiet his lungs.
For a while,
at least.
You're quite good
at this, miss...
What is your
name again?
Genevieve.
Lovely.
Perhaps you could
give me some pointers.
Certainly. Though it is a bit odd.
A vampire serving
as nurse.
Please, darling,
I'm an original vampire.
If my city
is under attack
from this
nasty influenza,
it is my duty
to lend a hand.
Besides, if this
entire lot dies,
who'd be left
to eat?
You're wicked.
You know, I think
you and I
are going to be
fast friends.
What say you
join me at this
swell, little
jazz joint
I've discovered on
basin street tonight?
We can toast to
the health of New Orleans.
Oh... I don't know.
You. You should
come, too.
After playing angels
of mercy all day,
I'd say we all
deserve some fun.
Uhh.
Anything?
They're putting eyes
and ears out everywhere.
Daywalkers are working
every contact we got.
Cops, dock workers,
guys in the treme.
Word is out.
Anyone trying to
earn favor with me
gets a lifetime of
it if they find them.
Good. I need
a pen and paper.
Hey.
Am I taking orders
from you now?
Or are we
in this together?
Pen and paper, Marcel.
Now.
Look, I want her back just
as much as you do, you know.
Both of them.
Hayley!
Elijah. You're back.
Did you find any... thing?
What is happening?
I need you to make
a list of these names.
Please.
Ok.
Sabine...?
Elijah, what is this?
I believe they
represent the names
of the women that
Celeste inhabited
for the past
two centuries.
It's called a devinette.
It's old school.
Kind of a riddle.
Witches use them
to teach their kids.
Solve it
and it disappears.
Why?
What's the point?
Celeste forced me to make a choice
between yourself
and my siblings,
and now she means
to mock that choice,
taunting me
with a childish
game.
The longer the game,
the more they suffer.
To find Klaus
and Rebekah,
we need to solve
this riddle.
The solution lies
somewhere in these names.
The name next to
Sabine... Annie LaFleur.
She's a witch that was
shunned from her coven
just over a year ago.
Never knew why,
but I can find out.
You poor thing.
Don't worry.
I'm here to help.
Annie was
a good girl.
Witches done her wrong,
shunning her like that,
saying that she's doing
dark magic.
There's no way.
But they had proof.
So, she just quit.
And I can't really
blame her for that.
Because once you've
been shunned,
what's the point
of going on, you know?
She killed herself?
Yes.
Drowned herself
in the Mississippi,
to be precise.
Celeste had clearly
tired of the body
and was ready
to take Sabine's.
How do you know that?
She leapt to her death
from the very location
Celeste and I had
our first kiss.
Poetic, I guess,
in a creepy,
vendetta kind of way.
All these names,
these lives,
stolen that Celeste
might take her revenge.
I suppose
we have no choice
but to see where
they take us.
Hayley, I have to go.
I'll call you back.
Elijah, wait.
What is it?
Ask Marcel if
he knows anything
about a name on that list...
Brynne Deveraux.
Sophie said that it was
her family's bloodline
that put the curse on
the crescent wolves,
but Celeste said that
she was the only one
that could break it.
If Brynne Deveraux
was actually Celeste
when she cast
the spell, then
maybe Celeste can
still break it.
I'll see
what he knows.
Elijah, I'm really sorry
that you're going
through this.
If I had known that
Celeste had made you
choose who to help...
You were going to
die in that fire, Hayley,
along with my
brother's child.
There was no choice.
My wound isn't healing.
The amount of dark magic
contained in that blade?
It's gonna take
a little while.
You're one of them,
aren't you?
The witches
back from the dead,
seeking vengeance.
Why show me kindness?
You never did
anything to me.
And the truth is,
seeing you like this,
I can't help
but pity you.
Then betray the others
and stand with me.
I will reward you
in ways you cannot
possibly fathom.
Klaus Mikaelson
offering a deal
to little ol' me?
I should be flattered.
But first... we need
to have a talk
about your sister.
Rebekah is of
no concern to you.
If you mean
to harm her...
Ah, the protective brother.
A shame that loyalty
isn't reciprocated.
But then,
I'm no stranger
to Rebekah's treachery.
Something you and I
have in common.
Here. Drink.
I'm just trying
to help you.
Heal you. Get you to see the truth
that's been right
in front of you
for almost
a century.
Your sister had
an unfortunate run-in
with some wolves
last night.
I imagine you're
tasting the venom
in her blood.
It's the only way
I can show you
what you need to see.
In her weakened state,
I'll be able to guide her
down memory Lane.
That's how I'm going
to have my revenge.
By showing you
her betrayal.
Niklaus.
Marcel.
Have some respect.
Yeah, I don't
think they mind.
Did you ask Genevieve
about doing the spell?
I will.
When the time is right.
Rebekah.
You've been hanging around
that witch for weeks,
waiting for the time
to be right.
She wasn't supposed
to become your sidekick.
One little spell and we could
finally be together for real.
What are you
waiting for?
She's a sweet girl,
is all.
If you must know, I feel
badly for using her.
Then we'll find
another witch,
one you don't have
to fake a friendship with.
Unless you've changed
your mind.
I want to wake up
with you in our home,
in the bed
that we share.
I want to walk down
the street with you by my side
so that everyone knows
that you are mine
and I am yours.
I don't want
to be afraid
of what my brother
will do to me
for loving you.
If this is the only way
to get it, then...
No, my mind
hasn't changed.
Oh! I didn't know
anyone was in here.
I'm so sorry.
Genevieve...
Genevieve, wait...
I'm sorry.
So, this is your
great betrayal.
My sister and Marcel.
They've been sneaking around
behind my back
for the better part
of two centuries.
Yes. Against all
your warnings.
You'd disciplined
them for it before,
had you not?
Harshly,
I understand.
I had my reasons.
Oh, you don't have
to convince me.
As far as
I'm concerned,
you only needed one:
That it suited you.
Have you ever read
the old testament, Nik?
You see...
God wasn't powerful
because he was right...
He was right
because he was powerful.
I don't know what
you're playing at,
but if the sum total
of your plan
to turn me
against my sister
was this revelation,
this will have been
a wholly ineffective endeavor.
You poor thing.
After 1,000 years,
dishonesty from
your family
has come
to be expected.
I wish that was
the sum total
of their treachery.
Unfortunately, it's not.
W-what do you want
from me?
Well, I assume
you're familiar
with this pigsty,
quite appropriately
known as the pit.
See, awkwardly enough,
only weeks ago,
a group of human beings
just like yourself
slaughtered many of
the companions
of the vampires that
you see assembled
before you here.
You run
the records room at city hall.
We're told the former mayor
kept a detailed record
of the supernatural
community.
A ledger of names of witches,
werewolves, and vampires.
Specifically, their
death records.
We need it.
I-I don't know
where it is.
I think we both
know that's a fib.
Anyone feeling hungry?
Oh! Ok. W-wait.
They moved the records.
After the mayor died.
They're at the sacristy
of St. Anne's church.
See? There.
Wasn't so difficult,
now, was it?
Aah!
Rough day?
Oh, becks.
Those bites are
looking nasty.
Why make me
relive the past?
We both know
how it ends.
You and I both know.
But I thought your brother
might like to hear our story.
So, I linked
your mind to his.
You're gonna
show him everything.
No. No, please don't do that to me.
I'll do anything.
It's too late, friend.
Aah!
Marcel, here's another
name from our list.
Brynne Deveraux.
Says here she drowned herself
some 20 years ago.
Do you recognize
the name?
Brynne? Yeah.
Yeah, we used to hang out.
Knock around a bit.
You can spare me
the details, please.
She used to do some spells
for me now and then.
Girl had power.
Cursed a whole pack
of werewolves
just because they
were pissing me off.
Speaking of...
What do you think
Klaus is gonna do
when he finds out
that you left him
to suffer
while you saved Hayley
and her wolf friends?
Let's avoid discussing
matters that are
not your concern,
shall we, Marcellus?
Oh, come on, Elijah.
I got guys all over this city.
You honestly think
that I don't know
that the crescent
wolves had a little
family reunion out at
the plantation last night?
Thanks for letting the house burn,
by the way.
Good riddance.
But my question is,
what's Hayley doing
with that bunch?
Marcel, I'm aware
of your history
with the city's wolves,
and I assume
you understand that if you
lay a finger upon Hayley,
it will be the last
thing you do on this earth.
I see I hit a nerve.
And just when we
were getting along.
We were right.
Every name
upon my flesh signifies
a witch who died
by her own hand.
All but one.
Clara Summerlin.
Ring any bells?
None.
Ok, well,
if she didn't
off herself,
then how'd she die?
Influenza.
Epidemic of 1919.
I suppose we have
our answer.
Only I have no idea
what it means.
No.
No! Please! Uhh!
Your sister's tryst
with Marcel
was only
the beginning.
You see, the burden
of your condemnation
had become
too great.
And as a result,
your deepest fear came to pass.
That their love
for each other
would overshadow
their love for you,
turn it into hate.
Nik, they conspired
to rid themselves
of you for good.
Yeah!
An abomination
of nature?
You're anything but.
Ok, next round's
on me.
Clara Summerlin, no.
I'll be soused.
Get it while you can.
It's the last
real gin in the city.
Bartender?
You're nothing like
I thought you'd be
when I first met you.
I was brought up to think
your kind were... well...
An abomination of nature?
You're anything bug
not just you,
your whole family is so...
Elegant.
Yes, I agree.
Elijah is quite peerless.
I don't know.
I mean, he's nice and all, but
if I had to go
for one Mikaelson boy...
Klaus?
Genevieve, who'd
have thought
a saintly, little
witch like you
would go for
the bad boys?
I knew we were
destined to be friends.
More gin, please.
Please.
Allow me.
Keep it.
It's yours.
Well, there's a load
of us Mikaelsons.
If you like bad
boys, you'd love
my brother Kol.
And where is this
mystery brother of yours?
It's complicated.
Like all siblings,
we've had our
ups and downs.
Family feuds.
In fact, I was
thinking of
reaching out to
someone we haven't seen
in a very
long while.
I was hoping that
maybe you could
help me contact them.
But it would have
to be a surprise.
No one could know.
Of course.
Do you want me to find
your brother Kol?
Actually, I'd like
you to find Mikael.
Our father.
Enough of your lies!
Don't dismember
the messenger.
Part of you
must have known.
Suspected, at least.
Your father came
to New Orleans
in 1919 to kill you,
did he not?
And as the city burned,
he nearly succeeded.
My family and I have done
some terrible things to
each other over the years,
but Rebekah would not
call my father.
No matter how angry she was.
It's sweet of you
to believe that.
To believe in her.
But by the time
we're done here,
you'll know just
how wrong you are.
Hey, look,
I found...
You were right about
the Deveraux witch.
Find anything about
Clara the mystery witch?
Not much.
She was a nurse
at the Fleur-de-lis
sanitorium.
Recognize her?
Top row,
second from the right.
No. I don't.
Marcel?
Do I need to remind you
that Niklaus and Rebekah
are somewhere
suffering horribly?
If you know something...
Talk.
The sanitorium.
That's where you'll find then.
Are you sure?
How do you know?
I just know.
If I'm right...
You need
to know exactly
what we're
walking into.
We did something,
Rebekah and I.
I think the witches are
trying to use it against her.
It's... something
that you're not gonna like.
Are you ready
to see more proof?
No.
What do you see?
My father's blade.
It went missing
when I was a boy.
He beat me
half to death,
so sure I had
stolen it.
Rebekah was
so kind to me
in the weeks
after the beating.
I should have known
she was the culprit.
She never could
stand weapons
were things not meant
for guns.
Pran ce mesaj sa a,
les cendres sur le vent.
No! Klaus!
My sister.
Rebekah.
Rebekah!
For the better part
of a century,
I have wondered how
father found us,
what foolish mistake
that we had made
to destroy our time
in the one place
that we could
finally call home.
Did you know, I even
blamed myself
for a time,
marcellus?
Elijah.
Niklaus treated you
like a son.
Rebekah...
I loved her.
I still love her.
All we ever wanted
was to be together,
but as long as
Klaus was around,
that was never
gonna happen.
But hey, I guess
you wouldn't know
anything about
that, huh?
When Klaus
learns the truth,
there will be
no end to his rage.
I will not
let my sister
suffer that wrath.
Then we need
to get to them
before he learns
the truth.
Just give
it up, Rebekah.
It's inevitable
at this point.
Sabine.
I prefer
Celeste, actually.
All these names I've
had over the years
and I still prefer
the first.
Perhaps it was
the way it sounded
on Elijah's lips,
like a declaration
of love.
Oh, he was
a good liar.
All of you are.
Say what you
want about me,
but Elijah is
a good man.
Still defending him,
even until
the bitter end.
Good. I'm counting
on that familial love.
It'll be the ruin
of you all.
Now that Klaus knows
what you've done,
he'll never stop until
he's had his revenge.
He'll kill Marcel.
Do something horrible to you.
Elijah will never
forgive him.
Your betrayal
will ultimately
pit brother
against brother.
And the fabled Mikaelson
bond will crumble.
I'll kill you,
you bitch.
You already did.
Though at the time,
I wore a different face.
Genevieve, we need to talk.
Privately.
I'll be fine here.
You go ahead.
You should
wash up anyway.
Hey.
Incinerate that
as soon as you can.
You were the other one.
Clara.
You should have minded
your own business.
I suspected my friend
was being exploited.
It was my business.
Call it off?
Are you mad?
I was wrong.
It was stupid
and... and impulsive,
and it will
ruin us, Genevieve.
Not just Klaus
but Elijah, too.
I risked tearing
our family apart
for my own
selfish happiness.
I'm begging you,
please,
don't bring
Mikael here.
If Klaus finds out
what we have done,
what you
have done...
Klaus will kill me.
He'll kill
my entire family.
Which is exactly why
I need you to undo it.
It doesn't
work that way.
There is no
undoing it.
Mikael is coming.
The only hope now...
Is tell Klaus
the truth.
Confess what
we've done.
That is not an option.
He will dagger me
and leave me
in a box for centuries.
You will not say a word.
You used me.
This whole time.
Our friendship.
All you wanted
was a favor,
and now you want
to take it back?
Well, you can't.
And I will not suffer
because I was foolish
enough to trust you.
It was a mistake.
I know that now.
But that one mistake
will destroy us.
Aah!
Uhh! Aah!
You brought this
on yourself.
I will not be destroyed
along with you.
Uhh!
I'm so sorry, Genevieve.
But if you tell Niklaus
you summoned Mikael,
you're dead either way.
Genevieve,
is everything all right?
So, you infected
me, too.
Compelled the orderlies
to keep us in quarantine
until we died.
Fortunately,
I just took another body.
Genevieve wasn't so lucky.
Well, now that
she's back...
You're the one
who's luck's run out.
I'm sorry.
I know how much
this hurts.
To see what she did...
To see who
she really is.
But you needed
to know.
You needed to see it.
And now that you have,
you can take your revenge.
Our revenge.
Please. Go ahead.
You'll need your strength
for what comes next.
Rebekah!
We should divide
the building.
I'll start at one end,
you at the other.
Nik. Nik,
it isn't true.
I want to believe
you, sister.
But your face tells
a different story.
You cannot hide
from me, Rebekah!
Nor can you run.
This ends now.
Uhh!
Hey, there,
witch bitch.
You and I are gonna
have a little chat.
Rebekah!
Tired of running?
I know how much
you enjoy the chase.
I'd sooner deny you
the pleasure.
Well, then I'll take my
pleasures in other ways.
No more "daggered
in a box" for you.
Trust me, sister,
you'll long for what
the dagger offered.
This... will be
far less merciful.
How to describe exactly
what this blade does?
You don't have
to do this, Nik.
After I plunge this
into your heart,
you will be immobilized,
imprispred in a state
of raw,
inescapable anguish.
Time loses all meaning.
It's not unlike
a living hell,
which I find rather fitting
given your treachery.
Then do it.
If that's what
you really want.
Are we skipping the part
where you beg for mercy?
For forgiveness?
Because I was really
looking forward to that.
I'll pass.
I know better
than to think
it would do me
any good.
That's it, then?
You concede?
Like a lamb
to the slaughter.
What would your father
think of you now?
Uhh!
Aah! Uhh!
Uhh! Aah!
Uhh!
Just the man
I wanted to see.
Uhh.
Rebekah's punishment
won't be complete
until she watches
you die.
Nik, it was my idea
to summon Mikael.
If you're gonna hurt anyone,
it should be me.
Such loyalty
to your beloved.
You know...
If you had offered me
even a fraction
of the same,
I wouldn't have
to do this.
Uhhaah!
Ohh!
Uhh!
Go.
Both of you.
Run as far and as fast as you can.
Run!
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/