Previously onWhy Women Kill...
He's a man.
Some of them cheat.
Not Rob. Not after
what happened to our daughter.
I am in love with you.
ROB: You knew the
rules. I will never
leave my wife.
Why would he even be with me
if he was so happy with her?
Maybe she did something
to hurt him
and he needs time
to forgive her.
I moved my lover
into our home.
The three of us are
officially a throuple.
My agent's gonna drop me
if I don't get him my script
by tomorrow morning.
Give me the 50 pages.Skip to what sucks.
That would be
your lead character.
What's wrong with Eva?She waits around for 15 pages
hoping a man will save her.
She's a victim.
I hate victims.
Hey, how did you come up
with that stuff anyway?
Maybe there's more to me
than meets the eye.
The man's a drug addict.
Half your savings went
up his nose.
Eli has changed.
Hold on, I have something.
Take this.
What happens when he
likes her more than you?
He said it's the best thing
I've ever written.
God, I am so happy for you.
[giggles]
♪
Are you having an affair?
Karl, I believe you're jealous.
Tell me who it is.
Is it one of our friends
from the country club?
SIMONE:
Tommy's back.
Wasn't that lucky, dear.
Seems Tommy was right there
in the bedroom,
ready to be useful.
Don't you see? We don't
need to get a divorce.
We have stumbled into
the perfect arrangement.
Everything is not a joke, Karl.
I want a man who
loves me so much,
that he would kill another man
if I slept with
someone else.
And I'm never gonna get that
from you, am I?
No.
["L-O-V-E" by Michael Feinstein playing]
♪ "L" is for the way you look
♪ At me
♪ "O" is for the only one
♪ I see
♪ "V" is very, very
♪ Extraordinary
♪ "E" is even more
♪ Than anyone
that you adore can ♪
♪ Love is all
♪ That I can give to you
♪ Love is more
♪ Than just a game for two
♪ Two in love can make it
♪ Take my heart
and please don't break it ♪
♪ Love was made
♪ For me and you...
Simone and I used
to be very close,
back when I was her hairdresser.
Taylor and I were
forced to socialize,
'cause I was
her husband's agent.
I didn't know Beth Ann at all,
even though she was a neighbor.
I used to gossip
with her for hours.
She adored me.
I tried to talk to her
at parties.
She never got my jokes.
I used to watch her
at the market.
She seemed nice.
It's funny about people.
They come into our lives
every day...
...and you never know who will
play the most important part.
A total stranger
might be the one to save you
or destroy you.
To be honest...
I feel responsible
for his death.
I'm not sure anyone would've
died if it wasn't for me.
I knew she was
going to kill him.
And I am so glad she did.
Oh, Simone.
What are you doing here?What a silly question.
You know how much
I adore our little gallery.
Oh, please. You haven't
stopped by in months.
Once we begin negotiating
our settlement, I know
you'll fight for this place.
You'll tell the judge
it should go to you
because I never helped out.
Well, here I am helping out.
WOMAN:
Excuse me.Yes? Hello.
Do you have any
Lichtenstein prints?
We're talking. Do you mind?
And with charm like that
on our sales staff,
these paintings should
just fly off the walls.
No Tommy today?
We spoke this morning.
Oh, yes? Was that on the phone
or did you roll over
and tap him on the shoulder?
I suggested we take a break.
My divorce lawyer feels
an ongoing affair
with a teenager could
make me seem unsympathetic.
You've hired a lawyer?
Bernie Morton.
He did my first two divorces,
so he knows what I like.
No, no, no. We-we agreed
we weren't gonna get divorced
until after Amy's wedding.
We agreed not to
announce it till then.
That doesn't mean we can't
get the ball rolling.B-But there's so much
coming at us
in the next few weeks.
I mean, Amy's Oklahoma in-laws
are turning up tomorrow
en masse.
Oh, God.
I'm dreading that dinner.
I spoke to Brad's mother
for two minutes on the phone.
I already can't stand her.Exactly.
If we're fighting each other,
how will we have the energy
to properly hate them?
After what you've put me
through, I have
more than enough rage
to go around.
All right. Clearly,
we need counseling.
I mean, can we at least wait
until after we've
seen a therapist?
It's over. No more waiting.
Accept it.
[sighs]:
Well.
I guess I've helped enough
for one day. See you at home.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sighs]
Hey.
Did you see Taylor's text?
Uh, no. I've been writing.
She got on an early flight.
She's gonna be here
in a couple minutes.
Oh, okay.So, um, I was
wondering,
when you want to tell her?
Tell her...?
About last night?
And how-how we fucked?
[chuckles]
Oh.
You-you want to mention that.
Well, it happened, so we have
to be honest about it, right?
Sure. Yeah.
Great. Awesome.Yeah.
I do wonder, though, um,
what-what do you think
Taylor's reaction will be
when we tell her?
I-I think
she'll be cool with it.
I mean, we're in a throuple,
she's seen us have sex before.
I-It's-- it won't be a big deal.
Mm. Interesting.
That's interesting.
What?
You think, you think
she might get jealous?
Maybe. Maybe jealous,
maybe furious.
I mean, likely furious.
Yeah, but don't you think she'll
be angrier if we don't tell her
and then she finds out anyway?
It-- well, see? See,
that's where the ever-popular
"take it to our graves"
philosophy would come into play.
You want to keep it a secret?
I'll be honest,
it's not my first inclination,
but hearing you say it out loud,
I like it.Eli.
No. I...
[exhales]
We can't. That-that feels wrong.
That's wrong.
All right, all right, all right.
You're right. You're right.[car approaching]
Anything less than full honesty
is a betrayal.
Okay.[car door closes]
Here she is.
Make me proud.Shit.
Hi.
Hey, babe. How was the flight?
Crying babies,
bitchy flight attendants,
they lost my suitcase
and I hate Uber!
[door closes]
What have you guys been up to?
Uh... nothing much.
[chuckles]:
Yeah. Yeah.
Just happy to have
this one home.
TAYLOR:
Oh, oh...
Mm.[exhales]
What do you say
we put you in a bath, huh?
TAYLOR: Oh, my God.You deserve it.
Salt, no salt?
So much salt.Salt it up.
♪
Whatcha doing?
I was just trying
to think of a place
to store all of Nana's linens.
If there's ever
a worldwide doily shortage,
we'll be sitting pretty.
It is done.
We are now
officially unpacked.
I thought you finished
weeks ago.
You said you hated seeing all of
the unpacked boxes lying around,
so I put them all
in the attic.
Every day, I would
bring one down and empty it.
You lugged all these
boxes to the attic?
Just so I wouldn't
have to look at 'em?
It was nothing.
You do so many things
each day to please me.
Things I don't even notice.
And I want to notice them,
so I can thank you.
I don't need to be thanked.
You know,
I've been working a lot of
late nights the past few months.
This project I've been
involved with, it's almost over.
It is?
Yeah.
Once I'm done,
we'll get back
to a normal schedule.
I'll be home in time for dinner,
every night.
That would make me very happy.
So, we're finally moved in.
How should we celebrate?
Hey.
Why not throw a party?
Like a housewarming thing?
Yes, we can invite
all the neighbors.
There's so many
I haven't met yet.
Oh. Let's do it next Saturday.
That would be wonderful.Fantastic.
You want me to throw
this box away for you?Oh, not just yet.
There's still some
photos in there.
I was going to put those
in the cupboard upstairs.
[stammers] Maybe we should
leave this one out.
Really?
You said it upset you.
Eh, that was a while ago.
[sets picture down]
It hurts to remember,
but it'd be worse to forget.
You're absolutely right.
Simone, we're going to be late.
I'm coming. Hold your horses.
Amy.
Are you coming with
us to the dinner?
We assumed you'd be going
with Brad and his family.
I was with them all day.
I need a break.
Oh, are they really that bad?
Do you know much about tractors?
Um, no.
You will by dessert.I think you deserve a drink.
I'm sure Brad
is very pleased
that you're making
such an effort.
Trust me,
I'm sucking up like crazy.
And if I make a good impression,
his parents might
buy us a house.
Ooh.
A house?
As a wedding gift?
Darling, we really need
to rethink those fondue forks.
Their farm sits
on millions of gallons of oil.
So whatever you think of them,
be nice.
I'm always nice.Really nice.
Not bitchy nice.
You're tying my hands, but fine.
[phone ringing]Don't pick up.
We're late.Uh, don't worry,
we've got one of those
newfangled machines
that takes a message.
You know, I don't know
how we lived without it.[machine beeps]
BERNIE [over phone]:
Simone, Bernie Morton here.
I'm working on your divorce
paperwork, but I still need
some financial forms, so...Bernie, it's not a good time.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
You're getting divorced again?
Now, Amy...
Right before my wedding?
It won't affect you.
Brad's parents are not
going to buy me a house
if they think I was raised by a
woman who's never had a marriage
last longer than a breath mint.
You're blaming me?
After three husbands, yes.
What's your excuse this time?
It's a charming story.
Y-Yes, well, we-we both have
charming stories,
but I don't want
to bore you
with a lot of what
we Brits call, um, tommyrot.
Fine.
Let's just go.
Tommyrot? Really, Karl?
You're hilarious.
At last, we agree
on something.
♪
[doorbell rings]
Good morning.
I'm Beth Ann Stanton,
your new neighbor.
My husband and I just
moved in down the street.
I-I know who you are.
Well, I hear your name is Mary.
Mary Vlasin.
It's nice to
officially meet you.
MAN [calling out]:
Mary!
That your husband?
Uh, yes.
Now's not a good time.
I'll be quick.
I have something
for the two of you.
It's the reason
I dropped by.
It's an invitation.
Rob and I
are throwing
a housewarming party
on Saturday; nothing fancy.
Just finger food and beer.
We'll be having
some old friends,
and hopefully some new ones.
[chuckles]
I can't remember the last time
I went to a party.
MAN:
Mary!
Uh, do you think you might
be able to make it?
I'm just doing a head count.
I don't know, um...
I was coming.
I was just, uh, talking
to our new neighbor.
Oh, hello there.
I didn't realize we had company.
I'm Beth Ann Stanton.
I've just moved in
down the street.
Ah.She invited us
to, uh, a party.
Oh.Just a little housewarming
thing on Saturday.
Mary said she wasn't sure
you'd be able to...No,
we'd love to come.
Really?Sure.
You want us to
bring anything, or...
No. No.
Just your lovely selves.
Well, all righty, then.
We'll see you soon.
Wonderful.
I'll check with the maître d',
see if Brad's family's arrived.
Oh, my God.
It's Hector.AMY: Hector?
He was the best hairdresser
I ever had.
I mean, until he dropped me.
Why did he drop you?
Who knows? One day, he just
stopped scheduling appointments.
Well, I'm sure you did
something to offend him.
Why would you assume that?
Oh, right, I'm horrible.
PATTY:
Amy!
Patty. Mom,
this is Brad's
sister Patty.
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
Thank you.
Oh, they've seated us
in a private dining room.
Did you arrange that?
I did. I wanted to
do something special
for my new family.
It's a great idea.
Now we can get as loud
and crazy as we want.Ah!
I don't know if Amy told you,
but I know how to yodel.
No.
I think I would have
remembered that.
Great, let's get
the party started.
Karl, everyone's here.Oh, good.
Hello.
Hi.
[mutters]
Hey, guys.
Patty.Oh, here they are.
What a pleasure it is
to finally meet you.
I'm Ruby and
this is Dwight.
Charmed.DWIGHT:
Well, hello, there.
Hi. Sorry we're late.
Well, if you were busy
making yourself beautiful,
may I just say,
mission accomplished.
Heel, Dwight.[laughter]
I see I'm gonna have to
watch my step around you.
[laughs]
I can't tell you
how thrilled we are
that Amy's marrying
a young man
as admirable as your son.
That voice.
He's like someone on PBS.
Now, who wants champagne?
I'm sure we could all
be persuaded. [chuckles]
I could just listen
to him talk all day long.
If you were married
to him, you would.
Well, Ruby and I are just
as crazy about your daughter.
The whole family is.
Patty hasn't shut up
about her.
'Cause I'm happy, okay?
I'm finally getting
a sister.
Well, I'm thrilled
to finally be a part
of a big family.
I've always dreamed of hosting
large family gatherings.
RUBY: You know
what I dream about?
Grandkids.
Oh, I've had that dream.
I always wake up screaming.
Now, why don't you
want grandkids?
Well, I'd have to tell people
that I'm a grandmother.
And let's face it,
who's gonna believe me?
Does anyone need
more champagne?
Oh, God, yes.
Yes, absolutely.
Uh, I'm terribly sorry.
Will you excuse me?
I, uh, I desperately need
to use the facilities.
Listen to him.
He even makes taking a piss
sound fancy.
[Dwight and Ruby laugh]
It is done!
I just wrote the words
"fade to black."
My script is complete!
Eli!
Aw!
Oh, my God. Oh.[Eli chuckling]
Honey, that's amazing.Yeah, it is.
You know what's amazing?
Somehow it all works.
I mean, the characters,
the plot, all of it.
I mean, I probably
used the word "fuck"
about 60 times too many,
but that's fixable.
I mean, the point is: I may
actually be a good writer.
[laughs]Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
JADE:
Oh...
Mm.
ELI: Mm. Oh, so
I called Lamar,
and he wants to
take us all
out to dinner tonight
to celebrate.
Oh, that'd be great.
We should go to La Serata.
Ooh, molto bene.
Yeah.
Hmm.Not to change the subject,
but I'm curious about something.
What's up?
While I was away,
did you two fuck?
I don't know why,
I just have a feeling.
Am I crazy?
[laughs]
We absolutely fucked.
Yeah.
Shit. Wow. Hmm.
Are you upset?
Um...
I'm not sure.
It's not like you and I have
never done it without Eli.
[chuckles]
That's true.
Mm.
Okay.
Okay?
I mean, obviously
I have some feelings
that I need to work through,
but this was...
this was bound to happen, right?
At some point,
since we're all together now.
And I love you both,
so why... why would I not want
you guys to get closer?
Yes, exactly, and I-I knew
that if we were just open
and honest about
the whole thing,
that it wouldn't
be a big deal.
Yeah. Well, thank you
for telling me the truth.
It feels good to know.Of course.
Of course.Mm-hmm.
Oh, you know what,
you should tell Lamar
that I know the manager
at La Serata,
so she can get us
a good table.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Totally. Great call.[phone chimes]
I will, um...
I-I will, I will
text Lamar right now.
Okay.
[phone chimes]
So I can tell Rob is still
mad about the other night.
He hasn't called in days.
I thought about
calling him,
but I don't want
to seem desperate,
although I am
a little bit,
but he doesn't need
to know that.
Anyway...
[chuckles]
what do you think I should do?
Hmm. What?
[chuckles]
Listen to me.
I must be boring you to tears
always talking about Rob.
No, I'm sorry.
I was thinking about
this woman I met today.
I can't get her
out of my mind.
Why?
I was at her door
dropping something off,
and, just, something
wasn't quite right.
How do you mean?
She was worried about
her husband.
I could hear him
calling for her.
There was just
something about his tone.
It scared me.
Then he came to the door,
and he was charming.
This woman, was she wearing
a lot of makeup?
She was.
How did you know that?
He hits her.
You think?
No, he isn't the type.
He's very successful.
My father was a doctor.
I used to watch my mother
apply makeup
to cover up her black eyes.
Oh, no.
She would smear green concealer
to cover the bruise,
and then she would apply
a second layer of concealer
that matched her skin tone.
And then she would do
the same thing to the other side
so that people wouldn't
notice the difference.
That's awful.
No, here's the awful part.
My whole family knew
what was going on.
Aunts, uncles,
cousins-- they all knew
what he was doing,
and they just looked
the other way.
I hate people that
look the other way.
And he told the owner
he was willing to match
any offer the Gibson twins
could come up with.
[laughs]
And that's how
Dwight cornered the
Tulsa County market
for earth-moving machinery.
[laughter]
The next thing that happened...
Please stop!
Until I find Karl.
[laughs]
He would hate to miss
this amazing story.
DWIGHT:
He has been
in the gents' room
quite a while.
Uh, you want me
to check on him?
[laughs]:
No. I-I've got this.
Ma'am, that's the men's room.Oh, I know.
My husband isn't hiding out
in the ladies' room.
[gasps]
So nice to finally
meet you, Lamar.
I've heard so much about you.
Heard a lot about
you, too, pretty lady.
And I have so many questions.
Please don't ask them.[laughs] Come on.
I'm paying for this meal.
All I want in exchange is
a few juicy details
about your new lifestyle.
All right, dude,
don't embarrass me.
I wouldn't ask
if I didn't need to know.
Why do you need to know?
Truth is, I've been
thinking about
bringing another woman into
my relationship with Delores.
And she's open
to the idea?
Absolutely not.[laughter]
All right, okay,
all right.
Let's talk about my script.Mm-hmm.
Eli said that you
think it's good.
No.
I think it's brilliant.
Okay, just tell me it'll sell.Oh, yes.
I already got four
different producers interested.
I'm expecting offers
in the high six-figure range.
[exhales]
Are you serious?
I joke about sex,
not money.
Wow. I-I've never had a script
get that kind
of reaction before.
You've never written a script
this commercial before.
And I guess we have you
to thank for that.
[laughs]:
Stop.
What?
It just--
Eli was having some
problems with his story,
so I read the
first 50 pages,
and I-I gave him
a few ideas.
More than a few. I mean, she
saved my ass is what she did.
That part at the end,
where-where Eva,
she burns the place down
and goes,
like, full-blown
arsonist on everybody?
Mm-hmm.Jade's idea.
Cool.
ELI:
Mm.
So, you let her read the script
before it was finished?
W-Well, yeah.
'Cause you never
let me do that.
[chuckles softly]No-- h-honey,
my back was up
against the wall on this.
I mean...
Huh.I-I also,
I-I gave him
some thoughts
on the lead character.
You know, I have insight
into the millennial
female brain.
And it shows.
Eva is the-the best character
he's ever created.
Ah, I-I don't know about that.
I do. Trust me, Eli.
Be good to Jade.
She's your muse.
ELI: You might be right.Oh, that's ridiculous.
LAMAR:
So, Jade, you ever think about
doing any writing yourself?
Um, yeah. I-I have,
I actually have
a couple script ideas, yeah.
LAMAR:
Well, I would love
to hear about them.
Really?
Yeah.
Um, excuse me
for just one moment.Yeah.
Are you sure?
He's always looking for
my replacement, so please.
[Lamar laughs]
What in God's name?
Shit. We...
We got a bit
carried away.
We haven't seen
each other in years.
Oh, my God. Is that why
you dropped me as a client?
Because you were screwing
my husband!
I couldn't look you
in the eye anymore.
It was impossible
to trim your bangs.
I think you should leave now.
For what it's worth,
I love the layers.
Go.
How could you?
You can't be
completely shocked.
You knew perfectly well
I slept with men.
But with Hector?
You're surprised that the man I
slept with was your hairdresser?
That is the gay sex equivalent
of "the butler did it."
What the hell
is going on?
Nothing. We're fine.
We are not fine.
You would not believe
how Karl betrayed me.
I don't care.
I've spent six months sucking up
to the Clampetts, and you're
not gonna blow it
for me in one night.
Now move it!
Come on.
Let's not ruin her chances
with unnecessary drama.
Fine. I'll wait till
we're in divorce court.
And what I do
to you then
will be very necessary.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
Gretchen, Dale!
Welcome to our little shindig.
Hi!Thanks for having us.
Wow, those are
some shorts.
Yeah. Bought 'em special for
the party. Aren't they great?
There's food and drink
in the dining room.
Please help yourself.Thank you.
See? She liked them.That's not what she said.
Hey, Beth Ann. Got any requests?
Don't play classical
until I want people to leave.
[chuckles]:
Okay.
Hey, hey, hey. What did I tell
you? No running in the house.
But it's not our house.
I swear to God,
Benny.
Come on. Nobody's
gonna vote for the guy
after what happened in Cuba.
Don't matter. I can't
think of one scenario
where Kennedy doesn't
get a second term.
Never gonna happen.
GENE: So you're telling me
you've never been for a ride
in a Cadillac? I'd be happy
to take you around the block.
Lenore, could you please help me
in the kitchen?
Thank you so much.
Honey, Miles is bragging about
his salary at Hughes Aircraft.
Can I tell him
how much I make?
Absolutely not.Oh, come on.
Cookies!Oh!
Mmm. Are those deviled eggs?
Help yourself.
Hi. You came.
Of course. We wouldn't miss it.I'm sorry we're late.
Don't be silly.
The party's only just started.
Nice place you got here.
We certainly like it.Well, I didn't want to come
empty-handed, so...You shouldn't have.
No, no. It was no trouble.
I used a mix.
Thank you again
for inviting us.
Look, honey, it's Dale Clark.
I know him. We should go say hi.
Look at those shorts.
♪
Taylor? Are you still in here?
Taylor?
Ah! There you are.
Are you okay?
The boys are starting to worry.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you sure?Yeah.
Doing my thing.
I'll be out in a minute.
Why are your pants on?
Why are you being weird?
Sorry.
Look, I understand
if you're upset.
Do you?
What happened with me and Eli
has obviously triggered
some hurt feelings,
and I totally get it.
Jade, believe me when I say
I don't give a fuck
if you screwed my husband.
Okay, so then
what's the problem?
His muse? What kind of
over-the-top
undeserved
bullshit is that?
Okay, he was just
trying to be nice.
You didn't save him.
You toss out
a couple ideas
and poured him coffee
while he pulled
an all-nighter.
I am the one who spent
the last two years
cleaning up the mess he made
of our lives.
What did he do?What didn't he do?
Speed, cocaine...
Christ, I can write you a list,
but this place
closes at midnight.
Jade, he's an addict.
He almost died.
And he would've if I didn't
force him into rehab.
[sighs]
I-I didn't know that.
Well, how could you?
I didn't say anything
because...
I thought we were fine and...
just having you here, it's...
What?
Ugh.
Man, that's just
shining a light
on the cracks
in our relationship.
I don't mean to...I know.
It's not your fault.
You did nothing wrong.
I'm just...
I don't know.
[sighs]
I'm just not sure
the current living situation
is working.
Are you saying
you want me to go?
I don't know what I'm saying.
I just don't think
this whole thing's working.
Sheila! Sheila! Come on.
What're you doing?
Don't you hear?
They're playing "The Twist."
That's terrific. I'm eating pie.Forget about the pie.
Come on. I want to dance.Well, here's your partner.
She's just like me,
but smaller and stickier.
Come on, honey,
and after we're done dancing,
Daddy's gonna tell you
about all the nice women
he should've married.
Oh.[laughs]
Hi. Joining us?Hey!
[Rob laughs]GRETCHEN: Let's see it.
Lift your leg.
[heel cracks]
You okay there,
Gretchen?[sighs] I broke my heel.
Oh.I'll be right back, Mr. Astaire.
[laughs]You're a killer.
Well, she is.
Mary.
May I have this dance?
Um... No, I don't think so.
Aw, come on.
Don't make me dance alone.
Seriously, I have two left feet.
Well, add them to mine
and we'll have four.
Okay, just for a minute.Yeah, now you're talking.
[laughs]
♪
Look at you go.
LEO:
Hands up!
[laughs] How low can you go?
[laughter]
[both laugh]
ROB: My mistake.
Oh, you're doing great.
[laughter]
Come on.
We were only dancing.I said come on!
[music stops]Buddy.
There's no need to be like this.
[guests murmuring]
You can cheat on your wife
all you want,
but you're not
touching mine.
[piano resumes playing]Did you see that?
Yeah.
He just grabbed her and pulled
her away in front of everyone.
He was angry that she was
dancing with me.
That's no excuse.
They went into the study.
You need to make sure
he's not hurting her.
Well?
What happens in their marriage
is none of our business.
Is that why we go to parties?
So you can flirt
with strange men?
People can hear you.Or do you
just enjoy humiliating me, huh?
Do you mind?
This is a private conversation.
[chuckles]
Look, I am so sorry
if-if we are being too loud.
We'll be out of here in two
shakes of a lamb's tail, okay?
Look, this is not my fault.
She always drinks too much.
I've just set out some angel
food cake in the dining room.
Why don't you
go have a slice?
[chuckles] No, thank you.
We're going home.
Maybe you'd like to stay
a little longer?
Give him a chance to cool off.
That'll just make it worse.
Mary.
It must be a wonderful thing
to be strong like you.
That's the reason we became
Southern Baptist.
Those Methodists were just
a little too liberal
for our taste.
Leave the bottle.
My darling,
don't you, uh,
think you've
had enough?
Of you? Yes.
Of chardonnay? Never.
Oh.RUBY: Patty!
Look at your new dress.
[giggles] Oh, darn.
Amy helps me buy something chic
and I ruin it first time out.
We'll just go shopping
again tomorrow.
For grease on silk,
you want talcum powder.
There's a travel size
in the rental car.
Okay. Excuse me.
Brad tells us you two run
an art gallery together.
What's that like?
Fun.
Challenging.
It's a challenge,
but a fun one.
Unlike our marriage,
which is purely a challenge.
RUBY:
Speaking of marriage,
I'm just curious, Simone,
how many times
have you been married?
Just three. Why?
It's just an innocent question,
my love.
I wasn't talking to you.I know.
Why are you
so cross with him?
I wasn't cross. Was I cross?
You were
definitely cross.
RUBY:
Um, not that it's
any of my business, but...
if I were twice divorced,
then hooked a man
like Karl,
I'd treat him a little nicer.
Now I'm curious
about something, Ruby.
How would you treat Karl
if you walked into the bathroom
and found him
kissing another man?
Mm.
Bravo, Simone.
That's right, sugar.
Karl is gay.
Still have a
crush on him?
Your stepdad is gay?
I thought he was just English.
That's why
we're getting divorced.
Dear God. Another divorce?
Not really
the headline, Dwight.
Oh, you poor, tragic woman.
I have suffered. It's true.
I-I'm sorry,
do not shed tears for Simone.
She is receiving ample comfort
in the arms
of her lover
Tommy Harte.
What the fuck?
Shut up, Karl.
You're sleeping with Tommy?
Who, for the newcomers,
is all of 18 years of age.
Oh, sweet suffering Jesus.
DWIGHT:
British homos,
teen lovers?
What kind of spangled hell pit
are you marrying into?
PATTY:
Hey. Found the talcum powder.
[chuckles softly]
Why is everyone so serious?
I never thought
I'd see the day our family
would have a homosexual in it.
Brad, you swore
you wouldn't tell.
No, Patty, Patty, I-I...
Oh, I-I don't know
what Brad told you,
but my feelings for you
are sisterly, not sexual.
Oh, sweet suffering Jesus.
[crying]
[stammers]
Patty!
Oh, come back!
DWIGHT:
Sweet baby,
please say it's not true.
Oh. She's a lesbian.
Mmm. How did I miss that?
Anybody want
an after-dinner cocktail?
Uh, not me. I have
the worst headache.
Why don't you go on upstairs
and lie down?
We can give you
a little space tonight.
That'd be nice.
Thank you.
I'm gonna have me a scotch.
You want one?
[drink pouring]
Jade?
How could you not tell me?
[chuckles]: I'm not sure
I know what you're talking...
The pills, Eli.
You're an addict
and you let me give you pills.
[sighs]
Shit.
How did you...Taylor told me.
At dinner, in the bathroom.
Shit. She d--
she doesn't know that I took
anything, though, right?
No.
Oh, thank Christ.Not yet.
No. No. No, no, no, no, no.
What do you mean, "No"?
I have to. This is too big.
Fuck.
[exhales]:
What am I gonna do?
I mean,
she's already questioning
our living arrangement.
If she finds out about this,
it doesn't matter
how she feels about me.
I am out on the street.
I don't have
anywhere to go, Eli.
And Willow and Mischa are gone
and Duke is still out there.Listen.
And I...Jade, Jade, listen-listen to me.
That's not gonna happen. Okay?
I'm not gonna let that happen.
I need you here.Why?
Because I'm your muse or am I,
am I just your dealer?
[stammers]
I'm-I'm done
with the pills. Okay?
Done.
So she doesn't need to know.
In that case, give them to me.
What?If you're done
with them,
then there's no reason
that you can't give them back.
So?
Look, the thing is, one of
the producers who's interested
wants a rewrite.I knew it.
[stammers] She's got
some really great ideas.
Lamar says if I can
turn out a draft
by Friday...Eli.
[whispers]:
J-- All right, fine.
Jesus, just take them....
[sighs]
Just, I'm-I'm-I'm so,
I'm so, so close
to getting my career back.
You can handle
a few rewrites without them.
[chuckles]
Yeah, all I know
is that I used to be a writer
and an addict,
and then I got clean,
and all of a sudden,
I wasn't a writer anymore.
But if I can do this,
if I can, if I can
finish this thing
and if I can get it
to them on time,
then, you know, I'm...[claps hands]
[grunts]
I'm back.
I will be legit again,
they will
trust me again
and the money
that will follow, Jade...
...I can take care of you.
Please.
I need them.
And you promise
you'll take care of me?
I promise.
[exhales]
Let's get to work on your movie.
Christ, what an evening.
I'm exhausted.
Oh, you're not
staying here tonight.
Is that so?
I want you to pack your
things and leave, now.
Oh, knock it off, Simone.
I'm angry enough as it is.
You're angry? My daughter
may never speak to me again.
Oh, and whose fault is that?
If you'd just kept your mouth
shut instead of humiliating me.
I was provoked.
Oh, so there was no possible way
you could suppress the impulse
to blow up the entire evening?
Says the man
who couldn't stop himself
from sneaking off
to the men's room for a quickie.
Oh, fuck you!
I've spent my whole damn life
controlling myself,
hiding the central fact
of my existence
so I wouldn't disappoint my
family, my friends or my wife.
Hector was
the only person
who ever saw me
for the man I truly am,
not the one
I was pretending to be.
You have no idea
what he meant to me.
Stop romanticizing
your grubby little fling.
I loved him!
He asked me
to run away with him.
Um, but I-I had made
a commitment to you,
so I chose to stay.
I am your wife.
Am I supposed to be grateful
that you didn't walk out?
I just want you to see it
from my perspective for once.
Just think
about what it may have cost me
to honor the vow I made to you.
So no, Simone,
I do not expect you
to be grateful
for the sacrifice I made,
but for fuck's sake,
at least acknowledge it.
I am going to bed.
Not in the guest room.
In our room, in our bed.
You sleep
where you like.
The Thompsons just left.
Said to thank you
for a lovely time.
So, you're not talking to me.
What am I
supposed to say?
It was a party.
I wasn't gonna cause a scene.
He hurt her,
right in front of you,
and you did nothing.
What was I supposed to do?
Hit him?
I mean, I'm sure our guests
would have loved that.
You could have at
least confronted him.
Reminded him that kind of
behavior is unacceptable.
The guy had been drinking.
I-I'm sure he didn't mean
to hurt her.
This is not the first time
he's gotten rough with her.
How do you know that?
She had several bruises
on her arm.
That's why she's wearing
long sleeves on such a hot day.
If it's that bad, why
doesn't she leave him?
And where would
she go, Rob? Here?
Will you let her
sleep on our sofa?
Jesus, Beth Ann, I don't know.
And what if Ralph comes
banging on our door
in the middle of the night
to try to drag her back?
Would you have the balls
to stand up to him then?
Don't use that kind of language.
Of course you wouldn't.
You would just slink away
like the coward you are!
Okay!
He's not
the perfect husband.
It's not my job to judge him!
Would you like the neighbors
coming in here and judging you
for not being
the perfect mother?
Huh?!
I'm just saying,
leave it alone.
[exhales] I didn't know
you were still here.
I was just upstairs.
Just... picking up some trash.
So you heard everything?
Yeah.
What was that all about?
Honey.
It's okay.
You can talk to me.
Whatever it is, I don't judge.
Our daughter died because of me.
I'm the one who's responsible.
[doorbell rings]
Simone.
What are you doing here?
I need to know. Do you love him?
I do.
Okay, then invite me in.
We have a lot to talk about.
♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org