You!
Another beer.
This one taste like monkey sweat.
Please!
What?!
You lecture me in manners?
You, dressed like prostitute!
Eh! It's six o'clock in the morning.
I want my breakfast.
Can we just get on
with the game, please?
Come on, then, little boy,
make your bloody move.
Yeah, all right.
I'll call you five grand.
Let's see what you got.
Hang on a minute.
I've been looking at you all night.
I'm flattered.
You're not really my type, love.
Trying to work out why I knew
your face, and it's just come to me.
Oh, yeah?
I think you're Kennedy.
The card counter.
I think you're Sean Kennedy.
Security!
ALARM
Argh!
Kensington.
Stop!
When will you be free?
I need to cash these chips.
I can't exactly go
back in the casino.
Well, well, well,
what have we here!
I'll call you back.
Five bloody grand you took off me.
I want my money, you cheating
pig, or I call the police!
Look, ok, ok, ok.
Look, mate, that's
only fair, all right?
Five grand, yeah?
There you go.
Sorry about that.
You want to cash the chips?
I'll do it.
I'll give you cash
for them, right now.
- How much?
- How much you got in there?
About 40K's worth.
I'll give you ten.
LAUGHS
You're having a laugh, mate!
- 15.
- No chance...
20, final offer.
20 grand cash, right now.
You make a bit, I make a bit.
What's not to like?
I'd like to cash these, please.
- Is this a joke?
- What?
I'm not cashing these.
What do you mean you're
not cashing them? Why?
Well why d'you think?
They're fake.
Obviously they're fake.
I think you're Kennedy.
The card counter.
I think you're Sean Kennedy.
Security!
Kensington.
20 grand cash, right now.
You make a bit, I make a bit.
What's not to like?
Argh!
Listen, cheers, Caz. You played
an absolute blinder as usual.
Thanks, babe.
Really sweet of you, that.
Sure we can't give
you a lift anywhere?
No thanks, Ash.
Not feeling too clever, to be honest.
I could do with a bit of a walk
and some fresh...
Whoa... Ooh!
Ambulance.
sync and corrections by Bellows
www.addic7ed.com
You're going to be fine, love.
Tough as old boots, you are.
Less of the "old".
Yeah, well, you know what I mean.
I don't want to die, Ash.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
No-one's doing any dying.
Besides, there's a queue.
And Albert's first.
Charming!
You're going to be fine, yeah?
I'll come back
with a bunch of grapes.
Are you next of kin?
Well, as good as.
There's no-one else.
Your friend's had a
very serious heart
attack and she'll be
in for quite a while.
Now, she's going to need
some stuff from home.
Is there any way you'll
be able to sort that out?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
consider it done.
Heart attack?
All right, thanks for
letting me know, Sandra.
Yeah, I know it couldn't
have been an easy call.
Right, thanks again.
Bye-bye.
Poor old girl.
I'll have a whiskey,
Eddie, large one.
I know how you feel, mate.
I might join you there.
Very upsetting news.
- You already heard?
- Yeah, Ash phoned me.
Well, I suppose it wasn't
a surprise to anyone.
She just went down
like a sack of potatoes.
It's awful.
In the end, they had no
option but to put her down.
They shot Carol?
No! El Matador,
at 10.30 at Chepstow.
I'm talking about Carol.
Oh! Carol is recovering
in the hospital.
And unless the NHS is in
more trouble than I thought,
I don't believe they're
planning on murdering her.
Right. Good, cos...
yeah, she's er... she's a...
she's a lovely lady, Carol.
Remember the
Downing Street switch?
- What, that was Carol?
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
- And the London Eye float.
- Yeah?
The bearer bond scam of 2000.
All hers.
She even...she even
took Mad Frankie Fraser
for ten quid when she
was five years old.
(No!)
Yeah, in her day...
Carol was one of the best.
So there's no fella
on the scene, then?
Not if this is anything to go by.
Whoa! Now that is what
I call comfort food.
No wonder she's not well.
What the hell...
"Eat Yourself Slender"?
Now, this I've got to see.
'Hey, I'm Dr Dean Deville,
'and I'm here today to tell you
about the EYS plan...
'the diet plan that has taken
the slimming world by storm.
'Eat Yourself Slender is the
diet plan that allows you
'to live the lifestyle you deserve
'while simultaneously
helping you to lose weight.
'How's that possible?
'Simple! By understanding
how metabolism really works.
'For the last five years,
I have worked with a
team of top nutritionists
across the globe,
'and what I've learned has turned the
science of weight loss on its head.
'Now it's time to share that
with you in the UK.
'There are four types of fat.
'Good fat, bad fat,
thin fat and fat fat.
'The Eat Yourself
Slender plan allows you
to eat all the good
thin fat you like,
'whilst at the same time
reducing your bad fat fat.
'This is Ray.
'Look at him before.
'And look at him now!
'He has lost 22 stone by
eating what he wants to eat
'on the Eat Yourself Slender plan.
'Gail used to be repulsive
'but six months on the Eat
Yourself Slender plan...
'and Gail's got the figure
she always wanted.
'So, don't delay.
'For only £99.99 a month,
you too can be part
'of the Eat Yourself Slender plan.
'Be the person you
always wanted to be.
'The Eat Yourself Slender plan.
'Because the rest of
your life starts today.'
Carol had been on the
diet for six months.
She was nine and a half
stone when she started,
13 when admitted to
hospital this morning.
And if you read these,
you can see why.
It is a recipe for heart disease, high
blood pressure, raised cholesterol.
It'd be funny if it
wasn't so dangerous.
Meanwhile, Dr Dean Deville and
his wife and business partner Dana
have gained quite a few pounds
over the last few years.
Yeah, over ten million of them,
according to Companies House.
Please tell me we think they
can afford to shed a few.
They sold Carol a diet plan
that nearly killed her.
I think we should take them
for everything we can.
Yeah, definitely.
Oh, yes.
OK. Good.
So, who are they?
Albert... history. Where did they come
from and why did they leave America?
Emma, check out their
business interests and
anything else they may
be involved in. Mm-hm.
Sean, check out the science.
Their labs and qualifications.
I'll do hobbies and
personal interests.
Ash, the legal implications.
How the hell do they manage
to keep selling a product
that is clearly so dangerous.
Right? Let's do this.
'I'm Dr Dean Deville...
Dr Dean Deville...
'I'm Dr Dean Deville, and I'm here
today to tell you about the EYS plan.'
Dean and Dana Deville.
Oh, these guys are pros.
They've been doing what
they've been doing
in one form or another
over the years.
They always manage to stay
just one step ahead of the law.
'With Pro-Butrimol-F and active
vita-beta-retinal 5 action,
'this is probably the best vitamin
in the world ever, ever.'
In 2005, they moved
onto the internet
and became the king and
queen of the infomercial.
'Just £9.99 is all
it'll cost to end
the pain of arthritis
forever, forever.
'And say goodbye to swine
flu misery with Pig-U-Go.'
There's no evidence to suggest
any products they sell
have had scientific testing.
And as far as qualifications
are concerned, well,
they're from a mail
order place in Tupelo.
Dr Pepper is more
qualified than these two.
They circumvent any legal issues
arising from this by selling them
as health supplements and like Albert
said, always just getting away with it.
Last year, they made
profits of over £2 million
getting away with it. Most of this,
it's invested in art purchases
which they store in safety deposits,
to sell for profit at a later date.
It looks like they have
an interest in art,
but it's done purely
for financial gain.
So I think it's pretty clear
that the accumulation of money
is their main hobby, but
what's their weakness?
- Arrogance. They think
they're untouchable. - Yes.
But the UK's much more strictly
regulated than the States...
it must be getting harder for
them to stay one step ahead
of the authorities.
So, I mean if you were them,
wouldn't you be looking
for a way out now?
A way to find the big one,
the ultimate, that one last
legitimate product that
would allow you to retire?
- So that's what we offer them?
- Yes. And we use their arrogance,
this feeling they can do anything,
to blind them to what we're doing.
So what's the actual con?
We are going to sell them
a genuine wonder product that
will make them billions.
Which is?
MOCK AMERICAN ACCENT: Which is the
best diet drug in the world ever!
All right, so what's the convincer?
Yes, these people are scammers
themselves. And pretty good ones.
They'll spot an ordinary
convincer a mile off.
So in order to outsmart them,
we'll have to be very clever.
Who's heard of the Montagne scam?
The guy that stole
the Venus de Milo.
Yeah, and more importantly,
sold it again.
So, our convincer, we are going
to sell the Devilles this.
The Lucien egg, one of a
pair of Faberge eggs,
and this one is currently residing
at the Tenguiz Gallery.
- Who owns the other one?
- The Devilles do.
The eggs together are worth much
more than the sum of their parts,
so unsurprisingly, the Devilles
have made repeated attempts
to buy the Lucien egg, but Josh
Tenguiz simply isn't interested.
They also tried to sell him their
egg at a grossly inflated amount
- but still, no deal.
- So?
A few years ago, the
Devilles were interviewed
by police in connection
to the purchase
and profitable sale
of some stolen artwork.
They claimed they did it in good
faith and there were no charges.
I think the jury's still out
on that one but I think it's safe
to say these people would stop
at nothing to snaffle up a bargain.
So Emma, Sean, I want you to check
out security at the Tenguiz Gallery.
Ash, we'll go and see an old friend
of mine. Albert, Dali Macmanus.
Wherever he is, whoever he is these
days, I need you to find him.
And one last thing...
We can't rush this.
To draw these people in
successfully, we need time,
so be patient and remember that
revenge is a dish best served cold.
Freddy the Face,
long time no see.
Hello?
No, I can't talk right now.
No, I'm going into the gallery.
No, I should be quick.
OK, hold on...
Cheers, darling.
- Well, I'm done, you ready?
- Yeah, let's do it.
Oh, my goodness. Excuse me, somebody!
This is something bad here!
There's something bad
here in this bag.
Evacuate the gallery as
quickly as possible!
Come on!
ALARM RINGS
If we're thinking of trying to
steal this egg, we're in trouble.
Why?
Because everyone of the
exhibits in this gallery
is coated with an invisible chemical.
A chemical which reacts to an infra
red light if taken through any
of the 56 internal doors
and sets off the alarms.
- Basically, we're buggered.
- We're buggered.
Excellent.
DOOR BUZZER GOES
That'll be the pizza.
Could you get that please, Sean?
Yeah, don't worry about it,
I'll get it.
Just push the door mate.
Oh, my gawd, I'm gonna have
a bleedin' 'eart attack!
What's the matter, lift broken?
Nah, it's not the lifts mate,
no, I'm just a fat git.
Glutton dressed as glam.
What d'you think?
Oh, my God!
So over the whole time
we set up the convincer,
me and Mickey will be in weekly
contact with the Devilles.
But each time we meet,
Freddy the Face will
have fitted me with
a smaller fat suit.
So by the time the convincer's over,
I'll appear to have lost six stone
in as many weeks and they
will want to know how.
- What?
- It's scary how well you carry it off.
Yeah. Sure you don't want
a bit of salad now?
PHONE RINGS
- Hey, Em. - The Devilles are
attending an art launch at three.
- Oh, that's fine. We'll see you there.
- Bye.
Do you think we can make
some money out of this one?
You never know.
- Another glass?
- It's free. Of course.
- Five seconds.
- Got it.
It's Balloon Cat,
Mr Branson, yes,
and Jeff Koons is hotter
than ever right now.
I think it's a steal at half a
million, if you'll pardon the pun.
A painting like that would be
worth ten times that at auction.
Yeah, I can talk to you later.
OK, bye.
- Excuse me, did we meet?
- I don't think so.
Dana Deville, Doctor.
Danny Mullen, dealer.
Oh, you're a dealer?
You got a card? My husband and I
are always on the lookout
for exciting new pieces.
I think I may have one.
Here, there we go.
"If you don't ask, you don't get".
- And what does that mean?
- Exactly what it says.
On the face of it, some pieces
may seem tricky to source.
But I say, I definitely can't
help you if you don't ask.
But if you do ask, you get?
I haven't failed yet.
What, ever?
Nope.
What if I asked you for something
that wasn't even for sale?
As I said, I haven't failed yet.
- Did she bite?
- I don't know.
The Koons that was stolen from
Madrid last month?
- The what?
- The Koons, from L'Escuela.
It was an early one,
worth maybe a million.
Well, I think that might just
have been the man who stole it.
Then there was Jessica,
my uncle's missus,
she was fit as a fiddle.
Bang, massive heart attack -
dead before she hit the ground.
Oh.
You know, erm, it's really nice
of you to come and see me, Eddie.
I hope you don't think
I'm being rude
but do you think there's any way
we can talk about something
other than premature death
from coronary heart disease?
Oh. Oh, 'course.
Sorry.
Stupid of me.
I'm sorry, Carol.
How about deaths from cancer?
Same, really.
Yeah.
Go on then,
what's your favourite?
Hey, now you're talking.
You know when I was a little girl,
it was the pink donuts, deffo,
but you know when you get a bit older,
it's the blue ones you like...
Well, this man's clearly
a player in the art world.
Clearly.
OK, hand me his card.
We're going to have to meet.
And I said, "Belushi,
you keep taking that crap,
"it ain't gonna do you no good."
The very next day, he was dead,
and I took that as a sign.
What sort of a sign?
Primarily that he was
sicker than I thought.
And also that I had a gift and it
was my duty to share that gift
and bring wellbeing and healing
and happiness to others.
And that's when
you joined the CIA?
Five years black ops and the
extraordinary thing is that...
Oh, enough of you, my sweet!
I think our guest is
a very busy man so
let's cut to the chase, shall we?
All right.
Fine by me.
Mr Mullen, have you heard of a
Faberge egg called the Laurentian?
Hmm... 19th century,
it's not really my speciality.
Well, we own it, it's one of a pair.
The other's called the Lucien Egg
and it's in the Tenguiz Gallery.
Now they were conceived as a
pair, they were made as a pair.
And I'd imagine worth a
whole lot more as a pair.
Great minds, Mr Mullen,
great minds.
Except that we've approached the
owner on a number of occasions
to buy the egg and he refuses.
Drivels on about its aesthetic beauty,
how it makes him feel
alive just to hold it
and we've run out of patience now.
And so, as requested, we've got
four words for you, Mullens.
Four simple words that
require one simple answer.
Can. You. Acquire. The...
Sorry, five words.
Can you get us the egg?
Well, if we already know that
Tenguiz won't sell it to you,
there really is only one
way of obtaining it.
Indeed.
OK.
As I say, this isn't really my area,
so I'm guessing that
each egg on its own is worth
maybe a quarter of a million?
As a pair, maybe three quarters?
The Tenguiz is a very secure
gallery. It would take organising,
which is expensive. I have a team
of trusted experts I always use.
I'd want 50K, cash on delivery.
Do you know who we are, Mr Mullen?
Of course, I always do my research.
Then you'll know we're
successful business people,
who did not get where they are
by being taken for fools.
And believe me, I have
serious respect for that.
But I'd need to know you trust
me or this won't work at all.
Now, excuse me,
I'm late for my next meeting.
We're not saying we don't trust you.
OK, how's this?
I'll involve you in the planning.
But this will take
some time to organise.
So, we'll have regular briefings,
updates, at yours, at mine,
wherever you want.
If you don't like something and you
have a better idea, we'll change it.
What do you think?
Weekly briefings.
You'll thank us for our input.
Then I think we have a deal.
I think we do.
You won't regret it.
I'll be in touch.
What time do you call this?
I'm sorry but I got held up.
Stop with the excuses.
Three quarters of a mil?
More like two.
Nearly £2 million profit!
The best art theft deal
in the world. Ever!
'There are four types of fat.
'Good fat, bad fat,
thin fat and fat fat.'
When setting up the convincer, Ash
and I will be in weekly contact
with the Devilles,
but when we meet them,
Freddy The Face will have
fitted Ash with a smaller fat suit.
So by the time the
convincer is over, he'll
appear to have lost six
stone in as many weeks.
'I'm Doctor Dean Deville,
I'm Doctor Dean Deville,
'and I'm here to tell you
about the EYS plan.'
The stakes are high.
Breaking into The Tenguiz Gallery
to get the egg is a tall order.
OK, that's how you get in.
'You, too, can be part of the
Eat Yourself Slender Plan.'
So, the chemical the
objects are sprayed with
is called Aceto-Styteline.
It reacts with the infra-red on
the doors and sets the alarms off.
But if you subject Styteline to a
15-nanosecond blast of black light...
It temporarily changes
its refractive index.
SHE GASPS
'The Eat Yourself Slender Plan lets
you eat the good, thin fat you like,
'whilst at the same time
reducing your bad fat fat.'
See you soon.
THEY LAUGH
I got to change my lens prescription.
Through the ducts
is the best way to get in.
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
Er, sorry, here are the, er...
Ah, good. Good. Now,
this is what we were missing.
'The Eat Yourself Slender Plan!
'Because the rest of
your life starts today.'
- You sure you're ready for
the break-in? - Yeah. 100%.
See you at the penthouse
tomorrow, eight o'clock, sharp.
We'll supply the popcorn.
My team should be arriving
at the gallery now.
They know this has to
go like clockwork.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
- Champagne?
- Thanks.
Please, have a seat.
Sailing bloody close to the wind,
bringing them in here.
The nearer we draw them to us, the more
they'll trust us. According to Mickey.
Ah, this is Claude. He takes
care of all our security concerns.
Ah, the old "in and out" guy, huh?
OK, we're in.
There they are.
Right.
OK. Let's do it.
OK, I'm here.
OK, cameras 19 and 24
will freeze when I press enter.
But the system's on an automatic
reboot every three minutes,
which I can't override.
'So, you have exactly 180 seconds
from when I say, OK?'
And, go!
Here comes the black light now.
Come on, come on.
How much longer does he have?
45 seconds.
Come on, fella, come on.
Now the moment of truth.
The black light should
block the security alarm.
Wow. Ha!
It actually worked.
What did I say?
Come on, Sean.
Eight, seven...
Six, five, four, three, two, one.
Uh! Ha!
Nice one!
So, give us 24 hours, let the dust
settle, and we'll meet up tomorrow.
- You know, Mullen, Bill Clinton
once said to me... - Shut up, Dean.
- No, Bill never said that.
- Goodnight, Mr Mullen.
Goodnight!
Softly, softly.
I bet you haven't seen
one this big before.
I don't think I have. And what
a funny colour, innit, it's just...
Can I have a quick word
please, sir?
Yeah, sure, yeah.
You like Carol, don't you?
Yeah, well, I do a bit,
yeah. Y'know.
She'll be ready to leave in a few
days. And she'll need someone.
To help her change her lifestyle,
to help her lose weight
and get fit again.
And I was just wondering that,
if you did it together
you might find that you wouldn't need
all the cakes and the sweets and...
As you can see, it's got
a time and a date on it.
So I'm hoping that'll reveal
who paid for five coffees,
four flapjacks and a croissant
here, Thursday last.
Beautiful, isn't it?
I think you and I could do a lot
more business together, Mr Mullen.
I very much hope so.
We will most definitely be in touch.
Oh, and remember...
TOGETHER: "If you don't ask..."
THEY LAUGH
What do you feed
your staff on, Mr Mullen?
I'm sorry?
Buddy, you're either on a hell of
a diet or you have terminal cancer.
Oh. You're right.
He has lost some weight.
Six stone, actually.
- What did you say?
- In as many weeks.
Six stone in six weeks?
How?
- Oh, no, that's private.
- Oh. Don't be like that.
You wouldn't want to make
little Dana cross, would you?
Weight loss is our business.
It's a new diet drink.
A diet drink?
Yeah.
Just one spoonful, and bingo.
What diet drink? Where did
you get it, this diet drink?
How come I haven't heard
about this new diet drink?
Tell me, or you'll be losing
a couple more ounces right here.
Cos it's not for sale.
Er, cos it's still being tested.
Cos I sort of... nicked it.
My missus works as a lab
assistant for Spitz-Kleinman.
They're a pharmaceutical company.
We know who they are.
Yeah, and occasionally she'd bring
some of her work home with her.
Anyway, she was talking about
this new weight-loss product
they'd been testing on rats,
called, er, Reducio.
It had been a bit of a
disappointment, she said,
so... she bought a few bottles of it
home to do some more work on and...
It's OK, Phillips, we
won't tell anyone. Go on.
Well, I just borrowed a bottle.
I've always struggled with me weight
and, well, I wanted to see
if this was the one, you know,
the one diet product
that actually worked.
And boy, did it?
Yeah, just one spoonful a day.
You know, you can still
eat anything you want.
And the fat...
It all comes out in your pores.
You sweat it out!
Yeah, you sweat all the fat out!
That is genius.
And what did your wife say when
she saw how much you'd lost?
Well my wife didn't say anything.
She didn't say anything?
You were a freak!
When you stood on the scales,
it just said, "To be continued".
She must have said something!
No. No, no, cos she didn't know.
You see, just before
I took the bottle,
she told me she was leaving me
for a body-builder from Purley.
She left that night.
DANA GASPS
Oh! Oh! Phillips! Excellent news!
What!?
That you have lost so much
weight is excellent news!
But let me just confirm one thing...
that your wife has absolutely no idea
the product worked so well for you?
No. No, none at all.
No.
Do you know when Spitz-Kleinman were
planning on starting human trials?
Well, er, it could be a
matter of months, she said.
Or even a year.
Do you, I mean to say, that is...
Do you think we could have
an incy-wincy little look
at this bottle?
Maurice?
Oh, I mean, I'd love to.
Dana.
HE INHALES DEEPLY
But I finished the last of it
two days ago, I'm afraid.
OK, no problem.
Well, why don't we
pop into the kitchen
and get you some lard
or refined sugars
or whatever it is you
generally like to eat,
while we have a nice little
chat with Mr Mullen?
Do you have any idea how much
a product like that could be worth?
One that actually does
what we say it does?
We could make billions!
Literally billions!
We sell it as a health
supplement, "aiding
weight loss", to
bypass the regs.
And beat Spitz to the market!
No more looking over our shoulders,
no more fighting off lawsuits.
Instead, we'd be feted,
we'd be honoured!
The Nobel Prize for services to fat!
Arise, Sir Dean and Dana!
Of Deville!
THEY GASP
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt, but aren't
you forgetting something?
He used it all, remember?
You don't actually have the drug.
What do have is a man who
successfully broke into
one of the most secure
galleries in London.
How much harder can it be
to break in to a laboratory?
- And steal the formula?
- Why not?
HE LAUGHS
Oh, no.
Equal share, the three of us.
This is big pharma, you're talking
about. Those guys are scary.
We pay you a flat fee, then.
You just help us steal it, don't
get involved in any of the rest.
Sorry.
- Same as for the egg.
- Not interested.
- 100, then. - Nope.
- OK, double.
200,000 sterling. COD.
Then you're out.
A quarter of a million,
and I'll do it.
Quarter of a million it is.
But this time, he'll
come along for the ride.
What?!
You want Dean to take
part in the break-in?
Just as an observer.
I want to be absolutely certain
that we're handing over a quarter
of a brick for the real deal.
- Er, sweetheart, can...
- Be quiet, Dean. OK!
It's your money.
But as an observer,
nothing more.
That's a kayaking course.
That one's rock climbing
up one of them walls.
Oh, and that's a
ballroom dancing course.
"The Merengue, the Salsa,
the American Smooth."
Blimey, just reading about
them's making me hungry.
But that's the thing, isn't it?
Nothing wrong with having a blow-out,
if you're burning off the calories.
Yeah.
I know, I know, I know.
What? Why would you not even try it?
Just one of 'em, surely.
- And why wouldn't you?
- I dunno. It's just...
What?
Oh, it's, going on
your own, isn't it?
It's the same for me.
If I had someone to go
with, I'd do it in a shot.
- Would you, really?
- Like a shot.
So don't you know
anyone, then, that we
can ring and ask, you
know, to take you?
Yeah, I do know this one fella.
He's a bit of a numpty, but
I just think he's painfully shy.
But I really like him
and I'd love to spend some more time
with him when I get out of here.
Oh. OK, yeah.
Pass us a phone,
I'll give him a bell.
Yeah, all right, there you go.
It's ringing.
Mine's ringing now.
Hello?
- Hi, is this Eddie?
- Yeah, speaking.
Hi, Eddie, it's Carol.
I'd like to know, when I get out,
will you go ballroom dancing with me?
Hello?
Anybody here?
Service!
Cor, disgraceful behaviour, innit?
Just can't get the staff these days.
So.
All we have to do,
is get in to one of their labs,
plant the formula inside it,
and get out of the lab,
so that we can get back in again
to take out what we've just put in.
- Simple!
- Ash, can you handle the data?
I've just lost six stone,
I am strong, I am empowered,
I am beautiful.
- Is that a yes?
- Go on, then.
Sean, we'll need
some promotional stuff.
Albert, fake IDs?
No problem.
Emma, we need you inside.
Now, they're looking for domestics.
Give them a call.
And I need to work out a way
to get us undisturbed access
to a lab for an hour or so.
The key, in jobs like this one,
is to contrive a way
to walk in through the front
door, find the right lab,
take the formula,
and walk out again, calmly,
without attracting attention.
Here you are.
And right now, I have a team
of experts working very hard
to make that plan work.
Dean.
You and I will be officers from
the National lnstitute for
Health and Clinical Excellence,
come to do a spot-check
on their clinical facilities.
Once we're inside reception, we will
tell security we need to inspect
two labs, that we will need
for no longer than 15 minutes.
We'll also tell them we
need those labs cleared.
Dean, you and I will have IDs and
numbers to call for verification,
though any call they make
will be diverted to one of my team.
You've done this before.
HE SMIRKS
All we need to do now is find out which
lab Reducio is being developed in.
My IT experts are hacking
their mainframe to find out...
so that we know which lab
we want to "randomly" check.
Once we have that information,
we're good to go.
- Healthy lifestyle, healthy fridge.
- Oh, Eddie.
Thank you so much.
You're such a lovely man.
Better than a kick in the teeth...
Sean Kennedy?
Yeah?
DS Rivet, Hoxton nick.
I think we need to have
a little chat.
Oh, no.
What the hell's happened?
They're questioning Sean
about the Tenguiz break-in.
Seems he dropped something
that IDs him.
- Oh, my God. Is he going to blab?
- No, of course not.
What's the problem, then?
Kid'll be out in ten,
still got time to make
something of himself.
The problem is that the police
are watching us like hawks...
so we're not going to go ahead
with the Spitz job.
Any of us.
It's suicide.
He's right, I'm sorry, it's over.
Wait!
They're not watching us.
They don't even know about us.
And?
Oh, no.
You mean we do it?!
The two of us?
The break-in?
Why not?
We could wear earpieces.
Mullen could talk us through it.
What do you say, Mullen?
- I say you're insane.
- Really? How hard can it be?
Honey, it could...
Shut up! Come on, why not?
We didn't learn this
business overnight.
- It takes years of experience.
- You underestimate me.
You have no idea of some of the
things I've done to make money.
We've never been beaten,
never failed.
Well, you have now.
It's a crazy idea.
Fine. Walk away from
250,000 sterling then.
When we're so close.
So close!
Come on, Mullen!
We can make this work.
Remember how good that
money felt in your hands.
OK.
OK, but we have to move fast, while
they're preoccupied with Sean.
HE CLICKS HIS TEETH
OK, I confess, I can't take it
any longer, I did it.
But of course you did it.
We all know you did it.
Yeah, I did it.
I went to the Tenguiz gallery
and I dropped a bit of litter
on the floor.
I wonder if you'll find it
so funny standing in the dock,
facing down a ten stretch.
Testing, testing.
Cor-blimey guv'nor, it's a real
pea-souper, make no mistake.
Remind me why we thought
this was a good idea.
Dean, they do have
American employees.
Cuppa Rosy-Lee, don't mind
if I do! Ta very much!
I bet Sean's more relaxed
than me right now.
Maybe this time, this time,
we may have gone too far.
Don't say a freakin' word
or I swear I'll never do the
thing with the mango again.
Mango?
Jessica Amwell, Paul Banstead, National
lnstitute for Clinical Excellence.
We're doing a lab spot-check in light
of the Strep-C outbreak in Munich
and we've selected two of your labs
at random, numbers three and 14.
'To inspect, we'll need uninterrupted
access for approximately 15 minutes.
'You will wish to confirm our IDs.'
You can talk to our authentication
department on this number.
Thank you so much.
MOBILE RINGS
Good morning,
National lnstitute for Health
and Clinical Excellence
Authentication department.
How can I help you?
'Emma? They're clearing everyone out
of the lab. Put the files in place.'
We had a scientist up in Scotland last
year who caught a new flesh-eating bug.
By the time they got to
him, all that was left
was one thumb and an earlobe.
True story!
Not too obvious, Em.
We're good from here, thank you.
Mullen, we're in.
'OK, now what have you got?
' Three computers, I'm on the first.
Opening it up.
'OK, I can't see anything,
'I can't see anything.'
What am I looking for?
Facts?
Come on, come on, come on.
Are we 100% sure
this is the right lab?
Let me try another computer.
OK, second computer.
- Security?
- Go ahead.
- There's a problem at reception.
- On my way.
Come on, come on!
Hang on.
I got something here, too.
Reducio Optimum 7?
'That's it, that's it.'
It's here, too.
These guys have got
no idea on branding.
It should be Fat-U-Sweat.
'Perspira-Go'.
'Or Fatooze.'
Guys, can we just download
the file and get the hell out?
Now?
Right, what have you got?
Look, this doesn't match.
Security breach.
We've got it!
So near, so very, very near.
This is a very strange sensation.
I'm rooting for the mark.
It's all gone weird.
The Americans
are on the third floor!
(Try the back exit.)
'Boys, the third floor.'
THEY WHOOP AND HOLLER WITH DELIGHT
Come on!
THEY CACKLE GLEEFULLY
'Woo! Woo!
'Go, go, go!'
Your money?
My money.
You... moron!
You didn't seriously think
we were going to give you a quarter
of a million G's, did you?
Why not, we had a deal?
I'll tell you why not.
Because we did all the hard work.
That's why not.
- I think you're being unfair.
- Really?
I did a lot of preparation
behind the scenes.
I did some work you didn't even see.
I don't give a rat's ass what
you did behind the scenes.
We have the formula...
it's being made up
right now... and we don't
need you any more!
Boo-hoo-hoo!
Seriously, what sort of
idiots do you think we are?
The sort who thought I was
attaching a microphone
to that brooch when
actually it was a camera.
A camera that filmed you and your
husband breaking in to Spitz-Kleinman.
Cup of Rosy-Lee, don't mind
if I do, ta very much!
The footage of which
I've put on a DVD
and have given to my assistant
who is at this moment
outside Scotland Yard
waiting for my phone call.
Those sorts of idiots.
250 grand, cash, please.
I almost feel bad.
Yeah, cos they think
that's the worst thing
that's going to happen to them today.
You know,
it almost seems unfair.
Almost!
THEY LAUGH
Are you sure this is
the right formula?
I stole it myself, so I think
I know what I'm doing.
Now shut up and give me the bottle!
- I want to sweat some fat.
- Yeah, me, too! Huh!
You're definitely sweating.
Oh, my...
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Cos that formula's just an emetic.
HE STIFLES VOMITING
A very powerful one, granted.
HE RETCHES VIOLENTLY
But an emetic just the same.
SHE PANTS
We just gave him 250 grand
for something that makes you sick?!
Well, at least we still
have the egg, honey.
HOARSELY: 50 grand for an egg
that's now worth 20 times that.
He may think he had us,
he may think he was smart,
but we're still way up
on the deal!
Who's the idiot now, Mullen?
Who's laughing now!
HE RETCHES
Excuse me?
Is that meant to be in there?
It's believed the egg might have
been accidentally moved by a cleaner
or even a practical joker,
but however it happened,
Lord Tenguiz declared
he was delighted to
have his egg back.
As you can see, the egg is now...
Mmm. I'm no legal expert, but I'd
imagine it's quite difficult
to charge someone for stealing
something that hasn't been stolen.
Wouldn't you say?
'The egg is now back in its rightful
place, and what a piece of art it is.
'It was created... '
But, but, no!
He stole it! He said,
if you used the black light...
If you subject Styteline to a
15-nanosecond blast of black light,
it temporarily changes
the refractive index.
And if you believe that load of old
cobblers, you'll believe anything.
We saw him leave the room with it.
We saw him leave the room with it!
No!
We do the cons!
We're the ones who do the conning!
This really has to be
your best work. The best.
We're the ones who do
the goddamn conning!
So they had to do
the robbery themselves,
or they could have
gone to the police.
Or come after us.
But now, they can't do either.
Yeah, but how would you know
for sure they would offer to do it?
Well, their arrogance,
their greed, their need?
All we had to do was convince them
none of us could do the job.
So you dropped the receipt
deliberately. Unbelievable!
How you lot pull it off,
I've no idea.
Oh! Says the man who pulled off the
greatest con of the 21st century.
It's quite remarkable, Eddie.
You managed to convince Carol
you're an attractive man!
Oi! We think he's a bit
of all right, don't we Carol?
I won't hear a word
against him. Mwah!
OTHERS: Oooh!
All right, how about a toast,
how about a toast?
To Eddie, to Carol, to all of us...
and our good health.
ALL: Our good health!
Hang on.
Crudites, anyone?
Low-fat dip?
He's a friend of
chairman Mao, isn't he?
Ooh!
Hey, Chinese... now you're talking.
Who's got a menu?
Cheers, all.
Cheers!
GLASSES CLINK
sync and corrections by Bellows
www.addic7ed.com