My siblings and I
are the first vampires
in all of history,
the Originals.
300 years ago,
we helped build New Orleans.
Now we have returned
to find the city has a new king,
one who rules with the aid
of a powerful girl.
They have taken possession
of my brother Elijah.
A coven of witches
want this girl for themselves.
The seek to enlist my help,
using my unborn child
as leverage,
though I suspect they have
ulterior motives.
So I've made a plan
of my own.
I will free my brother and
reclaim the city for our family.
Then I will be King.
Over the course of my life,
I've encountered no shortage
of those who would presume
to speak of good and evil.
Such terms mean nothing.
People do what is
in their best interest,
regardless of who gets hurt.
Is it evil to take
what one wants,
to satisfy hunger
even if doing so
will cause another suffering?
What some would call evil
I believe to be
an appropriate response
to a harsh and unfair world.
No offense,
but I'm not sure I follow
why you've
invited me here.
Because I enjoy
your company,
and I sense you have
the capacity
for understanding
someone of my complexity.
You see, I returned
to New Orleans
to investigate a threat
posed against me.
What I found was
a young woman,
pregnant, in need
of protection.
My brother, always
the do-gooder,
tried to manipulate
me into helping her.
He thought it might
redeem me.
Trouble is, I've
since learned
of another young women,
a girl really,
one with vast potential,
held in captivity
by a tyrant.
I want to help both
of these women...
Protect one
and free the other.
So tell me, Cami,
does that sound
evil to you?
I don't believe in
evil as a diagnosis.
I think you have unstable
personal relationships,
stress-related
paranoia,
chronic anger issues,
fear of abandonment.
I think you could benefit from
talking to someone professionally.
I think I prefer
to talk to you,
so I'm going to
offer you a job
as my stenographer.
Ok. What are we
writing?
My memoirs of course.
Someone should
know my story,
and it will give us time
to discuss
other riveting subjects
like your
handsome suitor Marcel.
Excuse me.
My private life is...
Your private life is,
as it turns out,
essential to my plans.
You see, Marcel
wants you,
and because of that,
he will trust you,
which serves me.
The thing is
the French quarter is
on the verge of war.
On the one side,
there's me,
and on the other Marcel
and an army of vampires.
What?!
You're frightened.
Don't be.
I'm not scared anymore.
That's amazing.
How did you...
It's called compulsion.
It's a neat bit
of vampire trickery.
I'll tell you
all about it,
but first, let's talk
a little more about Marcel.
Sucker's resilient.
He's like a cockroach
in a suit.
Doesn't matter. Time to give
old Elijah back to Klaus anyway.
You asked me to figure out
how to kill the Originals.
I'm not done.
Silver dagger
hurts them,
but that's it.
Davina, we've been
through this.
Klaus saved my life.
I owe him one.
Since he wants
his brother back...
Tonight's the annual Dauphine
street music festival.
I want to go.
Please.
The whole point of you
being up here
is so you're never
spotted out there.
You know what's smack in the
middle of Dauphine street...
Sophie Deveraux,
pain-in-the-ass witch,
and you know what the witches
will do to you if they find you.
But you control
the witches.
Make her go away.
Marcel,
it's one night.
I said no.
I do anything you say,
but sometimes, I think you
forget what I'm capable of.
Did you know I can make
someone's blood boil?
All I have to do
is focus.
Fine. We compromise,
all right?
You going out alone
too dangerous,
but I'll introduce you to a friend
of mine that's gonna be there,
all right, nice lady.
You two are really
gonna hit it off.
Hello, Cami.
How is it that when
you come up to me now
and no one else
is around
I suddenly remember
that you just told me
you're a vampire and
you're mind controlling me,
and then you leave,
and I go back to thinking
you're just
some hot guy
with a cute accent
and money to burn
on your
sprawling memoir?
Well, that's how
compulsion works, love.
Yeah, but what's
happening?
Is it hypnosis, are my neurons
being shut down somehow?
You're always
the curious scholar.
Let's talk about Marcel.
You said you have a
little information for me.
He's bringing someone
to the music festival tonight,
a girl he's mentoring.
Apparently she's going
through a hard time,
rebelling against authority,
anger issues,
that sort of thing.
I guess with my
psych degree
he figured I could
set her straight,
but I said no.
I'm gonna go ahead
and insist
you change
your answer to yes.
You're gonna force me
to do this, aren't you?
Why even bother
with politeness?
Because I like you.
I like the way
your mind works.
Under different
circumstances,
I think we might
be friends.
However, I don't
have the luxury
of passing up
tonight's opportunity.
You see, in addition
to being Marcel's
rather potent
secret weapon,
this girl Davina is
holding my brother captive.
In other words,
the girl needs
you help.
Call Marcel,
tell him you'll be
happy to oblige.
I told you, Agnes,
I feel great.
You are overdue
for a checkup.
What am I gonna do, pop into the
quarter for a quick ultrasound?
A pregnant werewolf
escorted by a witch?
Nothing to see here.
A lot of women
would kill to have a child.
Strikes me as odd that you're
not taking better care of yours.
I know a doctor out in
bayou off the beaten path.
Now I took the liberty
of making an appointment
for you tonight
after hours, just us.
Vampires will never
get word of it.
Ok. Fine.
Bayou baby doctor
it is.
Please, sister, tell me
you're not still at it
with the Internet
search.
How does one begin
anyway,
just type in
"anonymous attic"?
Someone has to
find Elijah,
even if I have to search
every bloody attic
in New Orleans.
Like looking
for a needle
in a rather large pile
of needles.
I remember details about
the attic Marcel took me to.
There were shutters
on the windows
behind Elijah's coffin.
Well, that should
narrow it down immensely.
Myself, I prefer
actual strategy
as opposed to
mind-numbing labor.
Marcel's delay
in returning our brother
makes me suspect he's no longer
in charge of the situation.
If Davina's loyalty
to Marcel is strained,
perhaps the young witch
will be open to
discussing
a new alliance.
As usual, your power grabs
are more important
than rescuing
your brother.
I prefer to think of it as killing
two birds with one stone...
Rob Marcel
of his secret weapon,
bring our brother home.
Hey, Diego.
Right. So, um, any
way to fast track
the whole getting
a daylight ring thing?
You get a daylight right when you
get invited to the inner circle.
For you, it may
never happen.
Yeah, but there's
an opening, right?
I mean, now that Thierry's,
like, you know...
You shut up
about Thierry, all right?
He didn't deserve
what he got.
Marcel was just
showing off for Klaus.
Can't wait till his
ancient ass is out of here.
You and me both.
Look alive, boys.
We got ourselves
one high-class
Original vampire.
Hmm. A real charmer.
What if I told you that
I could help you out
with your Klaus problem
in exchange
for the tiniest bit
of gossip?
Like what?
You might have heard the
rumors that Marcel and I
were quite the item
back in the day.
He seems to
have moved on,
and I would like to
know with whom.
You've seen him
with the bartender.
What, that plain Jane
that he carries on with?
Well, only a blind man
would choose her over me.
There must be another
girl in his harem.
Look. I just need the
tiniest bit of closure,
and then I can leave
New Orleans,
and I'll be sure to take
Klaus with me,
which, let's face it, would make
your life a whole lot easier.
Look. Marcel's got
a full plate.
If he's seeing
some other honey,
she's somewhere
in the quarter.
She's probably close by,
and that, my lady,
is all I got.
Big event tonight,
a lot of people drinking,
a lot of eyes
watching.
I don't want
any trouble,
which means
no witches.
Send word through
the cauldron.
Any witches come here,
we kill them,
and while we're
at it, no Originals.
I don't like how Rebekah's
been snooping around.
I got my girl Cami coming,
her and a little friend
of hers.
I want eyes on them
at all times,
eyes only, all right?
I don't want anybody going
anywhere near either of them.
Everybody's got a post,
everybody keeps an eye out.
You cool?
Come on!
So is it everything
you hoped for?
Yeah!
So we should probably
go over the rules.
I won't talk to anyone
about anything,
I won't say anything
about witches or vampires
or Originals or you.
But you said you weren't
gonna hover.
This is
the doctor's office.
Dr. Paige is only
this far out
because Marcel's men kept
terrorizing her patients.
Go. She won't bite.
Send them in now
and tell them to do it quickly.
It's good to see you.
I was worried you thought
I was some hot head
after that display
at the masquerade.
We all have
our hot-headed moments.
Anyway, I'm almost done
here until cleanup,
so the two of us girls
can hang out
if you need to go
schmooze or whatever.
You know, he was supposed to stop
hovering, like, 10 minutes ago.
You see what I mean?
Authority issues.
I'll go talk
to the mayor.
He actually knows how
to show some respect.
So what's his name?
Hot guy
with the fiddle.
Tim.
I knew he'd be here.
He always performs
at these kind of things.
How long have you two
known each other?
Since we were 10.
I had to leave school,
and I didn't get
to say good-bye,
so I was just hoping
to talk to him tonight.
That's it!
Church is closed.
You want your
horror fix,
go take
a ghost tour.
I don't much care
for ghosts.
I am, however, fascinated
by window shutters.
I've been on a town tour
of them all day.
I noticed the windows
of your attic have shutters.
Are you really
interested in shutters?
I can assure it's
my current life obsession.
What's your name?
Father Kieran,
and you are?
Mildly curious.
What happened here?
St. Anne's used to be the
heart of the neighborhood.
Its been abandoned
for a while now
since the night
of the massacre.
9 seminary students were
killed by one of their own.
You're standing
on blood.
I'm not squeamish.
Where's the attic?
Like I said, the church is closed.
Where is the attic?
Past the sacristy
up the stairs.
Thank you.
Now forget I was here.
I knew it.
What the bloody hell?
Rebekah,
language, please.
Elijah!
What is all this?
You don't remember?
You and I went to the
opera house together.
It was your first foray back
into New Orleans society
after Klaus removed
the dagger from you.
It's a memory that
only you and I share.
Also I need you to know it's
not another of Davina's tricks.
Well, how are you
even awake?
Davina withdrew
the dagger,
unaware that doing so
even once
would negate
its power.
In a few hours,
I shall be as good as new.
So put me back
into the attic,
and we can find a way
to get you out.
I'm afraid I'm not
quite ready
to leave yet, Rebekah.
This girl Davina,
she's curious,
willful, too.
Soon I shall be able
to speak to her,
perhaps even to propose
a truce of some kind,
so if we can end
this war
between the vampires
and the witches,
we'll be able to
eliminate the threat
to Hayley and her baby.
Perhaps then Niklaus
and our entire family
can finally know peace.
In the meantime,
I need you to look after Hayley.
She is our family
now, Rebekah,
so I need her
and her unborn child
to fall underneath
our protection.
Swear to me, Rebekah.
I swear.
Your baby's heart rate
is perfect.
I knew it.
She's a tough one like her mom.
That's a unique
birthmark.
We're pretty much
done here, right?
Your blood pressure's
a bit high.
I've got something
for it.
Uh, you know, I'm actually
not that good with pills.
Well, me neither,
truth be told.
Aah!
Hello, Tim.
I believe you and I
share an acquaintance.
Be a good lad and help
me send her a message.
Well, he couldn't
have gone far.
He just got offstage
a minute ago.
It doesn't matter.
This was a stupid idea anyway.
No, it wasn't.
Davina...
Just forget it.
Tell her this is
from one of the musicians.
She'll want to leave,
and you're going to help
her slip out the back exit
so Marcel doesn't see.
Whatever you do,
don't let her out
of your sight.
Wait, Davina!
I can't do this.
Hey.
Tim, I got your note.
I got your
text message.
Thanks for agreeing
to meet here.
It's so amazing
to see you.
I can't even believe
I'm standing here right now.
I just...
Wow!
So where have
you been,
and why did you
want to meet here?
It's so creepy,
all the terrible stuff
that happened.
I don't know.
I kind of like it.
You know, it's quiet.
I mean, the place can't
be bad for all time
just because one bad thing
happened, right?
Wait. No. All right.
Back up.
So where... one day,
you just stop coming to school,
and then it's like
you just vanished.
There was an emergency, and I
needed to take care of some things.
Oh. Are you ok?
I mean, you look ok.
You look great
actually.
So are you coming
back to school?
No.
But I need you to know
that even though I was away,
I miss you.
I miss seeing you
at school
and seeing you play
your violin.
Well...
This place does have
good acoustics.
The boy has a gift.
You can't compel someone
to play like that.
I know what you are.
It's crazy to me,
but at least it makes sense,
but this massacre was just
a pointless, brutal thing.
In all your life,
have you ever heard
of anything like that,
a good man,
an aspiring priest
just goes on a killing
spree out of nowhere.
I've seen
quite a lot
in my time.
The world is
a rather awful place.
Best to meet it
on its own terms.
No. The world
isn't awful.
People are
not awful.
They want
to be good.
Something makes
them bad,
something breaks
them down,
makes them snap.
There are always signs,
symptoms before someone
has a psychotic break.
The guy who did this
had none of them.
He didn't drink,
he didn't do drugs.
You're well-informed
on the matter.
You knew him,
didn't you?
His name was Sean.
He was my brother,
my twin actually.
I can't sleep.
I dream about
what happened,
and I hate it.
I hate that
I couldn't help him.
We all must stand alone
against our demons.
What if someday his
demons become mine, too?
I have some business
I should attend to,
but before I do,
you should go.
Enjoy the music,
put this out of your mind.
Marcel.
Father Kieran,
welcome back.
I wasn't sure when
you'd be coming home.
I can tell,
judging by what's going
on in my church attic.
Oh. I didn't think
you'd mind.
Lord knows, I'd done
you a favor or two.
I take it you know
the Originals have returned.
The sister Rebekah,
I saw her earlier,
snooping around the church,
asking about the attic.
She doesn't know
I take vervain.
You got a problem
on your hands.
No disrespect for
the grieving process,
for you and your church,
but just so I know,
are you here to help,
or are you just gonna
drop in with criticism?
Never forget, Marcel,
that you live
in this city by the grace
of those that know
your secret
and tolerate you.
And this city thrives
because of me
and my people.
Anytime you need
a reminder of that,
just let me know.
Marcel, Diego said
he lost eyes on the girls.
To be continued.
You two are
absolutely adorable.
It warms my heart,
it really does,
but I do need a word
with the young lady,
so, Tim,
go sit down,
count to 100,000.
Quietly now.
There's a good boy.
I assume you know
who I am.
Then let's get right to it,
shall we?
Your current dilemma strikes
me as a case of poor alliances.
You're loyal to Marcel,
and yet he keeps you
tucked away in an attic.
Surely you'd prefer just
a little bit more freedom,
and yet Marcel
keeps you prisoner.
Marcel doesn't
keep me prisoner.
He keeps me safe.
He's my friend.
Well, I have
no doubt he is,
but for a girl caught in a war
between the witches and the vampires,
I might be
a better friend.
I would keep you safe,
and I'd allow you
your freedom.
If Marcel could do that,
why hasn't he
done so already,
and it does
beg the question
if Marcel can't
protect you,
then what of those
you care about?
If anyone tries to hurt
anyone I care about,
I'll kill them.
Well, then.
Sounds like you don't
need Marcel at all.
Perhaps you've
suspected it all along.
Your dear friend
Marcel tricks you
into doing
his bidding,
and all the while, you
rot in an attic alone
while young Timothy
moves on with his life.
You feel that?
That's your blood
starting to boil.
Such a shame
to lose him
just as you found
him again,
and I really did admire
your skill with that violin.
Don't you dare
hurt him!
Well, I hope I won't
have to, sweetheart,
but then that
depends on you.
Let him go now!
You should know I don't
do well with demands.
Ugh! Aah!
Unh!
Impressive, but you don't
want to fight me, love.
Innocent people
have a way
of winding up dead.
Please let me go.
Your choice,
little witch.
Swear allegiance
to me alone,
and the boy lives.
Stand against me...
Aah!
I have to say
I'm impressed.
How'd you find me?
Your text got me
halfway,
vamp hearing
did the rest.
Who are they?
Witches, warlocks,
whatever.
There are more of them.
Run!
If I had a dollar
for every mess
my family's gotten
me into.
Rebekah!
Where is she?
Where's Davina?
She went to meet a boy
in St. Anne's church.
Stay here in case
she comes back.
What the hell?
Hayley? Hayley?
Tim.
What do you mean
she's missing?
What do you
think I mean?
There's blood and bodies
everywhere,
someone's ripped
this lot to shreds,
and there's no
smart-aleck pregnant girl.
Keep looking.
I'm on my way.
Please don't hurt me.
It wasn't
my intent to,
but sadly,
I've run out of time to play nice.
Tim? Oh, no!
No, please.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean
to hurt you.
One of the tragic
consequences of war,
innocent bystanders.
What terrible guilt
you'll have to live with,
young Timothy's blood
on your hands.
Get away from him!
Now, now, let's not
be hasty.
After all, I can
heal him.
All you have to do...
Is ask.
Please.
For you, Davina,
with pleasure.
You will forget everything that
happened after the concert,
including the fact
that you saw Davina.
What? No.
If he remembers
seeing you,
he might come looking.
If the witches learn
of him,
if they know you have
a weakness,
then poor Tim might
end up as leverage
in an awful scheme
to control you again.
Ok. Come on.
Up you come.
Take your violin case
with you.
You'll remember losing the instrument
backstage after the performance.
You really should be
more careful.
All fixed.
Now you owe me
a favor.
Davina.
What happened?
What are you
doing here?
I live her, remember?
Well, you abandoned
your quest for power
to help out
your family.
Having an off day?
Who took her, Rebekah?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
Then who killed
her attackers?
I don't know.
I had an arrow in my heart.
If it wasn't Hayley
who killed them, then...
Lovely. Perhaps her cousins
will know where she is.
Hayley, what happened?
Tell me what happened.
I can't remember.
You've completely healed.
There's not
a scratch on you.
One of the perks
of being a werewolf, remember?
No. Not that fast
Leave her alone.
It's the baby,
the vampire blood,
Klaus' blood in your system.
It can heal
any wound.
Your own child
healed you.
How did you escape?
You were outnumbered,
unarmed.
Those men were
ripped to shreds.
I think it was
the wolf.
I think it's trying
to protect me.
The witches were
supposed to protect you.
When I get my hands
on Sophie Deveraux...
It wasn't Sophie.
It was Agnes.
Fine. Agnes, Sophie.
It's all the same to me.
I'll slaughter
the lot of them.
Not if Elijah
gets there first.
Elijah?
Did you find him?
He's been in touch,
and he has a plan.
All he asked is that
we take care of you.
Hey. So can we
go home now?
I'd really like to
sleep for a few days.
Whoa!
I've got you, love.
I've got you.
I was crystal clear...
Eyes on my girls
at all times.
What? Girl's little friend
sneaks away from your party,
and that's my fault?
What, Marcel, you gonna send
me to the garden now, too?
When he wakes up,
tell him that an apology
would have gotten him
a lot further
than his attitude.
Awful what happened
at the church.
I hear they're
calling it a gas leak.
Such a pity.
I heard that you were quite
the woman on a mission today.
What can I say?
I want Elijah back.
Is that all you want?
You'll get Elijah back.
In the meantime,
stay out of this bar
and stay away
from my guys.
What's wrong?
You jealous?
Me? I've already found
my queen.
Cami the bartender?
Stop fooling
yourself, Marcel.
She's comfort food,
something to
distract you
from what you
really want,
which after all
these years
is impossible to deny
because I'm standing
right in front of you.
Klaus?
What are you
doing here?
I've had
quite a night.
I recall you mentioned something
about nightmares and insomnia.
I believe I can help.
May I come in?
This is superweird.
Come in.
Wait.
That's right.
I told you what happened.
I never tell anybody,
but I told you,
and you said something
about Sean standing
alone
against his demons.
When he killed
those men,
I thought he must be
mentally ill,
but what if
it was demons?
What if a vampire
compelled him?
And if so,
would you devote yourself
to finding
the guilty party?
Would you sacrifice everything
to find out the truth?
To what end?
This is the entire reason
I'm in New Orleans.
Cami, whatever lies on the
other end of this mystery
will only offer
you pain.
Nothing will bring
your brother back.
Your only hope for peace
is to forget this...
No.
And move on.
No. Don't compel me
to forget this.
And if I allow you
to remember,
the knowledge
will eat away at you.
Your quest for truth will
only put you in danger.
You don't care
about me!
You just want me to forget this
so I can be focused on Marcel,
so I'll be a good,
little spy for you.
I need your
loyalty, yes,
and, though that
may appear selfish to you,
the scope of my plan
goes far beyond myself.
Power aside, I am trying
to honor my brother.
What about my brother,
my twin brother?
We were bonded
our whole lives,
and I know, I know
he didn't just snap,
and I need to know
who did this,
and I need to
make this right.
No. Don't take this
away from me!
You will do nothing.
Your bother was ill.
He killed those people
and himself,
and it was a tragedy.
All you can do
is move on.
Know that your brother
is at peace
and that you
needn't worry.
I will find out
what happened,
and when I do,
I will make sure
whoever harmed your brother
will suffer,
and as for you,
tonight, you will sleep,
and you will dream of a world
far better than this one,
a world where there is
no evil, no demons,
and all people desire...
Only to be good.
It's all right,
Davina.
I don't mean you
any harm,
though I do think it's
time we had a talk.