Hello, Mr Herriot.
Hello, Tom. Good of you to
help out the Dalbys like this.
They've always been good
friends of my grandparents.
Mrs Dalby's up in t' field.
I'll take you.
Thanks, Tom.
Morning, Mr Herriot.
Thanks for coming out to see us.
And thank you for
being there yesterday.
Billy was a good man.
I wanted to pay my respects.
Their breathing don't
sound right, Mr Herriot.
They were really fit when they
turned out earlier this month.
Then, well...
Let's have a look, then, shall we?
The stirks have got husk, I'm afraid.
For an older cow
this may not be our problem
but as they are still so young...
Aye, and what is husk, exactly?
Well, it's a parasite.
A tiny worm which infests
the bronchial tubes
and sets up bronchitis.
The larvae climb up the blades of grass
and the cattle eat them as they graze.
Some pastures are badly
affected with it.
I'm sorry but they're pretty bad,
Mrs Dalby.
A mild attack isn't so bad
if you can get them
off the grass right away
but this has gone
a long way beyond that.
What can we do about it, Mr Herriot?
For a start, we can get them
all inside immediately.
Every mouthful of this grass
is adding to the worm burden.
Right you are, Mr Herriot.
Can I... tempt you with
the last egg, Mrs H?
No thanks.
Seems a shame to waste it.
I thought you'd be joining your friends
down in London for the cricket.
Yes, I thought so too
but unfortunately tickets require
money and money requires wages,
neither of which I possess.
So instead, my plan is
three uninterrupted days
with my feet up, the radio on
and a lovely, cool glass of...
Well, it took all of five hours
but Gladys produced
a whopping 18 piglets.
Darrowby record, I believe.
Smells like one, too.
They need cleaning. Get them off.
Any chance of some breakfast?
I can make you a bacon sandwich.
And those.
Think I've had enough pig
for one day. Got any eggs?
You can have the rest
of this one if you like.
So I'm out working my trousers off
while you're lazing around stuffing
your face with my hard-earned eggs?
Such is life, big brother.
Such is life.
Go and get changed.
I'll make you some toast.
You really didn't need to go
to all this trouble. Nonsense.
I hope that tea isn't too
strong for you. It's perfect.
Thank you, Mrs Dalby.
I'll be back up tomorrow
to check on the stirks.
Meanwhile, it's very important
that you keep them inside.
Oh. But they'll need feeding.
Well, at this point,
I would start by giving
them the best possible food -
good hay and high-protein cake.
Cake?
That's expensive stuff, isn't it?
And if we give them the hay now,
we'll need to buy more for winter.
I know but a good diet is
our best hope at this stage.
And they can't go out to
feed on the grass ever?
No. I'm sorry, not on those fields.
If it was a mild attack,
you could have turned them out
after the dew had left in the mornings
but that's not the case here.
Right.
Well, thank you, Mr Herriot.
We know where we are anyway.
Billy, love, why don't you take your
brother outside for a kickaround?
Have we got a young
Gordon Hodgson in the making?
He's my favourite player.
Good choice.
Go on, Billy, love.
Oi, you.
Excuse me.
Come on.
So cheeky.
Do you think we can save them?
Well... we can always hope.
Funny.
That's what my Billy
always used to say.
He was ever the optimist.
Even when the doctor
said it was cancer,
Billy still insisted he'd be fine.
Time is so fleeting, Mr Herriot.
Any other calls come in?
Nothing.
Shame.
I guess we will be taking a day off.
Not so fast.
Equipment needs polishing. Done.
Well, then, the medicines
need topping up. Done.
All done. Play starts
in five minutes, Mrs H.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What about the...?
What's wrong with Tristan
enjoying the cricket?
He spent all last night
polishing and topping things up.
There's always more to be done.
Lambing season's almost over.
Summer's our quietest time of year.
Surely the lad's earned
a day or two off now.
Earned?
Well, now he's passed
his exams and all.
Oh!
James, I'm so sorry.
I didn't see you there.
I've probably had worse flung at me.
I wanted to drop in and see
how you were after yesterday.
Oh, I'm all right, thanks.
It's Phyllis we're worried about.
I was just over there now.
Her stirks have got husk.
Oh, on top of everything else.
We offered to help
her out with the kids
but she's determined she can manage.
Our Jenny was around the same
age as Billy when my mam died.
All the things that family
never got to do together.
Now they never will.
Must have brought back
a lot of painful memories.
Life's cruel sometimes.
Be seeing you again soon? I hope so.
What are you doing tomorrow night?
Going out with you by the sounds of it.
I could pick you up at seven?
I'd like that.
Thank you.
What on earth?
Tristan, just the man.
Help me carry these out to the barn.
What's going on? You'll see.
Now, one cannot be a great vet
until one has reared one's own animals.
Funny, never heard that one before.
Mm-hm.
So here you are, Tristan.
Meet your new brood.
Wait, what?
May I suggest you make a start
building a nest box for them?
A nest box? Nothing like
a fresh egg, warm from the nest.
Hang on, how come James never
had to rear his own animals?
This better not be a flock of sheep.
Is Uncle Herriot here?
No, Uncle...
Mr Herriot is not here, I'm afraid.
As I'm sure you're aware,
Mrs Pumphrey is attending
the Test match in London and
I am under strict instruction
to deposit Tricki Woo into his
guardianship for the duration.
I'm sure Mr Farnon can
provide temporary guardianship
until Uncle Herriot returns.
Most kind.
Now the evening sun sends
long shadows over the gasometers,
Hutton has reached 150
and, with Leyland by his side,
looks like going on to 1,000.
Oh, thought you were Siegfried.
Since when do we have hens?
Since my big brother decided I need
to rear my own animals.
What for? Exactly.
I thought now that
I'm a fully qualified vet
he'd finally stop hectoring me.
Perhaps he just
doesn't know how to yet.
I don't know.
Doesn't seem to matter
what I do, it's never enough.
Then why don't you try
standing up to him?
Worked for me.
You make it sound easy.
Perhaps it is.
Have you met my brother?
What is this supposed to be?
A nest box?
Give it here.
How was your visit to the Dalbys?
It's not looking good.
Oh, dear.
This is Maggie, by the way.
Say hello, Maggie.
And, oh, look, this one here is Brenda.
Let me guess - they're all named
after your ex-girlfriends.
No, not at all.
Here she is.
This is Helen,
especially for you, James.
Who knows? This one might
even let you take her out.
I'll have you know that Helen and I
are going out on a date tomorrow night.
James!
That's fantastic... Sorry... news!
And where are you taking
the lovely Helen?
Probably just the Drovers.
The Drovers?
Look, tomorrow is your big chance
to finally impress Helen.
You should take her to the Renniston.
Trust me, women like
to be wined and dined.
Seems a bit grand.
Can't you see it, Jim?
The music oozing out of
Benny Thornton's trombone
and you full of champagne,
and Helen leaning across the table,
the look of love in her eyes.
Oh, kiss me, Helen.
Oh, OK.
Maybe.
I mean, after Hugh,
she is probably more used
to the finer things in life.
You still at it?
Sorry.
I'm still struggling to find
anything that might help Mrs Dalby.
Don't worry.
Here, I'll make a fresh pot.
Oh, Mrs Hall,
do you have a spare stamp?
Leave it here and I'll post it for you.
Thank you.
How is your mother?
Still struggling.
I'm just trying to help out
where I can but it's...
I'm sure she's grateful
for any help you can manage.
It still doesn't feel like it's enough.
To be honest, I just...
I still have no idea
what I'm supposed to do
about the Glasgow job.
Tricki's finally grown on you, then?
Like a fungus.
Well, he's definitely
taken a shine to you.
I assure you I've given him
absolutely no reason to.
Could say the same about Tristan.
He'd follow you
to the ends of the earth.
Only to push me off.
How are Phyllis's stirks
getting on? Not good.
It's the worst case of
husk I think I've seen.
Where are you up to?
So we've taken the stirks off the field
and I've suggested
a diet of hay and cake. Mm-hm.
But without an effective
treatment to speak of,
I'm a bit lost as to what else
I can do to try and save them.
Perhaps you can't save them.
Every problem has a solution.
I just need to find it.
I take it you've given them
the throat injection.
That's just an old farmer's tale.
Don't say that to their faces.
I don't want to give her any more
false hope than I already have done.
And there's not much evidence
to suggest it actually helps.
There's not much evidence
that it doesn't help either.
So what have you got to lose?
Morning, all.
Morning. Morning, Tristan.
Fresh eggs coming right up.
We'll make a poulterer of you yet.
Good morning, ladies.
What have you got
for me today, then, hey?
They're just getting used
to their new home.
Poppycock, they're chickens.
They don't know their beak
from their feet.
It's your job to know what's
best for them. My job - exactly.
And I say they just need a bit of
time and they'll figure it out
for themselves.
What they need is guidance.
Find yourself something resembling
an egg then put it in the nest...
No.
No, what? No, I'm not
listening to you any more.
You put me in charge of these hens
so I'm going to do it my way.
You're being ridiculous.
And I can guarantee that
by tomorrow morning,
these hens will have eggs
coming out of their...
..ears.
Wh...
Oh, God damn it,
you stupid bloody animal.
God!
Morning, Mrs Dalby.
Hello. How are they today?
Still fighting. I've been giving
them the cake and hay like you said.
I emptied my penny jar to pay for cake.
You're a good lad, Billy.
Your dad would be proud.
Hey, Billy, give us a hand with this.
I actually dipped into the family
savings to pay for the cake.
But Billy was so desperate to help
that I let him think
we used his pennies.
Probably scatter them on the farm
when he's not looking,
let him think he's found more.
What about a throat injection?
Farmers round here swear by it.
We could try.
It's a mix of chloroform,
turpentine and creosote.
There's no guarantee that it will
help but... We can always hope.
Right, Mr Herriot? Right, aye.
It's nothing serious.
Just a small cut, by the looks of it.
Well, thank God for that.
Mrs Pumphrey would
have our guts for garters.
That'll teach him to get
involved with the chickens.
Will it? What?
You know very well, what.
If you'd left well alone,
none of this would have happened.
How is it my fault that he...?
All he wants to do is make you proud
but you set these standards for him
that are impossible to meet.
If you just left him to it once
in a while, maybe he'd surprise you.
We're not talking about Tricki Woo
any more, are we?
We're simple folk, really, Mr Farnon.
We all just want the occasional
pat on the head.
Isn't that right, Tricki?
Hm?
Mm?
Thanks for helping us
with all of this, Mr Herriot.
Yeah, thank you, Mr Herriot.
Not at all.
You did all the hard work.
I had the easy job.
Mr Herriot! Mrs Dalby!
Hey, Billy, why don't you give me
a hand to fetch them some more hay?
I'm so sorry.
I'm not a farmer.
Billy was the farmer.
He knew everything there was to know
and he was so proud the life we'd
built here and I'm letting him down.
Phyllis, you're not
letting anyone down.
I know it can feel like that sometimes
but you're doing the best you can.
But what if my best isn't good enough?
What you're trying to do here is hard.
Anyone would doubt themselves.
Mum, are we going to be all right?
Come here, love.
Of course we are.
Here we go, James.
All fresh and aired.
Thanks, Mrs H.
Oh, very handsome.
It'll be a miracle if they
make it through the night.
Having been proved wrong
more than once,
I've learned never to underestimate
the resilience of nature.
Right, well, I best be off.
Cheerio. Good luck.
Oh...
Wait a sec.
I've posted your letter for you.
Thanks.
I know it's hard but you've done
what you can today
for Phyllis and your mother.
Now go have a wonderful time
with Helen. It's important.
Mr Ingledew. Good evening.
I presume this is yours.
I saw them arrive yesterday.
Tristan?
Tristan!
Thanks, James.
Come on, Annabel, let's get you home.
God!
That was close.
Damn it.
Oh, no!
Oh, dear.
You'd better come in, James.
Oh, dear, indeed.
The car ran into a bit of
a ditch on the way over.
Perhaps you can borrow
a pair of my dad's shoes.
Oh, no, that's quite all right.
You can't go out like that.
Dad, lend James some shoes
and socks, will you?
There's really no need...
Nonsense. Dad don't mind.
Here. You can wipe your trousers
down with this. Thanks.
There you go.
My old dancing shoes.
Been a while since
they've had an outing.
Oh... Honestly, I'll be fine.
Are they not to your liking, James?
No, no, these are...
They're perfect.
Thank you, Mr Alderson.
Aye.
I'll go see what Helen's up to.
James is here.
Can you make sure dad checks
the tarpaulin on the barn roof
and make sure...?
Stop worrying. Go enjoy yourself.
Me and Dad will be
just fine without you.
Sorry, James.
I thought we could go to the
Renniston for dinner.
I should go and get changed, then.
No, you look...
..perfect.
Go on, then. Don't want to
be late for the Renniston.
I won't be late.
Enjoy yourself, love.
Goodbye.
I'll get it!
Tristan!
I give you this simple, little job
one would have thought even you
would be hard put to make a mess
of it and look at the situation.
Not one solitary egg have we seen,
the bloody hens are flying
about the place like pigeons
and we are now permanently
estranged from our neighbours.
I'm sorry, Siegfried.
I'm sure I put the latch down.
I always double-check.
I don't...
..want to hear it. Just... try not to
burn the house down while I'm out.
Who's up for games night?
Sorry, Mrs Hall, I'm out
with Diana tonight.
In fact...
..I'm running late as it is.
I've got to see a man...
..about a chicken.
Sorry, Mrs H.
Right...
Just me then, is it?
Thank you.
Miss Alderson, how lovely
to see you again. Hello.
Would you care for a table, sir?
Yes, please.
Table for two.
This way, please.
Excuse me?
How's Phyllis getting on?
She lost one of her stirks
when I was there today.
Oh, James, I'm so sorry. That must
have been difficult for you both.
I just wish I'd seen them sooner.
She might have had
a fighting chance a week ago.
Well, you're there now,
and if anyone can pull it off,
it's Phyllis.
I just worry it's too little, too late.
It's not like you to give up so easily.
You didn't see her today.
She's already having to use
her winter supply of hay
and spending money that she
doesn't have on expensive cake.
I just want to give her
any more false hope.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't be
burdening you with all of this.
You're not burdening me.
It's nice that you care.
Farming's a tough life.
So much loss and hardship.
It's bloody hard work.
Do you ever think you could leave?
Do something different? Me?
I think about it all the time.
I think what it might be like to
not have dirt under my fingernails
every day, not have to worry
about money, or shovel muck.
Thank you.
I've been thinking
about Phyllis and farming
and what you were saying
just now and... and...
And what, James?
Well, perhaps it doesn't
have to be a struggle...
..for Phyllis.
All the other farmers think
she should sell the farm
and maybe they're right.
Maybe it's not too late.
She could sell up, move away,
make a fresh start somewhere new.
All the memories of Billy
are tied up in that farm.
All the boy's memories.
That would mean her leaving behind
everything she's ever known.
It's what I had to do.
That's different.
You made a choice to come here.
It doesn't mean it was easy.
My life was in Glasgow,
my friends, my family.
It's not the same.
Why not?
Because I'm not a farmer?
Because your life isn't
the ground under your feet.
You haven't poured blood, sweat and
tears into the soil you plough.
You haven't raised animals from
birth knowing they could be
taken from your any moment
and, with them, your livelihood.
I feel like you're making
my argument for me.
Billy Dalby took on
that farm from his father,
and his father before him.
It's young Billy's birthright.
So long as there's
something left to inherit.
So you can see yourself
ever leaving, then?
Well, I'm not going to
live with my dad forever
but I could never be too far away.
I can't expect you to understand that.
No.
You're probably right.
Is there a spare one of those going?
Coming right up.
Its not the good stuff I'm afraid,
Siegfried would kill me.
As long as it's strong and large,
I don't care.
Want to talk about it?
Not really.
What have you been up to?
The usual - disappointing Siegfried,
annoying the neighbours,
creating avian anarchy.
Siegfried still on your case then?
I think it's his life's work
to be on my case.
His magnum opus will be the utter
destruction and destitution
of his little brother.
Did you try standing up to him,
like I suggested?
I did, yes.
Now it's made everything worse.
But I've got a plan.
Won't it feel like a shallow victory?
A victory is a victory nonetheless.
Hello.
Look at that!
He's only gone and bloody done it.
The taste of a fresh egg,
can't beat it.
Are you heading up to
the Dalby's today?
Unfortunately, yes.
I have no idea what to say to the
poor woman. I could see the look
of hope on her face when I gave
the stirks the throat injection.
I don't know.
I just don't feel like I'm
being honest.
Honesty is the best policy.
Of course, the throat injection
was never going to work.
What?
But you were the one that told me
to give it to them.
This isn't about the injection.
Look, it's the worst part of the job
when you realise everything
is in the lap of the gods.
But at least now you can
look Phyllis in the eye and tell her
you have tried absolutely everything.
And as long as you've tried everything,
then you've done your job.
You'll find the right thing to say,
I have no doubt.
Thanks, Siegfried.
I know that I can set these high
standards at times,
and perhaps come across
as slightly overbearing...
Slightly.
It's only because I want
the best for you both.
And, Tristan, maybe I should
trust you a bit more.
And...
..recognise your successes
when you have them.
It's a week's wage.
Well done.
You were right about the hens
and you've more than proved
yourself of late.
Thanks, Siegfried.
You've earned it.
Actually, I've got
a confession to make.
I think I'd better get going.
Confession?
It's just, I wanted
so desperately to make you proud
and do something right for
a change and...
..I lied.
I bought the eggs from the grocers
and planted them
in the nest box last night.
Here.
Right...
Take it.
We all make mistakes.
The thing is to forgive and...
..learn from them.
What mistakes?
Well, it might have been me
that left the barn door open.
In my defence, Tricky had just
been attacked and...
I suppose that makes us even,
doesn't it?
Does it?
I'd take it if I were you.
I'll get it.
Thanks, Siegfried.
I see you've lost another one.
We have.
But Mrs Dalby's sure she noticed an
improvement in the others' appetite.
That must be a good sign.
Let's go have a look at them, shall we?
How are they looking, Mr Herriot?
I wish I had some better news,
but they're still very sick.
Now, I know you've told me
not to turn the young beasts
out onto the field any more,
but isn't there a way around it?
Perhaps it could help to get them
back outside.
No, I'm sorry.
Until there's a vaccine,
there's no way of safeguarding them
against husk.
Then we will just have to find
another solution.
I...
Mrs Dalby,
this is what I've been meaning to
talk to you about.
I've been giving the matter a great
deal of thought and, well,
you've lost so much already...
I just couldn't live with myself if
I didn't give you my honest opinion.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
I really am, but we've tried
everything now, and there's still
a very real chance you could end up
losing the entire herd.
So there's a chance that we
might not then?
A slim one, yes.
I've given you so much
false hope already.
I really think that now your best
course of action is to sell
the farm before it's too late.
There's nothing false about hope,
Mr Herriot.
Yes, but...
I appreciate your honesty, I do.
But I've been giving it a great
deal of thought too,
and I understand the risk involved.
But, when I look around...
..I don't just see the things
I've lost or might lose,
I see everything I have.
I see my boys.
How I have so much
worth fighting for still.
And I owe it to them,
to my family, not to give up.
Even if it is the slimmest
of chances, I'll take it.
I might not have been able to
save my husband, Mr Herriot,
but I can save our farm.
Our home.
So we're staying put.
Like my Billy always used to say,
only them as has them can lose them.
Now, come on,
you must have one of these scones,
they're fresh from the oven.
That's it, that's the record.
He's done it!
Brilliant, brilliant.
Wonderful.
I'll get it.
Tricky, Mummy's here.
Darling, dearest boy,
how have you been?
Mrs Pumphrey, do come in.
Thank you.
Forgive my early arrival,
our separation became far too
unbearable.
Quite all right.
I'll fetch some tea.
Do sit down, Mrs Pumphrey.
Allow me.
Thank you.
I so appreciate his Uncle Herriot
looking after him so well.
Where is our dear James?
Out on a call, I'm afraid.
Oh, what a pity.
How was your trip?
Hutton and Leyland made quite the pair.
I almost dropped my binoculars
in all the excitement.
We just heard,
Hutton beat Bradman's record.
Terrific!
Which reminds me, I do hope you are
practising your inswinger,
ready for
my little cricket match this summer.
Of course, wouldn't miss it for the
world, Mrs Pumphrey.
Wonderful.
Look, Tricky, your favourite.
He does love a home-made biscuit.
They're actually for you, Mrs Pumphrey.
Oh, I only eat a Fortnum myself.
But Tricky is a little less fussy.
And how was my darling boy been?
I do hope he has behaved himself.
Well...
Honesty...
Yes, um...
Truth be told, there was
a slight incident.
I took temporary charge
of Tricky while James...
While Uncle Herriot was on a call,
turned my back for a second
and Tricky did receive a tiny
peck from one of our hens.
I take full responsibility,
I'm terribly sorry.
Tricky always goes
completely cracker-dog
when there's a chicken in sight.
Tricky woo-lally I call it.
I couldn't tell you what
he has against them
but that will be the fifth peck
he has had this year.
Oh, right.
Perhaps it's because he's an only dog.
I do think that an only
develops more prejudices
than one from a large family.
Wouldn't you agree?
Try not to be upset.
You will see your uncles
again very soon.
And the pain of parting is
nothing to the joy of meeting again.
Thank you.
Good day, Mrs Pumphrey.
Goodbye, Tricky.
Oh, of course, Tricky, yes,
where are my manners?
Francois, would you mind?
You reminded me...
To say thank you.
Oh.
To his Uncle Herriot.
The kippers - exquisite.
Right, home, please, Francois.
Toodle-oo.
Bye-bye.
Come on!
Phyllis lost another stirk.
A few more are on their way out.
But she is determined to keep going,
even if it's only with half a herd.
You were right.
I get it now, and I'm sorry about...
This was my mum's favourite spot
up here on this roof.
Used to come up here at lunchtime
and eat our sandwiches.
She'd point out different
parts of the farm and tell me,
"That's where you scraped your knee
trying to jump over the bales."
"That's where you helped out
with your first lambing."
"And that spot there..."
"..that's where I told your dad
I were pregnant with you."
"And his grin filled
his whole face."
Subtitles by Red Bee Media