What time is it?
Nine.
But it's dark out.
That's because you aIways
sIeep tiII noon, siIIy.
This is what nine Iooks Iike.
I guess I'II get washed up then.
Watch that sunrise.
I'm getting tired of aIways
sneaking around.
Me too. What if we went away
for the weekend? No interruptions.
We couId be naked
the entire time.
AII weekend?
That's a whoIe Iot of naked.
I'II say I have a conference
and you can have a chef thing.
I wanted to go to this
cuIinary fair in Jersey!
Okay.
You know you're not, though.
-Let's go.
-Okay. Wait.
What about Joey?
The One with the Kips
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
I'm going to a cuIinary fair
in Jersey this weekend.
How weird! ChandIer just said
he's got a conference there.
That's funny. Seems Iike
ChandIer's conference couId've been. . .
. . .in Connecticut or Vermont.
I'm not in charge of where
the conference is heId.
Do you want peopIe to think it's fake?
It's a reaI conference.
-Is RacheI here?
-No, she's out shopping.
-Damn!
-What's going on?
I toId EmiIy to come.
And I just need to, you know,
taIk to RacheI about it.
Wait a minute.
When EmiIy comes,
you won't see RacheI anymore?
I'm focusing on the
"I get to see my wife" part. . .
. . .and not on the part
that makes me do this.
So you'II never be
in a room together?
How wiII that even work?
I have no idea.
I mean. . . .
But I assure you,
I wiII figure it out.
It doesn't seem Iike it'II work.
Hi, guys.
What's going on?
We're fIipping Monica's mattress.
So I'm thinking, basicaIIy,
we pick it up, and then we fIip it.
That's better than my way.
Hey guys, wouId you fIip mine too?
Oh, man.
Oh, Iook! A Ietter from my mom.
So, Rach?
You know how EmiIy's coming?
Oh, yeah. I know.
Can you hear anything?
Yeah, somebody just said,
"Can you hear anything?"
Hey, Joey's ass.
What are you doing?
Remember when they fought
and broke up. . .
. . .and we were stuck here
aII night with no food?
When Ross said " RacheI" at the wedding,
I figured it'd happen again.
So I hid this in here.
Candy bars, crossword puzzIes. . . .
Mad Libs ! Mine!
Condoms?
You don't know how Iong
we'II be in here.
We may have to
re-popuIate the Earth.
And condoms are the way to do that?
Anyway, it aII boiIs down to this.
-The Iast time I taIked to EmiIy--
-Oh, my God! Our dog died!
-What?
-Oh, my God! LaPooh, our dog!
LaPooh's stiII aIive?
It says he was hit by
an ice-cream truck and dragged for. . .
. . .nineteen bIocks!
-Oh, my God.
-Sweetie, we heard you crying.
-PIease don't cry.
-It's LaPooh!
I know, it's LaPooh right now
but it'II get better.
I can't beIieve it! We're here!
ChocoIates on the piIIows!
I Iove that!
You shouId Iive with Joey.
RoIos everywhere.
I'II be right back.
Oh, yes!
Get in here.
It's a high-speed car chase on!
We're switching rooms.
Oh, dear God!
They gave us gIasses!
The gIasses have Iipstick on them.
Who knows what eIse
they didn't change?
Sweetie. . .
. . .I just want this weekend
to be perfect.
We can change rooms, can't we?
Okay, but Iet's do it now.
Chopper Five just Iost its feed!
You know how there was something
I wanted to taIk to you about?
Oh, yeah.
I'm trying to work
things out with EmiIy.
WeII, there's this. . .
. . .one thing.
Here goes.
I made a promise that--
-What?
-Your nose is bIeeding.
Oh, God!
You're bIeeding.
Not again.
This happened when
my grandfather died.
Sorry.
Gross.
Okay. So I'm sorry.
What did you want to teII me?
Sorry. Sorry.
I can't see you anymore.
I know, it's ridicuIous.
I can't see you, either.
-I think you'II Iike this room more.
-Okay, great.
They say he's onIy got
haIf a tank Ieft.
HaIf a tank? StiII Iots
of high-speed chasing to do!
-We're switching rooms again.
-What? Why?
This has a garden view.
We paid for an ocean view.
Our Iast ocean-view room
was unacceptabIe to you.
Excuse me. Can I taIk to you
over here for just a second?
These cIowns want to take us
for a ride. I won't Iet them.
We're not a coupIe of suckers.
I hear you, Mugsy.
AII these rooms are fine.
Just pick one so I can watch the--
Have a perfect, magicaI
weekend together with you?
-This one I Iike.
-Nothing.
Nothing. It's over. Damn it!
This is reguIarIy scheduIed
programming!
Can we turn the TV off?
Do we reaIIy want to spend
the weekend Iike this?
Am I getting in the way
of the room-switching fun?
Don't bIame me for tonight.
Who shouId I bIame?
The nice beIIman?
Or the idiot who thought
he couId drive. . .
. . .from AIbany to Canada
on haIf a tank of gas?
Do not speak iII of the dead.
We're supposed to be spending
a romantic weekend together.
What's the matter?
I just want to watch
a IittIe teIevision.
Jeez, reIax, Mom.
What did you say?
I said, " Jeez, reIax, Mon. "
I've been wanting to teII you something
and I just have to get it out.
Okay. What's up?
You know how you said to do
whatever it takes to fix my marriage?
Yeah, I toId you to give EmiIy
whatever she wants.
And whiIe that was good advice,
you shouId know that what she wants. . .
. . .is for me not to see you anymore.
That's crazy! You can't do that.
What are you going to teII her?
Oh, my God!
You've aIready agreed to this.
It's awfuI, I know.
But I have to do this
if I want my marriage to work.
And I do. I have to make
this marriage work. I have to.
But the good thing is, we can stiII
see each other untiI she gets here.
Lucky me! Oh, my God!
That is good news, Ross!
That's the best news I've heard
since LaPooh died!
You have no idea what a nightmare
this has been. This is so hard.
Oh, yeah, reaIIy? Is it, Ross?
-Let me make this easier for you.
-What are you doing?
-Storming out.
-It's your apartment.
Yeah? WeII, that's how mad I am!
Damn RoIos!
You're back!
How was your conference?
It was terribIe. I fought with
my coIIeagues for the entire time.
Are you kidding with this?
So your weekend was a bust?
No, I got to see DonaId Trump
waiting for an eIevator.
You're back too.
CouId I taIk to you for a second?
-How was your chef thing?
-It was awfuI.
Some peopIe don't
appreciate good food.
Maybe the food tasted good at first. . .
. . .but then made everybody vomit
and have diarrhea.
How much was the room?
I'II pay my haIf.
Fine. $300.
$300?
Just think of it as $25 per room.
What are you guys woofing about?
ChandIer stoIe a 20 from my purse!
You know what?
Now that I think about it. . .
. . .I constantIy find myseIf
without 20s, and you. . .
. . .aIways have Iots.
You shouId've seen
the Iook on her face.
I don't want RacheI to hate me.
I don't know what to do.
-You want my advice?
-Yes. PIease.
-You won't Iike it.
-That's okay.
You got married too fast.
-That's not advice.
-I toId you.
I'm going to the bathroom.
If anyone asked me to give up
any of you, I couIdn't do it.
Me neither.
Maybe I couId do it.
I know you guys heard about
me and Ross.
But I've been obsessing about it
and wouId Iove not to taIk about it.
I don't know if this faIIs
under that category. . .
. . .but Ross is right back there.
-That's not Ross.
-Not that guy.
He does Iook Iike him, though.
Ross is in the bathroom.
Oh, my God! It's happening.
It's aIready started. I'm Kip.
Yeah, you're not Kip.
Do you even know who Kip is?
Who cares? You're RacheI.
Who's Kip?
My oId roommate.
We aII hung out together.
Oh, that poor bastard.
You toId me the story.
He and Monica dated.
When they broke up, you aII
promised you'd stay his friend.
And what happened?
He got phased out.
-You won't be phased out.
-Of course, I am.
It won't happen to Ross. He's your
brother, your coIIege roommate.
It was just a matter of time.
I just assumed Phoebe
wouId be the one to go.
You Iive far away,
you're not reIated.
You Iift right out.
Hey, Mr. Bing.
That hoteI you stayed at caIIed.
Someone Ieft an eyeIash curIer
in your room.
Yes, that was mine.
I figured you met
a girI and she Ieft it.
That wouId have made more sense.
I don't even feeI Iike
I know you anymore.
AII right, I'm just going
to ask you this one time.
Whatever you say,
I'II beIieve you.
Were you or were you not. . .
. . .on a gay cruise?
I'm sorry about the whoIe
"Iifting out" thing.
You got to come with me.
-Where?
-Wherever I go.
You and me, we'II start a new group.
We're the best ones.
Okay, but try to get Joey too.
Pheebs, do you mind if I
speak to RacheI aIone?
Sure.
Bye, Ross.
Forever.
Why are you here?
Isn't this against the ruIes?
I taIked to Monica.
Look, I'm the one
who made the choice.
I'm the one who's making
things change.
So I shouId be the one to,
you know, step back.
No, no, it's okay. ReaIIy.
PIenty of peopIe just see their
sisters at Thanksgiving. . .
. . .their coIIege roommates
at reunions. . .
. . .and Joey at Burger King.
Is that better?
No, it's not better.
I stiII don't get to see you.
What wouId you do?
If you were me, what wouId you do?
First, I'd have said
the right name at my wedding.
I can't beIieve this.
I know.
I am so sorry.
I know that too.
Hey, Rach?
Sorry to interrupt, but Phoebe said
you want to taIk to me about a trip?
I just came over to drop off. . .
. . .nothing.
So that weekend kind of sucked.
Yeah, it did.
So I guess this is over?
You know, you and me.
I mean, it had to end sometime.
Why exactIy?
Because of the weekend.
We had a fight.
ChandIer, that's crazy.
If you aIways gave up
after a fight. . .
. . .you'd never be with anyone
Ionger than--
This isn't over?
You are so cute!
No, no. It was a fight.
You deaI with it and you move on.
It's nothing to freak out about.
ReaIIy? Okay, great!
WeIcome to an aduIt reIationship.
We're in a reIationship?
I'm afraid so.
I heard you saw DonaId Trump
at your convention.
Saw him waiting for an eIevator.
Can I use your eyeIash curIer?
I Iost mine.
It's in the bathroom.
Can I taIk to you for a second?
Yes.
You?
And you?
But you cannot teII anyone.
No one knows.
But how? When?
-It happened in London.
-In London!
We didn't want to make
a big deaI out of it.
But it is a big deaI!
I have to teII someone!
You can't.
We just don't want to deaI with
teIIing everyone.
PIease just promise you won't teII.
AII right.
Man, this is unbeIievabIe!
I mean, it's great!
But. . . .
I know. It's great!
I don't want to see that!
We're so stupid.
Do you know what's going on in there?
They're trying to take Joey!
"The most popuIar Phoebe in tennis
is caIIed the overhand Phoebe.
If you win, sIap your opponent
on the Phoebe and say, 'Hi, Phoebe!' "
That's cute.
We reaIIy aII enjoyed it.
-But it doesn't count.
-For what?
Just count in our heads
as good Mad Libs.
-I got to go.
-Fun's over.
Wait, if we foIIow the ruIes. . .
. . .it's stiII fun
and it means something.
I'm going to take off.
Guys, ruIes are good!
RuIes heIp controI the fun.