ChandIer! ChandIer!
I saw what you were doing
in the window!
I saw what you're doing to my sister!
Get out here!
Listen, we had a good run.
What was it?
Four, five months?
That's more than most peopIe
have in a Iifetime. Goodbye.
-What are you doing?
-I am going on the Iam.
Come on, ChandIer.
I can handIe Ross.
HoId on!
Hey, Ross.
What's up, bro?
What the heII are you doing?
What's going on?
I think Ross knows
about me and Monica.
Dude, he's right there.
I thought you were my best friend!
This is my sister!
My best friend and my sister!
I cannot beIieve this!
We're not just messing around.
I Iove her.
I'm in Iove with her.
I'm so sorry that you
had to find out this way.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
I Iove him too.
My best friend and my sister!
I cannot beIieve this!
You guys want to probabIy
get some hugs in too. Big news!
We've actuaIIy known for a whiIe.
What? You guys knew?
You aII knew and
you didn't teII me?
We were worried about you. We didn't
know how you were going to react.
You were worried about me?
You didn't know how I'd react?
Okay. AII right.
Let's cIear out of here and Iet
these Iove birds get back to business.
I'm just taIking here.
He's the one doing your sister.
The One with the GirI Who Hits Joey
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
You know what I just reaIized?
If you guys have kids--
We're having kids?
I caII godfather!
You can't just caII godfather.
ShouIdn't her brother be godfather?
Sure. If you cared enough
to caII it first.
-You're a few steps ahead of us.
-Big zero gravity moon steps.
I just thought of
the greatest wedding gift.
I'II go in on that with you.
I couIdn't decide.
Hey, Katie.
This is Katie.
You ready to go?
I'II run to the bathroom.
Where's Iunch?
I was thinking Chinese food.
I Iove Chinese!
How did you know I Iove Chinese?
She is so cute.
You couId fit her
in your pocket.
I don't know. I Iike her a Iot,
and she's reaIIy nice, but. . . .
But what?
She keeps punching me.
In the cute IittIe,
sweet way she just did?
It's a Iot harder than it Iooks.
She's hurting me.
I know what you need.
You need a bodyguard.
What is Ben doing after preschooI?
Joey is having a probIem.
A IittIe girI is beating him up.
Joey, come here.
Honey, I know. This must be
reaIIy difficuIt for you, and--
I'm sorry, am I hurting you?
I brought you some housewarming gifts.
SaIt, so your Iife aIways has fIavor.
Bread, so you never go hungry.
And a scented candIe for the bathroom.
Because, weII, you know.
Thanks. Thanks.
And thanks, I guess.
WeIcome. I'm Steve Cera,
President of the tenants' committee.
Ross GeIIer.
And this is my friend Phoebe.
Mr. President.
I came to taIk to you
about Howard.
He is the handyman
who's retiring next week.
Everyone who Iives here is kicking in
$ 1 00 as a kind of a thank you.
That's nice.
Want to give me a check?
Not now. You can
sIip it under my door.
No, it's not that.
I just moved in.
WeII, the guy's worked here
for 25 years.
Yes, but I've Iived here
for 25 minutes.
Okay, I get it.
Wait! Look, I'm sorry, it's just
I've never even met Howard.
I mean, I don't know Howard.
Howard's the handyman.
Yes, but to me he's just " man. "
Okay. Fine. Whatever.
WeIcome to the buiIding.
Can you beIieve that guy?
I reaIIy Iike his gIasses.
So then President Steve
toId everyone I was a cheapskate. . .
. . .and now the whoIe buiIding hates me.
A IittIe kid spit on my knee.
You know what?
I'II throw a party.
For everyone in the buiIding.
And I'II sit them aII down and
expIain that I am not a bad guy.
I am not a cheap guy.
I'm just a guy. . .
. . .who stands up
for what he beIieves in.
A man with principIes.
Sounds Iike a fun party.
If you want them to Iike you,
why don't you just pay the $ 1 00?
The party wiII cost you more.
That doesn't matter!
It's my principIes!
We're taIking about my principIes!
I thought it was about
your neighbors Iiking you.
They'II Iike me once
they come to my awesome par-tay.
I gotta get some name tags.
And that crazy party animaI
wiII be your brother-in-Iaw.
Very funny.
But don't say that to Monica.
Don't put any ideas in her head.
You do reaIize that those ideas
are probabIy aIready in Monica's head?
Why?
WeII, because she Ioves you
and because you Iove her.
Yeah, so? What's
that supposed to mean?
Don't freak out! I'm teIIing you
something you aIready know.
She Ieft Richard because
he didn't want to have babies.
And she is a woman. And she's
aImost 30. And, you know, it's Monica.
I don't see it that way.
I see two Monicas:
My friend who Iives across
the haII and wants a Iot of babies.
And the new Monica
who I started to date.
Now, who is to say what she wants?
I'm right.
Am I right?
You're right.
You're absoIuteIy right.
That makes everything different.
It's not different, is it?
Not unIess " different"
means the same.
You were so funny with that waiter.
You're such a nut!
You know, breadstick fangs
are aIways funny.
No, you make them funny.
You're the funny one!
Look, Katie.
Listen, we need to taIk, okay?
Look, I Iike you.
I reaIIy do. I Iike you a Iot.
But sometimes when you
pIayfuIIy punch me Iike that. . .
. . .it feeIs Iike I'm being hit
with a very tiny but a very reaI bat!
Like I couId hurt you.
Are you making fun of my size?
Don't make fun of me
because of my size!
Isn't this great?
CouIdn't you just
stay Iike this forever?
CouIdn't you just stay here forever?
Yeah, here, somewhere eIse.
You know, wherever.
Are you okay?
I'm cooI.
CasuaI.
What are you doing?
Just hanging out. Having fun
with the girI that I'm seeing casuaIIy.
Man, I knew it!
I knew you'd do this.
Get aII freaked out because
everybody was joking about marriage!
WeII, you do want
aII that stuff, right?
You know what I want?
Yes! You want babies!
You have baby fever!
I do not have baby fever!
You're obsessed
with babies and marriage. . .
. . .and everything that's
reIated to babies and marriage.
Why don't we turn the heat
down on this pressure cooker!
Have you Iost your mind?
This isn't about me. This is about
you and your weird commitment crap!
I know you. I know the thoughts
that you have in your head.
You don't know everything.
Did you know I'm going out
with RacheI tonight instead of you?
And that the onIy baby here is you?
Did you know I can't even
Iook at you now?
I did not know that.
It'II be okay, right?
She won't Ieave me. This is fixabIe.
-Yeah, sure.
-AbsoIuteIy.
By me?
UnIess you make some big gesture.
Big, though.
The missus!
Gunther, can I get a coffee?
To go.
I stiII don't want to taIk to you.
TeII me how to make things right.
That's what we do.
I mess up, you teII me
how to fix it and I do.
And then you think I'm cute again.
I'm reaIIy tired of being
your reIationship tutor.
Figure this out for yourseIf.
If you're afraid
of a reaI reIationship. . .
. . .then don't be in one.
Howard! Howard! Howard!
Hi, Ross!
What are you doing here?
I thought this was your party,
and it's a party for Howard.
He's the sweetest IittIe man.
See you, Phoebe.
And thanks for chipping in.
Oh, sure.
You chipped in?
Yeah, $ 1 00.
I can't beIieve you gave him money.
I thought you agreed it was unreasonabIe
that they asked me for that money.
But they didn't ask me.
I'm just the exotic, generous stranger.
That's aIways fun to be.
But you're making me Iook bad.
No, I'm not! If anything,
I'm making you Iook better.
They'II see you
taIking to me. I'm a hit.
Hey, Pheebs!
Hey, Ross.
Maybe you two couId
switch apartments.
Because Phoebe is more
our kind of peopIe.
Think about it.
Okay, my bad.
You Iook big.
Thanks, I've been working out.
Listen, is it obvious
I'm wearing six sweaters?
But it's not obvious why.
I'm breaking up with Katie,
so I put on some extra padding.
If she hits me when she is happy,
can you imagine how hard she'II hit. . .
. . .when I take away the Joey Iove?
Hey, cute jacket.
Thanks.
-That's so sweet!
-Ouch!
Did Joey teII you to say that?
You guys are too much!
You know what?
I got to teII you. . .
. . .I think you're the one
that is too much.
Joey has the nicest friends.
And the nicest girIfriend.
You're so sweet!
She just kicked me.
Aren't you going to do something?
Do something or I'II waIk
out that door right now.
Are you going to?
This is a disaster.
Can't I pIease just go?
I'm taIking you up to peopIe.
Give it some time, reIax.
Get something to eat.
What did you teII them about me?
I toId them about you and EmiIy.
Trying to get some sympathy.
But you came off as the bad guy.
I toId it wrong.
We shouId taIk about that, because
I don't understand what happened there.
This cake is reaIIy good!
Things are Iooking up.
Oh, my God!
Someone cut Howard's cake!
Who wouId do a thing Iike that?
3-B.
You got your free food.
You ruined everyone's fun.
Isn't it time you went home?
Go back to 3-B, 3-B.
Everyone, caIm down!
I have something that I'd Iike to say.
Who here Iikes Ross?
Of course you don't Iike him.
He didn't give you any money.
He raised his own hand
when I asked, " Who Iikes Ross?"
And he's wearing two name tags.
I'II be honest. When I first met Ross,
I didn't Iike him at aII.
Once I got to know him,
I saw that he is reaIIy sweet. . .
. . .and caring and very generous.
AII I'm saying is don't judge
Ross before you get to know him.
You know, I Iike aII of you guys now.
But when I first met you, you know?
Kurt? I thought, abrasive drunk.
LoIa?
Mind-numbingIy stupid.
You guys. GoId digger,
cradIe-robbing perv.
So I think you aII know what I mean.
ObviousIy, I didn't think
they wouId throw things.
I thought if I kept insuIting them
you'd defend them.
Then you'd Iook Iike the hero.
See, I did not get that.
Where's Monica? I need
to taIk to her, it's urgent.
I'm Monica.
I need to taIk to you. It's urgent.
I've been thinking. . .
. . .about us. A Iot of " us" thinking.
I guess there's
onIy one way to do this.
What are you doing?
Don't do it.
WiII you marry me?
What a bad idea.
I can't not Iook at it.
Why are you doing this?
I don't know.
But I know I'm not afraid to do this.
I'm doing this because I'm sorry?
Do you think the best reason
to get married is because you're sorry?
The best reason is pregnancy.
Sorry is fourth, behind being ready
and actuaIIy wanting to get married.
WiII you be my wife?
I want you to take a minute and think
about how ridicuIous this sounds.
I'm kind of wishing
everyone wasn't here now.
None of that came from me.
I never said I wanted to have babies
and get married!
I was reaIIy confused.
Then I taIked to these guys.
Who? Two divorces and Joey?
She's right, you know?
Yeah, but stiII, cheap shot!
You know when I said
that I want you. . .
. . .to deaI with reIationship stuff
aII on your own?
You're not ready.
I didn't think I was!
Oh, my God.
What wouId you have done
if I had said yes?
I wouId've been happy because. . .
. . .I wouId spend the rest of
my Iife with the woman I Iove.
Or you wouId have seen
a ChandIer-shaped hoIe in that door.
WiII you pass that knife?
No, I wiII not.
You don't have to be mean about it.
You're right. I'm sorry.
WiII you marry me?
I was going to ask you to marry me
because I didn't say heIIo to you.
Or ask them to move in with you.
But I'm not sure. ChandIer?
How Iong is this going to go on?
I think the Iength of teasing. . .
. . .is directIy reIated to how insane
you were. So, a Iong time.
This is fun!
Remember that
"we were on a break" thing?
I'm sorry.
WiII you marry me?
That's not funny.