Mr Hulton's waiting for you
in the yard, Mr Herriot.
Thank you.
Mrs Hall?
Look at this, Mrs Hall.
There's a hole in my
cricket flannels. So there is.
I can't wear them
on Sunday with a hole.
What would Mrs Pumphrey say?
It's a good thing the Lord
invented darning then. Right.
Thank you.
I've just been speaking to
Richard Alderson. Oh, aye?
Apparently, we're still a man
short for Sunday.
It's bad enough that we've
lost our top batsman.
Tristan, I know you're still unhappy
with me, but this - this is cricket.
The annual Darrowby
match at Pumphrey Manor.
You're not just punishing me,
you know,
you're letting down the whole team.
Look, I told you -
I can't play for the Darrowby 11 any
more. Oh, that's just nonsense!
It's for local farmers
and vets by invitation.
And I, last time I checked,
am neither.
Herriot.
Thanks so much for coming out.
No trouble at all.
I understand you've a bull needs
ringing? I do indeed. This way.
Here he is.
This is Monty.
Only a year old,
but he's a powerful fellow.
No, I can see that! We also need to
move him later today,
so if you could sedate him
once you've got the ring in.
That shouldn't be a problem.
I will need a couple more men to
hold him, though.
So, Hugh definitely said
it was about a bull?
That's what he said. He's got a new
bull that needs ringing.
And he specifically asked for James?
He did.
It's about Helen.
It's got to be.
I reckon James'
sins finally found him out.
Don't be daft.
James has done nothing wrong.
Tell that to Hugh Hulton.
I won't be a moment.
Just going to give him an injection
of local anaesthetic.
Don't most vets just go ahead
and punch the hole?
They do...
I find this way works better.
All right, almost done...
Easy now.
Huh, look at that.
Didn't bother him at all.
It usually works.
Now, we just need the ring...
So have I missed very much
while I've been away in France?
Er, no, not that I can think of.
No great Darrowby dramas to report?
No, just things chugging along,
you know.
Have you seen much of Helen?
No, not a great deal.
But, well, now and again, you know.
She seems well, does she?
Yes... Yes, far as I can tell.
Right, shall we get on with this,
then?
I'm going up there later, actually,
to Heston Grange. Oh, yes?
Whoa! Easy, Monty.
I say, James, are you all right?
Come on ,Monty now.
Calm down.
I think I'll live. Glad to hear it.
So what's the verdict? Any hope?
Oh, there's always hope.
The adjustment nut's a bit stiff,
but once I've worked it loose,
I can raise the bob
and she'll run right to time.
That's all it needs?
Well, you have to know how
far to raise it.
Oh, of course. I don't doubt it
takes a lot of expertise.
Oh, don't know about that.
The main thing to remember is
lower is slower and left is lower.
Turn it to the right,
it'll go faster.
That's it.
Ah, so you've a cricketer
in the house. Hm?
Oh, we've two.
But it's Mr Farnon Senior who's
playing in the match on Sunday.
To be honest, I've never
understood the appeal.
I know,
and I call myself a Yorkshireman!
You'll be at the match, I take it?
I will.
In fact, I'll be scoring.
Ah, so you're something
of an expert?
An amateur enthusiast, perhaps.
Anyway, I'll...
I'll let you get on.
Oh, and thanks for the tea. Mm-hm.
What time did Hugh say he'd be up?
11 o'clock.
And he just said it
where about the lease? He did.
So d'you think he wants to sell?
Is that what he's coming to tell us?
You know as much as I do.
What if he's decided
not to renew the lease
because of what happened between me
and him?
Then I'd say you were right
not to marry him.
Darrowby, 2-2-9-7.
I'm sorry, I can barely hear you.
Ah, Mrs Pumphrey!
Hello, is everything all right?
Mr Farnon?
No, I see.
Well of course, if it's a
matter of "great delicacy".
I'll tell him now.
That was Mrs Pumphrey.
She asked if you could go up
to the manor.
Doesn't she want Tricki's
Uncle Herriot? Apparently not.
She said the matter requires
the utmost discretion.
Intriguing. Mm-hm!
"The utmost discretion"?
What's all that about?
I've no idea -
she said she'll only discuss it
with Siegfried... In person.
Hm!
So, spill the beans.
What happened at Hulton Hall?
Not a great deal.
What, Hugh didn't challenge you
to a duel for Helen's hand?
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but, no.
Well, has he seen her yet?
Er, no, he said he was going up
later today.
And that doesn't bother you?
Of course not. Why should it?
No reason.
Where are you off to? Nowhere.
I just, erm...
I need run an errand. Oh.
He's here!
He's here.
Hullo there. How do.
You got back all right, then?
I did. Yes. Thank you.
Can I make you a cup of tea? Er, no,
no, thanks. I can't stay long.
You said you wanted to speak to us
about the lease?
Yes, yes, that's right. Er...
Ah, here we go.
I intend to renew the lease
on the farm
for the agreed period of 20 years,
as per our existing contract,
but with a couple of
additional stipulations.
The lawyers have added
Helen's and Jenny's names
and specified that they'll inherit
the lease on the same terms.
That's assuming that they want
to continue farming.
That's wonderful. Thank you.
Thank you, Hugh.
It's very good of you.
Not at all, it's...something
that should have been done years
ago, but erm...
Well, it didn't really seem
necessary before.
Er...
Anyway, I think that
just about covers it.
I don't want to take up too
much of your time,
but there's something I'd like
to show you, back at the farm.
I don't understand. Consider it a
replacement, or apology,
if you like, for the difficulties
with the sale of your last bull.
Hugh,, this is too much...
We can't accept this.
Please, Mr Alderson.
It would mean a great deal.
He's good breeding stock,
excellent condition...
Ah, well even so...
I would really like to make amends.
Dad, why don't we think about it,
eh?
That's all I ask.
Just keep him here for now
and let me know what you decide.
Right. All right, then. Excellent.
Right, better get on.
Hugh.
Do you have to rush straight
off? Afraid so.
Estate business has rather piled up
while I've been away.
No doubt see
you at the cricket on Sunday.
You will. Jolly good.
Thank you so much for coming.
Not at all, I understand
Tricki has been rather distressed?
He's not himself at all.
Is he off his food?
Feeling lethargic?
Oh, no, no, there's no
problem in that department.
In fact, if anything, his appetite's
more robust than ever.
No, it's just, erm...
He's become...
..increasingly...
..amorous towards things.
It's quite unsettling.
In the end,
I had to take his cushion away.
I see...
Well, let's have a look at him,
shall we?
You know, Mrs Pumphrey,
the behaviour you're describing,
is perfectly normal.
Tricki's a healthy animal
in the prime of life.
And, as such, he's experiencing
some very natural...urges.
Yes, but he's just a baby!
He's never shown the slightest bit
of interest in...
..that sort of thing.
Well, it's a testament to the
excellent level of care
he's been receiving. His weight's
gone down, his exercise has gone up.
He's obviously feeling a great
deal livelier in every department.
You know, Francois did say
that on one of their outings,
he seemed intent on getting
into Mr Handshaw's yard.
And does Mr Handshaw own
a dog at all?
Oh, yes, a terrier.
Named Bella, I believe.
Well, that would certainly explain
it.
Less lethargic, more lothario.
So what can be done
to discourage it?
I'm afraid the heart wants
what it wants,
which, in Tricki's case,
would seem to be Bella. Oh, dear.
There is one effective
course of action.
It's a fairly simple procedure...
Oh, no, no, no, no, Mr Farnon, no.
Can't you just give him
a calming draught of some sort?
I'm sorry, Mrs Pumphrey.
He'll have to be fixed.
If not, Tricki will simply continue
his pursuit until he succeeds.
Hello, James.
Hello, Jenny. Hello, Scruff.
Wait till you see what
Hugh Hulton's brought us.
Have you ever seen anything like it?
And he'll be worth
a fortune in stud fees.
But Hugh won't accept a penny
for him, says it's an apology
because he wants to move forward
with a clean slate.
Jenny, run and put the kettle on.
Dad'll be wanting a brew
and I'm sure James'd like one.
Fine.
A pedigree bull.
Quite the gift. I know.
It were the last thing we expected.
We haven't said we'll take him yet.
Dad thinks it's far too much,
but even so...
And there you were, worried he might
not even renew the lease.
I know, that's all sorted now too.
He's even added mine and Jenny's
names, so it'll be ours to inherit.
Right. That's very decent of him.
Now, then...
Mr Alderson.
What do you reckon?
He's a fine specimen.
He is that.
Any luck with Reg Dutton, dad?
Nah, he's still over in Listondale.
Dad's a player down for match
on Sunday. Oh, yes?
And with Hugh back, they'll be
really up against it.
Hugh's on the opposing team?
He's captain.
Not to mention the star player. He's
the main reason they always win.
Er, not always.
Though Hugh is a good bowler,
there's no denying it.
You know, Mr Alderson,
if you need an extra man,
I'd be happy to help out.
I didn't know you played.
Yes, well, now and again... Oh, aye.
You reckon you're up to it,
do you, lad?
Absolutely.
Right.
You're in.
I'm really not much of a cricketer,
but I guess
if it's just a friendly match,
it's not too much to worry about.
Friendly?
James, I would not be exaggerating
to say that this is the most
important game in the
cricketing calendar.
Once a year, the Darrowby 11
goes up against the might
of Hulton Hall's invited gentlemen,
playing for the honour of Darrowby.
And get annihilated.
That's hardly the point.
It's really quite the event, James.
Mrs Pumphrey holds it on her own
private ground.
Sorry, she has a cricket pitch?
Ground, yes, down beyond
the orchard.
The old dear's
completely cricket-mad.
So, when you say you're
"not much of a cricketer"...?
Well, football's more my game.
But you have played?
Once or twice, probably just once.
Oh, dear.
Well, I had no idea it was so
important.
Oh, I'd say it's important!
For a Yorkshireman,
it goes King, God, Cricket.
I mean, if you get this wrong,
they'll string you up in the town
square. Oh, fiddlesticks!
James is fast and he's fit.
All right, it's not his game,
but with a bit of coaching,
he'll do perfectly well.
Quite right. We'll soon whip you
into shape, lad.
So, we've a day and a half.
That's what, 14, 15 hours of
sunlight?
Now, when you played before,
would you say you were more of a
batsman or a bowler?
Well, neither really.
It was on the beach at Troon and it
was probably more what
you would call French cricket.
But it can't be any tougher
than football.
At least in cricket,
no-one tackles you.
You haven't had a cricket ball
coming at you at 80mph.
Seriously, James, one of those could
kill you.
Right, follow me.
Jess, come on, give that,
the boys need it for the cricket.
Thank you. Right, come on.
Right, James. Take your guard.
Remember, middle and leg,
head over the ball, straight back.
Weight on the front foot...
And nice easy lob...
You need to maintain your guard.
How's he getting on? Try again...
You could give your brother a hand.
Yes, and he could apologise
for treating me like a fool.
But I don't see that happening any
time soon either. And...
James, please, try to concentrate!
I...!
Right, once more, take your guard,
middle and leg...
Oh, for the love of God.
James, pass it here.
Right, don't even think about
hitting it,
just think about blocking it.
Blocking it?
You just need to get behind the ball
and stop it, all right? Come on.
As long as it doesn't hit your leg
or the wicket, you'll stay in.
Well, there's a little more to it,
than that...
No, there isn't, not for James. But,
as ever, you're making everything
10,000 times more complicated than
it has to be...
He needs to know what
he should be doing...
No, he needs you to stop confusing
him with pointless stuff.
Just let the man breathe and he'll
work it out for himself.
James. Here, give it a try.
Right, that's it, just relax,
all you need to do is block it.
It worked! Course it did.
Now, just remember
the cardinal rule -
never step away from your stumps.
Well, at least he's making himself
useful. Despite the injured air.
He feels you still owe him
an apology. Utter nonsense.
So, you played a lot of cricket
at school, then, did you, Triss?
Yes, fair bit.
Captain of the first 11,
weren't you? Darrowby, 2-2-9-7.
Yes, we had a pretty strong
team at the prep school.
Even won the inter-school cup
three years in a row.
I didn't know that.
No? We actually set a new
record for the Under 12s.
The old man came to every match.
Pa used to watch you play?
He'd drive up in the mornings
and we'd make a day of it.
You know how he loved cricket. Yes.
Yes, I suppose he did.
Mr Farnon, Mrs Pumphrey.
She says she's in dire
need of your assistance.
Mrs Pumphrey, what can I do for you?
The workmen were putting up the
tea tent for tomorrow, you see,
and Francois was clearly distracted.
And, erm, poor Tricki, I mean,
he dashed through the main gate
and just ran and ran...
So Tricki is missing?
Foot to the bridge of the ball,
James!
Well, no, not, not exactly.
He was, erm...
He was heading in the
direction of Mr Handshaw's yard.
Ah. And I really can't ask
Francois... No, of course.
Er, leave...leave it with me,
Mrs Pumphrey,
you've nothing to worry about.
Oh, thank you, thank you!
Mr Farnon, when you see Tricki,
could you pretend that you
just happened to be passing?
He's terribly private, I would
hate for him to be embarrassed.
I understand. Of course.
Aye, he's a determined
little bugger.
Well, as I say, Mrs Pumphrey
did want me to pass on
her sincere apologies. Not to worry.
It's not like he's some stray.
A litter or two of pups wouldn't
be the end of the world.
Come on, then, young Trickiwoo,
let's put you back where you belong,
shall we?
See you at the match tomorrow,
Mr Handshaw.
Your brother still not playing? I'm
afraid not. That's a damned shame.
Might've given us a fighting chance.
Well, now he's been there once,
he'll be much more inclined
to visit again.
Right, seems we have no choice.
It's a very simple procedure.
In fact, I should be able to fit
him in on Monday. That soon?
Well, all right.
If we must, we must.
But until then, you really need to
keep him on a lead.
Oh, Tricki.
Will you ever forgive me?
All set for match tomorrow, I hope?
Absolutely. Raring to go!
Oh, that's the spirit.
And with James playing too, I really
think this might be your year.
I think we're all here.
Ladies and gentlemen, It's my very
great pleasure to welcome you all
to Pumphrey Manor for this year's
encounter between The Darrowby 11
and the Hulton Hall Chaps.
Has anyone seen Mr Rudd?
We'll be playing a timed game, with
the last 20 overs from five o'clock.
And, erm, I know we're all looking
forward to seeing some
excellent cricket.
So, erm, wi...
Without further ado, Mr Chapman?
Yeah?
If you would do the honours.
Certainly.
Well gentlemen, if you're ready,
will you two captains
accompany me to the
crease with the coin toss, please?
Thank you. Mr Alderson...
Mr Alderson. Young Rudds,
where's your father?
He can't come, Mr Alderson,
the sheep got out
and he needs to round 'em up.
You're kidding me?
No, we're not. We're not.
You're not.
So he's not coming?
So we're a player short.
Well, go on. You can't let them
go out wi' ten men.
I can always play, Mr Alderson,
if that would be any help?
Help? Yeah, that'd be a big help.
Shame you didn't offer before.
Go and help your dad look for them
sheep.
Welcome to the team.
Yes, thanks.
Afternoon.
Mr Hulton, would you like to make
the call? Heads.
We're bowling, lads.
We're batting.
Well, we've got to do it sometime.
I'd rather do it second, but...
Herriot.
Hugh.
Right, remember what
we did last year?
Come on, boys, stay alert.
Go on, dad.
Look lively, Herriot.
Come on, lads!
OK, play.
Knock to it, lads, come on!
Unlucky, unlucky!
Good shot...
Four!
Excellent opener, Mr Hulton.
Looks like Mr Hulton means business.
Herriot.
Oh, good shot!
Yours, Herriot!
Get behind it.
Come on, James!
Unlucky.
Just a single. Keepers' end.
That's Hulton's 50.
Herriot.
James! Ball!
Come on, lad!
Eye on the ball, Mr Herriot.
123...
..for no wickets.
Not out.
Chin up.
Unlucky. Next time, lads.
James is looking a bit hot.
Hugh's giving him
a right runaround.
Helen.
How are you?
Hello, Margot.
Yeah, I'm fine thank you.
This is my sister, Jenny.
Hello.
Are you enjoying the match?
I will once we start getting
some wickets.
Oh, yes, of course.
Anyway, I'm sure I'll see
you in the tea tent.
What was all that about?
Let's be having a wicket, Siegfried.
Hello there.
Hello.
I noticed you were rather
tied to your post
and thought you might
be in need of refreshment.
Oh, that's very kind of you.
Thank you.
Your Mr Farnon doesn't seem to be
having much luck.
Trouble is, he's overpitching.
When you say "overpitching"?
He's landing the ball too
close to the batsman,
making it easier to drive.
Go on, James.
He's making it harder for the
fielders.
So he does.
Are you all right, there, Herriot?
Fine, thanks.
Well,
you can't blame the bull this time.
Would you mind changing that to 138?
Mr Chapman. Mm?
I think that's enough.
Come on, Harry.
Ah, and that's the declaration.
Tea, everyone!
What's happening?
Hulton thinks he's got enough runs
to win so he's declared.
He's stopping.
Well, that's good news for us,
isn't it? Aye.
If you like charity.
I could certainly use a cup of tea.
Well, enjoy it while you can.
We're batting next.
And it won't be pretty.
Pork pie, you love that.
Oh, yum-yum-yum. No?
Or how about a tiny piece of
iced bun?
Oh! Oh, Mr Farnon.
I hope you're not too disheartened.
Oh, not at all.
We've got a lot of strength
in our batting. That's the spirit.
And, you have your secret weapon.
Your brother, of course.
Yes.
He opened quite gloriously
last year.
He did do very well.
Tricki, please.
He simply hates this horrid lead.
Well, it's only till the operation.
And what then?
Can you promise me
he'll still be my Tricki once he's
been emasculated?
Some dogs do present a slight
change in temperament.
Yes, that's what I feared.
It just feels too cruel.
Why shouldn't he be allowed to
express his true self
and experience life to the full?
And if Mr Handshaw were open to
an arrangement...
Well,
he certainly gave that impression.
Well, what would you do, Mr Farnon?
Do you know what, Mrs Pumphrey?
If I were you,
I would forget the lead
and just let Tricki do what
comes naturally.
Life's just too short, isn't it?
I knew you would understand.
Hugh, could I speak to you for a
moment?
Course.
I just want to say, how,
how sorry I am.
For everything that happened.
That's water under the bridge.
No, I know, but I've not had chance
to apologise properly.
In person.
I never wanted to hurt you.
We just weren't right for one
another.
And I knew I wouldn't make
you happy.
Well, I admit I...I was rather
devastated.
But in a way,
once the worst has happened,
it's actually rather freeing.
And I think part of me
always knew it wasn't right.
That we were good pals
and I know you were fond of me,
but...well, it was never a grand
passion, really, was it?
Well, no.
Maybe not.
Maybe one day we can be pals again.
I'd like that.
About the bull.
It was such a generous
thing to do... Did I overstep?
Because that,
that really wasn't my intention.
And me Dad knows you meant well.
We both do.
But we can't accept it.
Right.
Pay our own way.
Always have.
And you've no reason to feel you
have to make amends.
Didn't realise Herriot was
a cricketer.
Oh,
he stepped in at the last minute.
Ah, keen to impress the Captain,
no doubt.
We only started seeing each other
quite recently.
I mean,
there were nothing going on before.
Helen, really,
I'm just glad you're happy.
Well, I'd better get
back to the others.
Discuss strategy and all that.
Hello. Oh, there you are...
I saw you chatting with Hugh.
Yeah. We had a really good talk.
I feel like we cleared the air.
Right.
What's wrong?
I just wondered why
he was kissing you.
Kissing me?
Oh, that were nothing.
Right.
He just wants to be friends.
And he's given you a pedigree
bull to prove it.
Yeah, well, I've said I'm not
accepting the bull.
You're not?
Course not.
It were a kind gesture,
but we're not in need of charity,
however well meant.
Now, then Herriot.
I'll put you up to bat last with
you being a novice.
Right.
Very good.
Yeah. Let's hope that Hugh takes it
easy with you.
Right, ladies and gentlemen, I think
we are ready to resume.
Hulton's looking deadly serious.
But then I suppose he's
a lot riding on this.
How d'you mean? Well, all those
months he spent in France,
too embarrassed to show his face.
He'll be wanting a win to
restore his dignity. Triss!
Lovely shot, Tristan.
Cracking shot, Tristan!
Go on, Triss.
Brilliant!
Again.
Nicely done. Good running, lads.
Stay.
That's unlucky.
Now that's called a batting
collapse.
It's more exciting than I'd
anticipated.
We'll make a cricket convert
of you yet.
You know, I walk Rock
down by Copley Brook most evenings.
If you're ever out with Jess
and want a bit of company.
Well...perhaps we'll see you down
there.
Last over. Doubt you'll be needed.
They need to get two
wickets before you go in
and Siegfried is looking strong.
Catch it. Yes!
Just four balls to face, Henry.
Good luck, Henry.
Come on, Henry. Thanks, lads.
All the best, Henry.
Play.
I spoke too soon.
Right, Herriot, get padded up.
Henry's retiring hurt.
There's three balls left till
the end of the game.
If they don't get you out,
we'll draw.
And that's as good as a win.
Just do what you can.
All you have to do is stay in,
old chap.
Remember what we practised.
Protect your wicket
and guard your stumps.
Middle leg.
That'll do.
Go on, lad.
Three balls to come.
Fine.
You all right, Jim?
Well done, James.
Run.
It's gone for four.
Back this end, old chap.
Last ball of the match.
Just block it again,
exactly the same as before,
and Hugh'll be
crying into his beer tonight.
Come on, Mr Herriot. Come on, James.
Unlucky, batsman.
Hard luck, lad.
Thanks, Bert.
Funny that, almost looked like you
deliberately stepped
away from the wicket.
Why ever would I do that?
I've absolutely no idea.
Hey. Bad luck, Mr Herriot.
Nearly had a draw there.
Aye, still, well played, lads.
They were a tough side
and no mistake.
You carried your bat.
Great achievement.
Both of you.
The old man would be proud.
That's, erm, very fine batting,
young Farnon.
James didn't do too badly either.
Till he lost his nerve.
Dad!
Oh, well, I'm only saying it to him.
Good try, Uncle Herriot.
Thank you, Mrs Pumphrey.
Well done, Triss.
Thanks, Helen.
Well done.
I don't think your dad's too happy.
Don't worry about him.
James, I just wanted to say...
..well played.
You too.
I suppose the best team won.
Still, that took real grit.
Anyway, have a good evening.
Both of you.
So how does it feel?
What? To have missed the most
important ball of the match?
Is that what you did?
I felt I owed him a win.
I know.
And I love you for it.
You do?
Yes, I suppose I do.
Thank you, George.
Ah.
To your very good health.
Cheers.
You know, I don't remember Pa ever
visiting me at school.
No? He used to take me
out on his rounds, though.
I was nine
when I delivered my first lamb.
And you've never looked back.
No, I suppose I didn't.
I owe you an apology, Tristan.
For not telling you
the truth about your results.
I genuinely believed
I was acting in your best interests.
Right.
But I realise now, that
I may have been...wrong.
Anyway, the money's there,
if you decide you want to go
back to college.
Equally,
if you feel it's not for you,
well, it should be your decision.
Thank you.
Here he is! "An hour to play
and the last man in."
I think he did very well.
How're the ribs?
Bit sore, to be honest.
Oh, you poor old thing.
No Tricki Woo, Mrs Pumphrey?
Tricki.
Yes, Tricki has some personal
business to attend to.
Think it's time I made my move.
Well played, darling.
Hugh and Margot?
Wait, are they...?
I think you've missed your chance,
Triss.
Bad luck, old chap.
Well,
she wasn't really my type anyway.
Since when?
No, it's true, she was...a bit too
tall.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
She's a woman, not a pony.
Oh, height is a consideration.
You should be so lucky.
Nothing wrong with tall.
I'm a catch.
You're a liability.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media