Previously on Desperate Housewives...
The last two years
are a blank.
That's a fresh approach.
I believe you.
Mike couldn't place
a familiar face...
Whoever killed her...
The police couldn't
identify a murder victim...
-Pulled out all her teeth.
-There's no signature.
Gabrielle was getting
showered with gifts...
Buyer asked to
remain anonymous.
From a mystery suitor.
I'm gonna open up
a pizza parlor!
And Lynette
couldn't believe...
Oh, dear God.
What her husband
had done.
I wanna do what...
you wanna do.
Julie's first love
was two-timing her,
And Orson's first wife...
I'm Alma Hodge.
Wasn't going away...
-What do you think?
-I'll take it.
Anytime soon.
Your average housewife
worries constantly
about the dangerous people
she sees on the nightly news.
Which is why she buy
expensive alarm systems,
carries pepper spray
in her purse,
and keeps a gun
in her drawer,
so she can go about her day
feeling safe and protected.
Your average inmate
worries constantly
about the dangerous people
he comes in contact with every day.
Which is why
he takes ordinary items,
And turns them
into weapons,
that he always
keeps handy,
so he can go about his day
feeling safe and protected.
What is the difference between
the housewife and the inmate?
The inmate knows
the feeling won't last long.
Delfino, right?
Yeah.
So?
Come on, brah,
let's go.
You okay?
Yeah.
I owe you one.
Yeah. I guess you do.
Yes, we all need protection
from those who
would do us harm...
And sometimes from
those who protect us.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
Transcript by FRM
Wild parties.
Handsome strangers.
Tender kisses.
I had a great time.
Bye.
Yes, there were
many things
Gabrielle Solis liked
about being single again...
But coming home to
an empty house...
was not one of them.
What?
Hi. You're sleeping
at my place tonight.
Really?
What did you
have in mind?
God, I hate myife.
Honestly, did you think
I was gonna sleep with you?
It would be the polite
way to thank me.
Carlos, this isn't funny.
I am scared to death
of this maniac.
Since when?
Yesterday you were loving
all the presents, the intrigue.
The guy broke
into the house.
He went from secret
admirer to stalker.
For all I know, he's trying to kill me
so no one else will have me.
Why don't you just
call the cops?
And tell them what?
"911, sobody broke in the house
and left a 6,000 dollars dress."
Okay, so if this guy
shows up again,
what am I supposed
to do, exactly?
Nothing. Just having
you here helps.
Now that's very sweet.
Because when he breaks in and starts
hacking you up with his machete,
your screams will wake me up,
and then I'll be able escape.
Glad I could help.
Hey, stranger.
Hey.
You have good timing.
I just got all the
kids to sleep.
Ah, damn,
I wanted to tuck 'em in.
Well, you could
tuck me in.
I thought I smelled
your sex perfume.
Come here. Hi.
-Hi.
Oh, oh, oh. Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Don't  get me all
revived up just yet.
The printer said he was gonna drop
off my menu on his way home.
He already did.
Oh, you didn't look
at that, did you?
'Cause it's just
a mock-up.
Too late. I looked...
and it's great.
Really?
Yes. I love the font,
the color, everything.
I am so jazzed
to see the restaurant.
It is so good
to hear that.
So... any idea
when that might be?
Sure.
How about...
two weeks?
Hey.
You open in
two weeks.
Yeah. Well, that'd be a good
time for you to come by,
'cause there's free refills,
balloons, music...
Might there be
a V.I.P. preview
for people, say,
who bore your children?
-Lynette...
-Yeah?
I don't want you to see it
until it's all done.
Why not?
Because you will take
one look at the place
and then you'll have all
these tips and suggestions
that you just won't be able
to keep to yourself.
You think?
'Cause I just saw
a  take-out menu with
a 6-digit phone number,
and I kept that to myself.
See? There it is! That snarky,
know-it-all attitude.
What? I am snarky because I point
out one small, glaring mistake?
That's it.
Now you're banned
from the opening.
Fine! Good night.
So... we're not
having sex?
Hey, you banned me
from your opening.
All I'm saying is that I'd
feel a lot safer on the pill.
But if you're not 18,
you need parental consent.
Do we really need to give your
mother another reason to hate me?
She'll hate you a lot worse
if you get me... Hey!
Hi.
Hi
Bye.
-Bye.
Can't we just keep using condoms
and be extra careful?
Are  you crazy?
They're not dependable.
Sure, they are. Why do you
think everybody uses them?
They all have to
pass inspection.
It's too risky.
Condoms are only
85% effective.
Mom!
Mom, what happened?
Are you okay?
Oh! I was just, uh...
I lost an earring.
Mom, you're wearing
both your earrings.
Oh! I found it.
Austin, I would like to talk
to my daughter privately.
Sure. Call me later.
Why were you two
talking about condoms?
Why were you
eavesdropping?
Don't change
the subject.
Are you two
having sex?
Because I thought that I raised
you to be smarter than that.
Don't you realize that
sex is not fun and games?
It's dangerous.
Every time you turn around,
there's a new disease.
Do you want it to burn
when you pee?
-Mom! Mom!
-Sex kills!
What?
I'm not having sex.
Really?
Really.
Oh, thank God.
If you're not having sex, why were
you talking about condoms?
Because we know two
kids at school who are,
and they're only
using condoms,
which really stupid because
condoms are only 85% effective.
Yes. That's right.
A condom alone
will not protect you.
I totally agree.
Bree!
Alma!
I didn't know that
you knew Edie.
I told your friends at that dinner party
I was looking for a new house.
A house?
Yes, and Gaby
introduced us.
Oh. Well, um...
I don't want
to keep you.
I'm sure that Edie has lots
of other houses to show you.
Nope. We're done.
Alma took one look at the
Applewhite house, am bam...
love at first sight.
What?
We're gonna
be neighbors.
No!
I mean...
I mean, no, Alma,
you can't buy this house.
Why not?
Well, are you aware
of its history?
The previous owner...
was harboring a murderer.
It was her son.
Say what you like,
she was a great Mom.
They had a dungeon
in the basement.
I mean, people say they still hear
groans coming from the house night.
They're gonna hear groans coming
from your house if you don't zip it.
Don't worry, Alma,
I'm sure that, uh,
Edie can find you a house that
won't give you nightmares.
It's too late, Bree.
I've fallen in love
with this neighborhood.
And as for that haunted house
stuff, well, that's just silly.
People don't come
back from the dead.
Don't I wish.
I will not have that
woman as a neighbor.
You have got
to do something.
I said I'd talk to her.
So what are you
waiting for?
The house is dark.
She's not there.
Oh, so you're just gonna
wait until she moves in?
I will deal with it.
Bree, please calm down.
How can I be calm?!
For months, people thought
you killed your first wife.
No sooner does she show up
and clear your name,
than the police haul you off
to ask you about another murder!
They just had some questions.
Everybody has questions.
Susan and I aren't even
speaking because of it.
Bree, please.
I try to hold my
head up and smile
and just bake more pies
for the church social.
But now your ex is camped
out on our doorstep
like I am hosting some kind
of mormon slumber party,
And I do not know how I am gonna
bake my way out of this one!
Darling,
I swear to you, I will get
Alma out of that house.
I don't care if I have to live up to
my reputation and strangle her.
You're a good husband.
Have you lost
your mind?
I am not getting
you the pill.
Aunt Edie,
Julie and I are in love.
Oh, please. It's not love
you're feeling. It's hormones.
That's not true.
Okay, fine.
If you want to...
express your love, you
don't need to go all the way.
Kiss. Touch. Rub.
I mean, whatever happened
to heavy petting?
It's so underrated.
That's your advice?
Well, I'm sorry. I've never been good
at getting people not to have sex.
So you're not
gonna help us?
Julie, if I do this, your
mother would have my head.
You should
be talking to her.
I can't talk to her.
The whole idea of this
completely freaks her out.
She started screaming,
"sex kills."
So now it's
all in my lap.
God, she pisses me off.
Look, how about I spring
for a box of condoms?
Will that get you two
off my back?
Condoms are only
85% effective.
Is that true?
Damn. I thought I could coast
all the way to menopause.
Look, we're gonna have sex
whether you help us or not.
We're just trying
to be responsible.
All right.
But just so you know,
the responsible thing
is to abstain from sex
and focus on
your studies.
There. I said it out loud,
just in case anybody asks.
Gaby, I need
another pillow.
All right, don't take the
big one. That's my favorite.
It's only for
one night.
'Cause tomorrow I'm gonna be back
home sleeping in my own bed.
W hat?!
You can't abandon me!
There's a madman stalking me.
My life is on the line.
Do you know
how scared I am?
You're keeping that?
Hey, I'm scared,
but not of the dress.
Carlos!
Carlos, wake up!
I need you!
Oh, yeah, I thought
you'd come around.
What? No!
Hey!
He's here.
Don't!
Carlos, be careful!
He might have a gun!
I'm unarmed.
Stop kicking me!
Oh, now you're gonna
give me attitude?!
Gaby, we got him.
Maintain.
This jerk has been
terrorizing me.
He broke into
my house!
It  was a 6,000
dollars dress,
and my boss didn't want me
leaving it on the porch.
Your boss?
Hey, uh, ahem,
I'm sorry to wake you, sir,
But there was a problem
dropping off the gift.
Yes, and she's, uh,
right here... with me.
This is Gabrielle.
Who the hell is this?
Yes, I got your "token of esteem,"
and I'm not impressed.
Because you're freaking
me out, that's why!
No, I don't care how much it cost.
That's beside the point.
Really? That much?
Tell him if he doesn't stop harassing
you, you're gonna call the cops.
Look, I know you're
trying to be romantic,
but if you keep this up,
I'm gonna be forced...
What'd he say?
That's very
sweet of you,
but I am not the most
beautiful woman in the world.
Tell him you're gonna get
a restraining order on him.
Yes, I may be
in the top ten.
Gaby!
Hey, I'm talking here!
Your voice sounds so
familiar. Do I know you?
He says I know him,
and that he wants to
reintroduce himself at dinner.
Absolutely not.
I would not feel comfortable
meeting for dinner.
Good girl.
-How about lunch?
-Gaby!
But you have to promise to stop
buying me these expensive gifts.
Because I'm not
that kind of girl.
Well, for that many karats,
yes, I could be
that kind of girl.
Um,  I gotta go.
I'll talk to you tomorrow!
Oh, how about that?
And here I was, thinking some guy
wants to murder me in my sleep.
The night's still young.
How are those ribs?
Ah, just needed some tape.
Man, those guys were hard-core.
You really saved my ass.
Don't mention it.
No. Seriously.
Ever anything
I can do for you,
you just say the word.
I'll keep that in mind.
Hey, Delfino.
Yeah, boss?
You might wanna find
yourself another prom date.
Guy's not your friend.
How do you know that?
After those mutts knocked you
around the other day,
Your boy paid 'em off.
You sure?
I saw money
change hands.
Just watch your back.
So I was in the middle
of totally freaking out
when Julie assured me
that she's not having sex.
I can't tell you
how relieved I was.
Uh-huh.
Don't say "uh-huh" like that.
Julie wouldn't lie to me.
She says she's not having sex,
then she's not having sex.
Ooh-kay.
You can't say "ooh-kay"
like that, either.
Julie's not like other girls.
She's a straight-A student.
And you were
valedictorian.
What were you up to that
your mother didn't know about?
Okay, you search the closet.
I'm gonna look under the bed.
Wait, wait, wait.
First rule of ransacking...
Remember where
everything goes.
You are gonna make a really
good mother someday.
So what does this
diary look like?
Uh, it's small.
It's got a plaid cover.
Oh, and when you find it,
you have to read it,
because I promised her that I
would always respect her privacy.
Now help me
flip this mattress.
Oh( Oh, my God!
You found it?
This is adorable!
-You think maybe I could...
-No, you cannot borrow it.
Fine.
Why does Julie
have a VCR?
To watch movies.
Please. Kids don't watch videos
anymore. Everything's digital.
See? It's just a tape.
Is it?
Alma.
What do you think
you're doing?
Measuring for drapes.
I'm thinking damask.
You know
what I mean.
Why have you
moved here?
Well, it's a very
nice street,
and I've made
friends here.
People have taken
such an interest in me.
Yeah, they thought
you were dead.
The novelty of your not being
a corpse can't last forever.
What are you
after, hmm?
Are you still
punishing me?
You want me to pay
you to leave? What?
I want what I've
always wanted...
You.
I'm married.
And even if I weren't,
I don't love you.
You didn't love
the old Alma.
I'm not that
woman anymore.
I'm stronger,
more confident.
It may take you a while
to see that, but I can wait.
Alma, I love Bree.
But does she love you?
Oh, she may love
the Orson she knows...
But does she know
what you did to Monique?
Does she know you
ran over Mike Delfino?
I know all that.
I still love you.
Would she?
So I see you've
spoken to Mother.
Yes. It's nice to have someone
on my side in all of this.
Don't worry.
I won't tell Bree.
She might go
to the police,
And you're no good
to me in jail.
But if I thought I had
no chance with you,
no chance at all...
Well, there'd be nothing
to stop me from telling.
Please, Orson,
Don't take
away my hope.
She's not going.
Why not?
And what the hell was
that on the porch?!
She kissed me good-bye.
What was I supposed to do, slug her?
You went over there to
read her the right act.
Instead, it looked like you were
reading her a bedtime story.
Bree, I told her
we don't want her here.
I threatened, I shouted.
She refuses to go.
We're just gonna have
to make the best of it.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
You wanna meet for lunch?
No, honey, I got...
I gotta drive to greendale
to picout napkins.
Remember?
I told you.
Oh. Yeah, that's right.
So I'll, um,
I'll see you tonight.
Okay. Good.
I'll see ya.
Oh... my... God.
Hey, Mrs. Scavo.
Andrew, hi!
I thought you weren't
starting until the opening.
Oh, yeah, there's just so much
work that needs to be done.
Mr. Scavo asked me
to start early.
He's not here,
by the way.
Yeah, I know. And hey,
don't tell him I stopped by.
I'm not supposed to be here.
I just wanted to sneak a peek.
Shouldn't you
be working?
not be here?
Touché.
So, uh, how do you
like the place?
I think it's fantastic.
It's really coming together.
Oh, I love the bar.
Oh, yeah, it's, uh,
it's pretty cool.
It's too bad we can't
get a liquor license.
What?
Oh, uh, didn't
Mr. Scavo tell you?
No... he didn't.
Don't, um, restaurants make
half their money on the liquor?
Oh. Yeah. We're
completely screwed.
This is a nightmare.
How did this happen?
The city rezoned and said
he had to get all the residents
within a block to sign a waiver,
and there are
some holdouts.
He's kinda bummin'.
Well, then why isn't he dealing with
it Instead of shopping for napkins?
We could lose our
shirts in this dump!
Is this Dr. Marvin Tashman?
Hi. My name
is Susan Mayer.
My daughter Julie
came in to see you...
Yes, about birth control.
So I'm just curious...
Where do you get off prescribing
that without my consent?!
What?! No, I most
certainly was not there.
What do I look like?
I don't have blonde hair.
Wait, did my blonde
hair have dark roots?
I forgot to give you
the keys to the shed.
You got my daughter
the pill?!
Here. Catch.
Don't you walk
away from me!
-Do we have to do this now?
-Yes, we do.
You might have gotten your
first diaphragm with milk money,
but that doesn't give you the
right to corrupt my daughter!
Look, it's not like I went
after Julie and said,
"Hey, do you wanna go out for a
burger and some birth control?"
She came to me.
You do not get to
decide this for her!
What were
you thinking?!
I was thinking,
if Julie got knocked up,
that you and I could become
family, and I'm sorry,
-I cannot take that chance.
-Oh, you know what?
It wasn't till your rotten nephew came
to town that Julie was a perfect kid.
And now she's lying and scheming
and having casual sex!
She's just a boob job
away from being you!
Look, Mayer,
Julie has discovered sex.
The genie is out
of the bottle.
And you better get good with it,
or you could lose her forever.
'Cause like it or not,
she loves him.
And you know
what else?
He loves her.
Your gentleman friend
went to make a call.
-He'll be with you shortly.
-Thank you.
Gabrielle.
Zach Young!
Oh, my God!
It's been ages.
Look at you!
So handsome in a suit.
You look beautiful.
Aren't you sweet?
Uh, well, anyway,
I'd love to catch up,
but I'm kinda waiting
for someone.
Yes, I know.
So the dress fits. Cool.
I'd like a bottle of your 1982
Château Lafite Rothschild, please.
I'm sorry.
How old are you?
Why don't we say...
A hundred?
So you are.
Wow, someone got an
advance on their allowance.
I was my grandfather's
sole heir.
I'm actually
in the Fortune 400.
Does that seem
weird to you?
I'm on a date
with Zach Young.
Nothing's ever gonna
seem weird again.
Every cent we have
is circling the bowl,
and Tom never said a word.
Why didn't he come to me?
Well, clearly,
he's embarrassed.
-But I'm his wife.
-Don't be dense, Lynette.
Half the reason men
want to accomplish anything
is so they can show off
for the women they love,
and when they fail, they like
to keep it to themselves.
I'm gonna tell him.
I'm gonna tell him
I went to the restaurant,
and that I know he screwed up
and that I'm gonna fix it.
Oh, for God sake, it's bad
enough you cut off his cojones.
Now you wanna
juggle them?
My husband is
in trouble.
I love him. Shouldn't
I want to help him?
Well, if you really love him,
you should help him
without letting him
know that you did.
Yeah, so in addition
to my penthouse,
I also have a château
in Switzerland
and a cottage
in the Hamptons.
That's pretty
impressive, huh?
You got a little chocolate
on your shirt.
Damn it!
-Here, let me get it.
-No, I can do it! I can do it!
I'd like to do it myself,
thank you very much.
I'm sorry, I...
You know, I'll be neater
for you ne time.
Next time?
Honey, let's get real.
You are way too young for me.
I'm two months older
than John Rowland.
Well, John Rowland
was a mistake.
I was lonely.
You're not
lonely now?
You've heard
about my divorce.
Yeah. You were really smart
to get rid of Carlos.
You deserve
much better.
And let me guess,
now you're my upgrade?
Well, everybody knows you need
someone to take care of you and,
I'm rich now. I can give
you anything you want.
Wait a minute. Who says I need
someone to take care of me?
My Mom, her friends
from the neighborhood.
They said it was the only reason
you stayed with Carlos,
considering
how he treated you.
Well, they were wrong.
Thank you for
lunch, Zach.
Wait, Gabrielle.
I'm not that awkward
kid that I was before.
Can you please just...
Please take me
seriously.
I'm sorry. I just can't.
I'm not, I'm not
gonna give up.
Oh, sweetie.
I really wish
you would.
For God sakes, Zach!
Don't hijack a Ferrari if you
don't know how to drive!
Mr. Gaunt?
Hi, I'm Lynette Scavo.
My husband is opening the
pizzeria right down the block.
If it's about that
liquor license,
I'm not signing.
Please, I've been at this
for hours. Just hear me out.
Well, I never could
resist a pretty lady.
-Come on in.
-Thank you.
Did you live
in Las Vegas?
I was a croupier
for 40 years,
and as you can see,
I had a weakness for showgirls.
I bet you were
quite the player.
You have no idea.
Can I top you
off there?
No, thanks.
Two's my limit.
Well, suit yourself.
Look, I understand your
concerns about the license.
Your neighbors
had them, too.
But they signed the waiver
once I explained to them
that this is
a family restaurant.
No late nights,
no loud music.
If there's one thing
I learned in Vegas,
it's that booze turns most
people into noisy jackasses,
And I don't want 'em
puking on my doorstep.
Come on, Harry.
You are my last holdout.
What's it gonna
take? Cash?
Free pizza for the rest
of your life? You name it.
Look, I hate to disappoint a
pretty lady, but I'm not signing.
Harry,
my husband quit his job
to start this restaurant,
And if we can't sell liquor,
we can't make a profit...
And whoa, whoa, whoa,
Harry. eyes up here.
Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
This place is his dream,
and if he can't make it work,
then it's just gonna kill him,
And consequently,
it's gonna kill our marriage...
And, Harry, Harry,
what did I say?
I know, uh, uh,
I don't mean to be rude.
It's just that my showgirl
days were a while ago,
and I can't remember the
last time I laid eyes on a...
a beautiful woman's...
bosom.
Really?
Well, what if
I were to...
very briefly refresh
your memory?
Completely worth it.
Glad you thought so.
Come on, baby. Say it one
more time for Mommy.
So you can teach 'em
to say whatever you want?
Oh, yes. These birds
are very bright.
I think they're smarter
than people.
Some people, anyway.
Bree! Come in.
I just made some lemonade.
This isn't a social call.
We need to talk.
About what?
About what it's gonna take to get
you to sell this house and move.
Move? Why?
You're my husband's ex-wife.
You disappeared so people
would think he killed you.
Does my scomfort really need
any further explanation?
I had no idea
you felt this way.
Oh, please.
Orson made it perfectly clear
we don't want you here.
Okay, now I'm
really confused.
When Orson came by,
all he said was,
"Welcome to the street"
and did I need help unpacking.
That's not true.
You know what?
I think I've
said too much.
How about
that lemonade?
Ma'am, where would
you like this?
Ooh, uh, upstairs.
I'll show you.
Here, drink this.
You look a little pale.
Be right back.
Don't tell Bree.
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry.
I br... broke a glass.
Don't worry.
I'll get it.
Well, okay...
I have to go.
Bree...
Wait.
I understand why you might feel a little
threatened about my moving in here.
But in time,
you'll see I'm...
I'm perfectly harmless.
So... how was
the mystery date?
Uh, it was fabulous.
Thanks for asking.
Oh, come on.
I want details. Who is he?
He's some global financier,
Saw me on the cover
of "Paris Match."
Good-looking,
just not my type.
Really?
'Cause I always thought that you and
Zach would make a really great couple.
You son of a bitch.
You were there?
Parked across the street,
laughing my ass off.
I can't believe
you followed me.
I thought you were meeting a psycho
killer for lunch. I was worried.
Well, at least until they brought out
the crayons and children's menus.
-All right, off my porch.
-Okay, but don't forget,
you asked me to
watch your back.
Yeah, about that...
I'm installing an alarm
system tomorrow, so...
I'm not gonnaeed you to
look after me anymore.
Gaby, I don't mind.
I mind.
We're divorced. I can't keep running
to you every time I get scared.
I want to be the kind of woman
who can take care of herself.
Well...
Good for you.
I'm still right
down the block,
So if you do
need me...
I won't. But thank you.
Hi.
Hey.
You're home early.
I'm celebrating. We got
our liquor license today.
Really? That's great!
Yeah, Andrew said he went all over
the neighborhood getting signatures.
Good for him.
But I think he's lying.
I think somebody else
got the siatures.
Okay, let's say just for the sake of
argument, rhat someone else did,
someone who clearly
loves you very much.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing. Nothing. Order has
been restored in the universe.
You saved the day.
I'm a loser.
Ah, come on, Tom.
I tried for two months
to get that waiver signed.
You did it in a day.
Like I said...
You can't drown
in self-pity
just because I helped you
with one tiny little thing.
Okay, but if I tell you that
the plumbing's not up code,
that we have termites and that the chairs
won't be there until after we open,
can I drown
in self-pity then?
Why haven't you told
me about all of this?
Because I wanted to accomplish
something on my own.
I'm the man. I shouldn't have
to run to my wife to bail me out.
Ow!
Gambling with our life savings
and not asking for help
doesn't make
you a man.
It makes you an idiot.
Come on, Tom, for God
sakes, we are a team,
and that restaurant
is a huge undertaking.
No one could
do it alone.
You don't ask me for help
with your ad campaigns.
Ow!
I don't have to.
You're always giving it
to me, inspiring me.
Remember the mouthwash jingle?
You came up with the hook.
And what about
the Bartlett campaign?
Would I have ever come up
with tango-dancing fleas?
All you.
There's nothing that
I have accomplished
that I could have done
without your help.
Okay, fine. I help.
We're a team.
Just don't hit
me again.
So tomorrow, first thing,
we'll fix the plumbing,
we'll call an exterminator,
we'll rent some chairs,
and we will open on time,
and it'll be a glorious success
that you will have achieved
with my help, okay?
Okay.
And tonight I'm gonna slap on some sex
perfume and you're gonna get naked,
and then we're gonna
see who the man is.
God, I hope it's me.
Oh, I'm sure it will be.
Hey, Mom. What are
you doing out here?
Okay, here's the thing-
Don't worry, I'm not gonna
get mad. Just sit down.
You know what
upset me the most?
That you didn't trust me
enough to tell me the truth.
I tried to.
You freaked out.
Well, of course
I freaked out. I'm a parent.
You know, we hope that our
children will wait to have sex till...
after we're dead.
And you wonder why
I went to Edie.
Okay, that's the other thing.
That cannot happen anymore.
You and I have always had
an amazing relationship.
Let's not mess
it up now.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Look, I know you think
I'm too young, but...
Austin and I are in love.
Yeah, um...
About that...
God, I wish there was a pill you
could take to protect your heart.
What do you mean?
Honey, I...
I was over at
Edie's today and,
I walked in the door...
Uh, yes. I need to speak
to my husband.
Uh, yes. There he is.
Would you...
please ask him to come home
as early as possible tonight.
Thank you.
It's a dangerous world...
So we all look
for protection...
And whether we find it in
the arms of our mother...
Or at the end of
a jacket blade...
In the kiss of
our sweetheart...
Or at the end
of a barrel...
We do what we have
to, to feel safe...
Beacuse we know
somewhere in the world...
There are those who
will do us harm.