For those of you who are too
fucking busy,
here's what happened last week
on Shameless...
Karen, when do you want me
to come back in?!
Never!
That girl that you're with,
you'll knock her up.
You'll get a job at Best Buy.
And from that point on,
you won't be able
to hold the job very long
because you'll know the truth,
that you never lived
up to your potential.
I'm gonna give the baby up
for adoption.
How mucho we get for the baby?
I introduce you to a pool
of parents that want to adopt.
So you're a broker?
I'm gay!
You're the one that's pretending
to date Mandy
so you can fuck her brother.
Not doing this.
Doing what?
Figure out that chick
who's sitting on my sofa
wearing your wedding ring,
and then we'll talk.
Just don't give up on me.
You doing anything
this afternoon?
We need a coach.
Fiona go to the games?
Never misses one.
Call me "Coach."
Who's your friend?
Heard you can help me.
Need an alibi.
How much?
$1,500.
What are you doing?
Sending cash to my sons.
That will make Frank
very happy.
Frank gets none.
You and Monica are over, Frank.
Me and Monica are
getting married.
She's still married to me!
I have never, ever had
any intention of getting back
together with you, Frank.
Expelled?
You win.
School or leave!
What are you doing?
I'm not going back to school,
so I guess it means I'm leaving.
Good-bye, Sheila.
Good-bye, Peg.
Frank, your mother's passed.
Mom died!
Lip, come back!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ Know that it's not
for naught ♪
♪ You were beaming once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪ Round up the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that they're not
for naught ♪
♪ You were willing once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so... ♪
♪ Sure of? ♪
Lip?
Debbie?
♪ No one likes to be a fool ♪
♪ Calling down on
the telephone ♪
Lip?
Good morning, sweetheart.
Mom?
♪ Across the city,
across the sea. ♪
We don't have any money.
Mimosa?
Hello?
What? When?
Okay. Well, well, how much is
that gonna cost?
I-I have to call you back
with an answer.
Thank you.
Grammy died?
Honey, I am so sorry.
She was my mother.
I'm the one who's hurting here.
That was the Cook County
Hospital Morgue.
You need to claim her body
or they're gonna cremate her.
I am done running around
trying to please that woman.
Grammy died?
Debbie! Oh, Liam,
look at you,
my little Brown Bear.
Look how big you are!
How long is she staying?
Only forever and a day.
My camo pants still
in the dryer?
Ian! It's Ian.
Hell is she doing here?
I asked your mother
to come home.
Oh, wait,
you live here now, too?
I made breakfast.
Yeah, no, thanks.
Your mom spent a lot of time
making that breakfast!
Sit down, eat it!
This is bullshit.
Ian, wait.
I'm gonna wash
his mouth out with soap.
You can wash mine out.
I wanna fart bubbles.
Carlie!
Mom?
You're so big!
Come on, baby.
I made you breakfast.
Sit do and eat.
Where's Lip?
My mom showed up today.
She just came out of nowhere.
She staying?
Never does.
Lip playing hooky today?
He, uh, dropped out of school.
So Fiona gave him the boot.
I think he's
staying with Karen.
You know, you kill it
in one spot,
pops up in another.
You okay?
Yeah.
How's, uh, Mickey holding
up in juvie?
Called me a fuck-twat,
so he seems okay.
You should visit him.
Yeah, he's a little
pissed at me for something.
Thinks I pussied out.
Did you?
Kinda.
You're lucky your mom's dd.
Yeah.
So weird to have someone here,
and then they're just... gone.
I know.
What happens to their soul?
Maybe it's like what
happened to Karen in utero.
She was a twin, and then she
just absorbed the other one.
Whoa. You mean, like, maybe
Peggy's soul got absorbed by us?
Maybe.
Rats!
It says in order
to have a hospice license,
I have to get a nursing degree.
University of River Phoenix.
It's all online.
Seen the ads on TV.
Huh.
Hey! Hi!
Karen...
I know it's your choice,
but I just want
to go on record
as saying I think
you should consider
keeping the baby.
And Jody.
No offense, Lip.
None taken.
Since Frank bailed, can
I dump his Speed Stick
and English Leather
and put my stuff
back in the medicine cabinet?
Oh, sweetheart, you know,
both of you come sit down.
Sweetie...
ur grandmother's passing
has taken
quite a toll on Frank.
He just needs some time alone.
Mom, he packed
a duffle bag and left.
Sometimes when people
love each other very much,
they need time apart,
so when they come
back together,
their love is even stronger.
Okay, Mom.
Thanks for the talk,
Mrs. Jackson.
Sure.
Karen...
is Lip gonna stay overnight
again tonight?
I told you, he's just a friend.
Needs a place to stay.
Lip is very nice,
but I hope you see
what a catch Jody is.
Jody's an idiot.
Give it time.
"Then the window draws
full upon your mind.
There, beyond the sway
of curtains, men walk."
Maya Angelou said that.
I'm pretty sure she wasn't
talking about Jody,
but thanks, Mom.
Okay.
Are you really gonna do this
every morning?
Do what?
Show up, try to woo me?
I'm looking for Lip.
Uh-huh. What, I can't be
friends with your brother?
No, you can't.
Are we gonna have a funeral?
No.
Who died?
Grammy.
Wow. I'm sorry, guys.
A funeral requires a body,
and your father hasn't picked
her up yet.
So she's just laying somewhere
all alone?
Uh, we could have a memorial.
I mean, you don't need a body for that.
I spy doughnuts!
Hey, check it out, Steve.
It's a bloody butthole.
Awesome, dude!
School. Let's go.
Lunch?
Shit!
We already had that
for breakfast.
You know, sometimes
astronauts would have breakfast.
Lip never came back
after he blew out of here.
Check at Karen's.
Karen's?
Isn't she married?
Aren't you?
Technicality.
Good-bye.
Oh, such sweet sorrow.
You gonna drive us?
Absolutely.
No, he's not.
I mean it, Steve.
Stop coming around.
Who was that?
Are you still gonna be here when
we get home from school?
Absolutely.
I told you so.
Shut up!
You didn't believe her either.
You know what I think?
I think we should paint
your room a new color today.
Here. Go now!
Have fun at school!
Hey...
I got this.
So, where is Lip?
Really? That's what
you want to ask me?
Should've known.
He's always been your favorite.
That is not true, Fiona.
Oh, that's right.
You're your favorite.
So, uh...
Bob throw you out, or you
walk out on her, too?
Your father came to me.
He needed me.
Told me you needed me, too.
He lied. We don't.
I'm sorry. I'm here now.
I want to try and start over.
Will you let me?
Lip dropped out of school.
I told him, back in school
or he couldn't live here.
You threw him out?
He left.
He's family, Fiona.
Lip chose to leave this family.
That sound familiar?
Look at my two girls,
together in the kitchen.
I don't know which one
of you is prettier.
I don't have time for this.
I got to get Liam dressed.
Where you taking him?
He comes to work with me.
No, that's silly. Leave him home.
His mother.
Come on, let me prove to you
that I can take care
of him, please.
You're gonna be me all day?
Absolutely.
You're not going to ave
with him?
Run off and join the circus
or some crazy shit like that?
I just want to take care
of my baby, Fiona.
Thank you.
Ooh, we're going to have so much
fun, my little Brown Bear.
Uh, milk and water
from the sippy cup.
Got it. And he's got to drink
it from a big boy cup.
I'm going to drink a beer
from a big boy cup.
Want to watch?
Yeah.
You know, I saw
Choady sneaking out
when we came in.
My mom lets him in
when I'm not home.
It's like having
a wet Labrador.
Fucking clueless.
So... how long are you
planning on staying?
What, you mean here?
Mom wants to know.
Says I have to charge you rent.
Your mom wants me to pay rent?
Well, how much?
$100 a week.
What aunt dead daddy's
insurance money?
My check's tied up at
the claims department.
I could stay in the basement.
Could knock $20 off, but...
still going have to charge you.
Fuck you, Karen.
Isn't that how we got
into this mess?
You know what?
And fuck me going on any more
of the adoption interviews.
You know, good luck
signing off on an
adoption without
the biological father's
signature.
I'll get Frank to go with me.
Might not even have
to cut him in.
♪ Till you walked out the door ♪
♪ And I've seen
that face before ♪
♪ Now I'll always
wonder why... ♪
I'm always pleasantly surprised
we don't find dead hookers
cut up in the toilets.
There's still time.
Where's Liam?
Monica dumped Bob
and showed up on our doorstep
to play house.
She insisted on
watching Liam today.
He's probably got his tongue
in an outlet by now.
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
First thing she did
was bu my balls
for kicking Lip out.
You didn't kick him out.
Feel like I might have,
giving him an ultimatum.
I miss him.
Especially with Monica home.
Lip usually has my back
in that fight.
See, this is the kind of shit
I'm afraid of happening
if Kev and I have a kid or two.
Little fuckers gang up on you.
I've seen this movie before.
Monica comes home long enough
to reunite with Frank,
gets knocked up
with another kid, then splits.
Not this time.
Not gonna let her ruin Debbie
and Carl's lives, too.
Trash can's a foot away, people.
Why you got to be
such nasty pigs?
Human nature.
Given the choice, people
usually do the wrong thing.
Can't take it anymore.
I'm going to run home,
check on Liam
before we hit the ground floor.
Not a lot of trust in Monica.
Might be nice to have some time
for an actual life
while she's around.
Ain't you just the queen
of silver linings?
Live a little while you can.
Ugh.
What?
Hey, where'd you disappear to?
I didn't know I had to report
to you,
but if you must know, school.
Right. Look.
I'm sorry about that shit
that happened earlier.
Give me the rest of the day
to find a new place to stay?
Fine.
And, um...
I want to go on the rest
of the adoption meetings
with you, all right?
You know,
I-I'd kind of like to have
a say in where this kid
might end up.
Well, go if you
fucking want to go,
but I don't need help
or handouts from anyone.
Hey, Ron.
I need to talk to you.
What the hell
are you doing here?
My wife's inside.
Thing is, I'm kind of pregnant,
and it's yours.
What? I want to get an abortion,
but I can't afford it,
and I can't apply for a
credit card 'cause I'm not 18.
Hang on.
We had fun, though, didn't we?
Sometimes, when I see
the word "hospice"
on the screen, I pronounce it
"ho spice" in my head.
Isn't that silly?
Sometimes I do that
with "butt... ermilk."
But... "ermilk's"
not really a word.
Did you just hear
what you just said?
You said, "Buttermilk's
not really a word."
Oh. I did.
Did you hear that?
Been hearing a lot of
weird noises the last few days.
So have I.
Don't think I'm crazy,
but sometimes I think
Eddie's spirit is
still in this house.
Eddie?
Mom had a huge chunk of cash
lying around
before she kicked it.
Aah!
How much?
75 large. Oh, God!
I think it's at Sheila's.
Get it.
Hmm? Get it, and give it to me.
Yeah? Okay.
Yeah. Give it to me.
Oh! Jesus Christ!
Really? In the kitchen?
I thought you were
working, honey.
- Where's Liam?
- He's sleeping!
And I will remind you
this is our house
and we can make love
in any room we want to.
Your kids eat off that table!
Let's fuck in her room next.
Give it to me! Give it to me!
♪ "C" sounds like "ssss" ♪
♪ When it begins words
like "circle..." ♪
Circle doesn't start
with an "S"? What the fuck?
♪ Like cat... ♪
Cat! I know that shit, bitch.
That's a cat!
You ordering shit off the TV again?
Just a little bit
of this, honey.
Just a little bit of this!
Hey, I'll see you after work.
All right.
Bitch Karen's trying
to make me pay rent.
Can you believe that shit?
Hey, you want
to play a quick game
The Third before my shift?
What, you got it?
Hell, yeah, I got it.
I waited in line.
Hey, um...
cool if I stay at your place
a couple days?
Shit, yeah.
Kevin.
Kitchen.
Lip is not staying with us.
We are not getting in the middle
of this Gallagher shit storm.
You guys are taking
Fiona's side on this?
Fiona will have our asses
for harboring her fugitive.
What if we adopt Lip
as our own?
Wouldn't that change everything?
Damn. Calm down.
Go home Lip.
I'm sorry, dude.
You can't stay here.
Well, what the fuck, man?
Yeah, well, thanks
for all your help, Kev.
Your taxes done or your
liquor commission test taken
or you get your tongue stuck
to a frozen pole, all right?
I like to wash her
late in the day.
In the sun,
the water can dry too fast
and leave spots.
Good to know.
She send you?
No. She doesn't
know I'm here.
She needs you, Bob.
You're the best thing that
ever happened to her.
I don't want shit to do
with that bitch anymore.
Especially now that
her snatch is on
that nasty old
Irish cock of Frank's.
Pass.
You don't love her?
Love ain't got nothing
to do with it.
Living with Monica was like
living with a black hole.
Drained my spirit
and my bank account.
Bitch spent all my money
on meditation retreats
and unfinished,
half-assed
home renovations!
Thank the good Lord
Frank showed up when he did.
Frank came looking for her?
Crying like a little bitch
about his dead mama.
Shit, they're pathetic--
both of them!
Monica's your problem now.
Presenting His and Her Lordship,
Frank and Monica Gallagher!
Holy shit.
About time.
You still got an open
tab running, bitch.
Kate! How are you, baby?
Better without
your bad influence.
Oh, please, give me a break.
Hey, Monica.
Hi, Gus! Wow.
New tattoo?
Yeah, yeah.
Good one, huh?
Oh, Kev!
You remembered.
Irish Car Bomb.
How could I forget?
I'll have one of
those, too, K-Ball.
You can't handle
an Irishar Bomb.
You look good, Moni.
You back on your meds?
Ah, hell, no.
That crap makes me all foggy
and gets me fat.
Besides, I am not bipolar.
Give me a dollar.
Good to see ya, Monica.
Here you go, Frank.
Dance with me.
♪ I go out walkin' after
midnight ♪
♪ Out in the moonlight
just like we used to do ♪
♪ I'm goin' walking... ♪
When they're good, they're good.
I'm betting two weeks,
three tops.
♪ After midnight,
searchin' for you ♪
♪ I walk for miles
along the highway... ♪
I love you, baby. Aw.
♪ Well, that's just my way of
sayin' I love you ♪
She's in a better
place, Frankie.
♪ I'm always walkin' after
midnight searchin' for you ♪
♪ I stop to see a weepin' willow
cryin' on his pillow ♪
♪ Maybe he's cryin' for me... ♪
Most fun with...
Oh, my golly, I'm getting
felt up everywhere.
You are going into my...
Come in. Take your coat off. Stay a while.
Take all your clothes off.
Get nude.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, my baby.
Like a library in here.
♪ I remember ♪
♪ How the stars stole
the night away... ♪
Can you take this
somewhere else, please?
It's a school night.
The kids are already asleep.
Oh, come on!
You know Carl can sleep
through anything. Hey, hey!
Everybody, I found some chips
and semihard doughnuts.
Semihard will
still knock you up!
♪ Ba-de-ya ♪
♪ Say, do you remember ♪
♪ Ba-de-ya... ♪
Hey. Some of us want to
graduate and do something
with our lives, so
how about you all
shut the fuck up
and let me sleep?
Do not talk to your mother
like that, little fucker. Hey!
Hey.
Jesus!
Apologize to him.
What?
Apologize!
I'm sorry.
What is going on?
Grab your earplugs,
go back to bed, Debs.
Debbie!
Hi, honey.
Debs, now.
Debs, you want to come play?
Yeah.
No.
Butt off, Beezus.
Monica's got to go.
She's your mother, Fi.
You only get one.
It's like watching a
hurricane head for shore.
You had Monica for years
before she took
her little sabbatical.
Give Debbie some Mommy time.
Why am I always the
one compromising?
Nights like tonight are legend.
A memory
Debs can carry with her always.
Don't screw her out of that.
Might be the only one she gets.
♪ Only blue talk and love,
remember ♪
♪ The true love we share today ♪
♪ Ba-de-ya ♪
♪ Say, do you remember ♪
♪ Dancing in September? ♪
♪ Ba-de-ya... ♪
20 minutes, Debs,
then back in bed.
♪ Ba-de-ya-de-ya ♪
♪ Say, do you remember ♪
♪ Dancing in September? ♪
Out of my seat.
What, this seat?
You got to have this seat?
All right.
It's all yours, pal.
Shh.
Mom hid the money
in here somewhere.
Be vewy quiet.
I'm hunting wabbits.
Just the house... settling.
Wind. It's...
the wind settling the house.
Shh! Shh!
Karen?
Smells like Bengay in here.
Look inside the cushions.
Mom was always
a big cushion hider.
Okay.
Nope.
Go. What?
No! No, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait.
Eddie?
Is that you?
I don't know
exactly what it is...
that you want...
But I'm... I'm here
to talk.
Can you talk, Eddie?
Well, that's
a silly question, isn't?
'Cause, if you couldn't,
you wouldn't be able
to tell me.
Huh?!
Hey, Professor,
you got a minute?
Got a classroom
full of freshmen
staring at a Smart Board.
Just wondering if you,
uh, had any work for me.
Work after school?
Uh, no, I, uh...
I-I dropped out.
I got a baby on the way.
Was wondering if you
could hook me up
as a TA or something.
You can't do shit
without a diploma.
Well, tell them I'm an
idiot savant or something.
I'll tell them you're an idiot.
When don't you call me when you
graduate with a 4.5 GPA?
Wow, so, uh,
under the liberal beard
lives an uptight
bourgeois prick.
You think I like
being a soothsayer
and watching you live out
your Jerry Springer fate?
Congratulations--
you're a high school dropout
with a pregnant girlfriend.
And the only thing
that's missing for you
is a job at Mickey D's.
And if you work really hard,
you might
get your picture
with the dead eyes
in the employee of
the month frame
over the cash register.
Huh?
That would be fun, wouldn't it?
Go back to school.
Good boy.
Yum.
What's this?
There's no more room
in this world for
another Gallagher.
Birth control--
you either hop on
the Ortho bandwagon or leave.
It's okay to take it
with your shrink meds.
I checked.
That the same speech
you gave Lip?
Same speech, different outcome.
Thanks.
No biggie. If they
haven't shut down
our Planned Parenthood yet,
we can make you an appointment
to get your own RX.
No.
Thanks for everything.
For taking care of my kids,
my house, my husband.
We all did it.
No.
You did it, Fi.
And I know
what a huge sacrifice
it must have been.
And I can probably never
make it up to you,
but I want to try.
Thanks.
So the whole...
Bob thing
was just a phase or what?
You sure you're not
going to need these?
Mmm. Not lately, but who knows?
What about the guy
who came by yesterday?
Steve.
I remember him.
He's cute.
I would totally hit that.
Ew. Mom!
No, I'm not gonna.
Better not.
I'm already up against
a hot Brazilian.
He's got a girlfriend?
Wife.
Fiona!
Oh, you're going to judge me?
So... how we gonna
get rid of her?
Yeah.
She's gone!
Oh, this is nice.
Estefania's dad.
Huh. Now, you
realize you guys
basically have
the same name, right?
Look, I can get you
back in my sister's lap if you
let me stay here for a bit.
How long you need to stay?
Just till I'm back on my feet.
Well, always saw myself
living with a Gallagher.
Just always thought
it would be Fiona.
Listen, you put me up for a bit,
it'll piss her off so much
she'll be back at your doorstep
in a heartbeat.
Listen--
maybe, in exchange
for staying here,
you can help me out.
Putting together
a pretty big deal.
I-I don't know.
Last time I helped you out
with a deal,
I ended handcuffed to a bench.
You know how to hack
a voice mail?
Probably. For
the right price.
Hi. Oh.
Right. Remember me?
Uh, Lip.
Oh, that's...
There's a robe in the bathroom.
You can use the robe.
El robio.
Jesus.
R-Robio.
Oh, bye-bye.
Okay.
Shit, man, I got
to be somewhere.
You got a key?
Uh, I'll leave one for you
at the front
desk. Here.
I'll, uh, do my best,
Mr. Murdoch.
Hearing from you was a
wonderful surprise. Oh.
I thought we'd
lost you for good.
Well, my recently-deceased
husband was born again.
Mm-hmm.
So we went to that church
with all the guitars
and the minister
with the Hawaiian shirt.
Well, I'm just so glad
that you accepted my invitation.
Actually, there was a favor
I wanted to ask.
Mm-hmm.
Someone else home?
No.
Do you believe in
evil spirits, Father?
I believe people can
become harassed by evil spirits
as a result of evil actions.
Hmm.
Until they repent,
those spirits linger.
Well, any idea how one might
cast them out of one's house
before one opens
a hospice business?
Well, in Matthew
5:22, Jesus says
that we need to repent...
Mm-hmm.
Forgive and love.
Is there someone
you need to forgive?
Anything you need to repent?
Relax.
Go into the light!
Nothing comes to mind.
But I'll pray on it.
Jody! My man!
Hey, Frank.
You just missed lunch.
Just getting something
from the Kash and Grab.
Headed there myself.
Really sorry
about your mom, man.
Must be tough.
It is.
There's so much I still
want to say to her.
So many questions.
She loved you, Frank.
Just didn't know how to say it.
Yes. I know that now.
Also know she was sitting on
a pretty big pile of money.
Wanted me to act as an
executor of her will.
Any idea where
she kept the cash?
In the cushions.
I knew it.
But then she divided it up.
Gave Sheila a grand
to say thanks
and had me mail the rest.
What? Mail it?
Where? To who?
Whom.
What?
To whom.
To whom the fuck
did she mail the
fucking money?!
They were all Gallagher names.
It was, uh, Wyatt,
Clayton, I think.
My fucking brothers?!
Where were they at the bitter
end?! Holding her hand?!
No, that was--
That bitch!
Shit!
Talk to you later.
Fuck!
Goddamn it!
Oh, shit.
Carl, I might've
shrunk your jersey.
Oh, hi.
I thought you were Carl.
Mom?
This is Little Hank.
That's your mom?
Hey, handsome.
Made some cookies.
Did you pick up
Grammy's body yet?
No, not yet, honey.
It's expensive.
I have some money.
No.
Look at you.
Like living with
a slutty Doris Day.
Did you have any luck
finding it?
Nope.
No? Not even in her
box of horrors.
Mom sent it to my brothers
Deb, I made you
a matching cheer outfit!
It's up on your bed.
Grammy's body?
Not too cute in a cheer outfit.
Where is she?
They've got her on ice, honey.
There's no rush.
Heard a girl's mom's
the best way to tell how
a girl's gonna look.
You're gonna be
a fucking fox, man.
Hey, sweetie.
I made some cookies.
Oh, so now we're, like, square
for you abandoning us
and everything.
Hey.
Are you coming with us
to Carl's game?
Yeah, I'm going to Carl's game.
I always go to Carl's games,
'cause I actually give a shit.
Ian Clayton Gallagher,
I told you,
do not talk to your
mother like that.
You haven't even claimed your
mom's body from the morgue
and you want to tell
me how to treat mine?
He's got a point.
Your dad told me about
the kid in the store.
You must be sad having someone
you care about in jail.
But you should never
feel ashamed about
what and who you are.
I'm not.
Well, when I was with
Roberta, I was proud.
No, it wasn't a
perfect relationship,
but we were never ashamed.
Maybe you should have been.
So how about, after Carl's
game, I take you out?
Cheer you up.
Maybe.
Less ogling, more hacking.
Jesus, I'm in the
voice mailbox.
I just need to figure out
how to copy the messages
without people being able to
tell they were ever listened to.
You want to tell me
what this is all about?
Less you know, the better.
Now I'm off to lead a pack
of tiny, testosteroned animals
to victory.
Gonna warm 'em up and give 'em
my best Fray Night Lights
speech about
hearts and eyes or some shit.
I don't know.
Where go?
Uh, the game.
Football.
I go.
Uh, Lip, you mind
bringing Este later?
What do you think?
Uh, Lip will bring you later.
You go con Lip.
Ah, yes!
I come on Lip.
With!
You come with Lip.
Okay?
♪ You haven't even put me
to your mouth yet ♪
♪ And I'm already
ready to blow ♪
♪ White satin sheets
untouched for weeks ♪
♪ Not even
your girlfriends know ♪
♪ I swear if you touch me
I'm gonna explode ♪
♪ Plume of smoke for sure ♪
♪ And there ain't no way ♪
♪ For me to make it out
tonight ♪
Come on Carl!
I'll take two.
Your family's pretty cool, Red.
Hut!
Go, go, go!
Lip!
Lip! Come on,
honey, sit down.
Come on, sit with us!
What, I'm off the
boat for one minute
and there's a fucking mutiny?
Yeah, well no one told you
to get out of the boat.
Actually, you did.
Hey, Lip, don't
be mad at Fiona.
Come on.
Hey, Monica, shut up.
You know what,
like most of my life,
this has nothing to do with you.
I sit?
What? Yeah, sit.
Wherever's fine.
Oh, you babysitting now?
Roommate.
You're living at Steve's?
Yeah, no curfews,
no ultimatums,
no befriending the enemy
behind my back.
Come on. She just showed up.
What was I supposed to do?
Oh, really?
Oh, you're just gonna
storm off like a baby?!
Too bad there's no door
you can slam!
Your son's a real prick.
Hut!
That's what I'm talking about!
Yeah!
Yes! All right, nice effort
out there, D'Shawn.
Just try throwing the ball to
someone on your own team next time.
Lip's living with you?
He was sleeping on the El.
Kid had nowhere else to go.
They're ten. Have them
run the ball, for Christ's sake.
You're going out. You're going
out. Go, go, go, go, go, go!
So, my friend Flying Crow...
Yeah?
...said smudging is
a surefire way
to get rid of evil
spirits in a house.
Be gone, spirits.
In the name of
our Savior Jesus Christ,
we ask that you leave.
And you don't want
to piss him off,
so just go, okay?
I really am so sorry
about all of this with Karen.
Her throwing you out.
I-I feel so responsible
for her behavior.
Don't.
It's not your fault
she's going through
a hard time.
Yes, but even so,
you deserve better.
You're a good man, Jody.
We should pray on it.
Yeah.
Why don't you get
your own fries?
'Cause I want to eat yours.
So, I was minding
my own business,
listening in on
Estefania's phone call.
Turns out she's totally
in love with some other guy.
You know, she's playing Steve.
So?
So you think I should
tell him about it?
What's in it for you if you do?
It's not about me.
Exactly. If there's
no money involved,
don't get other people's
sh on your shoes.
So you're saying if I was rich,
then you'd consider
keeping the kid with me?
How rich? Because
if you were that rich,
there's no way you'd think
you still wanted this kid.
You might think you do now,
but in the long run?
Hi.
I'm Alana.
This is Jeff.
Sorry I got started
without you guys.
Have to keep
the little guy fed.
So, you're 17?
Oh, yeah, we both are.
So, what do you drive?
Your cars?
Um,
I drive
a Lexus and Alana's
got a Volvo.
Two cars.
You guys are flush.
Uh, is Lip here?
Oh, no.
Lip no home.
Nice surprise.
Throw him out.
What?
He needs to be in school.
I'm not his father,
and more importantly,
you're not his mother.
Yeah.
If I was, I would've
beaten him black and blue
with a wooden spoon.
You don't always have to be
responsible for everyone, Fiona.
Excuse me?
Monica's back.
Enjoy it.
Take the GED.
Read a book.
Fuck you.
Truth?
I took in the bear cub
looking to rile
the adult female.
Hoping she'd charge over here.
Dangerous.
She might rip your head off.
Hasn't yet.
Truth?
I'm here to see Estefania.
Really?
Hey,
Este, Fiona wants to
take you out tonight.
Huh?
Uh, drinking.
Dancing.
Con Fiona.
Ah!
You're such an asshole.
Enemies closer, right?
He can't stay here.
Promise me you'll kick him out.
Ah, Lip.
What the hell was that about?
You.
Me and Bob used to come here.
It's a great mix of gay, lesbian,
bi and some cool breeders.
It's, uh, a little weird
being ut" with you.
No shame, baby.
See? But don't even think
about coming out at school.
Somebody in that neighborhood
will knife you, for sure.
Think I'll get carded?
Nah. You're the bread
and butter here.
They need fresh meat to
keep the old guys coming in.
Ooh. 3:00. That guy
is totally checking you out.
You're kidding, right?
Shit, 9:00.
♪ 'Cause tomorrow morning,
we'll be leaving ♪
That kind of takes your mind
off the kiin juvie, right?
♪ You better jump right in ♪
♪ Tomorrow morning,
we'll be leaving ♪
He's in there 'cause of me.
♪ Let's keep it rockin'
till daylight ♪
♪ Gotta live like
we got one night ♪
♪ One night, one night,
gotta live like... ♪
I'm sorry you're hurting, baby.
♪ 'Cause you know we just got
one life, one life, one life ♪
Want to dance?
♪ Falling in love
on the dance floor ♪
Okay, okay.
♪ Girl, you and me will make
this last forever ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ The future is so bright ♪
Here's to shirking
responsibilities,
not working for the man,
and the women love.
All right.
Does Fiona talk about me?
What, you're gonna break
your happy home with Estefania?
I'm not in love with her,
but I shit myself every time
I think about what her dad
would do if I dumped her.
That's goo 'cause she
doesn't love you either.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No, I heard them on the phone.
Pretty hot and heavy.
Sneaky bitch.
She's such a fucking bitch.
I mean, how do you put up with her? You...
Estefania?
No, fucking Fiona.
You know what? she was right
to kick you out of the house.
You should be in school.
Yeah, well, maybe I'll
enroll again in May.
Just in time to take
your wife to prom.
Okay.
Uh, I'm gonna change.
Uh, my-my clothes.
Okay.
Uno momento. Si?
Why don't you just
donate her to science?
Don't want her!
Listen, please,
don't throw her away.
I-I... how much
would it cost to bury her?
That much?
I'm just so wasted right now.
Could we talk about
this tomorrow?
Please?
Thank you.
My mother, even dead,
she's a pain in the ass.
Hey!
Hi, you guys!
Wha...
Hey, hey.
Who is this?
Uh, that is Steve's wife.
Oh, the Brazilian!
Hi!
We brought doughnuts
and a bucket of chicken.
Oh!
Look what the cat drug in.
Hey, what are you doing?
Come on.
This is not okay.
Oh, come on.
Fi!
Fi, will you just...
Now it is.
Why the hell weren't we invited?
Vodka, lemonade, blender.
Everybody, shut up.
Hey! Debbie would like to
take this opportunity
to say a few words
about Grammy Gallagher.
Well, I guess what
I'm gonna say is that
Grammy will be missed.
And if she's watching
right now,
I want her to know
that we love her.
To Grammy.
Grammy!
I love this.
Being back with you guys, it's
like the best rush in the world.
I been working on it.
♪ A drug that's the high
and not the pill ♪
♪ But did you know
that when it snows ♪
♪ My eyes become large ♪
♪ And the light that you shine
can't be seen? ♪
Look at me!
♪ I compare you to ♪ Oh!
Mom?
- Can I come in?
- Uh, no,
honey, not right now.
I have to... um,
I'm busy with something.
♪ Now that your rose is in bloom...
♪ Ba-da-da ba-da-da-da-da-da
ba-da-da. ♪
Where the hell did you go?
Don't be mad.
I went ahead and paid
for your mom's ashes.
You need the closure, baby.
I can't believe
she's really gone.
Your mother...
was a real cunt.
Amen.
Breakfast of champions, I see.
Gallagher!
I paid you!
I paid you, Terry!
What the...?!
Shit!
What the fuck, Milkovich?!
Get the fuck off me, you crazy
bitch; this ain't about you.
Frank, what the hell did you do?
Why is it always my fault?
My... little...
princess...
Leave him alone!
My Mandy's pregnant,
and this little
shit's gonna pay.
Atta boy.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com