[Knocking on door]
[Grunts lightly]
Officer: Albuquerque police. Hello.
[Knocking continues]
Sir, we'd like to talk with you
for a minute.
Could you open the door, please?
Look, we know you're in there.
You're casting a shadow
through your peephole.
All we want to do is talk.
Would you please open the door?
[Sighs]
I'd, uh, I'd prefer not to, officers.
Tommy: Sir, come on and open up.
[Sighs] I have a condition.
Uh, I can't go outside
or be exposed to what's out there.
You were able to come outside
to steal your neighbor's newspaper.
Chuck: I didn't steal it.
I left $5.
The... the cover price is 50 cents.
Did your neighbor consent
to sell you her paper?
I, uh... [sighs]
She... I... Isn't...
[Sighs]
L... um, officer, let's... let's...
Let's talk about something
called "probable cause."
As I'm sure you know,
in the state of New Mexico,
there is a two-part test
to determine whether police officers
have an objectively reasonable basis...
[Birds chirping]
The situation a-as missing, versus Arizona,
as I pointed out, uh, creates an event...
Hey, Tommy. Come around here, would you?
And that's why the
10th circuit court of appeals
ruled that a coercive order...
Check this out.
Requiring an individual
leave his house is seizure...
And, therefore,
protected under
the fourth amendment, right?
Tommy: Whole lot of camp-stove fuel.
Guy sure as shit sounds like a tweaker.
You see what he did to the breaker box?
Is he coming out, or are we going in?
Officer: You got 10 seconds
to open this door,
or it's coming down. You hear me?
- Ah.
- Final warning!
Okay, I'll... I'll... I'll...
I'll let you in,
but you have to leave
your electronic devices outside.
No phones, no walkie-talkies,
no flashlights...
Definitely, definitely no tasers.
I can't emphasize that enough. Deal?
Or... look, look. I'll give the paper back.
[Thudding]
[Electricity hums]
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
[vehicle approaches]
[Beeps]
Big Ricky: Yeah?
Uh, James McGill to see Mr. Richard Sipes.
Ricky... call me "Ricky."
Come on in.
[Motor whirring]
[Brakes squeal]
[Sighs]
[Keys jingling]
[Exhales sharply]
Uh. Uh, this is my assistant's car.
[Chuckles]
Well, my Mercedes is in the shop.
[Clicks tongue]
[Chuckles] I ought to give him
a raise. You're right.
Big Ricky: Jim, I saw you on the TV...
That billboard thing.
And I had me a pair of insights.
[Operatic music plays] Insight the first...
You ain't afraid to put yourself out there.
And insight the second...
You believe in the real America...
Freedom, self-sufficiency.
I do.
I... I really do.
When I see a man like you
driving that foreign shitbox of a car...
Well, see, actually, it's...
It's a sign a good man
can't get ahead today.
It's a damned travesty. That's what it is.
Well, that may be [clears throat] Ricky,
but, uh...
I refuse to consider myself a victim.
You know, we are once again
at a point in our history
where the fly-swatting hand of government
is crushing the spirit
of entrepreneurship...
Taxes, osha requirements,
the I.N.S. poking their big, fat nose
into every mother-loving hire.
It's damned oppressive.
It's tragic.
It's un-American.
Jim, I think you are
just the lawyer I need,
'cause I got me a case...
Major... I say, a major case.
Are you ready to clear your calendar?
[Glass thuds]
[Sighs] Ricky, I'm all ears.
I want to secede from the United States.
Now, I got 1,100 acres of property here,
self-sustaining with solar power and wells,
a sovereign state immune to
the business-killing regulations
of the country in which
it geographically lies.
We are going to be America's Vatican city.
[Sighs]
Ricky...
I'm your man.
Yeah, let's do this.
Let's show 'em all.
Yee-haw!
Yee-haw! [Laughs]
Yes! We are doing this!
Ah. [Glasses clink]
Now, it's not gonna be easy, sir.
I mean, the government is
gonna fight us tooth and nail.
We could end up in the supreme court...
I'm talking thousands of man-hours...
I mean, years of effort.
[Sighs]
Are you ready for that?
Me?
I say bring 'em on.
Let's talk Turkey.
What's your rate?
[Breathes deeply]
$450 an hour.
The hell with hourly.
I want you on retainer.
How about $1 million even...
$500,000 up front
and $500,000 when we're done?
A million? [Clears throat]
That seems... Fair.
Would you like that in cash?
[Footsteps]
[Music continues]
[Lock clicks, handle turns]
Uh.
Well...
Tax-free and backed by
the full faith and credit
of the sovereign Sandia Republic.
It's, uh...
[Sighs]
Son... You are getting in
on the ground floor.
[Chuckling]
[Doorbell rings]
Mr. McGill, hi.
Thanks so much for coming.
Roland Jaycocks. Roland.
Hey, Roland. Great to meet you.
You can call me "Jimmy."
Jimmy, absolutely.
Uh, hello. Please, come on in.
Oh, well, thank you.
God, what was it like
climbing that billboard?
Must have been pretty scary, huh?
Guy needed help... that's all.
You know, if I could do it, anybody could.
[Chuckles]
Well, my hat is off to you.
So, here we are.
And patent law is something you...
Oh, yeah. In fact,
I... I do so many patent cases,
I should probably just go ahead
and specialize already.
[Chuckles] So, what do we got?
Uh, I feel silly asking this. Yeah.
But before I show you my invention,
would you mind signing
a non-disclosure agreement?
You got it. No problem.
It's my idea of a lifetime.
If Fisher-price or Playskool
ever got their hands on this...
No worries.
You ready?
I may have seen one of these before.
Not like this.
This one has this little unit I've added.
This is my invention.
Do you have children?
No.
My wife and I have two boys... 4 and 6.
And let me tell you...
Toilet-training them?
Nightmare, both times.
They just didn't want to use the commode.
So I wired a motion sensor to a voice chip,
and, well, no sense getting all technical,
but it's all about positive reinforcement.
Meet Tony the toilet buddy.
And when you sit down to do your business,
this is how he works.
[Clanks]
Oh, yeah, that's the way!
Gosh, you're big!
You're so big!
My goodness!
Look at you!
[Clanks]
Fill me up, Chandler!
Put it in me!
Chandler's my youngest... loves it.
Huh.
[Clanks]
Give it to me, Chandler! I want it all!
Mmm!
Ahhh!
Anyway, it goes on from there.
You get the picture.
Yeah, I, uh...
Yeah.
So, what do you think?
It's a little sexual, maybe?
Sexual? What... what does that...
Suggestive, maybe...
Maybe that's a better word. [Chuckles]
Look, I'm not...
I'm not saying
this thing won't make you rich.
I mean, some of your wealthier
pacific rim nations...
They'll love this... the crazy bastards.
[Chuckles]
I created this for children...
Children, understand?
Well, hey,
Viagra was originally invented
to treat hypertension.
Look how that turned out.
You're completely disgusting,
you know that?!
Hey, buddy, you're the one
with the sex toilet.
Get off my property!
Hey, you know what?
I hope you do make a fortune,
'cause Chandler's gonna need it
to help pay for his therapy!
[Brakes squeal]
[Gearshift clicks]
[Engine clicking, shuts off]
[Whirring]
[Sighs]
I found the alpine Shepherd boy!
[Whirring continues]
[Sniffles]
[Sighing]
[Whirring stops]
[Beeping]
No, no. You just stay put.
I'll be right over.
[Clock ticking]
[Sighs]
Oh.
[Clears throat]
[Breathes deeply]
Now, where were we?
Oh, would you like some more tea?
No! No, thank you. I'm... I'm fine.
Now, the Shepherd boy Hummel...
That's gonna go to your nephew Clarence?
As long as he finishes college. Okay.
If he drops out,
it goes to my niece Raylene.
But then, Raylene doesn't get the girl...
The girl with the geese. Mm.
Yeah. No, then that would go
to your cousin Helen...
Mm-hmm.
So long as she never remarries Frederick?
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
And no matter what,
I want the towheaded twins
to go to Reverend Lawrence's grandson.
Um, don't you mean Reverend Hanes?
'Cause Reverend Lawrence's
grandson is going to get
the, uh, lute-playing angel,
'cause he was in the choir.
Very sharp, Mr. McGill.
And here I thought all lawyers were idiots.
[Chuckles] No, only half of us are idiots.
The other half are crooks.
[Both laugh]
- Aren't you a spicy one?
- Well...
If I were 40 years younger,
I'd have you buy me a piña colada.
Well, if you want me to draw up a DNR,
I'll bring a blender and some pineapple.
[Both laugh] I knew I'd like you
when I saw how you saved
that poor man on the television.
Well...
Moxie is in such short supply these days.
[Sighs] Yeah.
Well, I pride myself on my moxie.
Now, I hate to do this,
but I do need to bring up my payment.
Um [Clears throat] and I'm sorry,
but I can't accept s&h green stamps.
[Chuckles]
Now, uh, my fee is $140.
$140?
I'll gladly accept $70 today
and $70 when I come back
with the completed documents, if...
[Rustling]
$20, $40, $60...
$80, $100...
And $20, $40.
Uh. Okay.
[Clears throat]
[Chuckles]
Shall we continue, Mr. McGill?
Yes. Yes, we shall, Mrs. Strauss.
[Sighs]
Kim: Put it on the nail, not the skin.
Jimmy: I can't help it
if your toes are too small.
They should all be the same size...
The size of the big toe.
That one I can do.
Yeah, that would be attractive.
[Both chuckle]
So... how's it go again?
[Imitating Tony the toilet buddy
] Oh, you're huge, Chandler!
You're a big, big boy!
Oh, where does it end?!
Oh, don't stop, Chandler!
Don't stop! [Laughs]
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, what is that?
- Is that a piece of corn?
- [Laughing] No, don't.
Did you eat corn, Chandler?
- Is that a niblet I see, Chandler?
- That's disgusting.
- No, don't.
- [Normal voice] Too much?
Hey, good times.
Oh. Even your lousy days
are more interesting than my good ones.
Yeah, well, we should definitely
do something about that.
Seriously, don't ever try
to make a living at this.
Stick with the law.
Yeah, because I'm really...
Lighting the world on fire
in that department.
Did two wills today.
Two wills, and I started a living trust.
Whoopee! Old people love me.
Maybe you got a future in elder law.
You think I could handle all that glamour?
No, I'm serious.
I... I've thought about
getting into elder law myself.
I watched my grandmother at the end.
It's...
It's awful what people have to deal with...
Insurance companies,
my scumbag cousins stealing
her savings and her pain meds.
Getting old sucks.
Seniors need someone on their side.
[Cellphone ringing]
It's Howard.
What the hell does he want?
- Shh!
- [Cellphone beeps]
Hi, Howard.
Uh, no. I mean, I haven't, uh...
Oh, my God. When?
Yeah, okay.
I'll see if I can, um, track Jimmy down.
I'll call you back. S-sure.
[Cellphone beeps]
It's Chuck.
[Electricity buzzing]
[Buzzing intensifies]
Jimmy: Chuck.
Chuck, you with me?
Chuck, hey, buddy. It's me.
Hey, can you talk to me? Jim...
Jesus Christ. These sons of bitches.
[Breathing sharply]
Hey, hey. Sir, you can't do that.
- All of this needs to stay on.
- No, no. No electricity.
- You understand?
- No, it needs to be on.
- I'm getting security.
- No, uh, wait, wait.
Wait, wait. Uh, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Jimmy: Huh? Why isn't that one going out?
- Jimmy. Jimmy.
- Damn it.
I just... Jimmy, wait a second.
Jimmy. Think.
- What's the plan here?
- Sir? Sir?
Sir, I need you to get down from there.
What the hell kind of torture
chamber you running here?
He... he's allergic
to electricity, all right?
- You heard the doc. Get down now.
- No, all these lights and machines...
You might as well throw him
into a microwave.
- Come on down now.
- No, don't touch me!
He is this patient's brother.
Please, listen to him.
[Remote control beeps]
[Breathing heavily]
- Let's go.
- Dr. Cruz: Hey. Wait, Edwin, hold up.
Hold on a second, Edwin.
Sir, are you ready to calm down now?
Yes. His name is Jimmy, and,
yes, he is gonna calm down.
I need you to say the words, Jimmy.
I need to hear it from you.
I'm calm, okay? I'm calm.
Edwin, why don't you
go wait in the hallway?
I'll call if we need you.
Okay, so, tell me about the electricity.
Yeah, look, I know how
it sounds, but it's real.
Oh, shit.
My phone and stuff...
Anything with a battery in it...
He can't have it near him.
Hang on.
Here's my phone. Okay, that's it.
[Breathing heavily] Thanks.
Okay, what the hell happened to him?
- Why is he here?
- Apparently, it started
when Charles stole
his neighbor's newspaper.
What? He... he never leaves the house.
I don't... I don't have all the details,
but the police found him
in a very agitated state.
He was confrontational and incoherent.
How come you didn't call me?
Uh, why did I have to hear about this
through my brother's
prick of a law partner?
The only contact information we could find
was a business card.
Jimmy, in my opinion,
Charles should be committed
for 30 days of psychiatric observation.
As a family member,
you can submit a petition
for him to be evaluated.
There's an excellent facility
in Las Cruces.
He can be there tomorrow.
I'd rather not. [Breathes deeply]
Hey, buddy. Hey, I'm right here.
Oh, hey, Chuck.
Excuse me.
Mr. McGill, my name is Dr. Cruz.
Do you know why you're in the hospital?
The police kicked in my door...
No warrant, no cause.
I wasn't incoherent.
They just weren't listening.
They tasered me, Jimmy.
Aw, Jesus.
Kim?
I'm sorry. I can give you privacy.
Oh, no, no, no. That's all right. Stay.
Howard... Called me.
He's very concerned about you.
How are you feeling now, Mr. McGill?
Uh, do... do you have a phone
or a... a pager,
anything with a battery?
I don't think so. I...
Uh...
Yeah. [Chuckles]
- [Breathing quickly]
- Oversight. Sorry about that.
Can you tell me a little more
about your... Situation?
It's not a situation.
It's a condition...
Electromagnetic hypersensitivity.
For reasons unknown, my nervous
system has become sensitized
to certain frequencies
of electromagnetic radiation.
Your brother called it
an allergy to electricity.
Well, it's an oversimplification,
but it's essentially correct.
Electronic devices create their
own electromagnetic fields.
The closer I am to such devices,
the worse my symptoms.
Which are?
Burning sensation on my skin,
a sharp, cold pain in my bones,
muscle fatigue, heart palpitations,
blurred vision, tinnitus,
vertigo, nausea, shortness of breath,
a general... it hurts.
Yes, it hurts.
When did you first experience
these symptoms?
[Sighs] Oh, it must have been...
Y... you left the office 18 months ago.
Huh. Well, in that case, uh,
must have been almost two years.
- Two years?
- Mm-hmm.
That's a... that's a long time
to live with discomfort.
Oh, there it is.
You think I'm crazy.
I never said that.
No, you didn't, because you're very polite,
but you think it.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be
talking about commitment.
You find that idea distressing.
Who the hell wouldn't?
I... I find it inappropriate
for a person suffering from
a physical condition.
[Breathes deeply]
Anyone who's spent more than
a few minutes with me
knows that this isn't
some kind of delusion.
Wouldn't you agree, Kim?
Jimmy: Of course she does.
Well, I'm not a doctor.
You've known me for
the better part of a decade.
Have you ever seen me exhibit any sign...
Any sign whatsoever of mental illness?
See?
If I thought for one second
you could cure me,
believe me, I'd jump at the chance.
But with all due respect,
psychiatry doesn't have the answers.
I'd very much like to try.
Section 43-1-11, part (E)(3)...
"The proposed commitment is consistent with
"the treatment needs of the client
and with the least drastic means
principle."
Chuck: Do you think subjecting me
to this kind of pain for a month
is the least drastic means?
He might as well spend
a month in a wood chipper.
Dr. Cruz: I understand
your frustration. I do.
You're obviously a highly intelligent man
in difficult circumstances.
May I ask you a question,
just for my own interest?
How do you meet the needs of daily life?
What do you do for light, or...
How do you prepare food?
[Sighs] I use white-gas lanterns.
For cooking, I have a camp stove.
I have a large cooler
I keep filled with ice.
It's not ideal, but I make do.
I see.
Well, thank you.
Would you mind if I took a moment
to speak with your brother?
Oh, uh, make sure you still have
your wallet when you're done.
[Chuckles] Funny guy.
Jimmy.
[Sighs] I want to go home.
[Intercom chatter]
That was a dirty trick.
That wasn't a trick...
It was a demonstration.
This allergy to electricity isn't real...
It's a manifestation of something deeper.
I'm not saying it's 100% real, okay?
But Chuck is smarter than you
and me put together,
so we're not talking him out of this,
and I'm not sending him to a rubber room.
No one is talking about rubber rooms.
There are specialists who will...
He's seen specialists, okay?
The best doctors from here to Denver,
and none of them helped... not one.
So you're ready to give up.
[Scoffs] Who's giving up, huh?
I'm... I'm the one
doing the heavy lifting here.
That white gas he was talking about...
Who do you think brings him that?
And milk and bread and toilet paper
and ice and every other
damn thing he needs.
Is that helping or enabling?
If you testify in a custodial hearing,
he can get the help he needs...
That's in your power.
To be committed involuntarily,
he has to be a danger to himself or others.
And he is.
Coleman lanterns indoors, a camp stove?
I mean, he could burn his house down
or the entire neighborhood,
and then you're looking at
a commitment of 10 to 20 years.
What if...
What if he just hurts himself
in a household accident?
How does he call for help?
You have the power to help your brother...
Truly help him.
Ignoring this won't make it go away.
What would you do?
All I know is...
He needs help.
[Sighs]
Untie him.
I'm getting him out of here.
A nurse will bring you the release forms.
[Keys jingling]
Oh, boy.
Jimmy. Jimmy. I found him.
I thought I'd wait till you got here.
Great. How's he doing?
Better. Resting.
Good.
Uh, Jimmy...
I want you to know
that I've talked to the D.A.,
and he absolutely will not sign
off on any commitment papers.
This is a physical condition,
not a mental one.
Chuck is of sound mind.
I think we can all agree on that.
[Scoffs]
You're a real peach, Howard.
Of course you don't want Chuck committed.
No, I don't. Why would I?
Because if Chuck were committed,
then I'd become his legal guardian,
and I cash him out of HHM.
Jesus, Jimmy. Now?
You want to hash that out
while he's lying in here?
You know, the tanning bed
must have melted your brain
if you think for one second...
Guys... Chuck. That's why we're here.
Yes. Let's stay on point.
We're talking about the well-being of a man
whom we all love very much.
There's many factors at play.
Spite doesn't have to be one of them.
You know what, Howard?
I was on the fence till you showed up,
but thanks for helping me decide.
Wave bye-bye to your cash cow,
'cause it's leaving the pasture.
I'm committing him.
Jimmy. Uh, j... wait.
Jimmy, wait. Jimmy.
Jimmy, can you wait?
Jimmy, wait a second.
Listen, I agree that Chuck needs help,
and maybe it's the right thing to do,
but you can't do it like this.
I just want to see
that son of a bitch sweat.
It's so obvious what he's afraid of.
I'm taking my brother home.
[Sighs]
Jimmy: There you go, buddy.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
Okay, some steps. One and two.
And there you go.
Hey, you're home, all right?
Everything's gonna be all right.
Uh, you want something to eat...
Uh, some tea... a cup of tea?
- Coffee?
- [Sighs] Yeah.
Coffee. Coffee it is.
Uh, Jimmy, I'm... I'm...
I'm gonna need my...
I don't... I... I... I... I...
Oh, it's...
[Sighs]
Yeah.
[Breathing heavily]
[Groaning]
You want to talk about this?
- There's nothing to talk about.
- You took the paper.
You saw this.
You got sick.
What's your point?
Chuck, I think you got sick
'cause you saw this story.
No, w... whenever you think
I've done something wrong,
something questionable, you get worse.
I didn't get sick
because I read about you in the paper.
I got sick
because I went out of my house
to retrieve the paper.
W... [sighs]
I'm too tired for this argument, Jimmy.
I... I've had it too many times.
You think this is the return
of slippin' Jimmy,
but it's not. All right.
Uh, you think the
billboard thing was unethical,
but it was... Promotion.
It was advertising... that's all.
Which wasn't even allowed until
five supreme court justices
went completely bonkers in
Bates vs. State bar of Arizona.
Aha!
But in any event...
It's legal.
If you want to advertise,
that's your business.
"Business" being
the operative word there, Chuck,
because I-I have gotten business
off of this...
Legit business... wills, uh, trusts.
Uh, I'm... I'm kind of starting
to specialize in elder law.
Elder law?
Yeah, the things the elderly
have to deal with...
I mean, you know, relatives
coming after their savings,
telemarketers, reverse-mortgage scams...
I mean, getting old sucks.
Seniors need someone on their side, so...
You're looking at him.
Well, that sounds...
Promising.
But it has nothing to do with my condition.
Chuck, listen. I'm gonna make
you a promise right now, okay?
- No, not necessary, not requested.
- Okay.
The billboard was a one-time thing.
I... I'm a good lawyer.
I just needed some razzmatazz, you know,
to get the ball rolling,
some showmanship...
That's all it was.
It's done now. It's over.
All right.
From here on out,
I'm gonna play by the rules.
As any lawyer should.
Exactly.
There are clients out there who need me,
and I'm gonna give them
the best representation
I know how to provide.
I... I'm on the up-and-up, okay?
I will be good.
Slippin' Jimmy...
He's back in Cicero, dead and buried.
[Clock ticking]
[Inhales deeply]
Okay.
We'll see.
Where you going?
Somebody's got to make that coffee.
I'm sure the truth will come out,
if, indeed, that's what
we're all interested in.
I know everybody in this
courtroom has strong feelings
about Nicholas Baron's past,
but I submit he is not on trial
here for his past.
He is on trial for the murders
of Donald Kovack
and Eddie Alonzo.
[Remote control clicks]
Single-breasted...
Light blue or cream.
Blue.
Linen.
[Sighs]
Single pocket.
[Indistinct conversations]
Hello, there.
James McGill, attorney at law.
How are you this fine morning?
- I'm just fine. And how about you?
- Very good.
Play fair.
Oh, what do we got here?
[Straining] I see.
A piece is trying to get away.
Enjoy the jello.
Get to the bottom.
Wait. Who's the banker here?
That's the only one I want to talk to.
There he is.
Hey. How are ya?
I'm good. Whoa! What a grip, young man!
Yeah, watch out.
That's my will-writing hand.
- [Speaks indistinctly]
- Okay.
Hello, ladies. You look beautiful today.
All right over there?
Very good. Play fair.
Ah, no betting.
Oh, wait a second. Is that Veronica lake?
Give me a hug, beautiful.
Yes. You look great today.
All right, no cheating.
No hiding the tablet.
Oh, what do we have here?
Hey, there he is... the man in the booth,
John Wilkes booth, booth Tarkington.
What you reading there?
"The complete annotated book of rules
for parking validation"?
No.
The rules for parking validation
are actually pretty simple.
Most people get it on the first try.
Well, you'll be pleased to know
I have the requisite stickers.
Well, be still my heart.
And...
You can have this, as well.
I'm doing elder law now.
Need a will? Call McGill.
So, give me a call if you, uh...
Uh, if, uh, you happen to know any elders.
Good night.
Couldn't have a bad one if I tried.
- Mike: Good night.
- Night.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Seat belt clicks]
[Engine turns over]
[Engine shuts off]
[Car door hinges creak]
Lucy: Out here in the hall and everything?
Don't be so silly.
Dan: Well, there's nobody around.
Oh, but you never can tell when there's
- someone around.
- Then I'll come in.
Oh, no, Dan, I wouldn't come in
if I were you.
- Really, we're going to be awfully late.
- Well, don't be bashful, Lucy.
Well, I'm not bashful, but
I've never kissed you before,
and I don't think
this is exactly the place.
Gosh, if you knew how crazy I am about you,
you wouldn't hesitate...
I can't sleep nights.
Oh, why don't you take some hot milk?
I guess I must be in love,
'cause it started right...
[Television mutes]
[Knocking on door]
[Knocking continues]
[Door hinges creak]
Long way from home, aren't you?
You and me both.