[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[BRAKES SQUEAK]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[SQUISHING NOISE]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
Can I make the call now?
[GASPS]
[NACHO GROANS]
Gotta make it look real.
Do it quick, before you pass out.
[GROANING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[♪♪♪]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
And?
What if I told you,
you could turn this into 4 grand?
For each of us.
Minimum.
This little fella,
he's called the "Merry Wanderer."
He's not much to look at, he's easy to find.
I got this one at a pawnshop for 20 bucks.
But he has a cousin
called "Bavarian Boy."
Almost identical.
Same umbrella, same swagger.
That one is worth a boatload.
And I gather you know
where to find a "Bavarian Boy."
I do indeed.
He's gathering dust on a shelf
in an office up on San Mateo.
He's been there for God knows how long.
They have no idea what they got.
To them, it's not "Bavarian Boy,"
it's "some junk Grandma gave me...
...I feel too guilty to get rid of."
That's where you come in.
This place, they're not exactly
what you call "security-conscious."
There's no cameras whatsoever.
There's an alarm on the door
that I could probably bridge.
And past that, you just pick a lock,
walk over to the shelf...
...swap this Wanderer for that Boy,
and it's five minutes, max.
Warm-up, gentlemen?
Yeah, thanks, Fran.
JIMMY: Oh, thanks.
- Heh. That's cute.
Isn't it, though?
FRAN: Yeah.
Have your food up in a jiff, Mike.
MIKE: Mmm.
Look, they're not even gonna know
it's gone.
They look at the shelf,
they see the same dumb tchotchke...
...they've been looking at for years.
There's no serial number.
These things are practically untraceable.
You send Pryce
or some other schlub to Dallas...
Next week, they have a collectibles expo.
Those people are hungry for Hummels.
Their eyes are gonna pop
when they see what we brung them.
And they will pay through the nose,
which we will split fifty-fifty.
So it's perfect, right?
We make
some nice Hummel-loving lady happy...
...and we make a bundle.
Let's do something beautiful here.
And how did you come across
this valuable wunderkind?
- What difference does it make?
- The guys in the office cross you?
Done you wrong?
Heh. What?
You're, uh, missing the point.
It's free money.
You walk by a 20 on the sidewalk?
No, you pick it up.
- Pass.
- What? Why?
It's not for me.
Not for you?
Is there some problem I'm not seeing,
like, with the swap or something?
Plan's fine, as far as it goes.
It's just not for me.
And I don't think
it should be for you either.
I'm sorry about your brother.
Yeah, thanks.
You're really not gonna do this?
Sorry.
FRAN: Eggs, easy.
MIKE: Thanks, Fran.
- Can I get you anything else?
- No, I'm good.
FRAN: Sure I can't get you anything?
- No, I'm not hungry. Thanks.
All right.
I, um...
If you don't want easy money,
that's your business.
I just thought I'd give you first crack
at a golden opportunity.
All right. See you around.
You take it easy.
[DOOR OPENS]
Yes, hello.
I was wondering if Dr. Caldera had
any openings today.
As soon as possible.
I have a very sick fish.
[♪♪♪]
[NACHO GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
[IN SPANISH]
Who did this?
Don't know.
Drove a silver car.
Firebird, maybe?
[GROANING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
KIM:
Oh.
Thanks. And, uh, thanks again for the lift.
It's outside your job description, I know.
VIOLA: It's no problem.
So the acquisitions?
Yes. We'll need to draft contracts
for the target banks.
The idea is to have the agreements
ready to go while doing due diligence.
You want me to start cracking
on a draft when we're done?
No, but thank you.
- I'll do the first pass, then you can proof it.
- Sure, whatever's best for you.
KIM: Here's what I'm thinking:
Looking at the competition...
...one opportunity stands out.
They don't have the market share, but...
And this is a big deal.
...Walker Ridge is eager.
I agree.
They took a hit in the market adjustment.
They're vulnerable and they know it.
We should prepare a package
for both with that...
Is that Kim Wexler I hear?
Kevin. It's good to see you.
Heard you were here,
wanted to say hi. Look at you.
Baby bird with a broken wing.
It's fine. Doesn't even hurt.
Just a pain in the butt.
Kevin, this is Viola Goto,
my new paralegal.
KEVIN: Kevin Wachtell. Welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
Listen, Kim, I just wanted to say
how sorry I am about Charles McGill.
It's no secret I had problems
with the man...
...but no one should go like that.
I just have to ask,
how's James handling it?
Oh, he's... He's getting through it.
He and the family appreciated
the arrangement you sent.
- Good. Well, glad to hear.
- Kevin, we're meeting the board at noon...
- ...to go over Kim's recommendations, so...
- No, no, no. I won't slow you down.
Oh, uh, one more thing.
And this will just take a second.
Kim, you have got to see the models.
The models?
Takes your breath away, doesn't it?
Look at this.
The whole side of this building is glass.
And it's on a north-facing lot.
I'm told that's energy-efficient,
so I'm excited.
This is, uh, Salt Lake City?
After Provo, why not?
And Cheyenne, Wyoming?
Yep.
Over here, North Platte, Nebraska.
[♪♪♪]
Now, these two you already know.
This one's gonna be Ogden, Utah...
...this one here is Tucumcari.
And over here on this side,
you got a few new ones.
Sedona. Pueblo, Colorado.
You know what?
That's just the tip of the iceberg.
After that, I figure, why not Las Vegas?
Nevada, I mean. Reno too.
Lubbock, Texas.
Amarillo, San Antonio, El Paso.
Then we'll get up
to the Pacific Northwest.
Boise. Bend, Oregon.
Eugene, Salem,
all the way up to Portland.
Now, this one is real special.
Denver. See here?
We're gonna add more trees
on the west side.
That'll be great. And then, maybe, uh...
...a bench or two on the outside.
Kim, is there something wrong?
No. No, no, no.
No, it's just...
It's a lot.
It's a very fast, aggressive expansion.
Kevin figures
once we get a foothold in Utah...
- ...then we'll file for federal charter.
- Yeah.
We're really building something here.
All your hard work is making a difference.
I mean, Kim, this is what it's all about.
So I can get the notes to you by EOD,
if that's okay.
Uh, yeah. That's fine.
Do you have a sense
when I should expect your draft?
I assume you're dictating it.
Actually, you were right before.
You take a stab at it, then I'll take a look.
Great. That works. I'll start on that
right after I get you home.
Uh... Instead of taking me home,
drop me off at the courthouse, would you?
I didn't realize you had an appearance.
I would've prepped.
No. No, I don't.
- You don't?
- Nothing to prep.
Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[DOGS BARKING
AND BIRDS CHIRPING]
CALDERA:
No. Not quite.
I... I've done business
with him before, yeah.
Once. Once.
Just the once.
Yeah. No. Yeah, I guess.
- He didn't say.
- Well?
Yeah, he's not into it.
He's not or you're not? Give me that.
Uh-uh. Doesn't work that way.
No direct contact, that's the point.
Just give it to me.
Thank you.
Hey, this is the interested party.
I have one question for you:
Do you shit gold?
It's a simple "yes" or "no."
No? All right, then.
Because unless you currently have
a gold nugget traversing your colon...
...this is the easiest money
you'll ever make.
How long does it take for you
to pick a Yale three-pin?
Then, in eight minutes,
you're gonna make 4 grand.
Ten minutes if you pick your nose.
In, out, no one comes looking for you.
Ever. How does that sound?
Yeah, I know where that is. Here. Pen.
Uh-huh.
In a half an hour.
Yeah.
Listen, I'm not trying to tell you
how to do your job, but...
WOMAN: Mr. McGill, you're all set.
- Thank you very much.
- See you next time.
- I hope she feels better soon.
JIMMY:
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
[♪♪♪]
Jesus.
All right, not here. Let me go grab my bag
and tell my staff.
Jesus.
[GROANS]
Can you not hit
every damn pothole, please?!
[NACHO GROANING]
CALDERA:
Careful. Careful!
- Up, up.
- Agh!
You, ayuda. Come here. Help.
[SNIFFING]
[NACHO GROANS]
[GROANING]
CALDERA:
Well, well. There he is.
You woke up.
That means
my Spanish is good enough...
...and Yul Brynner here
is actually O-negative.
[SIGHING]
Okay.
I had to leave a bullet in your shoulder.
It might set off metal detectors
from now on.
Gave you a dose
of broad-spectrum antibiotics.
Let's see.
Pulse is good. Now, sniff test says
you probably didn't perforate your bowel.
Probably.
I can't be 100-percent sure
you didn't get nicked.
If this starts to leak, you're gonna get
the worst infection of your life.
It's gonna hurt like hell,
and then you're gonna die.
So I advise you to go see a doctor
that has some imaging tech...
...in other words, one that's not working
out of the back of a Jiffy Lube.
Till then, keep these clean and dry.
Change the bandages daily.
You should be okay.
You understand me?
Good.
[WHISPERING]
Now, understand this:
After I walk out of here...
...I never wanna see you again.
Never.
This cartel shit is too hot for me.
You got it?
[DOOR OPENS]
[LOCK JINGLING]
[♪♪♪]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[SIGHS]
[GROANS]
[SIGHS THEN COUGHS]
[SIGHS]
[NEFF SIGHS]
It's me.
Can we talk, please?
I... I just wanna come home.
Okay. Thank you.
I... I just wanted to say...
...I'm sorry if you feel upset.
It was not my intention
for you to feel upset.
Well, my intention was for...
Honey, it is top-of-the-line.
Then... Then what is the point?
You're saying I'm a thoughtless...
That I don't care...
...but it is a very,
very expensive vacuum.
It never loses suction.
What you're saying is,
I gotta sleep in my office...
...because I got you a gift?
Lynette?
Ah. Damn it.
[SIGHS]
Hello.
Are you still delivering?
Oh.
Okay.
Uh...
Yeah, just a large cheese.
Yes, sliced, please.
Could you also throw in
some dipping sticks?
Two ranch and one marinara.
[SIGHS]
[BUZZES]
Hey. How'd it go?
Listen. Listen.
Look, the office guy. He's here.
- What?
- He's dug in for the night, man.
Come get me or... Come get me.
NEFF: Thanks. See you.
[SIGHING]
MAN [ON STEREO]:
Now, if you take out the listener's guide...
...you'll see a chart in there
showing four quadrants...
...I call "the time-management matrix."
The key words to understand
are "importance" and "urgency."
"Importance" basically comes
from within you.
"Importance" is your value system,
hopefully, based on principles.
"Importance" is your mission.
- Importance versus...
- Your central strategy...
...to accomplish
those high-priority goals.
- ...urgency.
- And the plans to implement that strategy.
[CAR ALARM WAILING]
Urgency comes from the environment.
It presses upon you.
It's proximate. It's right in front of you.
And it's often very popular.
It could be deep and...
[STEREO MUTES]
[ALARM CONTINUES WAILING]
[GRUNTS]
[ALARM CHIRPS]
[♪♪♪]
Son of a bitch.
[ALARM WAILING
AND HORN HONKING]
MAN [ON STEREO]:
"It's urgent" has the appearance...
...of requiring immediate attention.
Now, you have to decide
what is truly important in your lives.
Hey. Hey!
Hey!
Hey! Stop!
Stop! No, no!
No!
Hey! No! No! Why? Why? Stop! Stop!
[TIRES SCREECH
THEN CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
Hey, hey. So did you get it?
Shitting gold.
Yeah. Yeah, right?
IRA: I didn't say it was easy.
Car thing was pretty slick.
Don't know how you pulled that off.
JIMMY:
Worked, didn't it?
IRA:
Yeah, I guess so.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Yes?
BOLSA:
The Salamancas were hit.
Yesterday, on the way back
from their pickup.
Do we know who?
Not yet. Varga survived, barely.
But he couldn't see faces.
- Someone knows our business.
- Possibly.
It resembled the attack
on Hector's truck months ago.
And they knew
the Salamanca men were heavy.
Don Juan, we are about
to run another shipment.
If you think we're compromised...
Run dummy loads.
We'll see what we see.
No product crosses until we're certain.
I'll take care of it.
How long before our dealers run dry?
No more than a week.
This is a problem.
Find a local supplier on your side
of the border.
Cut a deal.
Don Juan, with all due respect,
Don Eladio forbids buying from outsiders.
- He's been very clear.
- Let me worry about Eladio.
Do it. Now.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
♪ And nickel, neptunium, germanium
Iron, americium, ruthenium, uranium ♪
♪ Europium, zirconium, lutetium
Vanadium, lanthanum, osmium ♪
♪ And astatine, iridium, and gold
Protactinium, and indium, and gallium ♪
♪ And iodine, and fluorine, and thulium
And thallium ♪
♪ There's yttrium, ytterbium, actinium
Rubidium, boron, gadolinium ♪
♪ Niobium, radium
Strontium, silicon ♪
♪ And silver and samarium, and bismuth
Bromine, lithium, beryllium, and barium ♪♪
Oh! Heh.
Uh, Mr. Fring. I wasn't expecting you.
- That's not a problem, I hope?
- No, not at all.
I was tinkering with something.
What's that?
Oh, it's, uh, technical.
I wouldn't wanna bore you.
Oh, you wouldn't.
Okay. You know when you put salt
into water, it dissolves?
If you stir the water, or heat it,
you can add more salt...
...before it falls out of solution.
I'm trying to create a solution like that...
...but with certain benzodiazepine
precursor compounds.
- That's fascinating.
- It will be if I can get it to work.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, I tested your samples.
[EXHALES]
They range from 39 percent
to 58 percent pure.
Except this one,
which hovers around 67. Heh.
Top of the class, so to speak.
You should tell the chemist
to check his or her cookware.
It's introducing contamination,
which would be easy to avoid.
Well, thank you very much, Gale.
That's very useful information.
Well, I should let you get back
to your work.
Mr. Fring. Um...
I don't want to cast aspersions,
but I have to tell you...
...these samples aren't great.
In fact, they're, um...
They're... They're not even good.
Basically, they're dreck.
I could do much better.
- Gale...
- Much higher grade.
I could make a kilo or more right here.
No one would know.
Wouldn't take more than a few days.
I wouldn't want to interfere
with your studies.
These are my studies.
Please, it's the least I can do.
- I wouldn't let you down.
- Oh. Heh.
I'm certain that you wouldn't.
But I'm afraid I can't allow it. Not yet.
You were meant for better things.
I'll see you soon, Gale.
Bye, Mr. Fring.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[MUSIC PLAYS OVER HEADPHONES]
♪ There's holmium, helium
Hafnium, erbium ♪
♪ Phosphorous, francium
Fluorine, terbium ♪
♪ Manganese, mercury
Molybdenum, magnesium ♪
♪ Dysprosium, scandium
Cerium, cesium ♪
♪ Lead, praseodymium
Platinum, plutonium ♪
♪ Palladium, promethium
Potassium, polonium ♪
♪ Tantalum, technetium
Titanium, tellurium ♪
♪ And cadmium and calcium
And chromium and curium ♪♪
I was worried about the wording there.
- Hm? No. No, it's great.
- Oh.
Really, really solid work.
Just make the change
to indicate the correct term...
...for the disbursement of funds,
then we should be good to go.
Don't mind me.
I know it's a law office.
Just walking around your law office.
KIM:
You slept late.
Yeah.
It took me a while to fall asleep,
actually, but, man, once I did, I...
Uh, you want some coffee, Viola?
Oh, no, thanks. We're just finishing up.
Unless there's something else
you need from me?
No, I think we're good.
Maybe, uh, you could also start looking
into federal charter regs.
No rush.
Got it. Will do.
Bye, Jimmy.
See you, Viola.
Bye, thanks.
[SIGHS]
What's up?
Jimmy, there's just a couple of things
from talking to Howard...
...that maybe we ought to go through.
Oh, yeah.
Okay. Let's get it over with.
You know, rip the Band-Aid off, right?
Yeah. Uh, this is a release.
It says, basically,
that you won't contest the will.
- If I sign it, I get my share?
- That's about the size of it.
So, uh, ahem, how much do I get?
Five thousand.
Ah.
Five K. Ah. Tsk.
I can pay off my Mastercard.
What else you got?
Um...
This is...
It's from Chuck.
Nobody knows for sure what's in it.
You don't have to open it now, but...
Let's see what the old boy has to say.
- Okay. I'll give you a minute alone.
- No, no, stay.
It's fine.
I mean, uh, you wanna hear this, right?
Yeah. If it's okay.
[SIGHS]
It's undated.
Okay, here it goes, ahem:
"Dear Jimmy...
...I have left many things unsaid
in our relationship through the years.
Rather than allow
these unspoken thoughts to die with me...
...I've chosen to record them here for you.
I hope you will take my words
in the spirit in which they are intended."
[JIMMY SIGHS]
New paragraph.
"I remember the day
you came home from the hospital.
You can't imagine the joy on Mom's face.
I can honestly say I never saw her happier
than she was on that day.
You brought a shine to her life
nothing else ever did and I'm glad of that."
New paragraph.
"We have not always seen eye to eye...
...I expect that will continue to be so.
However, nothing will change the fact
that we are brothers, flesh and blood.
Though we are very different,
I want you to know how much I respect...
...what you have made of yourself
in these last few years.
You have taken
the opportunity I gave you...
...and you have run with it, becoming
a valued member of the HHM family.
For all the problems in your past,
I'm proud we share the name 'McGill.'
I sincerely admire
your energy and resilience.
I used to worry about you
finding a place in the world...
...but I'm not worried about that anymore.
I'm certain,
no matter what the future may bring...
...you'll land on your feet.
I hope when you read this...
...you remember me not only
as your brother...
...but as a person who was always
in your corner."
And he signed it just "Chuck."
Well, say what you want,
the man could write a letter.
- Sorry.
- Hey.
- No, I didn't mean to make it...
- No. It's okay. It's a nice letter.
- Hey.
- No, just...
Just... Just give me...
Just give me a minute.
[SOBS]
Kim.
[♪♪♪]