Previously on "The Originals"...
I assume I have the misfortune
of speaking to my mother.
I have come to heal our family.
She'd prefer to place us all in new bodies.
Take the body of a mortal
and all be happy again.
It is time you bring Camille in.
There's no need for this.
My sons have taken quite the liking to you.
[Chanting]
Proud werewolves on a witch's leash.
I hope those rings you're
wearing are worth it.
You're gonna like me, Davina Claire,
and I'm gonna let you pretend a while
that you don't already.
Esther: When he wakes,
he'll make his own decision.
Klaus: You declared war when
you came after my family.
You don't understand.
Slap them on a witch,
can't do magic as long as they're on.
Kidnapping. Rather unpleasant way
to begin a family reunion.
Well, wait until you see how we end it.
[Child giggling]
Klaus: We arrive into
this world as innocents,
wide-eyed,
vulnerable.
It is the job of our parents
to nurture and protect us.
Unfortunately, our own
parents failed miserably
at even the most basic of parental tasks,
but we are not beholden to the past
they created for us.
Today, a new future awaits.
Forget your animosity
toward Elijah and myself,
and instead join us against she who truly
deserves your ire... our mother.
Do this, and we will
welcome you with open arms.
But if you continue to oppose us,
a denial of pastries will be
the least of your concerns.
If you all you wanted was my
allegiance against mother dearest,
you should have said so,
save me a night shackled to the wall.
This was Niklaus.
My recommendation was to remove
your limbs one by one until you comply.
Heh. We've... we've no
desire to torture you,
provided you vow to stand beside us
as brothers.
Brothers?
Does that word even apply to us
after all these centuries of betrayal,
and is loyalty to you ever really rewarded?
If so, tell me Niklaus,
where is our sister Rebekah?
She was blindly loyal to
you for a thousand years,
and now nowhere to be found.
Where did our sister go,
and how did she escape
your vile machinations?
Heh.
You think me vile?
Well, what then, do you make
of the one who cursed us?
She was trying to make you mortal again,
and you both refused her.
Only proves how far you've fallen,
but I expect Rebekah will
have a different response
to her proposal.
See, unlike the two of you,
she always did cling to her humanity.
Rebekah's off limits, too.
You pursue her, and you will suffer.
Klaus: Do not let him goad you, Elijah.
Neither he nor Esther will find Rebekah
unless she wants to be
found, and she does not.
Esther is quite determined.
She's been searching for Rebekah
since the day she returned.
[Birds fluttering, screeching]
I imagine it's only a matter of time.
I enjoy a good bloodletting
as much as anyone,
but our brothers have power,
as well as knowledge of Esther's plans.
We need them alive.
Can you imagine what they
would do to Rebekah, to Hope?
Rebekah has been cloaked by powerful magic.
Focus on the task at hand.
We need to persuade our brothers.
I'm through with persuasion.
Has the earth shifted on its axis,
you needing restraint from me?
[Cell phone ringing]
It's me. I have the baby,
and we're on the run.
Esther found us.
We're safe for now.
I've lost her bloody starlings,
but I have no idea where to go.
Tell her to head west.
I'll call Hayley.
Do not tell Hayley.
Esther's too smart for that.
The only advantage that we have is that
she thinks the baby died.
Text me with plans.
Go. I'll take care of Kol and Finn.
Splendid, and in your hands, I
assume they'll be dead by nightfall.
I will show restraint.
Hope needs her father.
What she needs, what...
what we need are allies to
help us defeat our mother.
Finn and Kol must be turned to our side.
Without their help, there will
be nowhere left for Hope to run.
Klaus, you child.
I have waited months
to see my daughter.
I can wait one more day.
Elijah.
Do whatever it takes to keep her safe.
I give you my word.
Wolves are freaking out.
They know it had to be an insider
who took down Vincent last night,
seeing as no one could
have been anywhere near him.
Anybody suspect it was you?
No, not yet, but they're
gonna figure it out,
which pretty much means I'm screwed
unless we come up with a plan.
Call a meeting, the whole pack tonight.
If they're so scared,
now's the perfect time
to convince them they need to ditch Esther.
She gave them moonlight rings.
Well, those rings make you slaves.
No. They make us powerful.
We were exiles before,
but now we run the city.
The vampires are scared of us,
and no one, including me is just
gonna walk away from that because...
set the damn meeting.
So are you gonna work on a rousing speech
or just get day drunk?
Little bit of both.
Jack, it's 10 A.M.
You know, for months, I wrote
down every single word Ansel said,
the entire history of our people.
If only I'd know he was Klaus' father,
I would have asked him
a hell of a lot more.
You know, I was up all
night looking through this,
trying to find something, anything
that will help me figure out how to get
the people back together.
Let me guess... no such luck.
Nothing viable.
And now Ansel's dead
along with Ollie, so forgive me
if I need a beer because right now,
I can use all the help I can get.
Davina: I screwed up, you guys.
I was with Kaleb last night,
and he took the white oak
stake when I was asleep.
I... I'm sorry. I never
should have trusted him.
Kol doesn't have the stake.
Klaus does. Matter of fact,
Klaus has Kol, too.
What? How is that possible?
D, I'm the one who took him.
I saw an opportunity, and
I wasn't gonna pass it up,
and trust me... we are all safer this way.
Not Kaleb. Klaus will kill him.
His name isn't Kaleb. It's Kol,
and Klaus has had a
thousand years to kill him,
and he hasn't, so worry less about him
and more about yourself.
All right. This guy is not your friend.
He wants to use you to get his own way.
You don't know him like I do.
I know him better than you do.
Now I'm sorry I had to go behind your back,
and I hate lying to you, I really do,
but believe me, this is for your own good.
I got to take care of
some business, all right?
Stick with Josh.
Everything's gonna be ok.
Elijah's off his bloody rocker.
We need to get out of here.
Are you gonna help me or what?
If you were a little more clever,
you would recognize that there's
opportunity in our current circumstances.
Opportunity to what, get a beating?
Gentlemen, I apologize
for keeping you waiting.
Good news is I have
returned with an old friend,
someone who wants to say hello.
Hello.
How's it going, fellas?
Ah, you again. You ever get bored
of getting bullied by my brother?
Oh, I volunteered for this.
- Did you?
- Yeah. The way I see it,
you have it coming.
First, you messed with Davina.
Now I hear you want to
drag Rebekah into all this.
Uh-uh. Not happening.
Well, I'd prefer you both to
join me against our mother,
but I'll happily settle
for one or the other.
Either way, if you continue to defy me,
your lives will be reduced
to an unending sequence
of agonizing torture.
So...
Which is it to be?
I've got to say I'm gonna enjoy this.
Out of the whole twisted
family... sit down...
you are the one that I like the least.
Yeah? Well, there's a pretty young lady
who disagrees with that opinion.
Then let me make myself perfectly clear.
You go near Davina, and I'm
gonna cut off parts of you
that you'd rather keep.
Ahh. More threats. How bloody inventive.
Thing is, Klaus needs me,
so that backs you into a
bit of a corner, doesn't it?
Well, until we get rid of your mom.
I wonder what happens then.
Well, Klaus might not
need me when mother's gone,
but you might.
Come on, Marcel. You were
king of the city once.
You really think he's just
gonna give it back to you?
You always got an angle, don't you?
You see, individually,
we can't do anything,
but together, well, Klaus
wouldn't stand a chance.
Probably not, but then
I'd have to trust you,
and I don't.
At least with Klaus, I know
exactly what I'm getting.
I thought you had more
fortitude, Marcellus.
You disappoint me.
Nobody cares for your opinion.
Klaus just wants to know what you're up to.
Tell me everything,
maybe you'll get to live.
If not...
Aah!
Josh: For the record, yes, I knew what
Marcel was up to, and you
can hate me if you want to...
I don't hate you, Josh.
I'm just sick of worrying about you
and Marcel, and most of all,
I am tired of Klaus always
being in the middle of it.
You know, every time I
try to stand up to him...
it hasn't worked out so well.
Yeah. Well, failure, party of two.
You seem to be doing all right.
Uh, yeah, except that every werewolf
in town is trying to kill me.
Well, except for the superhot
one that I'm sort of dating,
but that's got its own problems, though.
It's kind of a, uh, Romeo and Romeo thing.
And how hot is this Romeo?
Well...
Pretty hot!
Definitely worth the drama.
Yeah.
Invite him over.
Yeah. I want to meet him.
Come on. Do it.
[Humming]
Do you think our mother
is even the least bit
concerned for your well-being?
She knows I don't need rescuing.
Hmm? Ehh.
You can toy with me all you want, Niklaus,
but you've had innumerable
opportunities to kill me.
But I didn't, did I?
Finn, I understand your devotion to her.
She must have clung to
you with desperate need
after our sister Freya died,
making you believe
it was your responsibility to care for her
always and forever, hmm,
a burden which you
accepted without question
because you were a good son.
Small children lack the capacity
to question their parents,
but you're a man now, Finn.
Is that the extent of your argument?
I'm a man now, so I should
join your wretched cause?
Is it not better to join me
than spend the remainder
of your mortal life
aligned to a woman who
always manipulated you?
Brother, I offer you the
opportunity to free yourself.
Side with me, and I will give you
the life she never once offered,
a chance to choose your own path.
The choice is yours, brother.
Hayley: You want to
stop playing mountain man
and explain why you kept this from me?
[Sighs]
Why don't I jog your memory?
"The werewolf's power can be traced back
to the myth of the unification ceremony,
a ritual that bestowed
certain unique abilities
onto every member of the pack."
Do you believe this?
I didn't at first,
and then Ansel swore he
saw it with his own eyes,
and then he dies, and I find out he's
resurrected from a thousand years ago,
which means he was alive to see it.
How did I not know about this?
You didn't grow up out here.
Every kid grows up hearing the stories.
Back in the day, werewolf
bloodlines were all distinct, right?
Some had speed, some had strength,
some could sense enemies from miles away.
Now to evolve, you would perform a ritual.
A shaman would marry the
alphas of each bloodline,
and then the special abilities of each
would be inherited mystically
by everyone who participated in the ritual.
See, after a few centuries, everybody had
the same abilities, so Alpha
marriages became political.
They became about power, about territory.
But I have a unique ability.
Because I'm a hybrid, I
can control when I change,
so if this mystical marriage thing works,
then our people get my power,
and they can ditch the rings,
which means Esther no
longer has a hold over them.
Jack, this is exactly the answer
that we've been looking for.
Let's find a shaman, we'll say some vows.
Hell, we'll make it a party.
It ain't just a party.
If the vows ain't honored, it doesn't work.
It's got to be a real marriage in every way
for the rest of our lives.
Are you up for that?
Uh...
Didn't think so.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Hayley, hey. What's up?
I need a favor.
Are you sure you're ok?
Yeah. I must just be
coming down with something.
I'm sorry to drag you out of bed for this.
Please. You just discovered
an ancient marriage ritual
with pretty drastic supernatural
and personal implications.
The least I could do is get out of bed.
So this is everything I found
in my uncle's files about
werewolf ceremonies and rituals.
Mostly it sounds like
old folklore and fables.
But I'm guessing you're not here
looking for some kind of proof.
I don't know what I'm looking for.
Not to pry, but does
Jackson have any answers?
He doesn't even want to talk about it.
He doesn't even want to
put me in this position.
He's a good, decent guy,
if those even exist anymore.
And I'm assuming he knows about Elijah.
Elijah and I have barely spoken
since I became a hybrid,
but still he is...
Under your skin.
Ahem. Well, there's no
right answer to this.
You just have to figure
out what's best for you,
and think long and hard about your decision
because you're the one who's
going to have to live with it.
No pressure.
Hey. What's that on your back?
[Music playing]
Nice music. Girl's got taste.
Oh, please. That was my call.
She wanted Puccini.
Ha ha ha! You must be Aiden...
supercool, superhandsome...
Werewolf traitor.
I'm sorry. That was a dumb joke.
Uh, hey. I was gonna go order some food.
Do you like Thai?
Uh, sure.
Great.
That wasn't planned at all, was it?
Nope.
Hey. You ok?
The "werewolf traitor" thing, is there
more trouble with your pack people?
Guess we'll find out soon enough.
I actually called a meeting tonight
for Hayley and Jackson,
so one way or another,
it's all coming to a head.
You know, those people look up to you.
I mean, trust me. I've seen you in action.
You're a badass.
So just go in there and
tell them what's what.
I'm not the Alpha.
No, but Jackson is,
and the pack respects both of you,
so if you stand with him,
they will listen.
One thing I learned from Marcel...
Hmm?
Loyalty sends a powerful message,
and hey, look. If you get nervous
or, like, need a vote of
confidence or whatever,
just remember that, uh...
I think you're pretty amazing.
[Music continues]
I'm a little surprised we
don't hear clapping right now.
Yeah. Totally.
Hey, Davina.
You can come down now.
Davina.
[Chanting]
[Panting]
We can deep doing this as long as you want,
or...
I can kill you now and turn you into
a brand-new baby vampire.
Go on. Do it.
My mother's got plans for
me whether I like it or not.
If I die, she'll just
pop me into another body,
not that my family will care that much
if the death was permanent.
What are you really up to,
hmm, and what's it got to do with Davina?
You're afraid I'm gonna
break her little heart.
That's downright paternal of you, Marcel.
Easy, Marcel, easy.
Let's give Kol a little longer to decide
before we lop off his head, hmm?
Comments like that...
he already thinks that you don't care.
Is that so, brother?
You only daggered me a dozen times.
You always cared more for
Marcel than you did for me.
Well, I didn't realize
I'd hurt your feelings.
Well, that's the thing, isn't it, Nik?
You don't know squat about me.
Klaus: Ah, but thanks to Marcel,
I know all I need to.
You're desperate to be a part
of this family, aren't you?
All of your mischief was
just attempts for attention.
You know, the truth is, Kol,
you're right to feel slighted.
I mean that. You're right,
but perhaps there's still time
to make it up to you.
[Music playing]
[Cell phone vibrating]
Voice: You have reached
the voice mailbox of...
[music playing]
Tell me...
Has there been anyone out
of the ordinary here today?
Just you.
Oh! I am so sorry. Let me...
That's quite all right.
Thank you.
Tsk.
Esther: I told you to clean yourself up...
Aah!
That if you were clean, no one would know
what you aree, what you've done.
Klaus: So, brother,
ready to embrace your new life of freedom?
I'm already free, brother.
You're aware our mother
cares nothing for you?
Niklaus, I assure you, my mother loves me.
She loves all of her children.
We would not exist without her sacrifice.
Do you even know the truth,
that she was barren,
and she grew so desperate for a family
that she begged one of the most powerful
witches in history for help,
her sister Dahlia.
Of course, Dahlia's price was high.
She agreed to make our mother fertile,
but in exchange, she sought
the firstborn as sacrifice.
Having no other choice...
our mother gave away our beloved Freya.
Our sister died of plague.
Esther gave her away.
Think about that, the pain,
the grief.
If you what you say is true,
than death is far too
delicate a fate for her.
She loves us more than you realize.
And is love the reason
she wanted my child dead?
She was trying to protect
you from Dahlia's curse.
What curse?!
Dahlia demanded the
firstborn of every generation.
Had your child lived, she
would have paid the price,
and if anyone had tried to protect her,
Dahlia would come and destroy us all.
[Hope gurgles]
Look at you.
So big, so perfect.
I can't imagine the joy of
spending every day with her.
It's...
Quite lovely.
Feels so human.
Yes. Some would argue the
most human of experiences.
I know I have to give her back
to Hayley when the time is right,
but she's made me realize how much
I want that child of my own
that I know I can't have.
A lovely dream.
Unfortunately, it's one
that's just beyond our reach,
considering the curse of our existence.
Seems Esther's attacking
with her usual fervor.
Yes. Mother tortured me
for days with memories
I thought I'd buried long ago.
Then she made an offer
to make us all mortal again.
You see, sister, mother believes that
by placing us in new bodies
we could then reclaim some kind of purity,
even begin families of our own again.
And I have to confess, Rebekah,
this invitation, however
cruel the delivery,
had a certain kind of... appeal.
[Hope gurgling]
You needn't worry.
We're safe.
[Hope crying]
Looks like this little one
needs her diaper changed.
Here, my love.
[Gasps]
Klaus: I'm done leaving messages, Elijah.
To say this is urgent would
be a gross understatement.
We need to speak immediately.
I was wondering whether you'd show up.
I'm afraid I'm not done
torturing your darling Kol.
You best run along while you still can.
I'm not going anywhere, Klaus.
Marcel: Whoa. D, today is not the day.
Actually, I think it is.
[Neck snaps]
Looks like it's just you and me now.
I know you're angry and scared,
but we are a pack, no matter what.
You've been checked out for months.
Why should we listen to you?
Aiden: Because he's the Alpha.
You got a problem with that?
Hayley: I want to hear
what Jackson has to say.
This is a pack meeting.
You're not one of us anymore.
No?
I am still a wolf,
and I didn't need any magical rings
to control when or how I change.
You want the same? Then sit down, shut up,
and listen.
Klaus: You forget yourself.
You're not as powerful as you once were,
harvest girl.
Doesn't mean I can't still kick your ass.
Such hubris,
and from one who bleeds so easily.
Unh.
You talk such a big game,
but you couldn't even kill
Mikael when you had the chance.
He was right about you, you know?
You're weak.
Aah!
[Gagging]
It's impressive.
What exactly did you do to him?
Channeled dark objects,
turned my blood to poison.
How did you get free?
Oh, it's a long story. Better question is
if he's not dead, then what are
you gonna do when he recovers?
We have an hour, maybe less,
enough time to chain him, bleed him,
dump him in the river.
That's a bit harsh, isn't it?
Since when do you care
what happens to Klaus?
[Marcel groans]
Kol is with us now.
We're gonna be going up against Esther,
assuming Klaus is upright.
Look. Nik... he's a pain in the ass,
but, well, she's a problem for us all.
Klaus is the problem.
I don't give a damn what happens to Esther.
Cami: Yeah? Well, I sure do.
Should I even ask?
Cami, you should go. It's not safe.
No kidding. I woke up with puncture wounds
all up and down my spine and no idea
how they got there.
According to my uncle's files,
they're a part of this ancient spell,
and I don't know about you guys,
but when I see "ancient" and "spell"
in the same sentence,
I think Esther.
Hayley: You all need help, and you know it.
Now whatever it is that you think of me,
I was born a Crescent.
I'm the last of the Labonair line,
which makes me an Alpha.
Jackson is your Alpha.
Now I don't know how many of you
bought the story you grew up with,
the unification myth.
Well, it is all true.
Which means if Jackson and I get married,
anyone with the guts to
turn up to the ceremony
has as much control over
their wolf form as I do.
[Indistinct chatter]
Hayley, what are you doing?
What needs to be done.
This isn't just about uniting our pack.
It's about forming a new community.
This ceremony will
change everything for us.
It will give us the strength
we need to defend ourselves.
Then and only then will
we finally have peace.
The choice is yours.
Keep the rings and be somebody's bitch,
or be part of the greatest
pack that ever lived.
I'm in.
[Clatter]
Yeah, that's mum's work all right.
She must have wiped your memory.
Not the first time that's been done
by a member of this family.
What does it mean?
It's a byproduct of a preparation spell.
Preparation for what?
To make her a vessel.
He means Esther prepared your body
for someone to jump into.
Likely herself. I mean, knowing mother.
Where's Vincent?
[Footsteps]
Why me out of everyone in this city?
Because you're perfect...
healthy, beautiful, smart, and alone.
No one would question
any personality changes,
and as I discovered from our sessions,
Niklaus would never allow you to be harmed.
Fix this.
Do something to stop it.
I can't. Only my mother can.
I will step in front of a moving truck
before I let your mother take over my body.
She wasn't preparing you for herself, Cami.
She was preparing you for Rebekah.
[Hope crying]
Well, she is all sorted
and ready for an adventure.
Aren't you, luv?
It's difficult to believe we
were all this innocent once.
We mustn't let the world ever hurt her.
You're right. We mustn't.
[Crack]
How long do I have?
Well, now that Esther knows
where Rebekah's hiding, not long.
The only way to stop it is to stop her.
Then let's do this.
Marcel's a vampire,
you both are powerful witches.
Esther's stronger than
anything I've ever seen.
We go up against her,
we're gonna need Klaus.
No. No. We can do this without him.
I'm never gonna say this again,
but Marcel's right.
We do need the bastard.
Davina...
I know this is asking a lot,
but please.
[Chanting]
[Gasps]
[Groans]
What did you do to me?
All you need to know is
that I beat you again.
And yet you relented,
which means you need me.
Did I really lose?
I'm sorry I sprung that on you.
You know, I always thought it
would be me popping the question
instead of being the one put on the spot.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Are you?
Look. I knw you're only
doing this to help our people,
but I promise I will be
a good husband to you.
Hayley Marshall, will you marry me?
No ring?
Heh heh.
Quite nice of you coming
to my rescue like that.
You know, it's a good thing
you didn't actually steal
the stake from me,
or I'd have been the one torturing you.
That mean you trust me now?
Klaus: Provided you're not busy concocting
a new paralytic to use against me,
I'd like a word with my brother.
Well, to be honest, I can't
stand being around you anyway.
For the record, didn't know a bloody thing
about mother's plan for Cami, I swear.
Well, I think I can judge for myself
which of her schemes
she would entrust to you
and which she would not.
I believe this was Finn's task.
And where, pray tell, is he now?
He's waiting uncomfortably for me
to return and deliver his punishment.
Pass the beignets, would you?
Now it's only a matter
of time before mother
gets bored of waiting for you to let us go.
Well, Finn at least.
Don't expect she'd care
if I never came home.
A mother cares for her
children, a monster does not.
Once you accept she is the latter,
you'll stop expecting the former.
And despite what you might think, Kol,
I did mourn you after your death,
and I did attempt to avenge you.
I would do nothing less
because we are brothers
always and forever.
[Cell phone ringing]
Excuse me.
Where have you been?
Rebekah: Nik, it's me. Something's wrong.
Elijah slaughtered a dozen
people whose only sin was
their terrible taste in food.
I mean, when have you known him to kill
when he can otherwise compel?
It's the kind of act that will draw
our mother's attention.
Her torture must have affected
him more deeply than I realized.
Where is he now?
I broke his neck to keep us safe,
but I have no clue what to do next.
Do you recall where we dined
the Christmas after we fled Mikael?
Of course.
Go there now.
If you enjoyed last night's activities,
then you're in for a treat.
Klaus, listen to me. Our mother...
Not another word.
No more fairytales about witches an curses.
If it's a fairytale, then why
do I see fear in your eyes?
Marcel!
Bring it in.
No.
No, Niklaus.
Oh, don't worry, brother.
I made some air holes, small ones.
Aah! Aah!
[Music playing]
Klaus, have you seen Elijah?
There's something I need to tell you both.
You can tell me on the way.
What? Where are we going?
To see our daughter.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -