Works every... I'm
telling you, every time.
- Do it, try it.
- What? Right now?
All right, all right. (Howls)
- Kind of... Kind of that.
- (Chuckles)
- Got to work on it, bro.
- All right, man.
- Seriously.
- All right, bro, I'll work on it.
But... just, like,
when... when do you know...
Right before the cork pops, you know?
- (Laughs)
- Timing's important, but...
But you don't do it, like... in her ear.
- No, you don't do it in her ear.
- Because... yeah.
It's a given you don't do it in her ear.
But this is, like,
scientifically proven, okay?
- Really?
- This is, like, prehistoric stuff.
- (Laughs) Crazy, man.
- It's like the medulla, the wolf brain.
- The what?
- It's primitive stuff...
All right, let me try it again.
- (Howls loudly)
- (Laughs)
Yeah!
- Yeah? That's the wolf brain.
- Nice.
(Both laugh)
Man, this town sucks!
I'm sorry, bro. I know it's
yours and everything, but...
- It's not even 2:00.
- Yeah, it does kind of suck.
Hey, I know this
after-hours place over...
A couple blocks off
Cermak. You want to hit it?
Hells yeah! Let's do it. (Exhales sharply)
That's what I'm talking about.
Whew!
- (Howls)
- Okay.
(Both howl)
- (Both laugh)
- Not in her ear, right?
Not in her ear, not in her ear. Hey...
Bro, I never did catch your name.
- Saul. (Clears throat)
- Saul?
"S'all good, man."
- (Laughs)
- Get it?
- I do... All right, Saul.
- (Chuckles)
Hey, hey, brother, whoa.
Check it out. What is that?
Holy shit.
There's got to be at least a
thousand bucks in here, man.
Oh, my God, look at that. (Chuckling)
- Whose is it?
- Mine.
Hey, possession's like 4/10ths of the...
What did you call it, bro? (Chuckles)
- Like, is there an ID or...
- Yeah.
I don't know. Some fat guy.
(Chuckles)
I'm thinking that one.
Phew... Let's...
Jesus. Is he, uh...
- What?
- Is he, uh...
I don't know.
- (Grunts)
- Hey.
Hey, fella. You all right?
(To tune of "Smoke On The
Water") ♪ Uh-huh-huh ♪
♪ Uh-huh-huh ♪
- Hey, buddy.
- ♪ Uh-huh-huh ♪
- Would you answer me?
- (Groans)
Hey, answer this, you butthole.
- ♪ Uh-huh-huh ♪
- What? Butt-hole?
- What the hell?
- Hey, uh...
Hey, bro. Be nice, all right?
This guy right here is trying to help you.
Help yourself to some
of this, you butthole.
Hey, we're not butt-holes, all right?
- So stop saying that.
- ♪ Butt, butthole ♪
♪ butt, butt, butt-hole ♪
- Hey, man, what's your problem?
- ♪ butt, butt, butt ♪
(Slurring) My problem is I'm standing
here talking to a couple butt-holes.
Actually, you're not
standing, you fat bastard.
You're laying on your fat ass. (Chuckles)
Hey, I'll roundhouse-kick
you right in your head.
And if you think I won't,
I'll come to the McDonald's,
where you work and I'll buy...
the whole damn place
and then I'll fire you.
I'll say, "drop your mops, you
butt-holes, 'cause you're fired."
And then I'll roundhouse-kick
you right in your stupid heads.
Then I'll go "John"-Claude
Van Damme on you...
S-s-s... (Snoring)
You butthole.
(Snoring)
I'm keeping the money.
- (Jimmy chuckles)
- Here you go, fatty.
I got dibs on that watch, man.
Let me see that.
What kind is it?
I don't know. It's just a watch.
- We got to get out of here, man.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What kind of watch is it?
- (Sighs)
- It's... I don't know. It's...
- Well, then, let me look at it.
(Chuckles)
- It's a damn Rolex.
- Oh. I don't know.
Not cool to be greedy, bro.
- Uh, I didn't know.
- Not cool.
I didn't know what...
So, how do you want to split this up?
I'll tell you what... you keep the cash.
- I'll just keep the watch.
- But it's worth like 3 grand, man.
- $3,000 easy.
- No.
- Yeah.
- (Scoffs)
- Hey, hey, hey.
- (Sighs)
Come on, let's figure this
out. We gotta get out of here.
All right, yeah. You're
right. You know what?
I... sweeten the pot.
I got, uh, $5, $20, $40,
$60, $80... 580 bucks.
Add that to the $1,000...
It's more than half.
What do you know about that thing?
I mean, is it worth more than $3,000?
No, I don't... I don't
know. But we're good, right?
Yeah? We good?
- Okay?
- Well...
Later, sucker! (Laughs)
(Stevie howling in distance)
("Listen" plays in background)
- Jimmy: Six left.
- Can we get more?
God, I hope so.
It's like a license to print money.
(Both chuckle) A thing of beauty.
Hey, what was that, uh, crazy
stuff about roundhouse kicks?
Where the hell did you get that?
I don't know, man.
Just something in my brain, you know?
It just came out. Too much?
No. I loved it.
It was, like, deep or something.
(Scoffs)
You want to talk about
brilliant? I mean we...
You're the man, me... I'm just...
I love watching you work, man.
(Water bubbling)
It's good for making beer
money. That's about all.
- (Inhales deeply)
- ♪ or you can smile ♪
♪ That's all right, my friend ♪
♪ It could be so... ♪
synced & corrected
Betsy: Please, okay? No one has to know.
I mean, you could just
pretend you didn't find us.
We would never tell
anyone, would we, Craig?
- No, absolutely not.
- No.
Jimmy: I already called your lawyer.
(Chuckling) Besides, this
little family outing of yours...
It's put an innocent man in jail.
The cops are investigating
this as a kidnapping.
They already rounded up some poor suspect.
A working-class guy. Father... I think.
But anyway, you two... you
almost ruined someone's life.
- Potentially several someones.
- I... we had no idea.
Could this have been
the person in the van?
(Gasps) What if the man they arrested
Is the one we were warned about?
Yeah, maybe he's not so innocent, hmm?
Warned? Warned how?
Well, we had a phone call.
Someone disguising their voice.
Yeah, they said someone was coming for us.
And there was a van outside the house...
As if whoever was inside was watching us.
- Mm-hmm. - And, uh,
once that drove off,
- We... did what we did...
- For the kids.
I wouldn't know about any of that.
I just... (Clears throat)
I can assure you that you
and your family are safe.
I mean, the police are
all over this thing, so...
It... it doesn't matter.
Uh, we can't just go back.
I mean, it's... our case.
They'll crucify Craig.
Can't you just call Ms. Wexler again?
You know, tell her you
didn't see us after all.
If they think I ran away, it'll
look like I did something wrong.
We can't risk losing everything
just because of some teensy mistake.
- I mean, it's...
- Can I ask you something?
What... what were you hoping would happen?
I mean, before I found you,
what were you planning to do?
(Clears throat)
Well, we were in the process
of, you know, working that out...
- We were working that out.
- When you, um...
- Yeah.
- (Chuckles)
All right, well, uh...
You still got a little bit
of maneuverability, all right?
You... you're outdoorsy, right?
So you went on an impromptu camping trip.
I don't know. It's something
people do, apparently.
Uh, you left the house a mess, and you
kicked in your own front door because...
(Breathes deeply) It's a free country.
Kim Wexler is very good.
She'll make it work.
Yeah, what... what about the money?
Uh, well, if she knows about it,
she'll tell, right? She'll have to tell.
Well, like they say in Silicon Valley,
"it's not a bug... it's a feature!"
Did you ever hear of a bargaining chip?
What we have right here is the
mother of all bargaining chips.
Um, as in... You expect
us to give this back?
We are not giving this back.
Uh, we are not guilty.
This money belongs to us.
We... well, I mean, Craig earned it.
- I worked very hard...
- Yeah.
- You know, weekends, holidays...
- Yep, all unpaid, always.
And, really, just because you're salaried,
doesn't mean you don't deserve overtime.
I think that's only fair.
I mean, really, that's
what this is about, right?
- Fairness.
- Fairness, right.
I mean, not just what's legal.
If you want to talk
about legal, slavery...
That used to be legal.
Human slavery. So...
Yeah, this is right up there with that.
(Insects chirping)
(Children playing)
Please, just don't tell
anyone about the money.
- I can't take a bribe.
- Who would know?
- We won't tell anyone.
- Yeah, take it.
I can't take it.
Please, didn't you say
that you wanted to help us?
So just pretend you never saw
the money. How hard is that?
Take it.
- (Scoffs)
- Take it.
I can't... (Sighs) I can't take a bribe.
But... (clears throat)
You know what? I... I can take a retainer.
A retainer?
Yeah, for my services... as your lawyer?
- You're not our lawyer.
- Well, not yet.
Look... I know that HHM
is shiny and it's slick.
It's chock-full of lawyers and,
compared to them, I'm like a...
(Sighs) A kiddy lemonade stand
trying to compete with Wal-Mart.
But here's the thing...
What are you gonna get from me
That you're not gonna
get from those other guys?
Passion, commitment.
Ask yourself this... who found you?
- (Chuckles)
- I don't see Howard Hamlin...
ruining his $300 Gucci loafers out here.
If you're with me, you're
my number-one client.
Morning, noon, or night,
you call me... I'm there.
I would be singularly devoted to you.
(Chuckling) But why not?
I'm sorry. You're just...
Just... I'm what?
You're the kind of
lawyer guilty people hire.
(Vehicle approaches)
(Brakes squeal)
(Buzzer)
Did it make the paper?
- What?
- Did it make the paper?
- Did what make the paper?
- (Scoffs)
Okay, well, probably missed the deadline,
but check it out tomorrow
morning... front page.
The Kettlemans, all four of them...
Safe and sound.
- Looks like you called it.
- Yeah.
Camping... you know, pretty
much right in their own backyard.
Well... (Clears throat)
Five miles above it.
Jesus, the night I had. I
got pine nuts in my shoes.
But, I mean, can you believe it?
I-I guess you can. It's just, you know...
You assume that criminals are
gonna be smarter than they are.
I don't know.
It kind of breaks my heart a little.
Not the loquacious sort, are you?
We can't all be as blessed as you.
- Well, thanks for your help.
- Don't mention it.
And, uh, if you ever
need any assistance...
(Indistinct conversations)
(Telephone rings)
(Door opens)
Whoa, whoa. Why is my client in handcuffs?
This man is innocent. He's a victim.
(Chuckling) why... why on
earth would he be cuffed?
Just go... go ahead. Take
them off. There you go.
Free at last!
Hey, did he tell you the good news?
Never even kidnapped... how about that?
A family can't go on a little vacation
without the whole city going on lockdown?
By the way, where is your partner?
What? Did you lose the coin toss?
Because we expect an apology
from him, as well as you.
You really don't want to push
your luck with me, scumbag.
You got eyes on you, asshole.
One little slip... just one.
Yeah, well, you're... you're
both very pretty, so...
- (Door opens)
- (Sighs)
(Door closes)
(Sighs) Well... (Clears throat)
I believe I did more
than what you asked of me,
so, uh, that would make us square, yes?
Great.
You need a ride?
Camping?
You expect me to believe that shit?
(Chuckles) yeah, I know it.
The things people do, huh?
They decide to go camping
Right after I run my little offer by you?
Could be argued that all of
life is one great coincidence.
(Indistinct conversation)
Somebody told those
people to, um, go camping.
Somebody warned them.
(Clears throat) they're very woodsy.
And between you and me,
They're pretty rash when it
comes to the decision-making.
I mean, they're not really
the plan-ahead types.
Yeah, I'd cut the cute
attitude right about now
If I were you.
You ratted on me. There
will be consequences.
Hey, if somebody warned the Kettlemans,
it was probably somebody who
was worried about those kids.
You know how much trouble you caused me?
You didn't need any help
getting caught, okay?
The neighbor ID'd you. You were sloppy.
Any trouble you might
have... that's on you.
Not to mention the blood in your van.
Here's a thought... Ajax, formula 409!
You have no idea the tap-dance
I had to give those cops
To get you out of here.
You gave them probable
cause out the wazoo.
Now, and whoever the somebody is
who may have warned the Kettlemans
got them out of there before you
did anything even more stupid.
You should be thanking
this good Samaritan.
Because whoever he is, he did you a favor.
("The Battle Hymn of the Republic" plays)
(Insects chirping)
(Sighing)
Okay, um, I'm thinking hourly here.
There were some special
circumstances, so...
(Clicks tongue) Our
elite-tier pricing would be...
$950 an hour.
(Calculator clicking)
round it off to 20 hours.
(Clicking continues)
$19,000...
Plus $1,000 for travel expenses.
Consulting fees... $1,500.
And, uh, research... Five for filing fees.
I ate on the road.
And storage fees.
(Sighs) Miscellaneous expenses.
(Sighs)
Upon this rock, I will build my church.
Tailor: Double-breasted or single, sir?
Single. Now, I want you to
cut the armholes high, okay?
- Of course.
- And trim through the middle.
- Trim.
- Cloth?
Uh, oh, well, uh, wool.
- Yeah.
- Uh...
"Super 170 Tasmanian wool."
- Beautiful choice, sir.
- Thanks.
Uh, navy, all right?
- Yeah. -
Uh... Mm-hmm.
Oh, that's it. Perfect. Pinstripe.
Shall we discuss shirts?
Okay, I'm gonna need your
finest sea island cotton
with a white club collar and french cuffs.
I have the very thing.
And I'm assuming you
want to see some ties?
Yeah, I was, you know,
picturing something in a...
- A light-blue
knit. - Mm.
Oh, and, uh, could you make sure
Those are real mother-of-pearl
buttons on the shirts, okay?
None of this fake plastic crap.
Of course. I'll be right back.
Some coffee, David, for the gentleman?
(Mid-tempo instrumental music plays)
Tailor: Ah, here we are.
- Shall we?
- Yeah, let's go.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- (Conversing in Vietnamese)
- So, um, what do you think?
- "Strawberry Fields Forever"?
- Mm.
(Scoffs) No. Are you
crazy? It's not even close.
- Yes, it is. Look.
- No, no.
It's way more "Sassafras Glow". Way more.
Use your eyes...
Strawberry Fields Forever.
Ladies, back me up. Hey.
Is it... Sassafras Glow.
- Am I right?
- Woman: No.
Maybe "Rhapsody in
Blonde," but... Yeah, see?
They agree with me.
Whatever happened to "the
customer is always right"?
Sassafras Glow... mix it up, all right?
You're wrong. You'll see.
Big deal. I'll wash it out in the morning.
- No biggie. Geez.
- It's bleach.
- It doesn't wash out.
- What? It's permanent?
(Clicks tongue) We'll
Photoshop the color, okay?
(Sighs) Change of plan, ladies.
I want to go with a simple
curling-iron job, okay?
Uh, give me, like, ringlets...
You know, on top, like
Tony Curtis in "Spartacus."
Yeah, like the bath scene in "Spartacus."
(Speaking Vietnamese)
- Okay.
- "I am Spartacus."
(Claps hands) Stop talking about it!
Make me beautiful, already.
(Talking in Vietnamese)
(Engine revs)
(Indistinct conversations in distance)
(Telephones ringing)
(Dialing)
(Ringing)
(Click) Jimmy: (British accent) Hello.
You've reached the law offices
of James M. McGill, esquire,
A lawyer you can trust.
Kindly leave your information at the tone,
And Mr. McGill will phone you promptly.
(Beep)
Hey. Uh... It's me.
(Scoffs) Hi.
Anyway, uh, "The Thing" is
playing downtown on Saturday.
Thought you might be up for
some Kurt Russell action.
I owe you one, so why don't
we just grab some dinner first?
My treat.
And... Uh, you know, if not,
can you give me a call anyway?
I really want to talk to you.
- Okay. Uh, bye.
- (Knock on door)
- (Beep)
- Come in.
- Hey.
- Hey, hey.
How goes it?
Uh, tricky, for sure.
Craig and Betsy really put us
in a corner with the police.
Not to mention the press.
But this camping story of theirs...
They've been keeping
it consistent, at least.
If it's okay with you,
I think I should try to talk
them into hiring a PR firm.
Certainly for the next couple of weeks.
Mm-hmm.
So, okay on the PR firm?
- Do you have a minute?
- Yeah, of course. What's up?
Take a ride with me.
Uh, okay. Uh... Where are we going?
(Engine shuts off)
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
Shit.
Yep. (Sighs)
That's... I mean, that's my suit, right?
- Am I crazy here?
- No, you're not crazy.
Look at the logo. That's our logo.
He's just straight-up copying us.
I mean, what the hell
is he thinking with this?
I really... h-h-he's,
you know, a free spirit.
(Chuckles)
Yeah, that's one way to put it.
You two are still friends, right?
- I wouldn't exactly...
- You talk, though.
Not really...
Still, you're the one he called
when he found the Kettlemans
camped halfway up the Sandias.
He was just looking out for
his own client... that's all.
This isn't the third degree, Kim. I
really don't care one way or the other.
I just... (Sighs)
He's really forcing my hand here.
(Man singing in native language)
(Knock on door)
- (Bell jingles)
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Am I interrupting?
- (Bell jingles)
Not at all. Perfect timing. Come on.
Sit. Have a massage, free
of charge. (Clicks tongue)
- (Chuckles) Okay.
- Got to try the foot bath, too.
Oh, yeah.
Ah, give the old dogs a rest.
(Sighs)
And go for the deep-tissue
setting. Otherwise...
- Is that the small fist?
- Use the three arrows.
- I did. I pressed it.
- Just... yeah.
- (Chair vibrating)
- Now you feel it? Good.
- Ah, now relax, okay?
- Okay.
You deserve a break today.
(Clicks tongue)
- It's very nice.
- Told you.
I get this free every night...
Just one of the perks of salon living.
The others being... Free
cucumber water, obviously.
Obviously. Free mani-pedis?
Uh, deep discount mani-pedis.
Because the ladies still
got to eat, you know?
- Well, it's still a deal.
- Yeah.
(Clicks tongue)
- (Sighs)
- Living like a king, then.
Mm-hmm.
(Sighs)
(Clicks tongue)
What's this? Is this a cease and desist?
Yeah.
Yeah. How pissed was he?
Well, his head didn't actually explode,
but, you know, pretty damn pissed,
like "this won't end well for you" pissed.
Yeah.
- How about that?
- Jimmy.
- This is serious.
- I know.
- Do you? I mean...
- Yeah.
What the hell is with that billboard?
I know you have a problem
with Hamlin, but I...
I just don't get your angle here.
Aren't you trying to build
your own law practice?
Instead, you're spending
god knows how much money
turning yourself into
a little Hamlin clone.
I mean... Why are you
making this personal?
It's not personal? It is so personal.
It is completely and totally personal.
- No, no, no. It's not. No.
- Yes. Yes, it is.
(Sighs) Stop trying to pretend.
- I can advertise, can't I?
- (Sighs)
What, do I have to clear everything
past the great and powerful Howard?
Yes, you can advertise,
Jimmy, all you want.
That billboard is not advertising.
That is a declaration of war.
Declaration of war? That's...
It's right at Hamlin's exit. You
know he drives by it every day.
It's business. I'm building a brand.
You're ripping off a brand.
(Clicks tongue)
- There is nothing original in that ad.
- (Sighs)
It certainly doesn't
represent Jimmy McGill.
Hey, all right, now, he
fired the first shot, okay?
Trying to keep me from using
my name, my own name, Kim?
I get that.
But this... You're better than this.
- I'm better than this?
- Yeah.
- You are.
Well, you're better
than that schmuck Hamlin!
- Oh, come on, Jimmy.
- You could work anywhere.
You could be somewhere
where they appreciate you...
You know, where they
see how valuable you are,
where, I don't know,
maybe they care about you?
Forget it, okay?
If Hamlin wants to come
after me, he knows where I am.
I'll be ready, guns blazing.
- (Papers thud)
- (Sighs)
(Clicks tongue)
(Sighs)
(Beep) (Vibrating stops)
The cease and desist
is just the beginning.
The next step is an injunction.
You can't win this fight.
(Beep)
(Chair vibrating)
(Sighs)
(Lock turns)
(Bell jingles)
(Door closes)
Your honor, I'm a
humble solo practitioner,
merely trying to ply my trade
In an aggressive and evolving marketplace.
As I've argued repeatedly,
this is trademark infringement.
Mr. McGill's new logo is
an absolute copy of ours.
I think it falls firmly under fair use.
Fair use?
You're clearly profiting,
so fair use doesn't apply.
It... there are only
Does Mr. Hamlin outright own them all?
No, but we've been using this
and it, in concert with
our tri-rectangle graphic
and Hamlindigo Blue, constitutes
a trademarked brand identifier.
Whoa, whoa. Back up. Hamlindigo blue?
Yes. That is our trademarked name.
(Scoffs) Holy crap.
You seriously named a color "Hamlindigo"?
That is... yikes.
"Yikes"? From the man
dressed exactly like me.
Your honor, I feel like I'm in the
mirror routine with Groucho Marx,
Like we should be standing,
waving our arms at each other.
Really? I don't see it.
In addition, the name
McGill appears in both logos,
which, I believe, Mr. McGill is hoping
to further confuse potential clients.
So I can't advertise
under my own name now?
I'm to be penalized 'cause I happen to
share a name with one of HHM's partners?
You can't take my name from me.
The name is not the
problem here, Mr. McGill.
Uh, Mr. Hamlin certainly
seems to think so.
I mean, he wants me to change
my name 'cause he claims that...
That... what... it's some
kind of threat to his business?
- Your honor.
- This is restraint of trade, okay?
Whatever happened to the free market, huh?
- No, Hamlin here wants you to tell...
- Okay, okay, I've... enough.
Mr. McGill, I've heard enough.
All right, yes, you are within your rights
to advertise using your own name.
However, in my estimation,
the billboard clearly
and intentionally duplicates elements
of the Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill logo.
You're actively copying their
established brand for your own gain.
I don't see any other
reasonable explanation.
- Your honor, I...
- Jimmy, Jimmy.
Wise up. The billboard must
come down within 48 hours.
This is a classic David vs. Goliath story.
I mean, you got your gigantic law
firm Stomping all over the little guy.
Woman: Can you hold the door?
Yeah, but it's investigative
journalism at its best.
I-it's right up your alley.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, o-okay, well, let me
give you my cell just in case.
Uh... yeah. Thank you.
(Beep)
(Sighs)
(Sniffs)
(Beep)
Can I get the news desk, please?
I got a hot tip.
Don't you want to be the station
that brought down big law?
You could be like the reporters
that brought down big tobacco.
Look, I'm talking Woodward
and Bernstein here.
Hey, your exposé on predatory
ATM fees... that was... Wow!
Well, it's a miscarriage of justice,
And I think your viewers
would be very, very interested
And, uh, grateful to you
for exposing this injustice.
I wouldn't characterize this
as a community health risk,
But it's definitely in
the community interest.
No, yes, HHM is a pillar
of the community, yes.
No, I... the war is an
important story, as well.
That's why this action is so egregious.
Sure. Okay.
Well, at least consider the
human-interest angle here.
Are you kidding?
It's... lawyer pulls
himself up by his bootstraps,
Only to be ground under the
heel of the old-money megafirm?
That's hearts and minds! You... hello?
- (Sighs)
- (Beep)
Yeah, I have your number, too, so...
Yeah, I see.
- Okay.
- (Elevator bell dings)
(Dialing)
(Elevator bell dings)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, man.
Can't touch the goods.
I signed the form... only
I can touch the camera.
Fine, may I suggest you
widen the frame to include...
The billboard is the story, okay?
No, I'm also the story,
so... Got to get me in there.
Okay, so, get on your mark.
You know, uh, no offense to
your minutes of experience,
But I'd like to see what we
got before we do this, okay?
Other guy.
Other guy!
Only other guy that's here,
go stand where I was standing.
Uh... Shrink down. Shrink down.
You know, scrunch. Yeah. (Clicks tongue)
Okay, widen the frame. Get the billboard.
Okay, now get me. Me, me, me, me, me.
No. Not me... get him.
He's me. Yeah, like that.
Got it? Yeah.
Good.
(Sighs) Okay. Is he in the shot?
No. Dude, just go.
- (Sighs) How do I look?
- Great.
I'll, uh... no, this is my good side.
(Chuckles, breathes deeply)
Is, uh... is the billboard in? Yes!
Jesus, just... you said $100
for one hour, not freaking 3.
You clearly have a journalistic impulse.
You're a real go-getter, you know that?
Go get this.
All right, count me down.
In 5, 4, 3...
Gravitas.
(Breathes deeply) I'm James McGill.
Like most Americans, I'm a self-made man.
I put myself through law school.
Working in the courts
as a public defender,
I represented those with
nowhere else to turn.
I believe in service. It's
what I've built my career on.
But I've also had a dream, a
dream that many of us have...
A dream to own my own business.
Well, I-i scrimped and
I saved, and finally,
I was able to buy one billboard...
A tiny foray into advertising
for my fledgling law firm.
(Sighs) I've always been told
That America is the land of opportunity,
And I believed it...
Until today. (Chuckles)
Not 24 hours after my billboard went up,
a large law firm came after me.
They said that I was
hurting their business.
They're rich. They're
powerful. I'm just... One man.
So, who do you think
the courts sided with?
(Clicks tongue)
So now my little billboard comes down.
Let me tell you something...
If they want a fight,
they're gonna get a fight,
- Because I'm not giving up, not...
- (Screaming)
Holy shit! Dude, the dude!
- (Working guy screaming) Help!
- Dude, the dude!
- The worker guy!
- Holy shit.
Please! Aah! Get me down!
- Dude!
- Yeah, okay, call 911!
- Man: Help me! Ah!
- You got a cell?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Please!
Yeah, a guy just fell off a billboard
from frontage road south of mountain.
Hey, man!
(Grunting) Help me!
Hey, man, I don't think that's very safe!
You need to be, like, licensed for that!
- Working guy: Help me!
- Man...
(Panting, grunting)
Not looking down. One rung at a time.
Not looking down.
(Indistinct conversations)
(Man grunting)
(Grunting)
Hurry up!
Come get me!
Help!
(Grunting)
Help me! Aah!
- Sir, I'm right here!
- Please!
Please!
- Pull me up!
- Here, grab my hand!
Pull me up!
(Both grunting)
- Pull me up!
- Here!
- Aah!
- (Both grunting)
(Indistinct shouting)
(Both panting)
You okay?
Took you long enough.
I was scared, yes.
I mean, I'm not really
a big fan of heights...
Let me tell you.
(Indistinct conversations)
But, you know, something inside
me said, "you have to do this."
I'm sure our city's first responders
would have been here momentarily.
- Can you believe this guy?
- But at least I was able...
This whole thing was a
publicity stunt. It's got to be.
I think that's kind of all anybody
wants when they're in trouble.
Of course I didn't think...
You don't think anyone's
gonna actually buy this?
It's hard to say. People love a hero.
You take it as it comes, right?
The universe put me in
that spot at that moment.
Who am I to say no?
You know, as a lawyer, while
I help people every day...
- Whole thing's a damn stunt.
- But I think my clients know...
that when they're in trouble, I'm there.
I was just a guy who was in the right...
(Sighs)
(Breathing deeply)
(Dial tone)
(Dialing)
- (Ringing)
- (Sighs)
Female voice: You have seven new messages.
(Sighs)
To listen to your messages, press "1."
(Beep)
First message, received at 5:40...
(Engine shuts off)
(Sighs)
_
(Clicks tongue) It's
just showmanship, Chuck.
(Clears throat)
Yeah, right.
(Sighs)
(Birds chirping)
You're early.
- Did you...
- Yeah, I grounded myself.
Hey, big day. My phone's
ringing off the hook.
I have three consults
before lunchtime... three.
- That's great, Jimmy.
- Yep.
- The worm has turned.
- (Chuckling)
That's really great.
So, to what do you
credit this sudden change?
Well, I got to admit... you were right.
How so?
Well, you told me to keep
plugging and, uh, you know...
do good work, and the clients will come.
You know, I'll admit.
I almost lost faith a couple
times, but the worm has turned.
So, uh, what... you've been getting
referrals from your PD clients?
Uh, yeah. You know...
You work hard, show you got half a brain,
and people come knocking, like you said.
I just needed to get my face out there.
Oh.
So, prosecutors, then...
referring clients?
Yeah. Yep. Exactly.
Was it Bergeron?
When I was starting out, she
sent me a couple good ones.
Yeah, uh, it was...
It was someone on her team.
(Clicks tongue) You know?
I mean, hey, just took some
elbow grease and clean living...
People noticed.
I knew you had it in you.
I don't see the journal here.
- Right. Here you go.
- No, no, no.
Uh, Albuquerque journal... it's not here.
Oh, yeah. (Sighs) I didn't see it outside.
Wasn't out there? It's always out there.
I didn't see it. (Chuckles)
Maybe they forgot to deliver it.
Maybe some kids grabbed it. (Chuckles)
Because if there's one thing kids
love, it's local print journalism.
(Chuckles) I don't know what to tell you.
You got a ton of reading material there.
Look, hey. (Whistles) Financial Times.
You know, I know Albuquerque
is a hub of global intrigue,
but you think that'll tide you over?
All right, fine. But if
it's not here tomorrow,
I'm gonna need you to call
the subscription office for me.
Yeah, will do. Look, I got to go.
- I don't want to be late.
- Hey, good luck today!
- Thanks.
- Keep it up.
Hard work looks good on you.
(Engine turns over)
(Car departs)
(Plastic rustling)
(Sighs)
(Heavy breathing)
Oh!
(Gasping)
(Horn honks)
(Electricity crackling)
Ah!
Oh!
(Electricity humming)
(Electricity whining)
- (Grunts)
- (Electricity pulsing)
(Pulsing stops)
(Birds chirping)
Oh!
(Groans)
(Breathing deeply)
_
__
(Clock ticking)
(Sighs)
www.addic7ed.com