Klaus: In the beginning,
we were so naive.
Our mother hade made us
into beasts
that fed on blood,
but immortality was
beyond our grasp,
compulsion a trick
we had yet to learn.
All we knew was a fear
of being hunted.
That and a terrible hunger.
So we ran...
As a family...
And when we needed to...
We fed.
Unh!
[Neighing]
Kol, are you quite done?
Ahh.
Oh, bother, Elijah.
Is all this truly necessary?
Brother, the road is
a major thoroughfare.
If the bodies are found,
word of our presence
will spread to mikael.
We have run through
autumn and winter,
through sleet and snow.
Are we cursed to
forever live in fear
of our father?
I should say yes sadly.
Finn, please.
Niklaus.
Do we have any idea
where we're running
to next?
Why not just do
what we've all
thought of doing?
Split up.
We swore a vow.
Your vows haunt me
more than father himself.
At least he can't chase us all.
I say we take our chances.
Perhaps kol is right.
Thank you, finn.
Yeah, I've always said
eldest is the most intelligent.
Stop talking!
I take no joy in our assent,
but I do wish to sleep in a bed,
to bathe in a bath,
to feed of proper food.
If we divide...
Elijah: No, brother.
Niklaus is right.
We made a vow.
Family above all.
Always...
Forever.
Always and forever indeed.
Freya, voice-over:
"My dear rebekah...
"I hope this finds you well.
"I write to offer an update
"and to ask your advice.
"Our brothers remain at odds.
"Klaus will never apologize,
"not for the blood he shed,
nor the suffering
hayley continues to endure"...
"And Elijah cannot forgive him."
"Despite my efforts,
we are a house divided"...
"Which is not to say
I have no good news.
"Niklaus kept his word.
"Marcel controls the quarter.
"There he has founded
a fight gym
"in the old St. Anne's church,
"where he tests the mettle
of those who wish to join
"his vampire community.
"Elijah has begun joining
him for sparring.
I believe it helps him
work through his anger"...
"And he has much anger."
[Hope crying]
"While hope
continues to flourish,
"it is clear that
she misses her mother.
"Though niklaus remains
the doting father,
"he has been of no help
in finding a cure
for hayley's curse."
"Despite my best efforts,
"I have yet to find a means
to undo the spell
"placed on her
and the Crescent wolves,
"and hayley herself
continues to struggle,
"unable to see her child
except once a month
on a full moon"...
"And we're in no position
to ask for outside help."
Can you just hear me out?
No. Witches don't do
favors for vampires,
including daylight rings.
Those are the rules.
An act of good
faith will help
keep the peace.
The ninth ward coven
thinks I'm a vampire
sympathizer.
I won't prove them right.
You're on your own.
Freya: "Davina's rage
at our family
"has only grown,
"and as regent of all covens,
"she's far too formidable
to be swayed.
"Meanwhile, niklaus
has begun to see Camille
"for what he calls
their little chats.
"He claims a desire
to ammend his ways.
In truth, he seems
utterly free of remorse"...
around in his blood,
and that was the end of that.
"Which only drives
Elijah further away.
"I wonder if you would
write me with any advice
"you have on how to heal
their fractured bond.
Until then, I remain
your loving sister freya."
Camille.
Thanks for coming.
Why did you ask me
to meet you here?
Well, I had hoped
we might have one
of our little chats,
and I thought you might
appreciate the change
of venue,
so I'm allowing you
a private tour
of my exhibition.
These are yours?
Heh.
I spent the better part
of a millennia
trying not to draw
my father's attention,
and now he's dead,
and all those
who stood against me
have been vanquished.
I see no reason
the fruits of my labor
should go unappreciated.
I didn't come here
to appreciate art.
If you want to talk
about your progress
as a person striving
for empathy, fine.
If not, I'll go.
Have I offended you?
I agreed to see you
professionally,
but I was very clear
when I set our boundaries,
and they don't include
private art shows.
Oh. Well, then
perhaps you'd prefer
to escort me
to tomorrow's opening.
Call me if you want to talk.
Wait.
You're worried
no one else will come.
Rebekah's gone, marcel's angry,
Elijah won't even look at you.
You'll be alone.
You're scared because
the people you love
are angry with you.
Maybe you need to think
about that.
[Cell phone chimes]
I have to go.
[Siren]
Vincent: Ok. The thing
you got to understand
is me and nola pd got
a relationship
that goes back
to that nastiness
with my ex-wife.
I'm their expert
in anything that
seems occult,
and every so often,
they come across
the aftermath
of some black magic,
and they call me in.
This your friend the shrink?
Fantastic.
Will Kinney,
detective, homicide.
Cami O'Connell, bartender,
part-time shrink.
Why am I here?
Vince, show her the body.
We'll see if she
can do what you
said she can do.
So the cops want
a psychological profile,
and given what we've found,
I'd say this is
your area of expertise.
She's getting bigger
by the second.
Thank you for all of your care.
Tomorrow's the full moon.
I can help you
bring hope to hayley
if you'd like.
Won't be necessary.
You deserve a night off.
I'd offer to accompany
you myself,
but I fear my fragile ego
could not endure
the litany of insults
hayley has no doubt prepared.
Yes, I doubt that your presence
is particularly welcome
anywhere.
My own brother
greeting me
with such disdain.
What do you think, freya?
Is he still angry
for my part
in hayley's curse?
Need I remind him
it was my ploy that
kept her alive.
But of course.
Forgive me.
So you would call this
an act of heroism,
even as you bask in her torment?
Perhaps I'd be more sympathetic
if hayley apologized.
After all, it was
her that tried to run off
with my daughter.
Freya: Oh, if you
two must poke
at one another,
may I suggest doing it
elsewhere?
Nicely done.
At this rate, you'll drive
the entire family away.
Who's ready for the next course?
Finn: You're all
filthy gluttons.
And you remain ever the dullard.
Oh, such pretty clothes.
What a shame
they'll go to waste.
Rebekah, we have
discussed this
endlessly.
No. You've discussed this.
None of us had
any say in the matter.
This lot were traveling
somewhere.
Their car is full
of silks and finery.
5 of them, 5 of us.
Wherever they were off to,
why can we not simply
go in their stead.
Masquerade as nobles
from a land we do not know,
whose customs we cannot
begin to understand.
Ridiculous.
You saw the castle
down the road.
It was practically a gala.
If this bunch were
headed there,
then...
Look at them.
They're not any
better than we are.
We could live as they do,
at least for a time.
Think of it. Elijah, we
could hide in plain sight.
We could live ordinary lives.
Silence.
[Heartbeat]
[Gasping]
Well, aren't you a handsome one?
Kol: He looks like
dessert to me.
No! Wait, wait, wait!
I can help you.
Now I am... I am
the personal servant
to the count de martel
of the very estate
you just mentioned.
I wa... I was sent
to escort these guests
to his home for a lengthy stay.
I know their customs,
as... as well as
the count's habits.
If you mean to pose
as the family you
have slaughtered here,
then you'll need my help
to carry out your ruse.
Please can we keep him?
Elijah: Rebekah, no.
What is our most important rule?
Never leave alive someone who...
All: Has seen what we are.
Elijah: Thank you
very much.
A practice that has served
us very well indeed.
She has a point.
- He may be of use.
- Ah, a proper family squabble.
Perhaps we should
put it to a vote.
All those in favor
of letting him live.
Those inclined to gut him.
Well, Nik...
What shall it be?
Woman: It's a no-brainer really.
This penthouse is equipped
with all the luxuries
money can buy,
and while the asking price
may seem daunting,
rest assured that
your view of new Orleans
will be second to none.
- I do like it.
- Mm-hmm.
And as for the price,
well, nothing of worth comes
without sacrifice,
wouldn't you agree?
Mr. castle.
Please.
Call me lucien.
[Gasping]
I'm no forensic psychologist,
but whoever did this
took their time.
He bled a lot,
which means he was alive,
but it's like
he just stood here.
These ropes are
just for display.
He wasn't bound,
there are no marks
on his wrists,
no signs
of struggling
or clawing.
He was compelled, Camille.
Maybe rich boy pissed off
the wrong vampire.
Will: How are you guys
doing over here?
Tell me you got something.
It seems methodical, precise.
The wounds may have
a special meaning
for the killer.
Not a formal ritual
but intentional...
And the things we do on purpose
we tend to repeat.
[Indistinct chatter]
Davina: Thank you for coming.
I spent the night consulting
our ancestors.
They say we must remain strong
and to defend our homes,
but for now, no covens are
to expand into gentilly.
This decision is to keep us
from a violent turf war
with the vampires,
and it's final.
Excuse me, Kara.
I did not dismiss you.
Do not walk away from me.
[Chanting]
[Bones crack]
[Witches gasping]
[Chanting]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Men grunting]
Gnarly stuff.
Vincent: Yeah.
The guy was torn apart.
I mean, there are no
obvious puncture wounds,
but whoever did that
had to be a vampire.
And no one heard any screams,
so he must have been
compelled to just
stand there
and suffer.
You think this was us.
My guys know better
than to leave
a body in the streets.
Yeah? Well, how well
do you know your guys?
Dead bodies lead to headlines,
which means tourism drops.
We don't like
to mess with
the food supply.
Marcel, maybe someone new
lost control.
Maybe you should
consider that
my guys aren't
the only vampires in town.
You don't think this was Klaus?
Elijah says that
Klaus has been on
his best behavior.
I've known the guy
over 200 years.
Best behavior ain't
exactly his thing.
Sooner or later,
he'll cut loose,
or maybe, he already did.
Leon Bridges: ♪ ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ she was born
in new Orleans ♪
♪ new Orleans ♪
it's a derivative fiasco.
Little atmosphere,
less technique.
The work is nothing more
than a celebratory ego trip.
♪ Lisa Sawyer,
circa 1963 ♪
I wouldn't expect you
to host an art show
without compelling
the critic to speak
to your praise.
And I wouldn't expect
an uncultured savage
to crash such a formal affair.
Ah, not my usual scene,
but that mouthy blood bag
does have a point.
Your work is derivative
of degas, I'd say.
Of course, I happen
to know that you compelled
degas to mentor you.
I always thought
his work improved
after your influence.
Finally, someone
with an eye for art.
Well, live long enough,
you develop a taste
for it,
among other things.
Speaking of which,
can we please have a drink?
I am quite parched.
Ha ha ha!
♪ New Orleans ♪
[car approaching]
Hell of a spot for a picnic.
Yes. If you can tolerate
the mosquitoes,
it's actually rather serene.
Finger sandwich?
Trouble is you're trespassing.
This whole area is now property
of kingmaker land development.
In two years,
it's gonna be golf
courses and condos.
I take it you're not
on the board of directors.
No. My team and I
are animal control.
There's
been an influx
of wild predators.
My boss pays
top dollar to,
uh, wipe them out.
Wild predators.
Wolves if you can believe it.
Killed a half-dozen
last night.
This baby can take
a head clean off.
Hey. Anyway, um,
I'm gonna have
to ask you to
clear out asap.
Ohh! Agh!
[Grunting]
Call off your men.
You leave this place
and you seek
another line of work.
No more dead wolves.
I'm an independent contractor.
There are other teams out there.
I don't have authority to...
[snap]
There.
You see the count de martel?
You address him as "your grace,"
all other nobles as "milord,"
and when you speak to the count,
you should speak of hunting.
He loves his hawks
and his hounds,
and, um, bow deep,
milady rebekah.
He also relishes
a healthy cleavage.
For God's sake, all of you,
stop looking up.
Touch me again,
and I'll tear your
arms straight off.
Finn: Behave, kol,
or I will
bury you in
the ground to rot.
This isn't going to work, is it?
Lucien: Just speak
as we practiced
and know that you
look lovely, milady.
Are you worried, brother?
We're placing our
lives in the hands
of a stranger, niklaus.
Count: Lucien, you
were sent to fetch
the comte du guise.
Indisposed, your grace.
Gout.
May I present his children?
The lords finn, niklaus,
Elijah, and kol.
Also the lovely lady rebekah.
Your father never
mentioned you to me
in all our dealings.
Yes. Your grace,
do forgive us.
Uh, father was forever distant
with his travels,
and, uh, we were
largely raised by servants.
However, I do know
that father would
consider it
a glorious honor
that we should be
introduced to society
by your noble hand,
your grace.
Klaus: Your grace,
I look forward to hearing
tales of your hunting escapades.
May I present our sister?
Rebekah du guise
de rochefort en seine.
Charmed.
[Indistinct chatter]
You have proven to be
an immense help.
Heh. Of course,
milord.
Though I must say
you don't seem
at all disturbed
about leading us
into your master's home.
My master is a cruel drunkard
who torments his
minions for sport,
beggars who seek succor,
vassals who cannot pay a debt,
like my own father.
Ah.
A these gentlefolk
behind their silks
and their jewels,
they are slavers, killers.
Whatever evil you are,
you walk amongst
greater evil still.
What do I care if
you kill the lot
of them?
[Indistinct chatter]
Who are they?
Oh. They're
the count's children,
the lord Tristan and his sister
the lady aurora.
She is exquisite.
Yes. Um, as her
brother is wicked.
Might I suggest
that you avoid
them completely?
Would she really be
such a threat,
even to one like me?
The lady aurora doesn't
need teeth to tear
a man's soul out.
One need only stare
in her eyes
and be lost.
Ah.
Oh, kol... kol was
a bloody loon.
Loved it.
And finn... oh, finn.
Finn... finn was fine
as long as you didn't
actually have to
speak to him.
Have you spoken to her?
Who?
Oh, you mean her.
As you well know, aurora and I
parted ways centuries ago.
Please excuse me.
There's someone
I need to speak to.
Hmm. Anyone tasty?
Stay here and behave yourself.
Always.
Well, I suppose later
is better than never,
but you are late indeed.
I'm not here
for the show.
I have a problem,
and you weren't
answering your phone.
Who's the dirt bag
eyeing me like I'm
a rack of lamb?
Old friend?
Old acquaintance, nothing more.
Old acquaintance?
You wound me?
He can hear us?
Is he...
Hard of hearing?
Quite the opposite
actually.
A side effect
I inherited
from Nik.
We can discuss
my discourteous
friend lucien
at our next little chat.
For now, let's preserve
your precious boundaries,
shall we?
Someone tortured
and killed a local,
left the body
right out in the open.
I think it was a vampire.
Yes. Well, vampire
business is now
marcel's purview
or Elijah's when he's
not busy loathing me.
By all means, check with them.
[Digitalism's
"second chance" playing]
♪ We get a second chance
tonight ♪
♪ we get a clean slate ♪
♪ forget about
the past tonight ♪
♪ it's never too late ♪
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
Did I misinterpret
the kind of exhibition
you were attending?
I switched venues.
Aren't you the one
who said I deserved
the night off?
Forgive me. Someone
needs to watch hope.
I have an errand to run.
How ominous.
What errand?
A necessary evil.
I would rather our niece
not bear witness.
Fair enough.
Give me a minute.
I have an idea.
[Indistinct chatter]
Your pretty friend
seems to have fouled
your mood.
Why don't we go out,
paint the town red,
et cetera, et cetera?
Lucien...
What are you really
doing in my city?
News has spread, old friend.
Every vampire in the world
knows you've been attacked,
a number of times nearly killed.
Oh. Well, I can
assure you
that all those who
stood against me
ended up either
desiccated, dust,
or dinner.
Yes, but what if it
had gone the other way, hmm?
When finn was killed,
we all learned
the truth...
The life of every
vampire is linked
back to the original
who begat the line.
Kol's death confirmed it.
Two entire lines
of vampires wiped out.
As you can imagine,
the treat of it
doesn't sit well
with those of us that remain.
Anyone fearing death
as a result of my demise
should come see me.
I'll be happy to reassure them.
Of course. Heh.
You and your siblings
are mighty indeed,
yet the attacks on you
do show that you
are not completely invulnerable.
While you've wallowed
in your family affairs,
your progeny have grown
somewhat restless.
The world is
a finite place,
territory limited,
and even ancient
vampires are not
above vicious turf wars.
What if I told you
there's a growing
conflict
between the remaining
3 sire lines?
Suppose one of them
wanted to annihilate
the other
by killing Elijah, rebekah, you?
So you came all this way
to deliver a warning?
Think about it.
Kill an original,
wipe out an entire line
of competition.
A tempting goal, made more so
by the fact that
your family is divided
and thus weaker than
you have ever been.
My family is hardly weak.
In fact, we are unkillable.
The last of the white oak
is gone.
Are you so certain
it's all gone,
every last splinter of it
banished for good?
[Growls]
Lucien, if you had
even the slightest inkling
any fragment
of white oak still existed,
of course you would tell me.
Easy, Nik.
You are my sire.
My fate is linked to yours.
If you want to know what I do
about the dangers you now face,
trust me enough to come with me.
There is something
that you must see.
[Grunting]
I'd ask if everything was ok,
but you wouldn't be here
if it were.
You know, I was bored
out of my mind when I
lived up here.
I don't miss it,
but things were
a lot simpler.
And at least I felt safe.
What happened?
I was attacked.
One of my own people
tried to use a spell
to ruin my hands.
What's next, my eyes, my heart?
They hate me.
I knew that,
but I didn't think
they would just revolt.
Witches in new Orleans
have a habit
of getting homicidal, all right?
Why do you think I was
so hard on them?
But I'm regent.
They should respect me.
I didn't sign up for this.
Sure you did.
You chose to be their leader.
The target on your back,
it comes with the job.
So what do I do?
Say the word, all right?
Me and my guys will...
You'll what?
They see me
siding with you
against my own kind,
I'll just be proving them right.
"D," someone came at you.
It might be one today,
but if you sit back
and do nothing,
but tomorrow,
there'll be more.
You got to respond
with a show of force.
If not me, find another way,
but it's got to be done.
Hello, sweetie.
We'll have to excuse
your auntie freya.
I've had a few
big girl drinks tonight.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, my goodness.
Where are my manners?
Permit me to explain.
Ohh! Unh!
Unh!
[Man groaning]
Lesson one of the hunt...
[Grunting]
Lay the bait.
[Screaming]
How precious.
And just in time for lesson two.
[Elevator dings]
Please excuse the mess.
I've been entertaining.
[Dance music playing]
Well, you never were
one for subtlety.
Heh.
You brought me here
to have a seance?
Something like that.
I present
my personal forecaster...
The lovely Alexis.
Don't tell me you're
here to scry
some future portents of my doom.
Alexis is no back alley
palm reader.
She's an expert cipher
of patterns, trends, cycles.
She's extraordinary
on the stock market
and never fails
to guess the winner
of "the bachelorette."
A touch forward, isn't she?
I've heard so much about you,
the famous hybrid.
Your ancient heart beats
strong indeed
for someone in such danger.
If you have a warning
to deliver, luv,
best get on with it.
By all means,
but if you want the most
from the experience,
I suggest you feed on me.
As you do, I'll allow
you into my mind.
You can see for yourself.
Lucien: Come on.
How long has it been
since we shared a real drink?
Drink deep, but beware.
What you broke is past repair.
All your oaths you betray.
Your sacred vows you sever,
and now you see
that nothing lasts
for always and forever.
3 yet remain, 2 already crossed,
yet in one year's time,
you'll all be lost.
As your family is undone,
you will see the beast
that is to come.
Ohh! Do you think
you can fool me
with bad poetry
and parlor tricks?
My visions conjure from you.
The threat you face
will be more clear
the longer I'm in your presence.
Kill me, you'll
never see
what's coming.
Err!
[Panting]
You will provide me
with the precise
location
of every last one
of those vulgar traps,
as well as the routes
used by any of your
other men.
I... I don't know.
Unh!
Hayley.
Forgive me.
I... I thought...
I know who you thought I was.
Do you know where she is?
Judging by what
these hunters did,
the traps they set
and the blood I saw,
if she's not with her daughter,
she's probably dead.
Vincent: You seem pretty
convinced Klaus had
nothing to do with it.
Now that only leaves...
Thank you...
A couple hundred
vampires in the quarter.
That's the thing.
Even if we figure out
who killed this guy,
then what?
It's a vampire.
What are the police gonna do?
We'd be sending
the arresting officers
to get slaughtered,
and if we warned them,
we'd get locked up
for being insane.
Yeah.
That's new Orleans.
Our city, our streets,
not our fault,
but it is our problem.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
Hey. It's Kinney.
Wanted to let you know
you were right.
It happened again.
So if you're not busy,
I could use your brain.
Yeah. Of course.
I told you.
Something is coming.
You'll need me.
Aah!
I am Klaus mikaelson!
I don't need anyone,
nor will I be warned
by lesser men!
I am the thing
that lesser men fear.
Then act like it...
Ha ha...
Instead of doting
on your pretty human girls
and pouting about your
family's disapproval.
Yes, you are Klaus mikaelson!
You are the most
ruthless, wicked beast
to ever live.
I came here to remind
you of that
because, quite frankly,
I've been worried that
you've lost a step.
I need no reminding of who I am.
That truth has been clear
to me for a thousand years.
And in those years,
you've acquired
countless enemies,
and with the sire lines at war,
you now have mine, as well.
Anyone who would kill me
could now come after you,
and since I have
so many rivals
and because I do not
want to die,
I beg you let me help you.
From now on, I am
the only one
you can trust.
I don't trust anyone.
Unh!
I thought you said
no vamp speed, marcel.
Come on, Vincent.
If I move any slower,
I'll be going in reverse.
Ooh. Fighting angry.
Because they found
that second dead body?
You still think
it's my guys. Huh?
Don't matter what
I think, marcel.
News breaks there's
a killer loose
in the quarter,
tourism is gonna drop,
and who are your
vampires gonna
feed on then?
Locals? No.
Not unless
they want a war
with the covens!
Speaking of covens,
you remember davina,
girl you were
supposed to mentor?
I offered her my advice
months ago.
I told her to make
peace at all cost,
and she refused me.
All right. That girl's
got a bigger chip
on her shoulder
than you do.
[Both grunting]
You got her into this.
You should be
helping her out.
These witches keep
messing with her,
she's gonna get angry.
You think that's gonna
end well for anyone?
Huh?
[Sighs]
[Breathing heavily]
What the hell am I doing here?
Why am I trapped?
I used magic to draw you here
and to keep you
a captive audience.
Davina, I need to see
my daughter.
I'm sorry,
but there's something
I need you to do
for me first.
[Gasps]
Who's there?
You're on edge.
[Gasps]
And you're trespassing.
You can't just come...
I mean, Klaus,
seriously.
I didn't come here to quarrel.
I came to offer you a gift,
maybe in exchange
for one of our little chats
of which I'm in particular need,
given as my brother
doesn't bother
to answer my calls,
and now my old mate
lucien has swanned
into town
with all manner
of troubling news.
Fine. If you want to
talk it through,
come back tomorrow.
I'm afraid I need to
talk about it now.
No. No!
You don't get to just
come into my house
uninvited.
Well, you already
invited me in once, luv,
so technically...
Don't do that.
Don't be so flippant
and self-absorbed.
Right now, people
like me are out there
getting killed
by people like you,
conveniently timed
with the arrival
of your old acquaintance,
and you just barge
in here and start
mouthing off orders?
I get it.
You're a vampire.
It's a tortured existence.
I'm sorry, but do you
really have to be
such an insensitive
disappointment?
Wait.
That wasn't fair.
Keep the gift.
I painted it for you.
Klaus.
[Saxophone playing]
Good evening.
I wonder if we might discuss
your analysis of my work.
Aah!
[Klaus growls]
[Grunting]
Raah!
Noooo!
It won't be long now.