Here's what you missed
on Shameless last week:
a whole lot of shit happened.
Where were you?
- Think she'll come out today?
- Not likely.
FRANK:
Airplane wheel
missed her by an inch.
(screaming)
They found Eddie.
At the bottom of Lake Michigan.
Babe?
Your dad's dead.
Nice try,
but that doesn't
turn me on anymore.
This is a West Point
application.
I wanted to deliver it
personally. Is Lip home?
What, McNally brought
this for you?
- Not me.
- Congratulations.
VERONICA:
Malik?
ETHEL:
We're having a play date.
Sounds more like
a date-date.
I hope someone
takes care of him.
Don't you think Clyde
deserves that?
Oh, for sure.
You Clyde?
Ethel says hi.
Aah!
- Karen's pregnant.
- That's the Gallagher sperm.
Do the right thing.
Split.
Kids need a father.
Jody and I got hitched.
I want to know whose it is.
The kid.
Jody's the father.
- I'm not my dad.
- Get out.
You hear me?
I'm not my fucking dad!
- Hey.
You look great,
by the way.
SHAMELESS
S02 Ep 06 - Can I have a Mother.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
♪ ♪
♪ Think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ Know that it's not
for naught ♪
♪ You were beaming once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Round up the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that they're not
for naught ♪
♪ You were willing once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so... ♪
♪ Sure of? ♪
(indistinct chatter)
You had late pick-ups
on Monday and Thursday.
That's an extra $16.
I wasn't that late.
Fiona would charge you $20.
(beeping)
Come on.
Jesus.
It's a wonder I got
here in one piece.
(groans)
You're looking for
the Sunshine Adult Day Care.
It's up at the church.
Honey, only time I want
to go to church is when
I feel like getting molested.
What do you want? A tip?
Who are you two supposed to be?
I'm Ethel, and this
is Jonah, my son.
You look a little
crispy to be Liam.
- Oh, I'm Malik.
- Malik?
Yeah.
Jesus.
Enough with the fake African
spice rack crap.
A little advice?
Some people are racist. You
want to get ahead in the world?
Change your name so people
don't know you're black.
Honey, is that hot
water heater working?
Yeah.
Get me a towel.
I gotta have a bath.
I'm sorry,
who are you?
I'm your grandmother,
sweetheart.
You Carl?
Get me a crowbar
and a hammer.
(flushes)
(Estefania speaking Portuguese)
I've got to run an errand.
(speaking Portuguese)
So...
Uh, lock the door,
and don't answer for anybody.
Okay?
(speaking Portuguese)
If we were together
for 100 years,
I would never learn Portuguese.
Okay.
Why are we bashing
a hole in the wall?
We're remodeling.
Where's the rest of the litter?
Ian's at work, we haven't
seen Lip for days,
Liam's down in day care,
and Fiona's probably
trying to sleep.
She works nights.
- What about Frank?
- Doesn't live here anymore.
Good boy.
Now, out of the way.
- What's that?
- What's it look like?
- A finger.
- Ew.
You can touch it, but never
put your finger on the trigger
unless you're going
to shoot someone.
You like secrets?
So do I. Hold out your hands.
Our little secret,
all right?
There are important
decisions to be made.
This much money comes with
- great responsibility.
- Frank... can you run downstairs
- and ask Jody for the paprika?
- Investments, trusts,
tax evasion, liquidity.
Frank.
As soon as Eddie's
insurance claim is settled
and that check comes, we're
gonna have to make some...
- Frank.
- What?
I can't let you be in charge
of Eddie's insurance money,
sweetheart.
You're an alcoholic.
I wasn't talking about me.
- Okay.
- Did you think I meant me?
No.
We need a highly
experienced professional.
- Yeah, that's right.
- And just for the record,
many great men have
been well lubricated.
Henry Ford.
Scott Fitzgerald.
David Hasselhoff. They all
kept a bottle close.
Mom!
Beethoven's Fifth.
Coincidence? I don't think so.
I think you should do these
in the bathroom.
Ooh...
Sheila, please...
No, we can just put
down newspaper, honey.
There are important economic
factors at play.
It's gonna smell!
Use the tub.
Did you bring in the
filleting knife,
Our family's financial...
and, the, uh,
mesh gloves?
...security is in the...
oh, fuck it.
I'll be at the office.
Paprika?
(groans)
Um...
Honey, you know
what I was thinking?
Um, we could put
the food on the bed
and then do folding
chairs along the walls.
We can't hold a wedding
reception in your bedroom.
Honey, parties are
always in the living room.
This would be unique.
This is the start
of my marriage.
It's important to me.
You can do it, Mom.
It's just going to
happen downstairs.
You know what?
I am going to do
the fish in the tub.
Whoever that is better
have a death wish.
Sorry. Uh...
something's come up.
Grammy's back.
(doorbell rings)
(smacking lips)
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Uh...
I'm looking for Tony.
Honey!
Just a sec.
(quietly):
Okay.
She's nice, honey.
You got balls.
Coming back here.
I brought you something.
I don't take bribes.
Dude, you're living in one.
Think of this
as a donation.
Policeman's Ball.
Tsunami relief.
End Autism Now.
It's your choice.
(sighs)
Motherfucker.
Who the hell let you
back in the country?
They were patting down a 90-year-old's
diaper, and I slipped by.
Where the hell
have you been?
Brazil.
You get the works
or just a tummy tuck?
Just a dick reduction;
still too big.
Okay.
I see that Tony's
got a live-in, huh?
Yeah.
Second one this summer.
What do you want
with Tony?
Just family stuff.
Business, you know.
No, I don't know.
What kind
of business?
Morning.
Lip, where you been all night?
Grammy showed up.
What, Joliet Grammy?
She tunnel out?
Medical furlough.
Wow.
- Hey, good luck.
- Yeah.
Grammy?
Frank's mom.
Ran a slew of meth labs
till one exploded,
killing two college kids
she'd recruited.
Whoa.
I see that, uh,
Tony's got a live-in, huh?
Seems so.
Yeah, they're
redecorating.
A little China cup.
Laotian, I think.
Yeah, see, I can never tell the
difference between the two.
We should get together, have
lunch, just... catch up.
I'm seeing someone.
So am I.
Imported or domestic?
Import.
Hey, we could bring them;
a double date.
I'll show you mine
if you show me yours.
I've already told
her all about you.
No, you haven't.
Well, I mean,
a bit about you.
You know, I-I'm sure
that I have mentioned your name.
DEBBIE:
Oh, come on, don't freeze.
Please, don't freeze.
Jesus, we had better gear
than this piece of crap
in prison.
Okay, we're good.
Dr. Noah Pitts.
The Pitts Center
for Cosmetic Surgery.
Doctor, huh?
Well, he always
did know his drugs.
Same macroeconomic
headwinds, right?
So, how did they do a
$3 billion payback?
These investment banks,
we bail the fuckers out,
they don't loan a dime.
Just-just nod your head if any of this is
getting through to you.
You know what? Forget all
of this; all you got to do
is wear a suit, yes,
and say "net, net"
and "economic indicators."
Say it a lot.
Jesus. They let you out?
Yeah. They let me out.
KEVIN:
Surprised to see you, Peg.
Thought you were doing
20 to life.
Tricked them into
thinking I was dying.
So they let me out early.
Gin neat.
And something sweet
for the kid.
Thanks for the push.
What are you
doing here?
I'm conducting
the Chicago Symphony.
Frankie, what do you
think I'm doing?
(exhales)
Now, buy your mother a drink
and pretend like
you're glad to see me.
Oh, Jesus.
What's up
with you and Ian?
Did he say something
about Karen?
She's married.
You're skipping the
wedding reception, I hope?
Wasn't invited.
She moved on.
Hope you see the irony
in you giving
relationship advice.
Grammy staying?
You want to tell her to leave?
Guess we'd better steal
some fire extinguishers
from the school, then.
Make it right with Ian.
You two are my rocks.
I can't do it
without you.
One more.
That bastard Noah
dropped a dime on me.
No, he didn't.
Then how'd the cops know
about the meth lab?
I don't know--
the explosion?
We're going to take
a little road trip
to see my old friend Pitts.
You bring your car
around tomorrow,
6:00 a.m. sharp.
I don't have a car.
Christ, you're pathetic.
You bed-wetting excuse
for a son.
Can I borrow your truck?
- Not a chance.
- It's for me.
I need to see
a doctor.
Oh.
Take the bus.
(sighs)
Jesus. Don't worry.
We'll bring it back
with a full tank.
- A double date?
- I know.
(beeps)
You gonna go?
Ah, sending a signal.
Yeah, what's that?
I still want to sit
on your face.
- So you wouldn't go?
- Hell, yeah, I'd go.
I got to see what
the new bitch looks like.
- Who you gonna take?
- Adam, I guess.
Oh, really? The Boy Scout?
- Richard?
- Ugh!
The old guy
from the wedding? No.
- Steve's new girl is hot?
- Probably.
You're going to look
like easy pickings
for something
on the side.
It's not going
to happen.
Oh, like
Craig Heisner
wasn't going
to happen?
(train clanking and screeching)
Frank?
Huh?
What?
You wet the bed.
Oh. Sorry.
Grammy's back.
Just showed up,
in an ambulance.
You know, she, uh...
she didn't even call.
How fucked-up
is that, huh?
That's it?
Nothing?
You just gonna give me the chin?
How about now?
No?
Really? Still nothing?
No?!
GRAMMY:
Frank here?
Yeah.
Thanks for
the push, Carl.
My five bucks.
Hey.
I gave you
$60 yesterday.
Don't get greedy.
Who is it?
Someone for Frank.
Peggy Gallagher.
Frank's mom.
Oh... my goodness!
Oh, come in,
come in,
come in!
Oh...
You coming down?
I just woke up.
Look at me!
Darn it, um,
you caught us.
Uh, Frank?
He's still sleeping.
Oh...
you did such a wonderful job
raising that boy.
He's just so clean
and so...
No, he's not clean.
I mean, um...
Uh, Frank...!
Frank?
Frank? Frank?
Frank, guess who's here.
What are you doing?
Drying the sheets.
Frank, why didn't you tell me
that your mother was coming?
Jody and I
could have made
a coffee cake.
Look at me, I'm a wreck!
Get dressed!
Mr. Kevin,
is everything all right?
You sounded upset
over the phone.
WOMAN:
Ethel.
ETHEL:
Constance, Abigail,
- Ruth, Sarah?
- KEVIN: Ethel,
your sister wives
have some news.
Our husband Clyde
was murdered in the
American prison.
Yea, though I walk through the
valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil, for thou
art with me; thy rod and thy...
All right, will you
please cut that out?
I'm not even sure it's
allowed for you to be here.
We're working to bring you home.
She is home.
She was forced
into sexual slavery.
She married joyfully
of her own free will.
She was 11!
We've hired attorneys;
you'll be home soon,
dear sister.
Oh. Here is me
with Marshmallow!
(laughing):
My pony!
Oh...
he died.
I was riding him and
I thought he just tripped,
but he never got up.
And here's Uncle Wendel.
No, that's Aunt Jane.
(belches)
You know,
all this cooking we're doing
is for my daughter Karen's
wedding reception tomorrow.
We're having it here.
You should come. You must come.
(door opens)
Everyone in the whole
neighborhood is gonna be here.
Oh...
here he is!
Your ears must be burning.
GRAMMY: You were supposed
to pick me up
two hours ago--
now we're gonna
be stuck sitting
in morning traffic.
Oh, are you guys going out?
Because I just need
a few more things
for the party.
Let me get the list.
Christ in Heaven!
I thought I was gonna
have to shoot myself.
Are you sticking
it in that?
Bitch just took ten
years off my life.
Let's get out
of here before
that nutjob comes back.
You're a very
rude person.
GRAMMY: That's a new low
even for you, Frank.
SHEILA: I'd like
you to leave.
I'd nail a hooker down on Wacker
before I'd... (groans)
- Get out!
- Save your breath; I'm leaving.
Come on, you pussy.
(horns honking)
(horns honking in distance)
The kids are something,
aren't they?
Growing up.
You talk to Lip?
Off-the-chart smart.
Good genes.
And Ian's a real lady killer,
just like I was at that
age, you remember?
He's nailing all of 'em.
Fiona--
beautiful.
Gets that from
her mother.
Carl's into karate,
just like I was.
And Debbie's got that Gallagher
entrepreneurial spirit.
You see all those
kids running around?
I think it's a
school of some kind.
And how about little Liam?
You know, he's actually mine.
- Frank!
- What?
Shut up!
This doesn't interest me.
ADAM:
Now, he said 1:00.
Well, he's not
very good with time.
And what'd you say he does?
He's in automotive sales.
- Oh, here they are.
- Hey.
Steve, this is Adam.
Adam, Steve.
Hey, Estefania, Fiona, Adam.
(speaks Portuguese)
STEVE: Estefania doesn't
really speak English.
ADAM:
Oh, that's okay,
I spent a semester in Madrid.
Hola. ¿Como estás?
- Adam.
- STEVE: Ah,
Portuguese.
From Brazil.
Oh, how exotic.
Well, aren't we all modern?
(chuckles)
Well, you look
very "Master
of the Universe," Adam.
How does one afford
a suit like that?
Wait for Barney's
to have a sale.
Actually, Adam is
an investment banker.
Oh, well, it's nice to put a
face to all that bailout money.
And how do you pay
for your shirt?
This is full freight
from the Gap.
I'm in
pharmaceuticals.
ADAM: Oh, yeah?
Fiona said cars.
You're married?
(speaks Portuguese)
You two are married?
Ah, sí. Dos semanas.
Two weeks. Newlyweds.
That's excellent.
Wow!
Congratulations.
Excuse me, uh,
I'll be right back.
Passionate.
Yeah.
(door opens)
Boys' room is next-door.
Okay, I was helping
out a Brazilian friend
with a small import-export
business down in Sao Paulo.
You're married?
Her father was a competitor
and didn't appreciate our entry
into an already
crowded market.
You were smuggling cars?
The product
isn't important.
He cut my friend's ear off...
Drugs? You were smuggling drugs?
So I chose to help his
daughter into the States.
By marrying her?
Dad's very old-fashioned, okay?
She was banging
one of his top lieutenants
and he wanted her out
of the country fast.
You married a drug lord's daughter
to hang on to your ear?
Wasn't so sure he was
gonna stop at the ear.
Who'd you tell her I was?
Listen, it's no big
thing-- all you got to do
is wait until immigration...
Who does she think I am?
My cousin.
I missed you.
♪ ♪
(grunts)
You're married.
Only legally.
(grunting)
Oh, Jesus!
Hey!
Okay.
Whoa.
(panting)
(speaking Portuguese)
(continues in Portuguese)
I'm just gonna nod 'cause I have
no idea what you're saying.
Huh?
Sorry. I had to call,
check on the kids.
Did we get drinks?
In front of you.
Oh! Oh, my God! Sorry.
Okay. Oh, great.
What a coincidence.
I just ran into a guy I went to
high school with in the bathroom.
Did we get drinks?
You gotta be kidding me.
A Cobb salad's $22.
- Bye.
- You leaving?
What are we talking about?
You should probably
just shut the fuck up.
Have a nice life, Fiona.
- Adam... Adam!
- What?
Shit.
¿Steve, o que esta acontecendo?
No medication.
I'm sorry.
It's complicated.
No, really it's not.
Look, I like you, but maybe
we should've had some rules.
One of my unspoken rules
is you don't fuck somebody
else when we're on a date.
I guess I thought
that was just assumed.
♪ ♪
- How's she doing?
- Still praying.
I'm telling you, those
Jesus puppy mills
are gonna try and take Ethel
and Jonah away from us.
They can't just take them, Kev.
I think we should
adopt them.
I love 'em, too,
but we get paid to love 'em.
We adopt 'em, we love
'em on our own dime.
What sense does that make?
They were scary, V.
All dressed in
black and shit.
And the alpha witch
was, like... Whoa.
I'm talking
serious evil.
- Now they have lawyers.
- They can't do anything.
The State has custody.
They're not just gonna give
them back to the Waco wackos.
They're not evil.
They're my family.
Hi. I'm Dr. Pitts,
Mrs. Macgillicuddy.
I see you're thinking
about breast augmentation.
I was thinking
about the $200,000 you owe me.
I'm definitely getting
my tits done.
You got out early.
Yeah.
I only did 12 years.
Isn't that swell?
Pretty woman.
Your wife?
Two little girls.
Adorable.
Any of them know
you used to be a meth dealer?
I don't want
to keep you, Doctor.
I know you've got a waiting room
full of frozen faces.
So, the 200 thou that's
no longer in the deposit box,
that was mine, is now where?
Okay, don't threaten me.
I'm not some naive college kid from
Grand Rapids that you can intimidate.
Where's my money, Noah?
Fine. You went to
prison, you got out.
But you can't just waltz
in here expecting me
to cough up 200 grand.
The Pitts Medical Center?
I just finished my residency.
I'm in debt up to my ass!
We had a deal about what
would happen if shit went down,
and when shit went down,
you ran.
All right, I'll pay you back,
but it's gonna take some time.
That's the one thing
I don't have, my friend.
Tomorrow. All of it.
No. I can't do it.
You don't want to leave it
like this, Noah.
He gonna pay you?
This tastes like shit.
I shouldn't have gotten
the praline.
What's he owe you?
What'd you get,
the Captain's Swirl?
I think I got a right to know.
I'm involved now.
Here, trade with me.
What? No! What are you doing?
What's the difference?
Trade with me!
I don't like praline!
Come on!
No, I want mine!
- Mom, I want... I...
- I'm your mother!
Oh, Jesus! Take
'em both, then!
It's my truck.
It's not your truck.
It's traditional.
The driver gets a share,
he's a partner.
Son...
don't flatter yourself.
Usually there's some kind
of dollar amount per mile.
Shut up and look
for these two.
You're kidnapping
his kids?!
Are you insane?!
That's federal,
that's a federal...
Keep your damn voice down.
Hold on.
How much money are
we talking about?
You okay?
You look
kind of white.
I think I... just
stood up too fast.
(sighs)
Mom?
Just give me a
goddamn minute.
You want some water
or something?
I'm gonna... I'm gonna
go get you some water.
No. No.
Shit!
Go get this refilled.
I'm gonna sit here
and do some recon.
(loud chatter of children)
Uh...
What?
I... I loaned Sheila
the last of the cash.
All my life,
I waited for that phone call.
"Peggy, he's
not your son.
There's been a mix-up
at the hospital."
It never came.
(sighs)
All right, let's see.
Oh, yeah, this is healing
really nicely.
Very nicely.
I just need a sec with the doc.
Those look very real.
Jesus. So sorry.
Jesus, Frank.
I'm flattered you remembered
my name, 'cause
I didn't remember
yours. So...
time's up. I'm
here for the money.
She gave me until tomorrow.
Well, I don't think you
want to wait till then,
'cause she's about
to kidnap your kids.
Go Wolverines!
Hey, hey, hey, don't
you give me that look.
Try growing up with
her, coming home
to that every day after
school. You think I'm joking?
She sent me out
for chloroform and duct tape.
Seriously, Doc,
I don't think you know who
you're dealing with here.
(clicks tongue)
No. I know exactly who
I'm dealing with.
75. That's all I've got.
I've kept that
and these fake passports in here
in case she ever ratted me out
for a reduced sentence.
But this puts an end to it.
And if she ever comes near me
or my family again,
I'm going directly
to the police.
You tell your mother that
she better think long and hard,
what we know about each other.
Okay?
You don't have to go someplace
you don't want to.
I don't have a choice.
I'm a ward
of the state.
Well, what happens
if they send you back?
They'll find
me a husband.
- Clyde has a brother.
- A brother?
How old is he?
Caleb's much younger.
65 maybe?
He's very nice.
They're my family, Malik.
You're not a little kid
anymore.
You're 14.
You have to decide
what's best for you and Jonah.
Where'd you go,
Philadelphia?
I spotted the
older girl.
Nanny dropped her off
in a stupid fucking Smart Car.
Piece of cake.
Mama, I went back
and talked to Pitts.
You what?
I'm trying to help!
If you got caught,
you'd die in prison. Here.
$50,000. Take it.
And if you think it's right,
you can give me a cut, but
only if you think it's right.
You're amazing, Frank.
I was gonna get 200,
and you were able to
talk him down to 50.
Well done, fruit
of my loins.
Married?
Yeah, to some teenager
from Brazil.
- She cute?
- Very.
Who's cute?
Chicken in the bucket.
Steve's back, married to
some South American teenager.
- Really?
- So, what did Adam do?
Took off, left me there.
Can't blame him.
How's Ethel doing?
She's in shock,
I think. Poor thing.
Husband murdered
in prison.
Ooh. Who got murdered?
- Ethel's husband, Clyde.
- Hmm.
Cool.
VERONICA: Kev thinks the State
might send her back to that cult,
now that her sclerotic
husband is dead.
Grammy still here?
Uh-uh. Left with Frank.
Somewhere in Chicago,
a priest is being mugged.
FIONA:
Lip, there's chicken.
Still?
What's that all about?
Karen, I think.
Will this summer ever end?
50 grand, huh?
Not bad for a day's work.
(screaming)
Jesus! Mommy!
Give me the rest of it.
(yelling)
Oh, stop your squealing,
you little baby.
I barely broke the skin.
Give me the rest of the money.
Oh, Jesus!
Take it!
(grunts)
What is this, another ten?
Is this all?
Oh, fuck!
I deserve something!
It's tradition!
Is this all of it?
Yes. Yes!
I'm bleeding all over
Kevin's truck! Shit!
Oh, damn it to hell.
You got me going again.
Give me my prescription.
Oh, don't stab me
again, okay?!
(crowd chatter)
(laughter)
(indistinct chatter)
Don't call her by name,
and listen, just...
you know what to do.
I'll give you your cues, you
just be sort of authoritative.
What's with this
thing? (laughs)
I got it.
It's good.
He's doing, like, an urban
version of a tuxedo.
Nice, Jody!
Right? William,
what was the name
of that guy?
He was saying how this much
money can shock your system.
Who was that guy?
Guy inherited a little over
a million, destroyed his life.
Family-- vultures.
Lost his wife,
his health.
Ended up giving the money
to an orphanage.
Now, William
was saying
you and I together
could form a trust.
I think that's
a very good idea, Frank.
We should just
give our money
to an orphanage.
No, babe,
you misunderstood me.
That's not saying
giving it to...
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
There's just a lot of,
um, people here,
so maybe I...
I think I just left
something upstairs.
I...
Okay.
We'll talk about
this later.
William will be here.
Nice work, Billy,
jump in any time.
VERONICA:
I'm telling you, you can't turn
a whore into a housewife.
(laughs)
Wow, she's gorgeous.
Debs.
Wow.
Heard you were back
in town, Jimmy.
- Is this otra prima?
- You look great.
Where'd you get
that dress?
Oh, and married.
H-How's, uh,
how's school?
It's summer.
Right, right, right.
She's over you.
Really, you sure
about that?
Mm-hmm, absolutely.
You really did him
in the bathroom?
No, I didn't.
Oh, thanks, V.
- You said she did him in the bathroom.
- I said she almost did.
Why'd you have to
tell him anything?
She's my wife; she
has to tell me.
Hey, I don't have
to tell you shit.
(scoffs)
- KAREN: Hey, you okay?
- Yes.
Certainly are a lot
of people down there.
You're doing
great, Mom.
Yeah.
Yeah, sweetie,
I know.
Now, you can't drink
on your medication.
I know. You know what?
I just wanted
to hold this to make other
people feel comfortable
'cause I don't want
them to think...
Right.
So happy.
So you go, sweetie, go on.
- Okay.
- Everything's fine.
You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
- I love you.
I love you.
(gasps)
Whoo!
Once more into the breech.
What, you don't get enough
abuse just being Frank's son?
What? I wanted
to congratulate
the, uh,
happy couple.
Jesus, you smell
like a brewery.
It's hair of the dog.
Go home, Lip, please.
Uh, whoa, Jameson-- that's
not gonna last long.
FRANK: That's, that's why I'm
leaning towards hedge funds.
You're betting it'll go up
and you're betting
that they'll go down.
It's like if the Cubs won
the World Series
and the world ended
all in one day.
Fill her up,
Grammy?
You 21?
In four years.
Or gold, or gold.
It never goes down.
What?
What is she doing here?
FRANK: Oh, there's free
food and booze.
Mom won't miss that.
I don't care, I don't
want her in my house.
Get her out of here.
- I can't do that.
- Why?
Because she would slaughter me
and feast on my flesh.
What?
What are you doing here?
Brought a
Cuisinart.
(speaking Portuguese)
Yeah, no, of course, yeah.
Hi.
Hey, listen, about
the bathroom...
Nothing happened
in the bathroom.
Well, whatever didn't happen
in the bathroom, I'm sorry.
What didn't happen in
the bathroom, Steve,
did not happen.
(glass clinking)
Quiet, please.
JODY:
Quiet, everyone.
I'm sorry that I didn't make it all
the way down the stairs today,
but baby steps.
That's right, Mom.
(Sheila sighs)
Oh, my Karen, my baby,
all grown up.
I so wish
your father
could have been here today.
I wish
he could have seen you,
our sweet girl, all grown up,
and I know
he would be so proud
of his grandbaby, no matter who
the father was-- except Frank.
(laughing
nervously)
He hated Frank.
But it couldn't
be Frank
because there wasn't
any penetration.
Eddie didn't like
being penetrated.
He had
a funny bump
on the side of his penis
that we thought
was cancer,
but it turned out
I was just being
too rough on him.
So there's been
some obstacles
and some pitfalls,
but she's made
some wonderful,
wonderful friends
along the way, like Lip...
(mouthing) ...and all
the Gallaghers--
people I just used
to only know
as the ones
in that house
where the cops always came.
Jesus, is that bitch
ever going to shut up?
SHEILA:
And Frank's mother.
We're just so honored
that you're here,
even though
you weren't even invited--
and not really honored
because
you're a convicted felon.
But you're out
now, aren't you?
Why, why did they let you out?
'Cause you're a loud,
mean, vicious bitch.
Oh.
Okay, Mom, let's open presents.
Why don't you do yourself
and everyone else a favor
and shut up?
Have I offended you
in my home
where you're an interloper?
No one wants to hear it,
you fucking windbag.
Okay, Mom, let's
go upstairs.
She called me
a Wacker Drive whore.
Frank.
Oh, let 'em work it out.
And I don't know how an angel
like that man could have come
out of your poisoned womb.
Shut up, you batty bitch.
You know what?
You've got
a demon mind and a devil's womb
and heart,
and your coochie smells
of brimstone
and sulfur!
I will fuck you up!
Shit.
Oh, shit!
- Whoa! Whoa!
- Do it, do it!
♪ ♪
FRANK:
Oh, my God.
There's a woman with a gun.
She's at a party,
she's shooting people.
(sirens wailing)
Yes, yes!
- Shit, Tony.
- I got it.
Police.
Whoa, Officer Markovich
on the scene.
Sorry about that, guys.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, wait, wait!
Wait, wait!
(panting)
LIP:
You okay?
How do you like
my party so far?
I'm kind of digging it,
you know,
it's got
a certain energy.
So, the little missus.
Got your Cuisinart,
baby on the way.
Yep, I'm the
American Dream.
You are,
except, uh, Doofus is your
husband and that's my baby.
So, what, do you
want it on weekends?
Want to run away together,
get a double-wide?
No.
I want you to get
an abortion.
(knocking)
KEVIN:
Hey, Ethel, you decent?
Um, uh, just a minute.
Okay, come in.
Hey. Is he sleeping?
Okay.
I just wanted to make sure
you're doing all right.
I'm fine, thank you.
Look, I know
you're sad and stuff,
but I want you to know
that you can talk to us.
All right?
We're here for you
if you need us.
How was
the party?
It was good.
No one got hit.
They have to replace
the smoke detector.
But everybody was asking
about you, though,
where you were,
where Baby Jonah was.
So... good night, then.
Good night.
Mr. Kevin.
Yeah.
Thank you.
For what?
For everything.
You're welcome.
(snoring)
(snoring
continues)
(door opens)
Hey.
(grunts)
What's up?
Are we going shopping
for school clothes today?
(grunts)
Day care.
After?
Did I commit
to that?
Yep.
Then, yes.
(sighs)
What?
Was it weird
seeing Jimmy?
Jimmy?
Steve.
Jimmy.
Who's Jimmy?
Jimmy lives in
Lake Forrest
with his doctor father
and drunk mother.
They think he goes
to medical school
at the University
of Michigan.
Yeah, and...?
Jimmy is Steve.
KEVIN:
V, they're gone!
What?
Ethel and Jonah.
Well, maybe they went over
to the day care early.
No, all their stuff is gone--
his clothes, her
suitcase-- gone!
What?
(upbeat music plays on TV)
GRAMMY:
We a little mopey this morning?
No.
You're thinking just because
Carl got something,
maybe you should get something?
No.
Well, maybe
if you freshen up my coffee
and give your Grammy a kiss,
things will start
looking up for you.
For me?
- Yeah.
- Oh, Grammy!
Thank you! Thank you!
Hey, Jimmy,
it's Fiona.
I just wanted to say,
go fuck yourself!
- What's all this?
- DEBBIE: A new laptop.
This is so awesome!
Christmas in August?
Ethel and Jonah are gone.
FIONA:
What?
Did she say anything
to you, Debbie?
No.
What about Malik?
What time does he show up?
In about an hour.
You sure they didn't
just sleep
at their grandparents
or something?
Ethel packed everything.
Baby's stuff, too.
Okay. She's 14 years old with an infant.
How far can she get?
She doesn't
have any money.
It was those evil Jesus witches!
They took 'em. I know it!
We should call the
social worker,
see if she can get
the cops looking.
If she shows up,
call us right away.
Perfect. I'm solo today,
and we've got a full
house for day care.
I'll help you, honey.
Can we talk about these gifts?
You think I'm trying
to buy their affection?
Well, it's certainly
for sale.
I just had some money from
an old business arrangement,
and I thought I'd spread it
around a bit.
You didn't come
to see me
when I was in prison.
I was 11 when you went in.
I... hardly knew you.
Well, that's my fault, I guess.
500 bucks.
Figure,
from what I've seen
around here so far,
you need it more
than some digital shit
that's gonna be obsolete
before you can
get it out of the box.
It's not a bribe, Fiona.
I've got some serious
Grammy time
to make up for around here.
Oh, my.
What?
It's from Eddie's
life insurance company.
The check came?
Oh, my.
Stop saying, "Oh, my."
What does it say?
He left the money to Karen.
He changed the beneficiary.
No! Shit! Shit!
Shit, shit, shit!
Shit. Karen can't handle
that kind of money, Sheils.
She's too young, too headstrong,
too... too promiscuous!
- What's up?
- It's a good thing, Frank.
Remember what you were saying
about the orphanage?
Eddie was trying to protect me.
Oh, protect you, my ass!
Oh!
He did this to fuck me!
- $75,000?
- We can fight this, Sheils.
- We'll get lawyers.
- No, Frank.
This is good.
Eddie had a hard time
showing his affection to Karen.
This is his way.
This is good.
I'm happy.
Well, congratulations, my boy.
You hit the jackpot.
You have fallen into
a fucking field of
four leaf clovers,
first time up at bat.
Frank...
I have put in the sweat.
I've put in the time, I've put
in months of work, I have
literally taken it up the ass,
and you fucking waltz in here.
Frank.
What?
I think you should go.
No. Sheils.
I-I was just...
I didn't mean...
Now?
I just can't believe she hasn't
called us or even left us a note.
She's got to know we're sitting
over here sick with worry.
Yeah, yeah, no, here.
I'm still here.
Teenagers-- their hormone-soaked
brains aren't wired
to think about anyone
other than themselves.
Right, okay.
Thank you very much.
Okay, social worker's gonna file
a missing persons report
and call the sheriff to go out
to that cult ranch
to see if they're
over there.
She thinks we should drive
around the neighborhood.
- Kev?
- Ethel may not have gotten far.
Happens to a lot
of kids, she says.
But I just cannot believe
how selfish Ethel is being.
You think something horrible
might have happened to her?
A child kidnapper
or something?
"I hope you understand
why I had to leave.
"I know that God will
watch over you both.
I know we will see each
other again some day. Ethel."
I'm getting the truck keys.
We'll start over by the park
and then work our way
around back to the school.
What the
hell is that?
Oh, boy.
What?
Uh... Remember that pot
you wanted me to get rid of?
Yeah?
What if maybe
I didn't get rid of
as much of it
as I said I did?
You buried it?
Well, I mean...
How much didn't
you get rid of?
(mutters)
Well...
But how would
she sell it?
Nobody's gonna buy pot
off of a white girl
in a Little House on
the Prairie dress.
Looking for this?
I don't think Ginger will mind
that I opened her check, do you?
Seeing as how she's
dead and buried
out in the yard,
according to Carl.
You look like shit.
Get some coffee, 'cause
we have business to discuss.
Scamming Ginger's
Social Security checks.
(chuckles)
Clever boy.
But it's over.
Meet the new Ginger.
I'm gonna be here a while,
so get used to it.
I say, "Jump," you
say, "How high?"
Eat me!
I say, "Eat me!" I'm done
taking your shit! You got it?
I am a grown man.
This is my family, not yours!
You're a piss-poor
excuse for a mother!
I was hoping
you would die in prison!
You've made my life
a living hell, and I...
I want you out of here! Now!
Good for you.
It's great to get
that stuff out.
Feel better?
Now, this is what
I was thinking.
I'm moving into your room,
I like the light.
And I'm gonna need
a flat screen up there.
Don't worry.
I'll give you
the money.
Can I be honest with you?
I am not the reason
that your life is
a piece of crap.
You came out of me a loser.
Now run to the store.
I'll make a list, okay?
Give me my purse.
(phone ringing)
(turns phone off)
It's tough, huh?
(children chatting
and shouting)
My parents
suck, too.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
CARL:
Dad?
- FRANK: Hmm?
- Wake up.
- What?
- You wet the bed.
(groans)
Find a dry spot.