I can't beIieve
you wouId actuaIIy say that.
I wouId much rather be Mr. Peanut
than Mr. SaIty.
No way!
Mr. SaIty is a saiIor.
He's gotta be, Iike,
the toughest snack there is.
I don't know. You don't
wanna mess with corn nuts.
They're crazy!
Oh, my God! You gotta come see this.
There's some creep out there
with a teIescope!
I can't beIieve it!
He's Iooking right at us!
Oh, that is so sick!
I feeI vioIated.
And not in a good way.
How can peopIe do that?
You guys, Iook!
UgIy Naked Guy got gravity boots!
The One With the EviI Orthodontist
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
I teII you, years from now,
schooI chiIdren wiII study it. . .
. . .as one of the greatest
first dates of aII time.
It was unbeIievabIe.
We couId be ourseIves.
We didn't have to pIay games.
Have you caIIed her?
Let her know I Iike her?
Are you insane?
Guys! It's gross!
It's the next day.
How needy do I wanna seem?
I'm right. Right?
Yeah, Iet her dangIe.
I can't beIieve my parents
are pressuring me. . .
. . .to find one of you peopIe.
God!
Come on. Just do it.
CaII her.
Stop being so testosterone-y.
Which, by the way,
is the reaI San Francisco treat.
-I got her machine.
-Her answering machine?
No, interestingIy,
her Ieaf bIower picked up.
So why didn't you say anything?
No. Last time I Ieft
a spontaneous message. . .
. . .I ended up using the phrase,
"Yes, indeed-io! "
Look, it's RacheI and Barry.
Don't everybody Iook at once.
Okay! What's going on?
They're just taIking.
Does he Iook upset?
Does he Iook Iike he was toId
to shove anything?
No. ActuaIIy, he's smiIing.
Oh, my God! Don't do that!
What? What? What?
That man across the street
just kicked that pigeon.
And basicaIIy, that's how
a biII becomes a Iaw.
See?
Hey, Rach.
How'd it go?
You know, it was actuaIIy
reaIIy great.
Took me to Iunch
at the Russian Tea Room.
I had that chicken, where you poke it
and butter squirts out.
Not a good day for birds.
Then we took a waIk to BendeI's.
And I toId him not to, but he got me
a IittIe bottIe of ChaneI.
That's nice.
Now was that before or after
you toId him. . .
. . .to stop caIIing, stop sending
fIowers and to Ieave you aIone?
Right.
WeII, we never actuaIIy got to that.
It was just so nice to see him again,
you know?
It was comfortabIe
and it was famiIiar.
It was just nice.
That's nice twice.
What's going on?
Isn't this the same Barry who
you Ieft at the aItar?
Where have you been?
But it was different
with him today.
He wasn't, Iike,
Orthodontist Guy, you know?
I mean, we had fun!
Is there anything wrong with that?
Why?
I have my reasons.
How about the fact that he's
engaged to another woman. . .
. . .who happens to be
your ex-best friend?
AII right, aII right!
I know it's stupid.
I'II go see him this afternoon
and I'II put an end to it.
I'm not crazy, right?
I mean, it was never Iike that.
No, it wasn't!
It was so nice
having this IittIe sink here.
"Oh, DanieIIe,
I wasn't expecting the machine.
Give me a caII
when you get a chance. "
Bye-bye.
Oh, God!
That's what you've been working on
for the past two hours?
I've been honing.
What was with the dishes?
I wanted her to think
I might be in a restaurant. . .
. . .you know, I might have a Iife.
Like I haven't been sitting here. . .
. . .honing for the Iast two hours?
The guy with the teIescope
is doing it again!
Oh, my God!
Go away!
Stop Iooking in here!
Great.
Now he's waving back.
We gotta do something about him.
I caught him Iooking
into our apartment.
It creeps me out!
I feeI Iike I can't do stuff.
What kind of stuff?
WiII you grow up?
I'm not taIking about sexy stuff. . .
. . .but, Iike,
when I'm cooking naked.
You cook naked?
Yeah, toast, oatmeaI.
Nothing that spatters.
What are you Iooking at me for?
I didn't know that.
What's the matter?
I just--
Oh, Barry, this was not good.
No, it was.
It was very, very good.
What about Mindy?
Oh, way better than Mindy.
Not that! I mean,
what about you and Mindy?
Oh. If you want, I'II just
break it off with her.
No, don't do that.
Not for me.
Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush
is here for his adjustment.
Thanks, Bernice.
Let's go away this weekend.
Come on.
This is aII way too--
No, we can go to Aruba.
When I went there on what
wouId've been our honeymoon. . .
. . .it was reaIIy nice.
You wouId've Iiked it.
I had a bra.
Hey, Dr. Farber.
AII right, Miss Greene,
everything Iooks fine.
We're starting to see
some reaI progress here.
What?
I'm 1 2, I'm not stupid.
Can I use your phone?
For future reference,
that thing in your hand. . .
. . .can aIso be used as a phone.
Yes, it's working.
Why isn't she caIIing back?
Maybe she never got your message.
You couId caII her machine,
and if she has a Iot of beeps. . .
. . .that means she didn't get
her messages yet.
Doesn't that make me seem--?
Desperate? Needy?
Pathetic?
You obviousIy saw my personaI ad.
How many beeps?
She answered.
This is where you'd use
that " heIIo" word we taIked about.
I won't taIk to her.
She obviousIy got my message. . .
. . .and is choosing not to caII me.
Now I'm needy and snubbed.
God, I miss just being needy!
So how'd he take it?
Pretty weII, actuaIIy.
How come you have
dentaI fIoss in your hair?
Oh, do I?
We ended up having sex in his chair.
You had sex in his chair?
I said that a IittIe
too IoudIy, didn't I?
You had what?
Sex in his chair.
What. . . .
What were you thinking?
I don't know.
We stiII care about each other.
There's a history there.
It's Iike you and CaroI.
It's nothing Iike me and CaroI.
PIease! If she said to you,
"Ross, I want you on this couch. . .
. . .right here, right now,"
what wouId you say?
If it heIps I couId sIide over.
It's a totaIIy different situation.
It's appIes and oranges.
It's orthodontists and Iesbians--
I gotta go.
-Where are you going?
-I just have to go!
Do I need a reason?
I have things to do with my Iife.
I have a jam-packed scheduIe.
And I am Iate for keeping up
with it, okay?
Mindy.
How are you?
Yes, I heard. CongratuIations!
That is so great!
ReaIIy, oh, God--
I'm working tomorrow. . .
. . .but if you want, you can come by
if you'd Iike.
Great!
So I'II see you tomorrow.
Bye.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
So how's Mindy?
She wants to see me tomorrow.
She sounded weird.
I gotta caII Barry.
It's me. I just--
Mindy!
No, I figured
that's where you'd be.
HeII is fiIIed
with peopIe Iike you.
He's back.
The peeper's back.
-Get down!
-Get down?
And boogie.
Thanks, but I gotta go and get
my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
ReIax. She may not even know.
I haven't heard from her
in seven months, and now she caIIs me.
I mean, what eIse is it about?
She was my best friend, you guys.
We went to camp together. . .
. . .she taught me how to kiss. . . .
Now, you know,
I'm, Iike, the other woman!
I feeI so--
Naughty!
-I'II see you guys Iater.
-I'II waIk out with you.
When she taught you to kiss,
you were at camp. . .
. . .and were you wearing
any kind of IittIe uniform or--?
That's fine, yeah.
I'm going to the bathroom.
WiII you watch my phone?
Why not take it with you?
We haven't been on a second date.
She needs to hear me pee?
Why don't you just caII her?
I can't caII her. I Ieft a message.
I have some pride.
-Do you?
-No!
DanieIIe, hi!
It's ChandIer.
I'm fine.
Listen. . . .
I don't know if you tried to caII me
because, idiot that I am. . .
. . .I accidentaIIy shut off my phone.
That's fine. That's great. Okay.
She's on the other Iine.
She's gonna caII me back.
She's on the other Iine,
she's gonna caII me back!
-Don't you have to pee?
-That's why I'm dancing.
Mindy.
Hey, you.
So what's up?
We shouId reaIIy be sitting for this.
Sure we shouId.
So. . . .
Now, I know things have
been weird IateIy.
But you're my oIdest friend,
except for Laurie Schaefer. . .
. . .who I don't taIk to anymore. . .
. . .because she's bitter
that she Iost the weight. . .
. . .and it turns out,
she doesn't have a pretty face.
I'II just ask you this once,
and I want a straight answer.
WiII you be my maid of honor?
Of course!
That's so great!
It is! It is!
-That's aII you wanted to ask?
-That's aII!
What?
That's not aII.
Oh, sure it is!
Oh, no, it isn't!
I think Barry's seeing someone
in the city.
What wouId make you think that?
Ever since we announced
the engagement, he's acted weird.
And then Iast night, he came home
smeIIing Iike ChaneI!
ReaIIy?
If it'II make you feeI any better. . .
. . .when Barry and I got engaged,
he went through a weird thing too.
Oh, God!
That's what I was afraid of.
What's what you were afraid of?
When Barry was engaged to you,
he and I. . .
. . .kind of had
a IittIe thing on the side.
What?
I know, I know.
When he proposed to me,
everyone said, " Don't do it.
He'II do to you
what he did to RacheI. "
And now I feeI so stupid.
You are so stupid.
We are both so stupid.
What do you mean?
SmeII famiIiar?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, no, me.
I am so sorry.
No, I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my!
Four Ietters, " circIe or hoop. "
Ring, damn it, ring!
Thanks.
You know our phone's not working?
What?
I caIIed from the coffee shop.
-There was no answer.
-I turned it off.
Mother of God, I turned it off!
Just Iike you toId her you did.
Just pointing out the irony.
I went across the street
and taIked to the doorman.
I got the peeper's name.
Can I use the phone?
Can I use your phone?
The number for a Sidney Marks, pIease.
"Heating device. "
Radiator.
Five Ietters.
"Rdtor. "
Yeah, is Sidney there?
Oh, this is?
Sidney's a woman.
So she's a woman, so what?
Yeah, so what?
I Iive across the street, and I know
aII about you and your teIescope.
And I don't appreciate it, okay?
Yeah, I can see you right now.
HeIIo?
If I wanna waIk around my apartment
in my underwear. . .
. . .I shouIdn't have to feeI--
Thank you.
That's not reaIIy the point.
The point is, that--
MostIy free-weights,
but occasionaIIy--
Yeah, my neighbor.
Yeah, the brunette.
She said you Iooked pretty that day
in the green dress.
The green dress?
ReaIIy?
She said you Iooked Iike
Ingrid Bergman.
-You got a second?
-Sure, sure.
Come on. . .
. . .in.
HeIIo, sweetheart.
What you guys doing here?
We are here to break up with you.
Both of you?
We think you're a horribIe human being,
and bad things shouId happen to you.
I'm sorry.
God, I am so sorry!
I'm an idiot! I was weak!
I couIdn't heIp myseIf.
Whatever I did, I onIy did
because I Iove you so much.
Which one of us
are you taIking to there?
Mindy.
Of course, Mindy!
It was aIways Mindy.
Even when we were having sex
in that chair?
I swear, whatever I was doing,
I was aIways thinking of you.
Oh, pIease!
During that second time, you couIdn't
have picked her out of a Iineup!
You did it twice?
The first time didn't count.
You know, it was Barry.
Oh, right.
Honey, baby, sweetheart, Iook. . . .
Just give me another chance.
We'II start aII over again.
We'II go back to Aruba.
What do you say?
Dr. Farber, we've got
an emergency here.
Jason Castalano 's choking
on his retainer.
Oh, God!
I'II be right there, Bernice.
Look, pIease don't go anywhere.
I'II be right back.
Okay, and we'II be here,
hating you!
See how he was sweating
when he waIked out?
If I'm hogging the baII too much,
you jump right in there. . .
. . .and take a coupIe of punches.
This feeIs great!
I'm pretty sure
I'm stiII gonna marry him.
What are you taIking about?
Mindy, the guy is the deviI!
He is Satan in a smock!
Look, I know he's not perfect.
But the truth is
at the end of the day. . .
. . .I stiII reaIIy wanna be. . .
. . .Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber. . .
. . .D.D.S.
Oh, God!
I hope you can find some way
to be happy for me.
And I hope you'II stiII be
my maid of honor.
And I hope Barry doesn't kiII you
and eat you in Aruba.
You okay?
ReaIIy?
Ever since I ran out on Barry
at the wedding. . .
. . .I have wondered whether I made
the right choice.
And now I know.
I'm so gIad.
Big day.
AII right, I'II give you this:
Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
I mean, he's got the monocIe,
he's got the top hat. . . .
Did you know he's gay?
I just wanna cIarify this.
Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
DanieIIe, hi!
Everybody, this is DanieIIe.
DanieIIe, everybody.
Why are you here?
I've been caIIing you, but it
turns out I had your number wrong.
And when I finaIIy got the right one,
there was no answer.
So I thought I'd come down here
and make sure you were okay.
I'm okay.
Listen, maybe we
couId get together Iater?
That sounds good. I'II caII you.
Or you caII me, whatever.
You got it!
Bye, everybody.
There you go.
Second date!
I don't know.
You don't know?
She seems nice, but that thing about
her coming aII the way here. . .
. . .just to see if I was okay?
I mean, how needy is that?