Previously on AMC's
"Better Call Saul"...
You do realize you just
confessed to a felony?
For this, you destroyed our family?
You happy now?!
- Jimmy!
- What are you gonna do?
- He's got me boxed in.
- You can fight this.
I regret it all, more
than you can imagine,
'cause you're my brother.
I'm filing a motion
to suppress that tape.
Motions aside, that tape will be played.
Well?
Bingo.
Found a phone!
It looks like it's from
1967, but I think it'll work.
Just a sec, Jimmy.
Excellent. Thank you
for being so careful.
- Sir.
- Hmm?
- We have to get in your attic.
- For what?
Oh, the hook-up.
Oh, no. That's all right. Don't bother.
Oh, it won't take 20 minutes.
Plus, you really can't
use it if I don't do it.
No, it's all right. We're not gonna...
Uh, when you're done here,
would you get some more
lamps in the garage?
Thanks.
- So, we got a phone.
- Yeah.
The yard's half-mowed.
Uh, the sockets and
stuff are looking a-ok.
I'm gonna check again just to make sure.
We're almost there.
Good. Good.
Um, what do you think?
On? Off?
Ohh. I think... off.
Yeah. You're right. Off it is.
- Chuck.
- Hmm?
You sure this is the right play?
I mean, in my experience,
the bigger the lie, the
harder it can be to dig out.
I'll cross that bridge
when I come to it.
Hey, guys, think we're
set with the lamps.
Uh, could someone give me a
hand with this phone? Gracias.
Mmm.
It's open!
Rebecca.
- Chuck.
- You look lovely.
- Oh, it's so good to see you.
- And you.
- Oh.
- Hey,
what's with the candles?
Why you sittin' here in the dark?
Ye, I was wondering the same thing.
Oh, my God, the afternoon I've had.
Two hours ago, I take the sea bass out.
No sooner is it prepped and resting
then, boom... power goes down.
I get on the phone to the city.
To make a long story short,
those bozos at PNM mixed up my payment.
The deadbeat at 512 San Cristobal
hasn't been paying his bills.
And, of course, I'm...
- 215. Mm-hmm. Mm.
- 215, exactly.
They say they'll have
it on again by tomorrow.
In the meantime, I borrowed some
camping gear from my neighbors.
Hence, the rustic flair.
- Jeez.
- Oh, yeah.
So, what do we do?
Uh, get out of here
and go to a restaurant?
We could hit Seasons. Your treat.
We could, yeah.
But, um, you know,
dinner's almost ready.
And the fish... I would have
just had to throw it out.
All I have to do is toss it in a pan.
How about we just rough it?
Huh? You okay with that?
Uh, um...
Well... why not? It'll be fun.
We'll do an haute-cuisine camp-out.
Great! Then it's settled.
Let me take that. Take your...
- Oh, yeah, here. Oh, thank you.
- Here, I'll take that.
Mm-hmm.
- Mmm.
Oh, my God.
I can't eat another bite.
Cheers to the Galloping Gourmet.
- Mm!
- Ah.
Yeah.
Mm.
The Calvados is perfect.
Mm. You always liked it.
Here.
Uh, um...
- Let me get this.
- No, no, Jimmy.
- You don't have to.
- No, least I can do...
- is the dishes.
- Oh.
Thank you.
Thanks, Jimmy.
This turned out better than I thought.
Uh, I'm so... sorry about the lights.
Oh, it's nice. Atmospheric.
I mean, I still can't get
over Jimmy being a lawyer.
Neither can I.
He's got his own shingle
out and everything.
I mean, a real, responsible citizen.
I mean, who woulda thought?
Yeah.
Mm.
This place is the same.
I mean, I-I would've thought you'd...
change things up.
Move things around.
You've got great taste.
And if it ain't broke...
How's the tour going?
It's good. Good.
- Um, the Far East this fall.
- Oh.
Uh, China, South Korea, and Vietnam.
- That's gonna be exciting.
- Yeah.
And then, um, after Santa Fe this week,
- uh, we're back to Central Europe.
- And it's good?
- Well, it's a lot of hotels.
- Yeah.
I mean, in Budapest,
I think I saw mostly
the inside of the concert
hall and the Marriott.
But, you know, I shouldn't complain.
You're not complaining.
You're observing.
Did you finally get to see Salzburg?
Not yet, but next month, after Vienna.
Do you remember when we
tried to go to Salzburg?
And that crazy old
lady on the scooter...
- Oh, yes! Yes!
- Chased us out of the train station.
Yeah! And then, um...
and then we went and got, uh,
it was a-a-a raspberry
Linzer torte in Innsbruck?
- Mm.
- To make ourselves feel better?
Mm. You said, "We'll never finish this!"
And then we did.
So, what's after Asia? Any
plans for a stateside tour?
Oh, you know, hopefully next year.
You know, maybe a residency.
Oh, that would be sweet.
I mean, you know, I like the buses
and trains and planes fine,
but I, um...
I miss having one...
one place to hang my hat.
Oh, God!
I'm sorry. I-I-I hate that thing.
I feel like I'm on a leash. Ugh!
I'm sorry.
Oh. Oh, it's my conductor.
Um, I have to take this. I'm sorry.
H-Hi, Andre.
No, I'm just at dinner. What's up?
Well, I can do that at rehearsal.
Yeah, no problem. Yeah.
No, I-I know that they're
coming in late on bar 16.
Y-Yeah. Got it. Got it.
I will make sure that...
Uh, c-c-can you hold on a second?
Let me just get a pen.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. No, I-I...
Yeah, hold on one second.
Yeah, I can do it... I
mean, whatever you need.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
All right, shoot.
Okay...
Chuck?
I'm all right.
Well, do you want me to
rehearse the cellists separately?
Rebecca. Rebecca.
Well, no, it's not just
him. It's the whole section.
Rebecca!
Uh, no.
T-That's fine.
Yeah.
Chuck, what the hell?!
Andre?
I-I-I have to... I'll
have to call you back.
I'm sorry.
What is your problem?
Say something.
It is incredibly bad manners
to answer a cellphone in company.
It's very rude.
Uh, I-I'm sorry.
I-I didn't know that you felt that way.
I... didn't mean to offend you, Chuck.
I-I may have overreacted.
- That was very abrupt. Uh..
- No.
I understand.
Uh...
It's getting late.
Thank you for a lovely dinner,
but I should be getting
back to the hotel.
Just gimme a minute, and we can...
No. Uh, um, I'll just get a cab.
I don't want to put you out
any more than I already...
- Please, let me.
- No, really.
A cab is the easiest.
You gotta do somethin'.
Y-You can't let her leave like this.
- Just tell her what's going on.
- No. No.
She'll understand.
She'll... Would you rather
she think you're a raging prick
than know the truth?
No.
Look, if you won't
tell her, then I will.
No, no. No!
You will not tell her.
You... will not tell her.
All right.
Hi, Andre. Yes, I'm sorry about that.
I dropped the phone.
STRVINARKA
www.strvinarka.com
Jesus. What're you doing, man?
There's barely any oxygen in that bag.
- You're suffocating her!
- "Her"?
Yeah, just because you
don't see swingin' dicks
doesn't mean you can't tell
a boy fish from a girl fish.
Oh, yeah, see.
Now I can see the lipstick.
This is a living creature.
It's not a piece of furniture.
So, after this, you take her home.
You put her in a big
bowl, at least a gallon.
Get a good bubbler,
maybe a plecostomus.
And don't feed her too much.
People get fat.
Fish, they drown in leftover food.
All right already, Jacques Cousteau.
Point made.
Good.
I'm guessing our friend
didn't refer you to me
to get ichthyological advice.
I'm looking for someone
with a light touch.
I'm not talking some teenager
taking a five-finger discount
on string cheese at the Stop 'N' Shop.
I need highly skilled,
high-end, discreet.
A real pro.
You gotta fit him in a tight space?
I don't think so.
I got just the guy, then.
That's why I say golfing
is a contact sport.
Great job, Ms. Wexler. Very refreshing.
Believe me, uh, we're happy
to get this one off the docket.
Not as happy as we are.
Again, great job.
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
Ladies, dinner's on me.
Kim, I knew you were good, but
I didn't know you were this good.
Oh, I'm glad you're happy.
We couldn't have done it without you.
And I hope you realize this means
a whole lot a work comin' your way.
Oh, that's... that's great.
Well, you don't sound like it's great.
I hate to be a buzzkill, but...
there is something you need to
hear before we get any deeper in.
It's about your former
attorney, Charles McGill.
What about him?
Charles has been making
some very ugly allegations
about his brother, Jimmy,
with whom I happen to
share an office space.
Allegations? Of what?
Charles thinks that Jimmy
somehow took control of your documents
while he was working
on them at his home.
He believes Jimmy transposed
the address numbers.
Transposed the numbers?
How would he even do that?
Charles contends that
Jimmy took the documents
pertaining to the Rosella branch
and, while Charles was indisposed,
photocopied and doctored them.
That's pretty baroque.
The important thing here
is I think it could make
some noise in public.
Soon.
I wanted to tell you this in
the spirit of full disclosure.
I thought it was better
if you heard it from me.
If you have any reservations
at this point, or...
if you are not comfortable
staying with me,
we can discuss options.
If there's one thing I cannot abide,
it's a man who won't
own up to his mistakes.
Now, whatever mud McGill is slinging
he's not gonna screw
me out of the best...
outside counsel I've ever had.
That's...
I'm so glad to hear that.
We appreciate the heads-up, but
you can call this baby put to bed.
Now the most important thing... dinner.
7:00 good for you?
- Uh, works for me.
- Great.
We'll talk strategy...
We move on Colorado or Utah first?
See ya at 7:00.
This McGill thing.
You're sure it's not gonna be a problem?
I am.
Mesa Verde isn't involved
in any way, shape, or form.
Okay. Good.
Then, I'll see you tonight.
Okay, great. See you then.
Okay, this is it.
We can run without lights and mics.
We'll collect all cellphones
and hold them for the
duration of your testimony.
The, uh, court reporter,
would it be possible
to move him or her farther
from the witness stand?
Um, yeah, I think we can arrange
having them in the back of the court.
I'm sorry. There's nothing I
can do about the exit signs.
It's code.
I appreciate all
you're doing. Thank you.
Mr. Alley, I wonder if
you'd give us a moment.
I'd like to go over
something with my colleague.
No problem. I'll be
outside when you're ready.
Howard?
How you feeling, Chuck?
- I'll muddle through.
- Because this is a lot to ask.
And if you're not up to it...
just throwing this out there...
maybe you don't need to testify at all.
No, I do.
I'm the only person who
can adequately explain
the context of that tape.
Otherwise, the defense'll
tear it to shreds.
It's already a solid case.
We have Jimmy's statement from
the Pre-Prosecution Diversion.
There's my testimony
and the private eye's.
Maybe there's no need to put you
through the wringer like this.
This isn't about me or my health.
This is about PR.
We lost a client.
That happened because, while
you were... incapacitated,
your brother accessed documents
that should have been secured at HHM.
What Jimmy did is unconscionable, yes...
but one of my jobs is to
safeguard the firm's reputation.
This is not the time to
worry about how we look.
This is about what's
right and what's wrong.
I'm not gonna risk Jimmy getting, what?
A year's suspension? Maybe two?
He deserves disbarment,
not some slap on the wrist.
No, Howard. There's
only one way forward.
Let justice be done,
though the heavens fall.
Sorry to keep you
waiting. This'll do nicely.
Please extend my thanks to the
Committee for their flexibility.
Good morning. I'm Robert
Alley for the State Bar.
In the matter of James M. McGill,
the State Bar intends to
prove the following violations
of the Ethical Code.
16-102...
engaging in conduct a
lawyer knows is criminal.
Mr. McGill certainly knew that
breaking down his brother's door
was criminal behavior.
16-804...
committing a criminal act
that reflects adversely
on the lawyer's honesty or
trustworthiness as a lawyer.
Any reasonable person would agree
that assaulting another
lawyer in his own home
reflects badly on Mr. McGill's
fitness as an attorney.
16-304...
unlawfully altering, destroying,
or concealing material having
potential evidentiary value.
Mr. McGill broke into his brother's home
and destroyed an audiocassette
which contained a
recording of a conversation
between himself and his
brother, Charles McGill.
We will show that this
recording was evidence
in an ongoing legal case.
The State Bar believes that,
once we have presented the facts,
the Committee will agree
that disbarment is warranted
for James McGill.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mr. Alley.
Ms. Wexler?
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Good morning.
I'm Kim Wexler, co-counsel
with James McGill,
for the defense.
You've already read Mr. McGill's
Pre-Prosecution Statement.
We don't dispute he broke
into his brother's house,
an act he regrets...
deeply.
But there is another side to this story.
One not about calculation...
or ill intent,
but about about two brothers,
whose relationship,
after years of strain,
finally broke.
We believe that, after you
have the complete picture,
you'll understand
James McGill is an asset
to our legal community.
And he should remain a full
member of it in good standing.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ms. Wexler.
Okay, if, uh, everyone's ready to...
begin testimony...
Mr. Alley, call your witness.
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Then he kicked down the door.
Jimmy was very agitated.
He was shouting.
He demanded Charles turn over
- the evidence he'd been collecting...
- Objection.
We haven't established the
tape is evidence of anything.
The defense has only acknowledged
it as a piece of property.
Uh, allow me to rephrase.
Jimmy demanded an audiocassette
in Charles' possession,
which Jimmy proceeded,
with the help of an
iron fireplace implement,
to pry from Charles' desk.
He then broke the cassette into pieces
and went on to confront his brother.
What happened after the
defendant smashed this tape?
Mr. Brightbill and I...
That's the private
investigator that Charles hired?
That's correct.
He and I were concerned that
Jimmy might strike his brother.
So that's when we stepped in.
- Thank you, Mr. Hamlin.
- Certainly.
Nothing further at this time.
Ms. Wexler?
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
You testified you've known
my client for some time.
How long exactly?
Nearly 10 years.
How did you come to know him?
His brother asked to hire him
in the mail-room at our firm.
- And you did.
- Yes.
What was your opinion of him then?
I thought...
he had a lot of get-up-and-go.
He was a hard worker.
You had a nickname for him, didn't you?
"Charlie Hustle."
How'd you feel when you found
out he'd become a lawyer?
Surprised.
He'd put himself through law school
and taken the Bar Exam without
telling any of the partners.
Even Charles.
He bootstrapped his
way into a law degree
while working in your mail-room.
Did you consider taking
him on as an associate?
We did.
Briefly.
Sounds like you didn't
hire him. Why not?
With that kind of grit.
The partners decided it would be best
to avoid the appearance of nepotism.
We felt hiring Jimmy
might damage morale.
Nepotism.
Your firm is "Hamlin,
Hamlin, and McGill," right?
Who's the other Hamlin?
My father.
Which partner was the most
concerned with nepotism?
Charles McGill.
- So Jimmy's own brother blocked him.
- Objection.
How are the hiring practices of
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill relevant here?
It's relevant to understand
the relationship between these brothers.
We'll, uh, give you
some leeway, Ms. Wexler,
but don't stray too far.
Charles McGill is not the
subject of this hearing.
Thank you.
Did Jimmy know his brother was the one
that prevented you from hiring him?
No. He did not.
Eventually, he was hired
by the firm of Davis & Main.
I'd be happy to say more
about that, if you'd like.
No. Thank you.
When Charles' condition appeared,
Jimmy took care of him, didn't he?
I believe so.
Jimmy was struggling to
build his solo law practice,
and yet, every single day, without fail,
he brought his brother food, supplies...
even his favorite
newspapers. Isn't that right?
He did.
Could you speak to the terms
of Charles' leave of absence?
You know I can't.
It was an FMLA leave.
Anything more is confidential.
But you can confirm it was
due to mental illness, correct?
Objection! Charles McGill's
mental health isn't at issue.
This is a smear job on the
State Bar's upcoming witness...
nothing more.
This is not a competency
hearing, Ms. Wexler.
Mr. Hamlin is not a
psychiatric professional.
Do you have any questions
that would be more germane
to his experience?
No.
I have nothing further.
The witness is excused.
At this time, the State Bar would like
to enter Exhibit Five into evidence.
We ask that Charles
McGill's recording be played.
I'm respectfully renewing my objection.
The probative value
of playing this Exhibit
is outweighed by how prejudicial it is.
All due respect to Ms. Wexler,
but the State Bar feels
this is fundamental to hear.
We don't want to leave any question
as to the intentions of both parties.
Ms. Wexler, we already
ruled this was fair game
when we denied your motion to suppress.
I'll add, the rough-and-tumble
of your client's conduct aside,
we need to know whether one lawyer
attempted to tamper
with another's evidence.
Come here.
What are you still doing here?
- Flight's delayed.
- How delayed?
40 minutes, last I checked.
Shit. Okay. Keep me posted.
Um, yes.
Here we go.
Thank you for your patience.
The State Bar is ready to proceed.
Um, begging your pardon.
Um, the defense requests a
moment to review, if we could?
All right.
When you're ready.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
What are we doing?
We're stalling.
Yes. Yes.
My brother has many admirable qualities.
I-In some ways, I can say I admire him.
Too cold.
I love my brother.
But Ted Kaczynski's
brother loved him, too.
And he wanted to help.
That's sanctimonious.
I love my brother.
He's a good person. He has good in him.
But the law is too important.
Ah.
Be right there, Howard!
The law is too important.
Hmm...
I sure shit wouldn't
be tellin' ya otherwise.
But, yes...
it's the truth.
You'd go to such
lengths to humiliate me?
I did it for Kim!
She worked her butt
off to get Mesa Verde
while you and Howard sat around
sipping scotch and chortling.
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill...
more like Scrooge and Marley!
Kim deserves Mesa Verde...
not you, not HHM.
She earned it, and she needs it!
I did it to help her,
but I-I honestly didn't think
it would hurt you so bad.
I thought you'd just say,
"Oh, crap, I made a mistake,"
and go on with your life,
like a normal person!
But, oh, no!
Wishful thinking!
So, can I, uh, tell Howard
you're not quitting or
retiring or whatever?
And can we take all this
shit down off the walls?
I'm gonna go call Howard.
Jimmy.
You do realize you just
confessed to a felony?
I guess.
But you feel better, right?
Besides, it's your word against mine.
Uh. Um.
All right, uh, Mr. Alley, uh,
we need to make accommodations
for your next witness.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, Mr. Chairman.
All right.
For those who don't know,
we need to prepare the room.
Uh, the Clerk is going to
collect your, uh, cellphones,
watches, key fobs...
anything electrical.
If you prefer not to,
please secure your items...
- Thank you.
- Outside this room.
Thank you for understanding.
Your phone, sir?
I left it in the car.
- Oh. Excuse me.
- Sorry.
- That's yours.
- Thanks.
Please raise your right hand.
Do you swear or affirm to tell
the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth?
I do.
Could you state your name?
Charles L. McGill.
I'm a senior partner at the law
firm of Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill.
Can the court reporter hear me?
Yes, sir. I can hear you fine.
Mr. McGill, I'll try to be brief.
We don't need to dwell on the burglary
or the assault that you suffered.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
What I would like to
hear about is this tape.
What compelled you to make it?
I had a suspicion my brother
had tampered with documents
in a case I was working on.
And why would he do that?
Doesn't sound particularly brotherly.
I believe it was his hope
that the tainted documents
would cause the client
to become disillusioned
with my representation
and return to their previous attorney,
Ms. Wexler.
Which, I should note, is
precisely what happened.
Objection.
I'm not saying Ms. Wexler
knew what Jimmy was doing
or had any involvement.
I'm only stating that it happened.
Did you have any evidence to
support your suspicions about James?
No. My brother,
whatever else can be said
of him, can be quite clever.
Did an excellent job
of covering his tracks.
Objection. The witness has admitted
there's no corroborating evidence
this supposed crime even occurred.
I'd like to hear what he has to say.
We're going to continue.
Uh, we'll extend you the same
latitude on cross, Ms. Wexler.
Go on, Mr. McGill.
Without physical evidence,
I felt that a recorded confession...
if I could get one... was my best bet.
On its own, I knew the tape
would be somewhat flimsy,
but it was a start.
A foundation for a more ironclad case.
I suppose that Jimmy must have felt
the tape was decisive
evidence on its own.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
broken in to destroy it.
Objection. More speculation.
How can he know what was
going on in Jimmy's head?
Sustained. We just need to
hear what happened, Mr. McGill.
I-I apologize.
I recorded my brother to
build a case against him.
And at the time,
would you say that you were in
possession of your faculties?
All due respect, but...
but you do sound somewhat
unhinged on the recording.
Yes, I understand that.
But what you heard was theater.
A performance, play-acting.
I exaggerated the symptoms of my disease
to extract the truth.
Can we talk about your
disease for a moment?
I'd like everybody here to
be on the same page about it.
Of course.
It is sometimes referred to as EHS,
electromagnetic hypersensitivity.
I describe it as an acute
allergy to electromagnetism.
It's not a common condition, is it?
I know it sounds strange. I do.
But 30 years ago, no one had
heard of peanut allergies.
But you admit that no one...
uh, no doctor... has ever diagnosed you.
AIDS was not identified
properly until 1981.
HIV wasn't known as the cause until '83.
These things take time to
unravel, even for doctors.
Would you say that your illness
affects your ability to think clearly?
No. It affects me physically.
It causes me great pain.
However, I'm perfectly lucid.
Thank you.
Mr. McGill, I have only
one more question for you.
Do you hate your brother?
Absolutely not.
I love my brother.
There's nothing malicious in Jimmy.
He has a way of doing the worst things
for reasons that sound almost noble.
But what I know for sure is that the law
is too important to be toyed with.
It's mankind's greatest
achievement... the Rule of Law,
the idea that, no matter who you are,
your actions have consequences.
And the way my brother treats the law...
it breaks my heart.
That's why I did what
I did. Not to hurt him,
but to protect something
that I hold sacred.
Thank you, Mr. McGill.
The State Bar rests.
I think we need to put on the brakes.
I'm sorry. My co-counsel and
I need a moment to confer.
Please be brief, Counselor.
Yes, of course.
She'll be here.
Do you have anything for cross?
Uh, can I look at your notes?
Yeah, of course.
Can we, um...
Yeah.
- Hey.
So glad you made it.
Mr. Chairman, I'm sorry.
Um, might I have a moment,
uh, to get a breath?
Oh, of course, Mr. McGill.
Uh, folks, let's call this 15.
Everybody, please be back
and ready to go on the hour.
- Rebecca.
- Chuck.
It's good to see you.
I have to say, I'm a bit surprised.
Did Jimmy subpoena you?
You're not on the witness
list. You don't have to testify.
No, no, no, no. I'm not here for that.
Well, what, then?
Chuck, I wish you'd told me.
I-I can't believe what
you've been going through.
How long has it been?
Ah.
You're here to help.
Because all this is so stressful for me.
Is that what Jimmy told you?
He's worried about you, Chuck.
In spite of everything that's
happened between the two of you,
he... he cares.
What exactly did he say?
Um, well, that you had been sick.
Allergic to electricity?
He sent me pictures of the house.
Chuck, my God.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to upset you.
Worry you unnecessarily.
But now you're here.
And now you know.
I came because I thought
it was the right thing.
I thought... I don't know...
that you'd want me to.
But I guess that I'm
more of a distraction.
So, uh...
I'm gonna be in town for a few days,
and I would love to
spend some time with you.
But right now, I-I think I should go.
No. No, no, please. I want you to stay.
Really? You don't seem happy to see me.
I am.
Just surprised, that's all.
Please, stay.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
You've been sold a
bill of goods, Rebecca.
I want you to see what's what.
She's not what I expected.
Oh, yeah? What'd you expect?
I don't know. Just...
not her.
You know, she's gonna
hate you when this is over.
Yep.
All right, uh, Mr. McGill,
I'll remind you you're still under oath.
I understand.
At this time, I'd like to
turn cross-examination over
to my co-counsel, James McGill.
Uh, well, there's been
a lot of fuss about it,
but you and I have never really
talked about this tape you made.
We lost the opportunity
when you burglarized
my house to destroy it.
Fair enough.
Um, and I was in the wrong there.
But, still, I'd like to
try and follow your story
of why and how you recorded it.
Oh, is this where you
claim the tape is spurious?
That it's not really your voice?
No. That's me on the tape.
But, still, I have some
questions. Like, the recorder,
it must've hurt like hell
for you to touch that.
There was a degree of
discomfort, that's true.
And where did you hide it?
I mean, the sound's pretty clear,
so it wasn't in the
couch cushions, was it?
Tucked under a space
blanket. Out of sight.
Wow.
So there's no chance I would see it.
Not with the state your place was in.
- Isn't that right?
- I suppose.
Would you like to set the scene
for the Disciplinary Committee?
Tell them, you know, what
your house looked like
at the time of the recording.
Objection. Relevance?
Well, the circumstances of the
recording are materially relevant.
How can you know what
the tape really means
unless you know what was
going on when it was recorded?
Overruled. The witness
can answer the question.
I covered most of the walls
with Foil-Scrim-Kraft insulation.
I also hung a number of space blankets.
Compact Mylar sheets.
They insulate and protect
against mild electromagnetic radiation.
All right, so, shiny
insulation and space blankets
all over the walls and the ceiling.
It was like being
inside of a disco ball.
Do you have a point?
Well, um, I'm impressed
by how much work went
into entrapping me.
You went all out.
I didn't entrap you.
I provoked an admission
in adverse interest.
That's not the same thing.
How did you know it would work?
What do you mean?
How did you know your
"provocation" would work?
Why'd you think a bunch of shiny plastic
would make me say anything?
Isn't it because you knew
that it was precisely the thing
that would worry me so much
that I'd say anything to talk you down?
- Objection.
- Okay. Withdrawn.
Let's... let's get back to your house,
every surface covered in tinfoil.
Nothing crazy about that, huh?
As I've said,
I was playing up my condition.
Usually, it's a perfectly normal house.
You think your house is normal?
Can I call your
attention to Exhibit Nine?
This is your house, right?
Yes.
So, exposed wires.
There's a camp stove.
There's a lantern on top of newspapers.
You call this normal?
I call them adaptations.
A prophylactic measure for a
physical, medical condition.
Did the doctor who granted
me guardianship for you
- think this was a physical condition?
- Objection.
You can't introduce a TEG as evidence.
Besides which, the
panel has already ruled
that Mr. McGill's mental
health is not at issue.
No, the State Bar opened
the door to this on direct
when the witness talked about
his supposed "play-acting."
Allowing me to follow up
on cross is only reasonable.
We discussed the physical allergy,
not a mental disability.
Potato, po-tah-to.
It comes down to this...
In order to understand
what I was thinking,
you need to see Chuck through my eyes.
You need to know if I believed
that tape was evidence.
And I say it was evidence
of only one thing...
My brother hates me.
Now, he claims that he lied to
me to get me to tell the truth.
And I'm telling you
I lied to my brother
to make him feel better.
Which of us you believe
depends on how we all understand
the mind of Charles McGill.
Well, we did promise
the defense some leeway.
You may proceed.
- Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
- But watch yourself.
Chuck, I'd like to go
back a little further,
talk about when these
symptoms first started.
It was shortly after you
were divorced, is that right?
Yes.
You think the stress of the
divorce brought on the illness?
I doubt it. It was an amicable split.
My ex-wife and I are
still on good terms.
In fact, your ex-wife is present
with us today, is she not?
When was the last time
you two saw each other?
Objection. This is not family court.
We're not here to re-litigate
the witness' divorce.
I can't see what purpose this serves.
I can.
I'll tell you why my brother
brought my ex-wife to this hearing.
4,000 miles she came,
lured by concern for me.
What Jimmy's driving at
is the last time I saw her,
I covered up my illness.
I'd been suffering
from it for some time,
but I went to great lengths
to conceal that fact from her.
I'm sorry I deceived you, Rebecca.
I didn't want you to think less of me.
Now Jimmy has outed me in front of you.
You know why?
To rattle me.
He knows I still have a...
a lot of, feeling for my ex-wife.
He's hoping this will break me down.
Split me apart at the seams,
like a murderer confessing on
an episode of "Perry Mason."
Well, I'm sorry to
disappoint you, Jimmy.
Have I answered your
questions to your satisfaction?
Do you have anything else?
Yeah, I do.
Earlier, you talked
about other diseases.
Physical conditions, you said.
Uh, so, okay, if you'd
had, um... I don't know...
lung cancer, would you
have told Rebecca then?
If that had been the
case, maybe. I might have.
- So how is this different?
- Mr. McGill. Move it along.
You don't have to answer that.
I want to get down to brass tacks.
I want to be very, very specific here.
This illness, what does it feel like?
You mentioned it's painful.
It is.
There's a tightness in my chest,
difficulty breathing,
and pain, burning pain.
The pain spreads everywhere.
Sounds horrible. Does it hurt right now?
There's always some discomfort, yes.
Electricity is everywhere
in the modern world.
But I very much appreciate
the indulgence of the panel
for their accommodation here today.
I can handle this fine.
Right, so, with the lights
out, you don't feel them?
If the current's not flowing, no.
Oh. Sorry about the exit signs.
I guess they couldn't
kill those for you.
Well, they're not drawing much
current, and they're far away.
Intensity drops off with distance,
per the inverse-square law.
Okay, whoa!
Inverse-square... I'm not a physicist.
Could you dumb that down a shade for me?
The farther away it is,
the stronger the source
needs to be to have an effect.
Got it. Got it.
So, if I had a small battery,
say, from a watch or something,
and I got it close to you,
close to your skin, you'd know?
I would feel it, yes.
Can you feel more current
coming from any particular
direction right now?
Uh, from that back wall
or, uh, from over there
or up through the floor?
Can you tell us where
the nearest source is
right now?
Jimmy, do you have
something in your pocket?
Yes, I do, as a matter of fact.
My cellphone.
From this distance, you should
feel it, and you don't, do you?
Mr. McGill, you were warned to
leave your electronics outside.
It's all right.
May I?
Ah.
Just as I thought.
There's no battery in here.
You removed the battery.
That's a sorry little trick, isn't it?
Yeah, you got me, Chuck. Dead to rights.
I removed the battery.
- Objection.
- Sustained.
Y-You've taken all the leeway
you're getting, Mr. McGill.
Wrap it up fast.
God, Jimmy.
Don't you know by now this is real?
I feel this.
It's a physical response to stimuli.
It's not a quirk.
What do I have to do to prove it to you?
I don't know, Chuck.
Could you reach into your breast pocket
and tell me what's there?
What now?
Can you tell the court what that was?
- A battery.
- Mr. Chairman, please.
Do you recognize that man in back?
His name is Huell Babineaux.
He's on our witness list.
You bumped into him in the stairway.
He'll testify he planted this
fully charged battery on you
over an hour and a half ago.
Hour and 43 minutes ago.
An hour and 43 minutes.
Thank you, Mr. Babineaux.
And you felt nothing.
No, no, no.
- No, no. It's a trick. It has to...
- Enough is enough.
I submit that Mr. McGill's
mental illness is a non-issue.
- If he were schizophrenic...
- Schizo...
it wouldn't take
away from the fact...
- that the defendant...
- I am not crazy!
I am not crazy.
I know he swapped those numbers.
I knew it was 1216.
One after Magna Carta.
As if I could ever make such a mistake.
Never. Never!
I just... I just couldn't prove it.
H-H-He covered his tracks.
He got that idiot at the
copy shop to lie for him.
Mr. McGill, please. You
don't have to go in...
You think this is something?
You think this is bad,
this... this chicanery?
He's done worse. That billboard!
Are you telling me that a man
just happens to fall like that?
No. He orchestrated it!
Jimmy!
He defecated through a sunroof!
And I saved him, and I shouldn't have.
I took him into my own firm.
What was I thinking?!
He'll never change.
Ever since he was 9, always the same.
Couldn't keep his hands
out of the cash drawer.
But not our Jimmy.
Couldn't be precious Jimmy!
Stealing them blind.
And he gets to be a lawyer?!
What a sick joke!
I should have stopped
him when I had the chance!
And you... you have to stop him!
You...
I apologize.
I lost my train of thought.
I got carried away.
Do you have anything else?
No.
Nothing further.
Synced and corrected by STRVINARKA
www.strvinarka.com