Chuck: You can move
the red five up.
Man:
Oh, yeah.
Thank you, sir.
Why do the cards
have holes in them?
Oh.
They're, uh -- these are
used cards from the casino.
Once the casino pulls
a deck of cards out of action,
they drill a hole through them
and sell 'em to the public.
Just a buck or 2.
Look at that.
I suppose that's to prevent
people from cheating with them.
Yeah.
Makes for
a good souvenir.
These are
from caesars.
Mm.
I've never been.
Hmmm.
Getting dark.
I hate to say it,
but I think it might be time
to kill the lights.
Oh, yes, sir.
Of course.
You sure I can't make you
a cup of tea?
I'm fine, sir.
Thank you.
All right,
then.
Ohh.
Just what I needed.
Drink up, guys.
Don't need you fallin' asleep.
Hey, you take care
of that battery?
Oh, yeah.
It finally shit the bed,
but we swapped it out
a couple hours ago.
Okay.
How'd it go?
No problem.
Anyone see you?
Nah.
Dead over there.
A'ight.
Stay awake.
hello?
Jimmy: Oh, hey.
Come on in.
Hi.
I'm Francesca liddy.
I'm here
for the interview.
Oh.
Jimmy mcgill.
Hey, are you, uh, running early,
or am I running late?
No, sorry.
I'm a little early.
It's not a problem.
Never bad
to be early...
Except in death and taxes
and...Some other things.
Hey, can I ask you
a question?
Sure.
Does that
look straight to you?
Uh...
I think there --
that -- that side --
I think
you're a little crooked --
the bottom
of the "m" there.
Yeah.
A little crooked.
So, you're coming off
of seven years at the mvd?
I am, yeah.
Here's a question --
how come new Mexico
doesn't call it the dmv
like every other state?
Well,
that's a great question.
Uh,
just like in Arizona,
the motor vehicles division
is part of the dot, a division,
whereas,
in most other states, the dmv,
or department of motor vehicles
is its own entity, so...
I don't know
if that answers the question,
except to say
that's the government for you.
You got that right.
Well, I, for one,
am not calling it the mvd --
dmv all the way.
What do you think you learned
the most working there?
Patience, diplomacy.
Uh, you meet a-all sorts
of people down there,
a-and most are really great,
really friendly,
but you encounter some
who are upset, belligerent.
What about old folks?
Uh, you get
your fair share of them?
Oh, lots of
elderly drivers.
After 75, they need
to take their test again,
so if
they don't pass,
you have to
explain to them
why their license
isn't being renewed,
which is hard
for them.
What do you say then?
Do you ever...
Yell at them?
I mean, geezers,
right?
How can you not?
No,
i would never.
No.
Nor should you.
That was a trick question.
You passed
with flying colors -- very good.
Okay.
Well, then, so, Jimmy and i
have very different needs.
His practice is mostly wills
for senior citizens,
while I'm focused on
a single client at the moment,
mesa verde,
with banking regulations
that generate
a ton of paperwork,
so I'm looking
for someone
with an eye for organization
and detail.
Jimmy: Well,
dmv's great for that --
tons of detail
in those driver's licenses.
We did see hundreds of people
every day,
and you'd never
want to let a mistake
slip through
on their forms.
You'd just have
a horrible cascade of problems.
Sounds challenging.
So, why the law?
I mean, why leave the dmv --
or mvd?
I have to imagine
you'll be giving up
a good benefits package.
Good healthcare
and retirement plans, but...
There's a bureaucracy
to government work
that ultimately
became too frustrating.
I guess what you'd call it --
too much red tape.
I just want to be somewhere
i can make a difference.
Well, that's us. We're all about
making a difference.
And I see here
both word and excel --
you're comfortable with?
Absolutely.
Excel and word?
Wow.
Well, you had me
at old people.
Hey, here's a question --
can you start today?
I, uh...
Can --
yes?
Fantastic.
Now,
can you --
Can you just
give us a second, Francesca?
Absolutely. I...
Of course.
Um...
Thank you.
Uh-huh.
What are you doing?
What?
I like her.
"Can you start today?"
Don't you think we should see
some more résumés --
like,
a lot more?
She is
our first interview.
We haven't even
checked her references.
So we'll check 'em.
Kim, you've been takin' forever
searching for a paralegal.
We need help here.
I haven't found
the right fit.
Yeah, 'cause you're searching
for perfection,
and perfection is the enemy
of perfectly adequate.
Oh, so that's the bar here --
adequate?
She's more than adequate!
She worked at the dmv.
That's like
the fifth circle of hell.
Look,
she's overqualified.
I-if it doesn't work out,
we can fire her.
It's no big deal.
Don't you think someone with
some actual legal experience
would be better?
Look, I've got a commercial
airing in...
11 minutes,
so the phones are
gonna be ringin' off the hook
and I need help.
Can we give her
a test run, please?
I got a good feeling
about this.
Come on, Kim.
Now, getting these oldsters
to call --
that's half the battle,
so they need to hear
a friendly voice.
Friendly? Absolutely.
Speak loudly
and clearly,
but, uh, be careful
with the loud and clear,
'cause it can come off
as angry.
Be folksy.
Put a little sunshine
in your voice.
Got it.
Okay.
You need coffee
or water?
You need to hit the head
before things --
Oh, there it goes.
Offices of Jimmy mcgill.
How may I help you?
I'm sorry.
May I put you on hold?
Thank you.
Offices of Jimmy mcgill.
Please hold.
Sorry about that.
What can I do
for you?
Uh, that's right.
Jimmy mcgill
from the commercial.
Would you look to come in
for a consultation?
Folksy -- be folksy.
Say, is that
a dog I'm hearing?
It is?
Aww,
what's her name?
Yeah,
cracker barrel.
It always helps
to mention cracker barrel.
Well, I think it's great
you let Margaret play inside.
It's a hot one
out there.
I was thinking
of going over to cracker barrel
because they've got
such great air-conditioning.
Well, yes,
i love their biscuits, too.
Well,
that's wonderful.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, I think a will
is really important.
When would you like to come in
and meet Mr. mcgill?
"Jimmy"! Jimmy.
Always Jimmy.
Uh, this Friday
is open.
Yes.
Jimmy has a 9:00 free.
Will that work?
Fantastic.
Can you spell your name
for me?
And a number
we can reach you at?
Okay, Dorothy.
Look forward
to seein' ya.
You betcha.
Bye, now.
I am so sorry.
Thank you for holding.
How may I help you?
Well, I can set you up
with an appointment.
Jimmy is busy at the moment,
but if you'd like --
uh, you sound like
you're outdoors.
Are you staying
out of the sun?
It's a hot one today.
I'm sorry, but Jimmy
is unavailable at the moment.
If you'd like to leave
a message, Mr...
Ehrmantraut?
"Trout,"
like the fish?
Uh, I hear cracker barrel
has excellent air--
this one really don't want
to talk about cracker barrel.
Yeah,
patch that one through.
Mr. mcgill
will take your call.
Hey.
Mike: Your new assistant's
a real pip.
Yeah, thanks for crushing
her spirit on the first day.
Thank you, sir.
You drive safe.
You the only one
on this line?
Jimmy: Yeah, only me.
What's up?
You free
for breakfast tomorrow?
Mike: All right,
this is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna go inside,
buy a cup of coffee, a meal --
whatever --
and sit in a booth.
Sometime in the next
10 to 15 minutes,
a guy
in an old green Chevy blazer
is gonna pull into
that parking lot.
He'll take a knapsack,
and he'll go inside.
I need you to keep an eye
on the knapsack.
Let me know
what he does with it.
Does he take
anything out of it?
Does he switch the bag
with someone?
Does he leave
something from the bag inside?
Jimmy: Right, right, right.
I got it.
Green Chevy blazer,
black top.
Yeah.
What's in the bag?
Is it money?
It's got to be money.
Drugs?
Is it drugs?
Something else?
Well, um,
I'm Guessing money.
Tell me I'm right.
He is gonna be here
any minute.
Now,
i need you inside.
You gonna do the job
or not?
Fine.
I'll do the job.
You charmed me into it.
Welcome to los pollos hermanos.
May I take your order?
Uh, I'll have a pollos classic
and a coffee, black.
Would you like the pollos
bonus size for 50 cents more?
No. Normal.
Dining in
or to go?
Dining in.
Will that
be all today?
Uh, yeah.
Your total's $3.19.
Do you want
any extra salsa?
Uh, no.
Ketchup.
Oh, hi.
What can I do for you?
Here you go,
sir.
Oh.
Have a great day.
Yep.
You, too.
Woman: Oh, sure,
if there's one open.
Oh, yeah.
Woman: Hi.
Welcome to los pollos hermanos.
Can I take your order?
Man:
I'm gonna have the sausage.
Man: Is that for here
or to go?
Man #2:
It's for here.
Really?
Yeah.
Woman: Hi.
Welcome to los pollos hermanos.
May I take your order?
Gimme a number three.
Potatoes, coffee.
Would you like the pollos
bonus size for 50 cents more?
No.
Dining in or to go?
In.
Will that
be all today?
$4.89.
Yeah,
no problem.
Woman: Do you need
any extra salsa?
Yeah, gimme that.
Woman:
Here you go.
Have a great day.
Woman: Thank you for coming
to los pollos hermanos.
Have a great day.
Man:
Can I help you?
Uh.
My watch, uh,
clasp is loose.
It...Falls.
I tried to reach it.
Oh.
Well, I'm sorry.
Allow me.
Y'know,
they say a nice watch band
is as important
as the watch.
That's what I get
for cheapin' out.
We'll find it
for you.
Where the heck
is it?
Oh, don't worry.
If it's in here,
I'll -- ah.
There it is.
Oh.
May I clean this
for you?
We have alcohol wipes.
Oh, nah,
it's been in worse places.
Thank you.
That was
very nice of you.
No problem.
It's my pleasure.
Is there anything else
i can do for you?
Uh, no.
Thanks.
You take care.
Mike:
Tell me again.
Jesus.
How many different ways
you want me to say it?
Just tell me
what you saw.
He came in,
like you said he would.
He ordered the number three
with potatoes and coffee,
went bold
with the extra salsa,
and he paid cash
out of his left front pocket.
Uh, took his tray
of food,
sat in a booth on the east side
of the restaurant,
and put the knapsack
on the floor.
Where on the floor?
Under his seat,
between his legs.
Nobody touched it.
He didn't talk
to anybody.
He didn't even
look at anybody.
Finished his meal
in five minutes, tops,
and skedaddled --
didn't leave anything behind.
And you're sure of that?
I literally
checked the trash can.
There was nothing in there
but trash.
So...What's our next move,
huh?
Are we gonna follow
this guy?
'Cause you -- you got some
real James Bond stuff in here.
This car doesn't have
an ejector seat, does it?
I think
we're done for today.
That's it?
That's it.
I mean,
i cleared my morning.
What --
we're not gonna do, like,
uh, Tail him
to a new location?
Or, I mean, we got to
sit on him, at least. I --
thanks for your time.
Hey,
who's got your back, huh?
Me -- that's who.
I'll keep that
in mind.
Torrent downloaded from RARBG
Oh, Kim, the conference call
with the Arizona regulator
needs
to be rescheduled.
Thursday okay?
Oh, yeah,
that's fine.
Okay.
Francesca,
have we got any more
of those dietetic
butter cookies?
I can check.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Welcome, folks!
Hey, Ernie. What's up?
Can't you just come inside?
Sorry.
Thanks.
What are we doing
out here?
I didn't want
to call you
because then it would leave
a phone record.
I was gonna come in,
but then I thought
maybe Jimmy shouldn't see me.
So...
But you just called me.
Oh.
Guess I screwed up already.
Ernie,
screwed what up?
Why don't you want
to see Jimmy?
Well, it's just...
I'm not sure
how to start.
You can start
by just telling me.
Here's the thing.
I have
some information,
but I don't want
to get in trouble.
Trouble with Jimmy?
No.
With hhm.
I think I'm bound
by confidentiality, maybe?
I'm a little hazy
on the legal points,
but if I tell you what I heard
and not Jimmy directly,
like...
Like, we have a buffer,
then legally, I'm safe?
Ernie.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm -- I'm just worried
about Jimmy.
But if I tell him...
I don't want
to get in trouble, too.
Tell Jimmy what?
Lily, I want to thank you
for bringing your mom down.
It was a delight
to meet you, young lady.
Oh. Thank you, Jimmy.
And you tell your friends,
even if they already
have a will, it's important
to get it updated,
just like you did.
I'll tell them.
Now,
you remember Francesca --
she'll take care of you
the rest of the way.
All right, who's next?
Mr. witchell.
Mr. witchell,
come on down!
You're the next contestant
on "the price is right"!
Jimmy,
can I have a moment?
Excuse me, sir.
Um,
looks like everything is...
Apologies,
Mr. witchell.
Uh, I'll just be
a second, folks.
Oh, my gosh.
Have you guys had the soup
over at cracker barrel today?
What?
What?!
Hey, come on.
I got people
out there.
Hello.
I can't --
gimme a dollar.
Give you a dollar?
Yeah,
just hand me a dollar.
Okay.
C'mon.
All I got's a $20.
Fine. Whatever.
All right.
I'm your lawyer now.
If anyone
asks me what I know,
we have confidentiality.
Why do we need
confidentiality?
Jimmy,
what did you say to Chuck?
Oh.
Here it comes.
Howard, right?
Did Howard call?
R-relax.
No.
Let me explain, please.
Please.
Kim, let me set the stage
for you, okay?
When I went
to Chuck's place last week,
it was like the inside
of a jiffy pop wrapper,
all right?
There was mylar
on the walls.
on the ceiling -- the ceiling.
He thought
his brain wasn't working
because of
the mesa verde of it,
and so I kinda told him that
he was right about everything.
I had to.
He -- he --
Kim, he was broken.
He was
a broken man!
I couldn't leave him
in crazy town like that!
So I told him, you know,
just to make him feel better,
but it doesn't matter
what he says --
it doesn't matter
who he tells,
because it's my word
against his!
Jimmy,
there's a tape.
What?
There is a tape recording
of you talking to Chuck.
What do you mean?
Who? Who?
He -- he taped me?
How?
I don't know how.
He just did, okay?
Ernie told me.
Ernie told you?
He said Chuck
has a tape recorder
wrapped in a space blanket
in his desk drawer.
Ernie was putting new batteries
in it for Chuck,
and the tape rolled
for a few seconds,
and he heard you --
your voice --
saying something about
switching 1261 to 1216.
So, clearly, it was
this confession of yours.
He taped me?
Yes, Jimmy.
But I'm not sure
what he can do with it...
...legally, anyway.
I'm gonna have to
do some research.
He made that tape
for a reason,
and we just have to
figure out why.
Jimmy?
I gotta
get back to it.
The lobby's
full of clients.
Okay.
We'll figure this out.
Yeah. I know.
Sorry for the delay,
everyone!
Mr. witchell,
thank you for your Patience.
I see
you brought paperwork.
I got to say,
i would never have thought
to collect bottle caps.
Oh,
it's a wonderful hobby.
What excites me
is the hunt.
I can imagine.
Pleasure doing business
with you, Mr. tiller.
Why,
thank you, Jimmy.
All right, then.
You drive safe.
Oh, I do.
Is that
the last one,
or we got any stragglers
coming through?
Francesca: Last one.
Well, hey,
thanks, Francesca.
You were great today.
You, too.
Those folks love you.
Who doesn't?
And that's
U.S. v. McKeever?
Right. No, it makes sense.
You were a tremendous help,
professor.
Thanks for finding the time.
You, too.
Thanks again.
Francesca,
could you do me a favor?
Can you go through the
mesa verde files in my office
and pull all the ones
labeled "cra evaluations"
and sort them
by date?
I need to make sure
i have the most recent.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
I'll join you
in a minute.
Okay.
So...
Just got off the phone
with my old
crim-pro professor.
Oh, yeah?
What'd he say?
Well, as we know,
new Mexico is one-party consent,
so Chuck had a right
to make the recording.
But you went to him
worried for his mental health.
You said the things you did
to make him feel better,
which
Mitigates
the admission of guilt,
at the very least.
We can poke holes
in the custody,
throw doubt the voice
on the tape is even yours.
Even failing that,
its probative value doesn't
outweigh how prejudicial it is.
I think we can get the
whole thing bounced under 403.
Probably get it
excluded outright.
So, then...
Outside the courts,
what can you do?
Play the tape for Kevin
at mesa verde?
He hasn't
up to now.
I'd have heard something,
for sure.
And you know what?
I don't think he's going to.
I don't think Howard
will let him near mesa verde
with that tape.
Howard knows it would make hhm
look terrible.
If Chuck has a plan
for this tape,
I don't know
what it is.
At this point, all we can do
is wait for his move,
then act accordingly.
All right, then.
Thanks.
Sure.
Oh, hey,
what do you think?
Um, it's "etude in blue"
over "daydream harvest."
I wanted it to look like morning
over the sandias.
I like it.
It looks nice.
It doesn't look like
a stock-market crash?
No.
It doesn't look like
a stock-market crash.
It's nice.
Thanks.
You okay?
Kim, I'm good.
Yeah.
Howard,
what are you doing here?
Chuck,
do you have a second?
Did you --
you parked
over on the next block?
Oh, yeah.
Mm.
Way over.
Uh, phone.
Keys.
Hey, you have to
hide them.
Everything okay,
sir?
Yes,
thank you, David.
Give us a moment.
Yes, sir.
What's up?
Chuck...
This has been going on
for eight days now,
and really, no indication
that it's going to work.
It will work.
I think
I've been very patient,
but the cost of these
'round-the-clock
private investigators is...
Really starting
to add up.
Howard,
this is our duty.
As officers
of the court,
we have
an ethical obligation to --
yes.
My brother
broke the law.
We can't just sit back
and do nothing.
I'm not talking about
doing nothing.
I just want to...
Free up our minds
and be open
to alternate strategies, please.
Meet me halfway here.
I suppose -- I suppose
we could limit the investigators
to just nighttime hours.
Nighttime.
Yes.
Jimmy will most likely
break in
while he thinks
I'm sleeping --
I mean, I wouldn't
put anything past him.
It just
makes the most sense
he'll try to steal the tape
under cover of darkness.
You really think
he's going to do that?
I do, indeed.
How can you be
so sure?
Howard,
I know my brother.
Jimmy: Chuck!
Chuck!
Open the damn door,
Open the door,
damn it!
Open it! Chuck!
Chuck:
Jimmy, go away!
Open the door!
Open it now!
I'm not
opening the door!
I swear to god,
Chuck...
I am not op--
Jimmy!
You taped me?!
You asshole!
Jimmy!
You pulled that heartstrings con
job on me?!
You piece of shit!
"Ohh, my brain
used to work.
I'm sick.
I don't know what to do!"
Asshole!
No wonder
Rebecca left you!
What took her
so long?!
There it is!
Oh, here we go.
Here we go!
Oh!
Is this it?
Huh?
For this,
you destroyed our family?
You happy now?!
For what?!
For nothing!
Is that
all there is, Chuck?
It's all the --
all there is?
Or'd you make copies?
Huh, Chuck?
Huh?
You tell me,
or I'll burn this whole
goddamn house to the ground!
Jimmy! Jimmy!
That's enough!
You need
to step away.
Howard...
You were a witness
to what happened here?
I was.
And you?
I'm a witness.