Here you go.
And I hope you enjoyed
dinner and the show.
The show being me pretending
I'm happy as a waitress.
Caroline, where is Max?
And I've already checked
the bowels of hell.
Yeah, I know where I work.
Max is going to be late today
'cause she got stuck on the subway.
But you said yesterday she was late
because she was stuck on the subway.
No, I believe I said yesterday
she got stuck under the subway.
Oleg, a little help.
Oh, Max?
Today she got stuck on a bus.
And you said that the
day before yesterday.
- Earl?
- She got stuck between the moon
and New York City.
I know it's crazy, but it's true.
Sorry I'm late.
I couldn't find our cat, Nancy.
Also, I was stuck on the
bus or under the subway.
Unless they told you
something different,
then I was doing that.
Oh, come on. That excuse
was less satisfying
than the end of Serial.
Max, really, what do you take me for?
Well, I know where I can't take you.
On the big rides at Disneyland.
Nancy still hasn't come home.
I'm freaking out.
She's the only thing I love.
[gasps]
Whatever.
I had a cat once. He was cool.
He was black and very sexually active.
Oh, wait, the cool cat
I'm talking about was me.
Earl, be careful, at your age,
you could die having sex.
I know.
Those ladies don't know
whether I'm coming or going.
(Peter Bjorn and John)
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
[cash register bell dings]
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
I think Nancy might be gone for good.
I just can't believe she
didn't take me with her.
We had a deal.
Max, she'll come back to the apartment,
even if she doesn't want to.
I mean, I always do.
I am not surprised you're not worried.
You never really liked Nancy.
You call her "that cat."
As in, "that cat" peed on my pillow.
While I was sleeping on it, Max.
Well, blame me. I got her drunk.
Hey, everybody!
Look, girls, I got your
pussy in my purse.
Either that's a cat, or you
two got to keep better track
of your belongings.
Yay!
That cat's back.
See, Max?
I am excited.
[baby talk] Oh, I missed you so much.
Oh, yes, I did.
That's not Nancy.
That is a boy.
Well, Max, sorry I don't
check out a cat's junk
the second it comes through the door.
Yeah, you only look at the face.
That's the difference
between you and me.
See, look, the name tag says "Cinnamon."
No wonder that little girl
kept crying and saying,
"Give me Cinnamon, Give me Cinnamon."
I looked her right in
the eye and I said,
"I don't carry spices in my purse."
Max, you are completely overreacting.
- It's just a...
- Oh! Just a what?
Say it!
- It's just a cat.
- [gasps]
You!
Hey, I'm the one who fronted us
that dollar to get her name tag.
Thanks to me, someone's
gonna pick her up,
look at it, and say,
"Oh, you must be lost,
little... cat."
Nancy! Her name's Nancy!
I know her name!
It got momentarily pushed out of my head
to make room for those
1,600 cupcake T-shirts
we can't unload or pay for.
You think I don't wake up screaming
four or five nights a week
about those T-shirts?
But I know our cat's name.
You don't wake up at night ever.
No, I sleep like a dead
baby, it's my one gift.
[phone rings]
Oh, the phone! [gasps]
Unknown number. This could be it!
I like my numbers like my condom
expiration dates, unknown.
Hello?
- Yes?
- Who is it, Max?
You have her? Yay!
Oh, sure, great.
- Thank you.
- He has her?
He has Nancy?
Please, too little, too late.
Max, we're in $10,000 worth of debt
and you spent money on new kitty litter?
Relax, I'm going to pee in it, too.
Well, I guess it beats
that Sprite bottle
you've been using in your bedroom.
It's just such a long
walk to the bathroom
that every time I have to go,
it's like I'm raising money for MS.
Oh, I have good news.
I found your lost bra in the litter box.
Don't think I'm not still wearing it.
I mean, why not?
I ate a hot dog that rolled
under a car the other day.
I left a couple of big clumps in,
just to help you out a little.
[knock at door]
Oh, okay, that's Nancy.
Here's a chance for a
fresh start for you two.
And don't bring up the bra, we
don't know why she wanted it,
but I'm sure she had her reasons.
Fine, I'll be on my best behavior.
But you watch and see how she treats me.
It's a two-way street.
Hi, I have your cat.
And surprisingly, your doorknob.
Oh, that gum wore out already?
[gasps] Hi, buddy!
Hi, I'm Caroline. This is Max.
Thank you so much for bringing back...
- Nancy!
- I know!
And please note, she did
not even look at me.
Hi. I'm Owen.
Well, we are "Owen" you a big thank-you.
Kind of low on cash, how would you feel
about 1,000 cute cupcake tees?
Yeah, I don't need 1,000 pink T-shirts.
My dad's already mad at me
I don't care about sports.
How do you get this thing open?
We usually just take Nancy around
in an old vacuum cleaner bag.
Also doubles as my "going out" purse.
Pardon me, may I get past?
Oh, manners.
In our doorway?
I don't know what to do.
What's next, a front stoop with
no discarded heroin needles?
Yeah, I just came up there.
Not today.
Here, let me help.
I mean, I'm the dumb one who
paid $2,000 for a cat carrier.
Hmm. I miss being that stupid.
You know, my cat can't
get this open either.
It must be the lack of thumbs.
Rich, funny, and in a suit at 9:00 A.M.?
I really don't know what to do.
You know, my cat,
Dickens, loves your cat.
Oh, Dickens, after the author?
Dickens, after the author, Max.
Yeah, I know who that is.
The guy who wrote
Muppets Christmas Carol.
There. I knew I'd get it.
'Cause I have thumbs.
[baby talk] Oh, there she is.
- [cat meows]
- Yes.
So I take it by the cat, you're single?
Big time.
So, do you and Dickens live alone?
Oh no, she's trying to flirt.
I travel a lot for work.
I'm a venture capitalist.
So you know how it is.
Oh, I do. I absolutely do.
- I...
- Here it comes.
- Went to Wharton.
- Boom.
Well, if she gets lost again,
you know where to find her.
She's been hanging around
outside our window
every day for the last couple of months.
So I let her in. I hope that's okay.
Is that okay? It's awesome.
I hope your girlfriend didn't mind.
We just broke up.
So I'm single.
And I better get going.
I've got a 10:00 meeting.
Max, give the man his case.
He has a 10:00 meeting.
She doesn't want to get
out of cushy this thing.
I totally get it.
I had to be dragged out
of that massage chair
at Brookstone by mall security.
Well, here's my card, just give me a call
when you want me to pick up the case.
You have a card?
A card, a meeting, a suit, a joke?
Are you the next bachelor?
Well, thank you, Owen Charles Boyd,
for bringing back our beloved...
- Her name's Nancy!
- I know her name.
Why do I have to say it so fast?
She's joking, she's just
not as funny as you.
Well, it was nice to meet you.
Bye, Nancy.
Okay.
Yes, I was flirting.
But I was doing it for our business.
You should really be doing
it for your business.
'Cause your business is
going out of business.
He has a card.
And it's not for medical marijuana.
He's a venture capitalist.
That's the kind of fat cat
that can help us get back on our feet.
Speaking of fat cats,
Nancy's looking like
she might need to give Jenny a call.
Hey, girls.
Oh, you found Nancy.
I knew she'd come back pregnant.
Wait, Sophie, how can
you tell she's pregnant
and just not fighting the same
battle Jonah Hill is fighting?
Well, her fur is thicker, she's
got a little sparkle in her eye,
and there's a little kitten head
about to pop out of her patoot.
[Nancy meowing]
Come on. Push, Nancy.
Come on, we all know what you did.
Now is not the time to be shy.
You do know what you're
doing, right, Sophie?
This isn't like the time you told us
you could do your own
bikini wax with a candle?
'Cause I still have the
vanilla-scented scars from that.
Don't worry.
In my village, all the Kuchenskis women
acted as animal midwives.
It was the best way to meet guys.
Strap in, girls.
- [Nancy meowing]
- Ah! She's crowning!
I can't believe it.
I thought Nancy was smarter than this.
But it turns out she's just
like the rest of the women
in my family.
Screwed by some stranger
she met in the dumpster.
Okay, here we go.
[Nancy meowing]
Oh, there goes my ring.
I... sorry, Nancy.
(Sophie) Oh, here we go!
Come on, girls, I need some
hot water and fresh towels.
We do, too. For, like, four years.
Uh...
how about some of these T-shirts?
Oh, sure why not use those?
They used to be our bright future.
Now just a ShamWow
for illegitimate cats.
[Nancy meowing]
Oh, my God, that must be the sound
of a surrendering cat uterus.
Well, it's the first time
a uterus has surrendered
in that bed in a while.
[kittens meowing]
I don't know why I'm not throwing up.
Oh, wait. I'm starting to.
[kittens continue meowing]
Well, I'm off Korean dumplings for life.
This one... this one won't come out.
It's like the Queen Latifah of kittens.
Sophie, I got your text that
you were in bed with Nancy.
Who is this Nancy,
and when did we go back
to doing three-ways?
Nancy's a cat.
Mm, that's a no.
I've got to draw the line somewhere.
Well, I heard the news.
Looks like you two are
grandmothers before you're 30.
Can't say I'm surprised.
Okay, before you even ask,
I don't pay for cat maternity leave.
This isn't Google.
This isn't even Ask Jeeves, Han.
Well, I can help you get
the kittens good homes.
The people in my building are very nice.
Except if you don't recycle one
bottle of sparkling cider,
then nobody talks to
you in the elevator.
Han, we're not giving the kittens away.
Nancy landed herself a rich cat,
we're gonna be living off
a hefty kitty support.
Only you two would be desperate enough
to try and find a sugar catty.
So has Owen called you back yet?
Um, we're trading.
"We're trading"?
"We're trading" is
lonely white girl talk
for "he hasn't called me back."
I can't believe this.
He's a deadbeat dad.
Max, he's just busy.
And I think you might
be projecting a little
because of your dad.
Not that I'm a therapist.
I mean, I can't even afford a couch.
I'm not projecting.
I just know a deadbeat dad
when I don't see one!
Where's his card?
I don't remember where I...
[gasps] Max, let go! I've got this.
That guy can really help
us with our business.
Please, let me handle this.
Look, Ryan Gosling.
[gasps]
- I got this.
Keep going, girls, I'm almost there.
I got this, Max.
And when he comes to
get the cat carrier,
I'll talk to him.
You're way too emotional.
You just went to third
base with my apron.
Sitting on this stoop is nice.
How come we never sit out here?
[gunshots ringing]
[woman shrieking]
There it is.
Oh, please, it's just Rico.
Rico looks good. I think
he got another tattoo.
Look, when Owen gets here,
should we still be alive,
please let me do the talking.
Kittens aside, Owen can help us.
A venture capitalist buys companies
and turns them around.
Yeah, I've seen Pretty Woman.
That's how I realized I
wasn't charging enough.
Go, Max, here he comes.
All right, but I'll be watching
inside from the window.
It's probably better, because
I don't trust Nancy alone
with those kittens.
She's got some serious postpartum.
When I left the room, she
was lighting a Menthol 100
with a shaky paw.
Hi.
Crazy we live walking
distance from each other.
We don't. The Uber driver
wouldn't go past the fire
hydrant on the corner.
The one with the bloody
shoe hanging from it?
That's the one.
[woman screaming]
You know what? I'm just
gonna take the cat carrier.
Before you go...
we have this small cupcake company
that's just begging to be an empire,
and I wanted to pick your brain
about some business stuff.
Okay, so your Dickens
got our cat pregnant,
and she just had five kittens.
And at her age, it's a miracle
we didn't have to pay
for in vitro.
How do you know they are Dickens's?
I'm not saying that Nancy's easy,
it's just, I've seen her go in and out
of a lot of windows.
[police sirens blaring in the distance]
Did he just drop a gun?
It's fine. He has more.
Okay, call my assistant,
you can pick my brain.
I just don't want it
to be off the sidewalk.
Really, I got to go. I can't get killed.
I'm wearing new suede loafers.
Uber, an assistant, and suede loafers?
Are you for real?
I hope I'm not intruding.
No, come in.
I was just brushing my new loafers.
I bought them as a
break-up gift for myself.
But unlike my ex-girlfriend,
these have a sole.
I didn't wanna mention the cat
situation to your assistant.
Next thing you know, it's
all over the lunch room:
Owen Charles Boyd's cat is a raw-dogger.
Said it was an accident.
Didn't feel like one.
One shoe yes, but both?
Highly unlikely.
Owen, sometimes in life, it's
not just an innocent cat
that gets screwed.
A girl can get screwed as well.
Oh, hey, hi. What's happening?
As in, screwed by one
bad business decision.
My partner, Max, and I recently invested
all our savings in...
well, here, take a look.
- [gasps]
- Oh, my coffee!
- Oh.
- My loafer!
My coffee's on my loafer!
Here, let me.
No, you dab. You don't wipe suede.
You dab.
Dab. Dab. I'm sorry.
I used to know that.
That's Rich 101.
Let me just go find some water
and I'll dab, not wipe, this out.
We're not done yet. I'm going back in.
It's going really well though.
Where's water?
Do you know how to unsend an email?
If I did, my rich ex-boyfriend
would've never found out
what I thought of his lisp
and I'd be living in the
"thouth of Franth" right now.
[elevator bell dings]
Where is he?
He needs to see these adorable bastards.
Max, how did you find me here?
I told you I was going
on a "think walk."
I followed you.
I never noticed how much
you check yourself out
in store windows. You have a problem.
Do either of you know a
way to turn the phrase,
"self-absorbed, ridiculous pig"
into a compliment?
If I did, I'd still be
on The Apprentice.
Owen's going to see that email
and I'm going to get fired.
I have to start paying
attention to details.
I'm just gonna go back in.
What? I don't care.
Not without me you're not.
Max, please, let me handle this.
I'm begging you.
We're getting close, look,
I'm holding his shoe.
If he doesn't step up here,
these kittens will feel neglected,
and it is only a matter of time
till they are waitressing or worse.
Max, you're wrong.
There's nothing worse than waitressing.
Max, stop!
You'll ruin everything.
I can fix this and us.
We are beyond help.
It's all about these kittens.
- Now move, I got this.
- No, I got this.
- I got this.
- I...
- [gasps]
Oh, my God.
What the hell is happening?
[kittens meowing]
That's right. I came to your
office with a basket of cats.
Max, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, well, he's the one
who should be sorry.
I want you to look these
kittens in the whiskers
and tell them that Dickens
is not their father.
What makes you think they're mine. Why?
Because they look just like Dickens
when he was a tiny baby kitten.
Oh, and this one's even cuter.
And that one.
I'll take them all.
But not that one. Seems a little off.
Not quite as alert as the others.
Oh, she's not good enough for you?
- Max. Projecting.
- I'm not projecting.
He said she's not good enough for him.
What?
Just because she was unplanned
and not good at math?
Developed boobs way too early?
Okay, fine. I'm projecting.
What is going on?
Caroline, are we gonna hook up or what?
This is, like the
weirdest foreplay ever.
Hook up? What would make you
think I want to hook up?
Oh, because I business flirted?
That's Wharton 101.
It was more than business flirting.
You begged to come to my office,
show up wearing a see-through shirt.
That was not by choice.
It is cheaply made.
I came here to talk to you
about our business,
and possibly get you to invest
in a small, but spirited...
Invest? This is the financial
capital of the world.
[baby talk] Yes, it is.
Why would I invest in a
desperate little cupcake shop?
(both) You!
That's it!
No cats for you.
(Caroline) You know what?
You are a self-absorbed, ridiculous pig.
Says you.
And your assistant.
Check your email.
I was able to unsend it.
Yay!
Yeah, might want to re-ignite
that LinkedIn profile.
You're gonna be home a lot
more, you want a cat?
- [gasps]
[kittens meowing]
Thanks for taking the kittens, Han.
I feel like you have an understanding
of small creatures, being one yourself.
Have no fear, my building
is loaded with lesbians.
They take home rescue cats
faster than they take
home other lesbians.
Okay, let's discuss my terms.
Unlike all my non-animal children,
I want to know they're taken care of.
What part of lesbian
don't you understand?
They'll be swaddled in
a flannel shirt by nightfall.
Okay, now this one, I call Junkie.
'Cause he's got a
serious Catnip problem.
Oh, so you raised a drug
addict within a week.
Sounds about right.
These two should try and stay together.
We call them Game of Thrones One
and Game of Thrones Two.
'Cause they're siblings and lovers.
This one's the boy.
Watch him and learn
what humping looks like.
This one's pretty bland.
She lays around, doesn't meow much,
and when she does, she's
kind of phoning it in.
We call her Amy Adams.
Yep.
This last one gets special attention.
She's the smallest, but
she's got potential.
I mean, look at those nipples.
And now the nipples are all I see.
Have a nice life.
I'll find you on Instagram.
Check out Grumpy Cat.
Do what he does.
Well, bye, kitties.
And remember, stripping isn't dancing.
And now all I can see is
them wearing pasties.
You know what, Max?
We don't need that rich
guy to fix our business.
We can do it ourselves.
Who am I kidding?
Our business is in worse shape
than two retired guys in a golf cart.
Well, you know what we'd better fix?
Nancy.
'Cause he was right, she's a slut.
Someone just found her
69-ing a tabby in the alley.
[cash register bell dings]
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.