Ok...
The X10's are online
Gentlemen, I am now about to send a signal
from this laptop through our local ISP
racing down fibre optic cable at
the speed of light to San Fransisco,
bouncing off a satellite in
geosynchronous orbit to Lisbon, Portugal,
where the data packets will be headed off
to submerge transatlantic cables,
terminating in Halifax, Nova Scotia
and transfered across the continent
via microwave relays back to our ISP
And the extend receiver attached to this...
Lamp.
Look at me, look at me. I've got juice bumps.
- Are we ready for the stereo?
- Go for stereo.
- Hey guys.
- Hello.
It's a little loud.
No problem...
Turning it down.
San Francisco, Lisbon, Halifax...
...et voilà!
- OK, thanks.
- Hang on, hang on. Do you not
realise what we just did?
Yeah, you turned your stereo down with your laptop.
No, we turned our stereo down, by sending
a signal around the world via the Internet.
Oh. You know you can get one of those
universal remotes from Radioshack?
They're really cheap.
No, you don't get it.
Howard,
- Enable public access.
- Public access enabled.
- Boy, that's terrific. I'll see ya.
- No hang on, hang on...
See?
No.
Someone in Sichuan province,
China, is using his computer
to turn our lights on and off.
Oh, that's handy.
Here's a question...
Why?
Because we can.
They found our remote control cars!
- Wait, what's on top of that?
- Wireless webcams, wave hello!
The monster truck is out of Austin, Texas,
and the blue Viper is being operated
from suburban Tel Aviv.
- You may want to put on slacks.
- What?
Ew, stop it! No!
Leave me alone!
- Who's running the red Corvette?
- That would be me.
The Big Bang Theory - Season 1 - Episode 9
You know in the future,
when we're disembodied brains in jars,
we're going to look at this as eight hours well wasted.
I don't want to be in a jar.
I want my brain in an android body.
Eight feet tall and ribbed.
I'm with you.
I just have to make sure if I'm
a synthetic human I'd still be Jewish.
I promised my mother.
I suppose you could have
your android penis circumcised.
But that's something your rabbi
would have to discuss with the manufacturer.
Not to mention you'd have to
power down on saturdays.
Sheldon, why is this letter in the trash?
Well, there's always the possibility that
a trash can spontaneously formed around the letter
but Occam's rasor would suggest
that someone threw it out.
It's from the Institute of
Experimental Physics, they want us to
present our paper on the properties of supersolids
at the topical conference of Bose-Einstein condensates.
I know.
I read it before I threw it out.
Ok, if I may drill down to the bedrock of my question:
why did you throw it out?
Because I have no interest in standing in
the Rose room of the Pasadena Marriot,
in front of a group of judgmental strangers
who wouldn't recognise true genius if
it was standing in front of them giving a speech.
Which if I were there, would be.
I don't know Sheldon.
Those topical conferences on
Bose-Einstein condensates' parties are legendary
- Forget the parties!
- Forget the parties? What a nerd.
Are there any other honours I've got that I don't know about?
Did the UPS dropped off a
Nobel prize with my name on it?
Leonard, please don't take this the wrong way,
but the day you win a Nobel prize,
is the day I begin my research on the drag coefficient of tassles on flying carpets.
the only thing missing from that insult was: "your mama".
I got one...
Hey Leonard,
- Your mama's research methodology is so flawed...
- Shut up, Howard.
- Sheldon, we have to do this.
- No, we don't.
We have to take a nourishment, to expel waste,
and inhale enough oxygen to keep our cells from dying.
Everything else is optional.
Ok, let me put it this way:
I'm doing it.
You can't. I'm the lead author.
Come on, the only reason you're the lead author is because we went alphabetically.
I let you think we went alphabetically to spare you
the humiliation with dealing with the fact that it was my idea.
Now to put too fine a point to it, but I was throwing you a bone.
You're welcome.
Excuse me, I designed the experiment that proved the hypothesis.
That doesn't mean proving.
So the entire scientific community is just supposed to take your word?
They're not supposed to, but they should.
Alright, I don't care what you say.
I'm going to the conference and
I'm presenting our findings
And I forbid it.
You forbid it?
If I'm not taking credit for our work then nobody is.
- So, you admit that it's our work.
- No.
Once again, I'm throwing
you a bone.
And once again, you are welcome.
So, how's it going with Sheldon?
Are you guys still not talking to each other?
Not only is he still not talking to me,
but there's this thing he does where he stares
at you and  tries to get your brain to explode.
You know, like in the classic sci-fi movie "Scanners"?
Like.... Bzzz.
Nevermind.
How about this one?
It says, I know my physics, but I'm still a fun guy.
Oh, I didn't know they still made corduroy suits.
They don't, that's why I saved this one.
Ok, well, let's just see what else you have.
Ok, here. Take this.
and this, and this,
and this, and these...
Is this all stuff you want me to try on?
No, this is stuff I want you to throw out.
Seriously, don't even give it to charity,
you won't be helping anyone.
What's this?
That's the bottled city of Kandor.
You see, Kandor was the
capital city of the planet Krypton.
It was miniaturised by Brainiac before Krypton exploded
and then rescued by Superman.
Oh, nice.
It's a lot cooler when girls aren't looking at it.
Here, why don't you put these while I find
a shirt and a sport cut match.
Right, be right back.
Where are you going? Just put them on.
Here?
Oh, are you shy?
- No, I'm not shy.
- Don't worry I won't look.
I know you won't look.
Why would you look?
There's nothing to see...
Well, not 'nothing'...
Sweetie, put the pants on.
So, you know, isn't there maybe
some way you and Sheldon could
- compromise on this whole presentation thing?
- No, No.
Scientists do not compromise.
Our minds are trained to synthetize facts
and come to inarguable conclusions.
Not to mention, Sheldon is back-crap crazy.
What is this?
Oh, careful.
That's my original series Battlestar Galactica flight suit.
Oh, why didn't you wear it on Halloween?
Because it's not a costume, it's a flight suit.
Ok, alright, moving on.
Oh, wow. A paisley shirt.
It goes with my corduroy suit.
if you mean it should end up in
the same place, then I agree.
Is this your only tie?
Technically, yes. But, if you'll notice...
It's reversible!
So it works as two.
Sweetie, I don't even think it works as one.
- Is this all your clothes?
- Eh, yeah.
Everything since the eighth grade.
- The eighth grade?
- My last growth sprout
Ok, well, let's go back to the curdoroy suit.
- Great.
- Yeah.
I said no. Put it down.
Hey Sheldon.
Hello Penny.
Get anything good?
Just the latest copy of
Applied Particle Physics quarterly.
Oh, you know, that is so weird
that yours came and mine didn't.
It was a joke.
Yep.
Tip you waitresses.
I'm here all week.
Penny, just to save you from further awkwardness,
know that I'm perfectly comfortable with
the two of us climbing the stairs in silence.
Oh, yeah ok, me too. Zip it, lock it.
Put it in your pocket.
- So, you and Leonard...
- Oh dear God...
Little misunderstanding, huh?
A little misunderstanding...?
Galileo and the Pope had a little misunderstanding.
Anyway, I was talking to Leonard this morning
and I think he feels really bad about it.
How do you feel?
I don't understand the question.
I'm just asking if it's difficult
to be fighting with your best friend.
I haven't thought about it like that.
I wonder if I've been experiencing physiological manifestations
of some sort of unconscious emotional turmoil
Wait, what?
I couldn't poop this morning.
You should just talk to him,
I'm sure you guys can work this out.
- Certainly preferable to my plan.
- Which was?
A powerful laxative.
You absolutely should talk to him.
Look, I know Leonard values you
as a friend and he told me himself
without your little idea there's no way
he could come up with this whole experiment thing.
Excuse me. "Little idea"?
Yeah, I mean he tried to explain it to me,
- I didn't really understand it but...
- Of course you didn't.
He said: "Little idea"?
Oh, well, no...
Not...
- Not in those words.
- In what words then, exactly?
Oh, you know... Gee. The exact words are...
It's more the spirit in which he said...
- What did he say?
- You had a lucky hunch
Hey, Sheldon, I've been thinking, instead of arguing about this...
Don't you ever speak to me again.
What...?
Ok, I'm leaving for the conference.
Have fun presenting my "lucky hunch"
Shel, I didn't mean it like that.
- Then why did you say it?
- I don't know, I wasn't...
- Were you trying to impress Penny?
- No, no, not at all. A little bit.
How did that work out for you?
- Leonard, ready to go?
- Libido: 1 Truth: 0.
Ok, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
We did the work together,
let's present the paper together.
And I'm telling you for the last time,
it's pandering, it's undignifying, and bite me.
Let's go.
- Bye Sheldon.
- Goodbye Penny.
One of these days... bshh!
There you go.
You're right this side does look better.
No, no, I didn't say better, I said "less stained".
I just checked the house.
There's probably 20-25 people in there.
- You're kidding!
- Is that all?
"All?"
In particle physics 25 is Woodstock!
- Then good!
- I wasn't expecting such a crowd,
I'm all nervous.
It's ok, just open with a joke,
you'll be fine.
A joke... Ok.
How about this? Um, ok...
There's this farmer
and he has these chickens but they won't lay any eggs, so...
he calls a physicist to help.
The physicist then does some calculations,
and he says: "I have a solution,
but it only works for spherical chickens in a vacuum".
Right?
Oh, sorry, I just had heard it before.
- Let's roll. Hey, nice suit.
- It's a classic, right?
I really should have brought my own car.
So, in conclusion,
the data show that at temperatures approaching absolute zero,
the moment of inertia changes, and a solid becomes a supersolid,
which clearly appears to be a previously unknown state of matter.
Thank you!
- Are there any questions?
- Yeah.
What the hell was that?
Any other questions?
Doctor Sheldon Cooper here, I am
the lead author of this particular paper.
Thank you.
And you sir, you have completely skipped
over the part where I was walking through the park
and I saw these children on a
merry-go-round which started me thinking
about the moment of inertia in gases like helium
at temperatures approaching absolute zero.
I didn't skip it. It's just
an anecdote, it's not science.
Oh, I see. It was
the apple falling on Newton's head,
- was that just an anecdote?
- You are not Isaac Newton.
No, no, that's true. Gravity
would have been apparent to me without the apple.
You cannot possibly be that arrogant.
You continue to underestimate me,
my good man.
Look, if you weren't happy with my presentation
then maybe you should have given it with me!
As I have explained repeatedly,
unlike you,
I don't need validation from lesser minds.
No offense.
Really, so why did you come?
Because I knew you'd screw this up.
I didn't screw it up!
Oh, please. I admit that spherical
chicken joke,
- that was hilarious.
- Thank you.
But it was straight downhill from there.
I've had enough of your condescendship.
Maybe I didn't go to college
when I was 11 like you.
Maybe I got my doctorate at
24 instead of 16
but you are not the only person
who is smarter than
everyone else in this room!
No offense.
And I am clearly not the only person
who is tormented by insecurity
and has an ego in need of constant validation!
So you admit you're an egotist?
Yes!
My name is doctor Leonard Hofstadter
and I can never please my parents so
I need all my self esteem
from strangers like you!
But he's worse!
Ok, that's it!
Stop it!
You cannot blow up my head
with your mind!
Then I'll settle for your aneurism!
- Stop it!
- You hit me!
You saw that he hit me!
You tried to blow up my head!
So it was working!
It wa... It was not!
You're a nutcase!
We'll see about that!
Heads up, you people in the front row!
This is a splash zone!
Stop it!
Just quit it!
Is this usually how these physics things go?
More often than you think.
You could have offered me a ride home.
You're lucky I didn't run you over.
I really don't understand what you're so unhappy about.
You begged me to come, I came.
There's just no pleasing you.
You're right, I'm the problem,
I'm the one that needs help.
Well, that's not much of
an apology but I'll take it.
Excuse me,
is there anything you would apologise for?
Yes.
I'm sorry I tried to blow up your head.
It was uncalled for.
You won't believe this.
Somebody got the whole thing with their
cell phone and put it on YouTube!
What?
- Who would do that?
- That would be me.
Hey, check it out,
it's a featured video!
He hit me!
You saw that he hit me!
[i]You tried to blow up my head![/i]
- Then it was working!
- It was not working! You're a nutcase!
We will see about that!
You people in the front row
heads up!
This is splash zone
Stop it! Leave it,
leave it!
You want a volcano nerve pinch!
You should clip your fingernails!
Those hurt!
Oh, Jeez. does this suit really look that bad?
Forget your suit,
look at my arms waving.
I'm like a flamingo on Ritalin.
Howard,
would you like to explain to me
why your Facebook page
has a picture of me sleeping
on your shoulder
captioned "me and my girlfriend"?
Uh oh, here comes
the talk.
- You hit me!
- You tried to blow up my head!
- So it was working!
- It was not working! You're a nutcase!
We will see about that!