All right,
that's the last servo.
Behold the Mobile
Omnidirectional Neutralization
and Termination Eradicator.
Or...MONTE.
Featuring one articulated razor-sharp
killing saw,one polycarbonate grinding
and flipping wheel,
steel-armor plate exoskeleton
top and bottom,and enough horsepower to drive
a 110 pounds of mechanized death
from zero to holy crap
in 4.8 seconds.
Is it wrong to say I
love our killer robot?
As with my father,
I both love and fear it.
All right, enough chitchat.
Let's destroy something.
1,2,3
Okay. What shall be first
to taste the wrath of Monte?
*************
**************
Did it when I was four.
It's an icosahedral dye
floating in tinted blue water.
Man, call "spoiler alert"
before you say things like that.
How about the toaster oven?
What did the toaster
oven ever do to you?
What did I ever do to Jimmy
Mullins in the third grade?
He still punched me in
the face with my own fists.
Sorry, you little nerd, you were just in
the wrong boys' room at the wrong time.
Gentlemen, goggles.
This is an auspicious moment.
Like Robert Oppenheimer
or Neil Armstrong,
we need the appropriate words to
mark this historic scientific event.
How about "Die, toaster, die"?
That'll do it.
All right, what's next?
No, I think I'm just going to
stay in tonight and do laundry.
Oh, yeah, this door got the full Monte.
Leonard?
What the hell?
Killer robot. We built it.
Yeah, well, it almost killed me.
If it wanted to kill you, you'd be dead.
So, who exactly does it want to kill?
I'm sorry, are you unaware of the upcoming Southern
California Robot Fighting League Round Robin Invitational?
You know, since I moved last year,
not all my mail has been forwarded.
It's a big deal.
There's an awards banquet
and a dance afterward.
Perhaps you'd like to come with me.
I know the other fellas would be
really excited to see a girl there.
How is it supposed to be a
dance if I'm the only girl?
Well, that may be a slight exaggeration.
You'd be the only doable girl.
You're a pig, Howard.
How is "doable" anything
but a compliment?
Howard, why don't we
just work on the robot?
Please, Leonard, not now.
Once again, Penny and I
have begun our little tango.
Our tango?
The carnal repartee,
the erotic to and fro.
But as delicious as
the appetizer might be,
at some point we will have to succumb
and eat the entr\e while it's still...
hot.
I'm begging you, stop talking.
Look, normally I can just ignore you.
I mean, I get it--
you're a little peculiar.
You know, like Sheldon.
Excuse me, Penny, but in this
room, you're the one who's peculiar.
Yeah, you might be right.
But back to you.
I know you think you're some sort
of smooth-talking ladies' man,
but the truth is, you are
just pathetic and creepy.
So what are you saying?
I am saying it is not a
compliment to call me "doable."
It's not sexy to stare
at my ass and say, Ooh,
it must be jelly 'cause
jam don't shake like that.
And most important, we are not dancing
a tango, we're not to'ing and fro'ing.
Nothing is ever going to
happen between us. Ever.
Wait a minute. This isn't
flirting. You're serious.
Flirting? You think
I'm flirting with you?
I am not flirting with you.
No woman is ever gonna flirt with you.
You're just gonna
grow old and die alone.
Thanks for the heads up.
Howard, where you going?
I'm going home to live
my creepy, pathetic life.
Well, someone had to say it.
What?
He said maybe we should enter you
in the killer robot competition.
Howard, the phone is ringing!
Here's a crazy idea, Ma: Answer it!
Hello?
All right, hold on.
It's your friend, Leonard!
He wants to know why
you're not at school today!
I don't go to school, Ma.
I work at a university.
That's a school! Now pick up the phone!
I don't want to talk to anybody.
Should I ask Leonard to
bring over your homework? !
I don't have homework.
I'm a grown man with a
master's degree in engineering!
Excuse me, Mr. Fancy-Pants.
Want me to get you a Popsicle?
Cherry, please!
I ate the cherry. All
that's left is green.
You make me want to kill myself.
What's going on?
I don't know, now they're
just yelling about Popsicles.
Sounds like Penny really got to him.
I'm not surprised.
Despite his hard and crusty shell,
Howard is a very sensitive man.
Do you know he writes poetry?
Mostly about men from Nantucket
and hermits named Dave,
but he does it with real sensitivity.
Hey, Hofstadter.
Word around the pwasma
wab is you built a wobot?
Yes, we did, Kripke.
His name is Monte.
Well, if you have any dewusions
about entering him against my wobot,
the Kwipke Kwippler in the Southern California
Robot Fighting League Wound Wobin Invitational,
aka the S.C.R.F.L.R.R.I.,
his name is gonna be Swrap Metal.
Come on, is that really necessary?
Leonard, I believe it is.
This is trash talk, and trash talk is a
traditional component in all sporting events.
Kripke, your robot is inferior
and it will be defeated by ours
because ours exceeds yours
in both design and execution.
Also, I'm given to understand
that your mother is overweight.
Oh, snap.
Now, of course, if that is the result of a
glandular condition and not sloth and gluttony,
I withdraw that comment.
What difference does
it make? Fat is fat.
There are boundaries.
Tell you what, forget
the S.C.R.F.L.R.R.I.
Wet's settle this woboto a woboto.
What do you mean?
There's no guarantee we're gonna go
against each other in the Wound Wobin,
so let's throw down.
You know, unless you're afwaid.
We accept your challenge.
Name a time and place.
Tomorrow, 3:00, the kinetics wab.
Make it so.
No, don't make it so. Barry,
we can't fight you tomorrow.
Our engineer is incapacitated.
What's wrong with him?
He's depressed because he's pathetic
and creepy and can't get girls.
We're all pathetic and
cweepy and can't get girls.
That's why we fight wobots.
If you're not there, you'll
be exposed to widicule.
I'm curious, what part of
America is that accent from?
Hey, you got a minute?
Yeah, come on in. What's up?
- I need you to apologize to How...
- Get out.
Come on. Wolowitz won't come out of his
house and we need him for a robot battle.
Well, then have the
robot go and get him.
The robot didn't hurt his feelings.
His feelings needed to be hurt.
He's been in bed for two days.
Yeah, probably with a blow-up doll.
He's not with a...
Does it really matter
who or what he's with?
The guy is devastated.
Oh, please, how could I
possibly devastate Howard?
Okay, don't take this as a criticism,
but you kind of have that
overexposed-to-gamma-rays thing going on.
What does that mean?
You know, like, most of the time,
you're the easygoing Bruce Banner,
but then, when you get angry, you
kind of turn into, like, you know...
I turn into a bear?
Seriously? Gamma rays? Bruce Banner?
You didn't get The
Incredible Hulk from that?
Never mind. Just, please go talk to him.
And say what? That I didn't
mean it, because I meant it.
Well, maybe you can go at it
from a different angle, like, um,
you see a glimmer of goodness in
him and you only said what you said
because you want to nurture
it and make it shine.
Okay, let's try it this way.
Remember the day that we first met
and you asked me to go to your
boyfriend's apartment to get your TV back
and he was nine feet tall and he
took my pants off and you said...
What was that? What did you say?
Oh, yes. You said you owed me one.
Okay, come on, that's not fair.
I came home with no pants.
Fine, I'll go over there tomorrow.
Thank you.
I should probably give you
a heads up about his mother.
What about her?
She's a delightful
woman. You'll love her.
Howard, there's a blonde
girl, Patsy, here to see you!
Who?
Okay, now she's saying it's Penny.
I don't want to talk to her.
Ma!
She ran past me.
Was I supposed to tackle her?
So, I just came by to
see how you were doing.
I'm fine.
Good. Your mom seems nice.
People move away from her on the bus.
What do you want?
Okay, look. Howard, I
just want to apologize.
For some things that I have said.
About you.
I've been informed
that you have feelings.
And apparently, I have hurt them.
So, I'm sorry.
Howard.
Fine. You're sorry. Good-bye.
So... you're okay?
Hey, I'm a big boy.
I'm not traumatized by some random
comment from some random woman.
I mean, get over yourself.
Okay. Well, bye.
So close.
Oh, my God. That's Kripke's robot?
As you can see, the Kwippler is
weducing the Chevy Cavawier to wubble.
I can't watch anymore.
Sheldon, we have to call it off.
We don't have that option.
We've accepted the challenge.
We can't run away from a fight.
Oh, please, we've spent our whole
lives running away from fights.
Personally, I can squeeze through
a hole in a fence half my size.
Impressive as that may
be, Monte is not us.
Monte has no fear.
Sheldon, did we all not
just watch the same video?
Kripke's robot just had angry
sex with a mid-sized automobile.
You are overlooking the fact that
we now know what we're up against
and we can modify Monte
so that he's prepared.
You want to prepare him?
Install a bladder and a pair
of shorts so he can wet himself.
Excuse me, but how are we going to
make any modifications without Wolowitz?
- Have you heard from Penny yet?
- Not yet.
Have faith, gentlemen.
We don't need Wolowitz.
Engineering is merely the slow
younger brother of physics.
Watch and learn.
Do either of you know
how to open the toolbox?
And then, when I was
14, I met Marcy Grossman.
She was so beautiful.
She just got her braces off but
they left a little of the overbite.
It was so hot.
Like a sexy little chipmunk.
I didn't have the
courage to ask her out,
but I dedicated a song to her
at the ninth grade talent show.
Aw, that sounds sweet.
* Marcy Grossman is sunshine *
* On a cloudy day *
* When it's cold outside *
* Marcy Grossman is the month of May *
Oh, it's cute.
* I guess you'd say *
* What can make me feel this way *
* Marcy Grossman, Marcy
Grossman, Marcy Grossman *
* Talkin' 'bout Marcy * That's great.
* Grossman.*
Oh, it's fun.
And then she came up with
that sexy little chipmunk mouth
and spit in my hair.
Which brings us to tenth grade.
Howard, do you think maybe
sometimes you try too hard?
Look at me.
What chance do I have
if I don't try too hard?
Well... you'd have a terrific chance.
I mean, you're smart, you're
funny. You have a cool job.
You build stuff that
goes into outer space.
I guess.
Look, I'm telling you, I've known
you for, like, a year and a half
and this is the first time I feel
like I'm talking to a real person.
And you know what? I
like him. He's a nice guy.
You really think so?
Yes.
I don't know.
I do.
Nice little bot you've got here.
I'm aware.
- What's this do, spin?
- Yep. At 3400 RPM.
It can cut through
steel like it was wubber.
Neat.
Good work.
Sheldon, we've got to call this off.
No, Leonard.
For years, merciless thugs like Kripke have
made my life a series of painful noogies
and humiliating wedgies and the
insensitively named Indian burns.
That stops now.
But, Sheldon, we don't have a chance.
The only improvement you were able to make on the
robot was to put fresh batteries in the remote.
What you fail to realize is
Kripke suffers from a fatal flaw:
overconfidence from his robot's
massive size and its overwhelming power.
That's not overconfidence.
That's observation.
Trust me, Kripke will fall easy prey
to my psychological warfare. Observe.
Kripke.
I would ask if your robot is prepared to
meet its maker, but as you are its maker,
clearly the two of you have met.
What is his pwoblem?
Way to bust out the
Jedi mind tricks, dude.
I just want to make sure
that we're all clear.
Standard robotic fighting
league rules apply.
Are you cwazy? This is a stweet fight.
The stweet has no rules.
He's right, Leonard. The
paradigm is to the death.
I will, however, give you the
opportunity to concede my superiority now
and offer me your robot
as the spoils of war.
Never.
I'd rather see Monte
dead than in your hands.
That could be easily arranged.
Ready, set, go?
Do it.
All right then. Weady. Set. Go.
Come on, Sheldon, you got this.
Indeed. We are prepared for
anything he can throw at us.
That's new.
- Run, Monte, run!
- Go, Monte!
- Monte!
- Go, go, go, go!
Don't hurt us, don't
hurt us, don't hurt us!
Well, so much for making up for
the emotional wounds of childhood.
I did this.
Monte was killed by
my hubris and my pride.
No matter what anybody
says, this is my fault.
No one's arguing with you, dude.
I got your text. How bad is... Oy.
Forget the robot. What happened to you?
He slipped and fell.
Yes, I slipped and
fell. In the bathroom.
Bounced right off the tub.
Yes, now he knows what bathtubs are capable of
doing when you don't treat them with respect.
Yeah.
They sucker punch you
when your eyes are closed.
So what do you think, Howard?
It's not that bad, right?
Oh, no. A little electrical tape,
some solder... Are you insane?
I've seen space probes that crashed into the
desert that were in better shape than this.
You're right. Monte's gone.
We'll bury him in the morning.
A simple ceremony. I'll speak.
Leonard, you'll play your cello.
Sheldon, honey, aren't you
getting a little carried away?
I mean, it's just a toy robot.
Just a toy robot?
Penny.
I know, I got it.
Sheldon, I'm sorry.
Well, don't get the wrong idea.
The way I see it, I'm
halfway to pity sex.