Previously on Why Women Kill..
They pumped my stomach.
I'm not paying for that.
Not when a good burp
would've saved you.
NAOMI:
I've known for some time
about Karl's indiscretions.
I was picking up
my dry cleaning,
and there was his car,
parked across the street
at some seedy motel.
You still want
to make love to me?
- Yeah.
- I'm free today at 4:00.
Where should we go?
You're a man now;
figure it out.
There's no way I'm getting
into your mobile sex den.
You seem, uh... energized.
Do I?
Have you embarked on
a new exercise regimen?
I plan on working out
as often as I can.
ELI: The other day,
she was going on and on
about how much
she liked my movie.
You know what? We've already
got an open marriage...
I'll ask her for a three-way.
If she says no...
She says yes.
Oh, my God.
You in love with her?
TAYLOR:
You've been insecure lately
- because of your career.
- Are you in love with her?
No.
BETH ANN:
Has your married man
ever told you
why he feels the need to cheat?
He was bored with his wife.
SHEILA: It's a manual.
For married couples.
These are dirty pictures.
They're scientific.
(whispering):
I have to concentrate.
Ow, ow, ow!
Rob, please don't go.
This has been
an awkward night.
I need to make an appearance.
They must be important clients.
Don't wait up.
(door closes)
♪ ♪
♪ L is for the way you look ♪
♪ At me ♪
♪ O is for the only one ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ V is very, very ♪
♪ Extraordinary ♪
♪ E is even more ♪
♪ Than anyone
that you adore can ♪
♪ Love is all ♪
♪ That I can give to you ♪
♪ Love is more ♪
♪ Than just a game for two ♪
♪ Two in love can make it ♪
♪ Take my heart
and please don't break it ♪
♪ Love was made ♪
♪ For me and you... ♪
(tango music playing)
It begins quite slowly.
With a look.
Or a gesture.
And once the invitation
is accepted...
The tango begins.
It is a dance of anticipation.
- Seduction.
- Desire.
And love.
You know, some say
it takes two to tango.
But sometimes,
lurking in the dark...
Is a third.
Now, if you choose
to dance with him,
be prepared to deal
with the consequences.
For passion can
turn to jealousy.
Love can become violent.
Yes. The tango exists
to remind us
the greatest love stories...
End in death.
(gasping)
Just a reminder,
I've got that project
due tomorrow.
So you'll be working late again?
Afraid so.
Sorry, honey.
What are your big
plans for the day?
Oh, nothing interesting.
Need to drop by
the dry cleaners.
After that, I'll go
to the market for some shopping.
And then I might have lunch
with a new friend.
This is your phone number.
Oh, I thought
you should have it,
now that we're getting
to be chums.
This way,
if you ever need someone
to go with you to the movies...
I can call you up. Got it.
Now, I rent a room
from a lovely couple.
The wife's name
is also Sheila.
- Oh.
- So,
if you call and she answers...
Then I'll ask
for the other Sheila.
Exactly. Busy this week?
Uh, my schedule is pretty open,
except for tonight.
I have a date.
(laughs)
With your married man?
He finished some big project
at work. To celebrate,
he got us reservations
at this really fancy night club.
He's taking you out?
In public?
For the first time.
It's like an actual boyfriend.
(laughs)
Isn't that nice?
(kissing, moaning)
(laughs)
(chuckles)
What are you smiling about?
Oh, the absurdity of it all.
I'm having the best sex
of my life
in the back of a catering van.
Well, maybe when Mr. Grove
moves out,
we could start
doing this in your bed.
Yes...
So, about that...
Karl may be staying in my home
longer than we discussed.
How much longer? A week?
Longer.
Two weeks?
He won't be leaving until
after my daughter's wedding.
(stammers)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
(chuckles)
That's two months away.
Well, I don't mind the van.
No, that's-that's not the point.
Simone, he cheated
on you with men.
Why would you let him stay
for five more seconds?
Well, I tried to throw him out.
- And he wouldn't go?
- He said that if I made him leave,
he would tell all my
friends he was gay
and embarrass me
before the wedding.
So he's threatening you?
No, it's just
a little light blackmail.
All right.
I'll take care of this.
What does that mean?
Nothing. I'm just gonna convince
him that he's making a mistake.
(gasps)
That's adorable.
Hey, I'm serious.
Please, let me help.
Absolutely not.
I'm not gonna break any bones.
I'm just gonna
bend some stuff.
Tommy, how do you expect our
secret affair to remain secret
once you've been
arrested by the police
for beating up my husband?
I was just spitballing.
Well, I appreciate
the passion,
but save it for the van.
I'd still love
to meet Karl alone
in a dark alley some night.
Careful.
He might enjoy that.
Yes. Um, no, I understand,
it's just that I've been through
the deposition twice
and I couldn't
find anything useful.
- (electric guitar playing)
- Eli.
Eli.
- Oh, hey.
- Yes.
I will check again.
- Sure.
- (strumming guitar)
What's that?
Got it this morning.
It's pretty sweet, right?
Uh, don't you already
have a guitar?
Yeah, no, honey, this is a bass.
Five strings, it sounds
totally different. Check it out.
♪ ♪
- Very cool.
- Yeah.
- Oh, are you going to the kitchen?
Could you grab me a soda?
Sure.
With the, the crushy ice?
- Mm-hmm.
- Love you.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Hey.
Hey. Did you hear the big news?
Eli bought a bass.
Oh, I heard.
He thinks it's gonna help him
work through his writer's block.
Great. That's how he ended up
with his other guitar,
the Xbox and the elliptical.
Got it.
So, how was your day?
Mm.
It was crazy busy. I didn't
even get a chance to eat lunch.
Oh, God, you have to try this.
Here.
It's hot. Careful.
Mmm.
- That's amazing.
- It's good, right?
Yeah. So, did Eli get
any work done today?
I'm not sure.
I was running errands.
- Why don't you ask him?
- No.
If I ask Eli,
"Did you get any writing done?"
what he hears is,
"nag, nag, nag, nag, nag."
- Ah.
- I'm just gonna say nothing and be supportive.
This is my supportive smile.
Tell me what you think.
It's terrifying.
(both chuckle)
Hey, I have an idea.
After dinner, let's go dancing.
- Tonight?
- Yeah. There's this new club
in Silver Lake
I've been dying to check out.
I have a lot of reading
to do for work.
Oh, come on.
You've been so stressed,
and I can't remember
the last time
we went dancing together.
I could use some alone time,
just you and me.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
So we can go clubbing?
- Clubbing?
- Eli.
Thought you were
playing your bass.
grabbing me a soda.
I was getting to it.
So you guys
are going clubbing, huh?
(soda can clicks)
Yeah. Yeah, we are.
All right. I'm in.
Eli, you don't dance.
I dance. In my way.
When you dance, you're
in everyone's way.
Oh...
(chuckles)
What? You guys really
don't want me to come?
No. No, no, no.
We'd love for you
to come. Right?
Absolutely.
Whoa. Creepy smile.
(chuckles)
(sighs)
Karl?
NAOMI:
There she is.
Naomi.
(chuckles)
Did we have plans?
No, I just popped in
with a question.
Karl said you went
to the post office,
and so I waited.
For an hour.
Yes. We need
to talk about
the entertainment
for the benefit.
Benefit.
(gasps)
For the burn victims.
Oh, my God.
I forgot all about it.
Simone, you're in charge
of the decorations.
It's fine. I ordered
everything weeks ago.
My mind's been elsewhere
because of recent events.
Are you still up
for your number?
Simone promised the two of
you would reprise your dance.
From the country
club's talent show.
Oh, did she?
I'm not sure I'm up for it now,
given recent events.
Well, if you don't
do something,
Ida Ford is threatening
to sing opera.
Oh, darling. Haven't the burn
victims suffered enough?
All right.
We'll perform.
I'm so glad.
And remember:
if you ever need
to talk about anything,
I am always here.
Yes. You certainly seem to be.
- (Naomi chuckles)
- (door closes)
Why did you let her inside?
I'm the one
who should be miffed.
Why didn't you tell me
Naomi saw my car at a motel?
We're lucky that's all she saw.
If she knew
you were having
anonymous sex
with strange men...
It was never anonymous.
And only a few of them
were strange.
(gasps)
I am not the audience
for that joke.
- What are you doing?
- Benefit's in two days.
We need to rehearse.
Ugh, what was I thinking?
I can't dance with you,
I'm still furious.
You'll forget all about that
when we're the center
of attention,
drowning in applause.
Stop trying to charm your way
back into my heart.
It won't work.
Now, you see,
I think you've forgotten
how much fun we have together.
And I am determined
to remind you.
Why are you trying so hard
to hold onto me?
Because I love you, my darling.
- (tango begins playing)
- Well, I'm not sure that's enough.
Well, try this on
for size.
I actually like you.
How many of your husbands
can say that?
♪ ♪
(dance music playing)
Oh, hey. Ooh, thanks.
Oh, crap.
What? What's wrong?
I think I just saw
my agent.
Lamar's here?
Why don't you go say hi?
No, he's just gonna
give me a hard time
about finishing the script.
There's an easy way
to get him off your back.
- What's that?
- Finish your script.
This kind of attitude is why
I introduce you to people
as my first wife.
Yeah, that's funny.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I just really want
to dance with you right now.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- WOMAN: Jade!
Oh, my God!
Wischa! Oh, my God!
(laughing)
Did she say "Wischa"?
- I think so.
- You guys.
These are my friends,
Willow and Mischa.
Wischa. Ah, I get it.
This is, uh, Taylor and Eli.
How do you two know Jade?
- Oh...
- (all laugh)
We met her last year.
Oh, and it was
love at first sight.
JADE:
Oh, my God, you guys!
Girl, you look
fucking amazing.
Mmm, when fucking
doesn't she?
Fucking never.
(laughing)
I'm getting the feeling that we
weren't Jade's first threesome.
Mm-hmm.
I don't get it.
Why would you want
to start palling around
with this tramp?
Because I want to stop her
from seeing my husband.
And how is buying her
popcorn at the Rialto
gonna make that happen?
I'm trying to
establish trust.
If a stranger came up and
said your dress was ugly,
what would you say?
I'd say fuck off.
But if a dear friend
gently suggested
orange is not
your best color?
I'd get rid of the dress.
If I'm to convince April
it's not in her
best interest
to date a married man,
first I must become
her confidant.
Her close advisor.
Okay.
So when does this
new friendship
- begin to blossom?
- Tonight.
I thought Rob was taking her
to the club tonight.
Do you honestly think I'm
going to let that happen?
(chuckles)
- (elevator bell dings)
- You all right?
- No, I'm nervous.
- Why?
Everyone we know
will be in this room tonight.
You've dazzled them all
a hundred times.
Because I knew how much
they envied me.
They'd laugh in my face if
they knew the truth about us.
Here's a thought.
Don't tell them.
People will be able
to figure it out.
Do you honestly believe
we're the only couple here
pretending to be something
that we're not?
- No.
- Trust me,
there is not a woman
here tonight
who wouldn't trade
all of her problems for yours
if she looked
half as beautiful
as you do right now.
But what good is
other people's envy
if it's all based on a lie?
- (elevator bell dings)
- I'm not sure.
Let's find out.
(lively music playing)
Simone!
You look stunning.
And you look like a teenager.
- How do you get your skin so soft?
- Oh!
(whispering)
It's called a chemical peel.
I know. One more
and she'll be
the Phantom of the Opera.
- Simone!
- Darling. Hello, Barclay.
Sandy, you're out of rehab.
Don't worry, I'll be back.
(chuckles)
- Maybe I should go and find our table.
- No need.
I've arranged for us all
to sit here.
Together? What fun.
I think this is a good time
to find the bar.
Liquor's on it's way,
Simone, brought to you by
the most adorable waiter
at the party.
Wine, Mrs. Grove?
Tommy.
You're our waiter?
Yes, Mrs. Grove.
Mr. Grove.
Hello.
Shall we, darling?
So, Mischa, what do
you guys do for a living?
Oh, uh, we're influencers.
Influencers?
On Instagram.
We're sort of famous.
Are you?
Yeah, it's called
@UnderwearEverywhere.
All these underwear brands
pay us stupid money
- to post pictures wearing their stuff.
- (chuckles)
At famous landmarks,
like, all over the world.
Yo, check it.
TAYLOR:
Oh, wow.
And the Taj Mahal people,
they were okay with that?
Ah, we were in and out
lickety-split.
We had the best time.
We've missed you,
little Jade.
Oh, I missed you.
So, um, how long
are you guys here?
We leave tomorrow night
for Venice.
- No.
- Oh, so soon.
Oh, that sucks.
I was hoping I'd have more time
to hang out with you guys.
Yeah, it sucks.
- Wait, Mischa.
- What?
I just had an idea.
I know what you're thinking,
and it's fucking brilliant.
What are you thinking?
Come with us to Venice tomorrow.
- Oh, my God.
- Tomorrow? Really?
Yeah, it would be so much fun.
Well...
She doesn't have
a plane ticket.
Our assistant can
take care of that.
- You guys have an assistant?
- BOTH: Yeah.
Guys, come on,
it's such short notice.
That'll cost a fortune.
Oh, please, we've got
tons of miles.
- JADE: Really?
- WILLOW: Yeah.
Do you have
a current passport?
I think so, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Um, hold on.
You can't just leave
the country on a whim.
It's irresponsible.
Okay, Mom.
Geez, calm down.
Excuse me?
- (dance music blaring)
- Oh, my God!
Oh... this song is my jam!
Guys, let's dance.
Come on.
- Yeah, let's dance.
- All right, let's do it.
Come on.
Let's go, bro.
- Me? Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
I'm going with him. So...
♪ ♪
(phone ringing)
Stanton speaking.
Rob, it's me.
Well, this is a nice surprise.
I don't mean to bother,
but I'm making tuna casserole
for dinner.
Do you prefer bread crumbs
or not?
Honey, I told you
I'm working late tonight.
Oh. Did I forget?
Yeah, our deadline for
the project is
tomorrow morning.
Right.
What was the name of that again?
The Delphi Project.
Of course.
Of course, well,
I'll let you get back to work.
Now, remember, don't wait up.
I won't be home
till the wee hours.
Oh, poor baby.
Well...
♪ ♪
Hello, Claire.
Mrs. Stanton.
Your husband didn't tell me
you were gonna stop by.
Oh, Rob isn't expecting me.
This is something of a surprise.
(chuckles)
I am desperate
for a cup of coffee.
Could you be so kind?
Well, I'm-I'm not supposed
to leave my desk.
Claire, how often do I
ask you for favors?
Sure, Mrs. Stanton.
I'll be back in a jif.
Don't rush, dear.
Take your time.
Hi there.
Beth Ann.
What are you doing here?
I couldn't bear
the thought of you
getting your dinner
from a vending machine.
Wow, that's thoughtful.
I know you have a kitchen
around here somewhere.
You can pop it in the fridge
until you're ready to eat.
Sure.
Claire, can you come
in here for a second?
Claire?
Ah, she must have wandered off.
I'm sure she'll be back soon.
Now, Robert,
I went to all the trouble
of making this casserole.
I don't want the tuna to spoil.
(groans)
I will put it
in the fridge.
♪ ♪
Mrs. Stanton,
here's your coffee.
Oh, you're so sweet.
It's very hot. You might
want to give it a moment
- to cool off.
- Oh, I don't have time to wait.
I have things to do.
Oh, it'll just take a sec.
You're a treasure. Tell Rob
I'll see him back home.
Who said you could have
a coffee break?
NAOMI: (gasps)
I was so flattered.
Usually when Tommy's company
caters one of my events,
he refuses to wait on me.
But tonight, he asked
for this table.
Did he?
KARL: The theme
of this evening
is "South of the Border."
- Yes.
- So, who chose
the flamenco outfits
for the waiters?
I did. Why?
Flamenco is Spanish.
Isn't that what
they speak down there?
Spanish, as in Spain.
Yes, but it still counts
as south of the border.
Yes, if the border
is with France.
Oh, do you see what
I have to live with?
Such a know-it-all.
Yes, I'm forever
flouting my knowledge
that Spain is in Europe.
SANDY:
Naomi,
can I just say I'm stunned
at how handsome
your son's become.
I'm stunned he can
breathe in those pants.
Karl...
you're making
Tommy uncomfortable.
Me? I'm not the one
who dressed him up
as a backup dancer
to Liza Minnelli.
Another scotch,
please, young man.
Yes, Mr. Grove.
Very good.
Thank you.
(giggles) Hurry back, Tommy.
Can you believe how she's
flirting with my son?
Oh, Sandy is just being playful.
He's 18. She's 32.
Don't you think
that's pathetic?
Excuse me.
Vodka rocks, please.
You have to switch tables.
I can't.
Then at least
stop glaring at Karl.
He's such a jerk.
He's just trying
to be funny.
He's insulting
your dignity.
You can't say that
in those sleeves.
Ah, vodka rocks.
Thank you. Mmm.
You've found
your calling.
(dance music playing)
Hey!
There you are.
- Here I are.
- Why aren't you dancing?
I'm tired.
- Are you about ready to go?
- Now?
- Yeah.
- I'm having so much fun with Wischa.
TAYLOR: Well,
it's after midnight,
and I got to
be up early
and go to my job
that requires me to, you know,
wear clothes, so...
How many of those
have you had?
A couple.
Maybe two couples.
You seem angry.
I'm not angry.
Unless you're going to Venice
with those low-rent Kardashians.
Hey. Taylor, be nice.
Those are my friends.
Yeah, and I'm just
the person who saved you
from an abusive relationship
and let you live in my house,
but fuck me, right?
Okay. Um, I think maybe
you should go home,
and I will...
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Are you going to Venice?
I don't know yet.
Fine. Go!
Have the best time.
♪ ♪
- Come on.
- What? Now?
- Yeah, now.
- Okay.
- (telephone ringing)
- Stanton residence.
ROB (over phone):
Honey, thank God you're there.
Rob.
You sound upset.
Listen, when you were
in my office earlier,
did you happen to move
any papers?
What are you talking about?
The final draft
of the Delphi Project.
It was here on my desk
and now it's gone.
Did you look under your desk?
Yes, I've looked everywhere.
Now, this is
incredibly important.
Are you sure
you didn't touch it?
I know better than
to touch your things.
Damn it.
If I don't find this thing, I'll
have to stay late and redo it,
the whole goddamn thing.
I thought you were
working late anyway.
Uh... that was on
something else.
It doesn't matter. I have to go.
I-I have to go.
(children chattering)
(telephone ringing)
Yeah?
APRIL (on phone):
Hi, I'd like to speak to Sheila.
You're talking to her.
Who's this?
I think I mean your roommate,
the other Sheila.
Um, this is April
from the diner.
Oh, oh!
Oh, uh, Jesus,
all right, hold on.
(whoops)
(excited chatter)
(doorbell rings)
(panting):
You-know-who
is on the phone.
She wants to talk to you.
Hm. I thought she might.
April?
APRIL:
Hi. I know this is late notice,
but would you like to come
with me to the club tonight?
Rob cancelled on me.
I'm a mess
right now, but
I guess I could
throw myself together.
Oh, good.
It's the White Diamond Bar
in Burbank.
I'll meet you there in an hour.
I'll be there.
- What's going on?
- Show some respect, kids.
You're in the presence
of greatness.
TOMMY:
Careful, everybody.
- These bowls are hot.
- Ooh!
Tortilla soup.
You can't say this isn't
"South of the Border." (laughs)
Given Simone's grasp
of geography,
I'm surprised we're
not having clam chowder.
- (laughter)
- (glass clinking)
By the way,
have you all heard the latest
news about Larry and Sue?
What about them?
(whispering):
They've separated.
- (gasps) No!
- Are you really that surprised?
They fought constantly.
In my day, people stayed married
and found a way
to work things out.
Well, that's not
always possible.
NAOMI:
Simone's right.
People can care deeply
for one another,
it doesn't always mean that
they should stay married.
You see, this is where
I think commitment
becomes essential.
Everyone
makes mistakes,
but if love is there,
then there's a path
to redemption.
BARCLAY:
Easy for you to say.
You and Simone
have the perfect marriage.
Oh, hardly.
There are days
when Simone regrets marrying me.
Am I right,
my darling?
- More than a few. (laughs)
- Yes, I imagine she dreams
of stifling me
with a pillow
or casting me aside
like an old shoe.
Oh, honey, you know
I'd never throw away a shoe.
But you don't get rid of me that
easily. You see, she gave me
her hand in marriage.
- SIMONE: Karl...
- KARL: And I'm never
going to let it go.
- Oh!
- (gasps)
KARL:
Bloody hell!
Tommy, how could you
be so clumsy?
Sorry, Mr. Grove.
Let me get you some napkins.
Clearly, he did that on purpose.
No, he just wasn't
paying attention.
You know how
teenagers are.
- (groans)
- Okay, sober person, here we go.
Give me this.
Stop. Hey.
Eli, don't rush me.
I'm not rushing you. There.
You know what? I don't get it.
What's that?
What don't you get?
I don't get what Jade sees
in those people.
- Wischa?
- Yeah.
They're fake as shit.
Yes, they are.
Okay, legs, pants.
(groans)
And you know what?
Why would anyone want to see
them in their underwear?
Ugh.
'Cause they're not even
that pretty.
Do you think they're pretty?
Only their bodies
and their faces.
And now Jade's going with them
to Venice?
- Mm-hmm.
- Fuck her.
- (chuckles)
- What's funny?
You. You're funny 'cause
you're drunk and ridiculous,
and that's a nice
change of pace.
From what?
Well, usually you're the one
taking care of me
when I'm doing something stupid.
- I do take care of you.
- Yes, you do.
- I take care of everybody.
- Okay.
(sighs)
Hey, don't feel bad
in the morning, okay?
Why would I feel bad?
'Cause you'll remember
how rude you were to Jade.
Don't worry, she'll forgive you.
Mm, fuck you.
And so will I.
I am so happy you came.
You look amazing.
It was very kind
for you to invite me.
I never go to places
like this.
Well, if you hadn't come,
I would've had to stay home,
and where is
the fun in that?
(chuckles)
It's a shame your fella
couldn't make it.
Yeah, he said he had
to work late, but who knows?
Married men who cheat
also know how to lie.
It must be frustrating.
Never knowing if Rob
is going to stand you up
for his wife.
It can be annoying,
but it's a trade-off.
So what do you get
out of the deal?
Freedom.
See, I don't want
to get married.
So this is just a...
casual fling?
Yeah. Rob's wife will get him
back when I'm done with him,
good as new.
And if he keeps
working late,
it's going to be
in a couple of weeks.
Oh, good. For you.
I mean, good for you.
(chuckles)
Where is our waiter?
So, April, why don't you want
to get married?
Because I want to have a career.
Doing what?
I want to be a singer.
- Really?
- (chuckles)
That's kind of why
I wanted to come here.
They have girls that sing
with the combo on the weekends,
so I'm gonna introduce myself
to the manager,
and then I am going
to audition for him.
I had no idea you sang.
I started in the church choir
back at home.
Folks there think
I'm pretty talented.
I'm gonna be somebody someday.
You just watch.
I love music.
I used to play the piano.
No kidding.
Yeah, I took
lessons for years.
Well, do you
still play?
The truth is,
my husband didn't care
for my playing.
I made the mistake of telling
him I wanted to give a recital,
and he just laughed.
He said I wasn't as good
as I thought I was.
That sort of
took the wind out of my sail.
Oh, honey.
Your husband's dead.
Don't you think it's time
you stopped listening to him?
Can I just say I am very happy
to be here tonight?
(laughs) Well, here's to us.
(giggles)
(clattering)
Taylor, what are you doing?
You were right.
I have to go find Jade.
It's 4:00 in the morning.
I was such a bitch,
and now she's going to Venice,
and it's all my fault,
and I have to fix this.
All right, well, you don't
even know where she is.
Yes, I do, okay?
I-I... She's at their hotel.
- How do you know that?
- I put Find My Friends on her phone.
- You're tracking her?
- I got to go.
(groans) Oh, my God.
Hey, what the fuck
has gotten into you?
I can't lose her.
Well, you can wait until
she gets home to talk to her.
What if she
doesn't come back?
What if she's already
on a plane to Venice
and I never see her again?
You just said
she's at the hotel.
(sighs) I need her.
If she leaves, this whole
fucking thing falls apart.
(door closes)
No...
- (engine starts)
- No.
Stop the car.
What does that mean?
What whole thing falls apart?
Eli, get off.
No, you're gonna get out
and you're gonna
talk to me right now,
Taylor.
Really?
Just talk to me, Taylor.
What's going on?
Come on.
I asked you before
if you were in love with her.
I-I know, I know.
- You lied to me.
- Not exactly.
Then what the hell
are we doing in the driveway?
Eli, come on, please.
This is, this is too hard!
- What?
- I-I don't know.
- My life, my l... my life is so hard!
I-I... The hours I work,
the cases I take.
And then I come home
to this house.
This big, fucking house
that we can't afford!
And I have
to pay for it
because you haven't sold
a script in two years.
But I can't
bring that up
because then I'm a bitch.
So I say nothing.
And Jade is the only thing
in my life that is easy.
'Cause she
doesn't take.
She only gives.
If she leaves,
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Why didn't you tell me
any of this before?
Come on.
I don't want to hurt you.
Oh, well, great call.
'Cause it hurts.
So, I mean...
Do you want me to go?
No.
Eli, I love you.
But you want her to stay.
I mean...
How does that even work?
I don't know.
I don't.
But it has to.
Because otherwise, it's just
too hard to be married to me.
No. Eli...
(door opens)
(sighs)
(door closes)
(indistinct chatter)
(lively music playing)
I got fired.
I'm not surprised.
What you did was childish.
- He was grabbing you.
- He was holding my hand.
- Why do you keep defending him?
- I'm not.
He's lied to you,
he's cheated on you
and he won't
leave your home.
The situation is complicated.
Well, yeah, it must be,
because it makes no sense.
- You should hate him.
- I know, I know, it's just...
He's my husband.
He puts up with my extravagance
and my nonsense.
He tells me I'm beautiful when I
need to hear it the most and...
he makes me laugh
in a way that no one else can.
Simone...
One day, I will divorce Karl,
but I will
never hate him,
because I can't.
Where does that leave me?
In the back of a van
having a marvelous time.
Yeah, well, van came
with the job, so...
Don't worry.
We'll figure it out.
Mrs. Grove.
Mrs. Harte says
it's time for your number.
Thank you.
I have to go.
(door opens)
Hi.
(whispers):
Hey.
Listen, about tonight,
I'm so sorry.
- You don't have to apologize.
- No, I do.
I really do.
Thank you.
So, I decided to go to Venice
with Mischa and Willow.
Oh.
JADE:
It's time.
Being here with you
and Eli, it's...
...starting to feel like a home.
I'm getting attached.
Which always leads
to me getting hurt.
When it ends. So...
I should go.
ELI: What if it
doesn't have to end?
What if you stayed?
What if this was your home?
Here with us.
(Jade stammers)
What are you saying?
Live with us.
Be with us.
Yeah.
There's no reason
to leave.
You just got home.
(door opens)
Hi.
Oh, you're still up.
Of course.
Did you get your work finished?
Yep.
I redid the whole project.
It took forever.
I could fix you
a snack if you like.
No. I'm gonna make myself
a martini, take a shower
and go to bed.
All right.
Would it bother you if I played
the piano for a bit?
It's after midnight.
I know. If you'd rather
I didn't...
Nah. Whatever you want.
(playing tango music)
♪ ♪
Honey, I need an olive
for my martini.
Check the fridge.
♪ ♪
- I can't find the olives.
- Top shelf.
I checked. They weren't there.
Check again.
- Honey!
- (piano stops)
It's not really a martini
without an olive.
(glass clinks)
Thanks. You know,
it is so late.
We should turn in.
(tango music playing)