Welcome to the Williamsburg
Diner Awards Night!
And here's your host,
Neil Patrick Hairless!
This is the night
where everyone is recognized
for their, well... let's call it work.
Nice suit, Han.
I loved you in The Penguins of Madagascar.
Here we go. The award for
Worst Excuse for Being
Late to Work goes to...
Earl, for: "I died."
It was true.
I was dead for a full 60 seconds.
And the Foreign Film Award goes to...
Oleg, for always being
covered in a foreign film.
Yeah. I have so many bacteria to thank...
but a special shout-out to streptococcus!
And the winner for Best Lie
Told to Get a Bigger Tip
goes to...
Good luck, girl.
It's an honor to share
this category with you.
It's Max... for showing customers pictures
of her three small children
on a regular basis.
Wow. Oh!
This award is dedicated
to the lights of my life...
Maxine, Max Jr.,
and Maxi-Pad.
I know only one of you can see and hear me,
so please tell the others I... love... you.
And the award for Best Waitress goes to...
It better not!
Caroline! No!
Well, I guess it's true...
women only win awards
when they take on roles
that are humiliating.
And the Best Animated Short
goes to Han Lee!
(Peter Bjorn and John)
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
2 Broke Girls  - 04x13
And the Great Unwashed
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
Here's your menu.
I'll be right back with your water
and a stomach pump.
Keep it. I know what I want.
Me too. But it just seems like
Taylor Swift is never going away.
You're funny. Yeah.
I'm not in the mood for funny.
I will take tomato soup, house salad,
extra croutons.
And you can charge me extra...
if you have no heart behind those gazongas.
It's cool. The guy at the counter
has no teeth, so you can have his.
Less funny... more salad. Right?
Maybe the blonde one should bring it.
Oh, you want her to bring it?
Maybe clear your calendar.
Uh, the lady in the booth
doesn't like my attitude
and wants you,
so I guess what I'm saying is
I still got it!
Wait, a customer asked for me
and didn't follow it with,
"I'd also like to see the manager"?
That's a first for me!
Yo, Blondie!
Croutons!
[ding ding]
Pick up. Tomato soup, house salad.
And I'm also running
a special on D batteries.
Buy both, and I'll thrown in
this bootleg copy
of Horrible Bosses II.
Here comes Horrible Bosses Too Small.
Need some new batteries
to keep walking and talking?
No, Max, I'm not powered
by double Ds like you.
Preach.
Don't buy batteries from that guy
unless you want your heart
to stop on the bus.
Oleg, this is supposed
to have extra croutons.
It's for my regular.
Yeah, you heard me. It happened.
Oh, no, "Extra Croutons" is here again?
Make sure you charge her extra.
I'm not made of stale bread!
No, you're made of Legos, right?
We are not charging her extra.
She looks like she can't afford it.
If she could, why would she be eating here?
Well, don't judge a book by its cover.
People look at me and...
Think you're bad in bed?
What's your point?
For your information, Max,
I'm not bad in bed.
In fact, I'm quite the stud
in my Sims community.
You wouldn't be a stud
in a retirement community.
[bell dings]
Hi! Here's your salad...
Uh... five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Uh, continue.
And I wanted to introduce myself.
I'm Caroline, you're regular waitress.
Ah.
Oh! My turn. Sorry.
I live alone,
and my plants aren't this needy.
I'm Nola.
And this is Max. Max, this is Nola.
'Sup, Lola?
It's Nola.
See, this is why I like the blonde one.
She listens.
May I please have a cheesecake?
Sure. And thank you, Nola.
I think it's important to listen to people.
Coming right back with that cherry pie.
I'll tell her if she ever stops listening.
I think Nola knows
I'm more than just a waitress.
She can see right through this uniform.
And so can I... in just the right light.
- Close the door!
- Oh, my God!
Sophie, you scared me!
You're scared?
I just saw the expiration
date on this milk!
Come on, close it, quick!
I'm in here hiding from Oleg.
If you wanna get away from Oleg,
just go anywhere they sell floss.
I think that Oleg is cheating on me.
Look. Oh, God!
Now she's gonna start whipping it out?
Look...
He has a second secret phone.
It's a boner phone.
You mean a burner phone.
Same thing.
Sophie, how do you know
he just doesn't use it
for long distance or...
Or for the woman
that I'm calling right now?
Oh, put her on speaker.
I've nothing else to do. I'm at work.
(woman) Da? Oleg?
[grunts hoarsely] Uh... ah...
(woman) Oleg?
[hoarsely] Uhh... ah!
That... is a terrible Oleg.
He is not that articulate.
[woman speaking in Russian]
Hah! That old whore!
What did she say?
I have no idea!
I don't speak Russian, but...
I do speak "old whore."
Tell me, what is his problem?
He has a sweet, young filly like me at home
and he needs to go out and plow
some old Russian field?
Well... I'd ask what
you three are doing in here,
but it's never gonna top
what I'm imagining you're doing in here.
I can't believe
Nola didn't come in tonight.
This is exactly what happened
with my Starbucks barista guy.
One minute, he's suggestively
arranging the bananas at me,
and then next minute, he's face-down,
dead in a puddle of soy milk.
Max, what if something happened to her?
More croutons for us!
She said, "I'll see you tomorrow."
That doesn't mean anything.
It's just an expression
like, "Employees must wash hands."
Or... or, "The baby is yours."
Hey, everybody!
Oh, Sophie, it's just you.
You're poor!
And now we're even.
Look, I stole it again. Where's Oleg?
I'll tell you where he's not...
Culinary school.
He's on break.
Oh, she's gonna be sorry!
Oh... no one comes between
Sophie and her man.
You know... unless we pay them to.
Couple things...
A... does anyone ever work here?
Caroline, stop worrying.
Extra Croutons is fine.
She just called to order
some diner food to be delivered.
Oh! So she wants to die at home.
I said we don't do deliveries.
I told her you two can barely get the food
from the window to the tables!
Max, I had to stop by
and bring Nola her salad and croutons.
I mean, she's kind of
my biggest fan right now.
True...'cause you just lost me.
I know you think this is crazy,
but there's something about
the way Nola looks at me.
It's like she's seeing something in me.
The woman wears two pairs of glasses.
To her, you're just a chatty
yellow and orange blur.
I was told you didn't deliver.
By who, her old boyfriends?
Are you two gonna kill me or something?
Because if you are,
I would like to put on a different hat.
No, no, no. She got worried.
See, you're her first regular.
I'm just here for the story.
I figured there'd be something
freaky behind this door
like a 50-foot python
and what's left of the UPS guy.
And Earl guessed you were a man.
No man.
No, just me in here with
my vagina and my photographs.
Oh! You're a photographer?
I love photography!
And I love privacy.
And I love pot.
Oh, I thought we were going around.
Come on. You better come in too.
You're the Yin to her Yap.
Hey, careful where you step.
I can't find my third pair of glasses.
It's on top of your hat.
No, that's my fourth pair.
Hey!
This is Billy the bum!
He used to live in a box around
the corner from my apartment.
He even let me stay over once
when I had to get away
from this bad roommate.
Oh, the one before me? No, it was you.
You two are a riot together.
You remind me of me
and my old photographer friend
Annie Leibovitz.
Course, this was before...
Before she got famous?
No. Before she hit on me.
I told her I wasn't into girls.
But... I think she was
confused by the derby.
Yeah. I think we're all
a little confused by it.
Nola, I want to ask you
if you've ever had any success,
but I don't know how to
do that without insulting you.
That's correct. You don't.
Oh! You're having a gallery show in SoHo?
Good-bye.
Uh, it was nice of you two
to, uh, come over, check on me.
Uh... weird, but nice.
Perhaps we could come to the opening.
Oh. Oh, you don't need to do that.
I know we don't need to,
but maybe I want to support
you and your amazing work.
- And Max would enjoy. the free wine.
- Yes, I would.
[laughs] No.
Oh, I would.
No as in, "No, don't come."
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I wanna eat my croutons
without the vaudeville stylings
of Shecky and Nosy.
Here.
Oh, yeah, good. I was looking for this.
I can't believe you're doing all this
for a diner regular.
I haven't seen you
this desperate since Monday,
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday.
I know... on the weekends, I just give up.
Look that title!
"The Great Unwashed."
Are Oleg's balls here?
Max, it's the "art scene."
Class it up. At least say testicles.
Evening, ladies.
Earl, what are you doing here?
And, Han, your sweater's eating your head.
I'm here for the champagne
and because I couldn't find my way out.
I just walked into a picture of a door.
Some of these are going
for thousands of dollars!
That Nola bitch is rich, and I bet she has
a frigging summer house
made out of my free croutons!
Han, it's the art scene. Class it up.
At least say "freaking." Also, "testicles."
Well, I'm not wasting
this new turtleneck on you two.
I'm going to go mingle.
A high fashion model was giving me the eye.
Then she'd have to be high.
Uh, Han, I believe I'll stay here.
Nobody wins with a Teenage
Mutant Ninja Turtle
as a wingman.
Oh, hey, everybody.
Hey, Sophie. Hey, Oleg.
So can I class it back down now?
Sorry we're late. I was just over there
admiring the photo of the happy
couple under the bridge.
Happy couple? Sophie, they're two junkies
sharing a needle.
Yeah, well,
at least the lady junkie
knows where his needle's been.
I don't even think she knows her name.
She knows more**
She knows everything.
You guys had been here for a while.
Where's the best place
to steal some food?
- Max!
- Sorry, sorry.
Classing it up.
Testicles some food.
Oh, Max, I can tell by your sassdemeanor*
you haven't seen your photo yet.
The photo.*
Yep, that's me, all right.
I recognize that "I don't care" pout
and the Thousand Island
dressing in my hair.
Max, just because you're hanging on a wall
among the poorest,
most lost souls in our city
doesn't mean your life is...
I'm hanging right behind me, aren't I?
Oh, my God!
It could be worst. You could be naked.
This is worse than being naked!
I'm wearing polyester!
It's bad ou I'm a waitress in Brooklyn.
Now I'm a waitress in Manhattan,
and these guys didn't even tip!
No, no, no, it's a photograph
so it's more symbolic.
It's called "Waitress"
And I'm holding a checkpad.
What those blue dots mean?
Is my picture in trouble?
That's how many time
your print has been purchased.
Over here, Max, away from that phatetic
blonde lady with a waitress uniform.
Could you relax?
No one even recognized you.
No one? What about that art critic
who said "my smile on the photo
"was a study of tragic, foolish optimism
in a hopeless, dead-end life"?
Oh, him.
Hopeless, dead-end life and the worse
no one buys me?
I'm not even a success.
It's a failure.
You're totally a sucess
as failure.
Then where are the blue dots , Max?
20 people bought you.
Whatever you do, don't turn around.
Look at these dots!
♪♪
Man, woman, black, white.
Are you putting the dots
by your friend's photo?
How many extra croutons can you buy
with *** of money you're making
from these photos?
♪♪
Okay, okay, I get it. *
I'll tell you what.
I will give you a free print on your photo.
Look, keep the photo.
I don't want a picute of me
marrying kepchups.
I don't want a picture of me
marrying anybody.
But you can pay me back
in another way.
I told you. I'm not a lesbian.
I just wear hat!
Your friend said you hated your photo.
No! I enjoyed being secretly photographed
while I'm stealing someone
extra, extra croutons.
For the record,
I never saw your smile as foolish.
I saw it as, uh...
just a little big.
Uh... I'm trying to pay you a compliment.
Well, you failed.
All this time, when you looked at me,
I thought you saw something special,
but all you really saw was
someone reading the specials.
I have a question for you.
Okay, fine. I wear the derby
because I have a little bit of a bald spot.
Why didn't I sell?
The picture sucks.
One of my worst.
If you're still trying
to give me a compliment,
you're still failing.
Look, a good photograph
captures the truth.
And I guess no one really believes
you as a waitress.
That is the single nicest
thing anyone's ever said to me.
So it's not where you wanna be... I get it.
Look, it's taken me 50 years
to be where I am.
And you are still  so young.
That is the second-nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me!
The road is long, and trust me,
it can be really hard.
So whatever you do,
you hold on to that
foolishly hopeful smile.
And... your funny friend.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Uh, everyone, tonight we are witness
to the amazing work
of Nola Anderz.
[applause]
Why don't we all just stand here quietly
for a moment and let Nola's pictures speak.
[cell phone ringing]
That's my phone. Where is it?
[ringing]
Baby, why is my phone in your bra?
Shh, please!
It's your secret phone!
I know all about it.
[ringing] You took it? Give it to me.
Who is she, Oleg?
Who is this skanky old whore?
Security! Security!
What... no, no, no!
Stop, stop... she has my phone.
It's his boner phone, everybody!
It's his boner phone!
And you had the testicles to think
I was gonna embarrass you.
Hey, Sophie.
Hey, girls.
Did you hear that?
It sounds a little
bit like... I don't know.
The sound of cheating.
You guys haven't made up yet?
Don't make up here.
No. I slept on the couch.
I missed her so much, I watched a romcom
while eating a whole box
of her edible underwear.
Still not talking to me, Sophie?
For the last time,
there's nobody else but you.
- I use that phone...
- Yes?
To... Go on.
- I use it to call...
- Cut to the chase!
My mother.
Is there no one he won't sleep with?
I didn't tell you because
I didn't want you to think
I was a mama's boy.
Except when we play "Mama and Boy."
Well...
I'll tell you what I told that girl
at the Yankee Candle store.
"I'm not buyin' it!"
It's true, Sophie.
I'm afraid I'm... losing my hair.
Oh... Oleg.
But don't you know...
I mean, you could be
balder than Jeremy Piven was
15 years ago, and I'd still love ya.
[phone ringing]
Where's my... [ringing]
Busted.
Caroline, I have something for you.
I'm not signing another one of those
giant birthday cards again.
It's my picture.
Great. Now I have two of you
that don't wait on tables.
"Thanks for the croutons. Nola."
Max, where are we gonna hang me?
Maybe you should hang yourself
in the bathroom
like I thought you would three years ago.
Yep. I lost $20 on that bet.
You know, Max,
maybe I have to stop running
away from this part of my life
and embrace it,
see it as part of my journey,
my... beautiful, exciting journey.
If you don't shut up,
I'm gonna hang you right here.