You'll let me have your redraft
on establishment levels by Thursday?
You need it that early?
I don't need it that early,
but the Minister has to read it
before facing the select committee.
What makes it harder, he has to remember it.
Harder still, he has to understand it.
Incidentally, did you write
the Minister's Washington speech?
Yes, Sir Humphrey.
- Splendid. Well done.
- Thank you, Sir Humphrey.
The Minister's in now.
Good. Right, thank you all.
Have you enjoyed having
your Minister away for a week?
Not very much. Makes things very difficult.
Ah, Bernard!
A Minister's absence is a godsend!
You can do the job properly for once.
No silly questions, no bright ideas,
no fussing about the papers.
I think our Minister doesn't believe he exists
unless he's in the papers.
I'll bet the first thing he says is,
"Any reports on my Washington speech?"
- How much?
- A pound.
Done. He won't because he's already asked!
In the car on the way back from Heathrow.
You're learning, Bernard. Sit down.
See why a Minister's absence is a good thing?
- Yes, but so much work piles up.
- There we are.
With a couple of days' briefing
before he goes and debriefing after,
he's out of our hair for a fortnight.
If he complains of being uninformed,
say it came up while he was away.
Hence so many summit conferences?
That's the only way the country works!
Concentrate all the power
at Number 10 then send the PM away
to EEC summits, NATO summits,
Commonwealth summits, anywhere!
Then the Cabinet Secretary
can run the country properly.
We ought to see him now.
What do you think of the Washington speech?
"British administration as a model
of loyalty and efficiency.
"A ruthless war on waste,
cutting bureaucracy to the bone.
- "Britain can teach the world!"
- Can we prove it?
A good speech isn't one where
we can prove he's telling the truth.
It's one in which nobody else can prove he's lying!
But even so, I'm sure it was good,
but I just wondered whether
it was boring for the audience.
Of course it was boring!
Bored the pants of them!
Ghastly to have to sit through it, I should think!
Ministers' speeches aren't written
for the audience.
Aren't they?
Delivering a speech is just a formality
you go through to get into the papers.
We can't worry about entertaining.
We're not writing for a comedian.
Well, not a professional one!
The point is the speech said the right things.
- But why say it in public?
- It's vital.
Once it's printed, the Minister has
to defend us in select committees.
- He defends us anyway.
- Well... only to a point, Bernard.
Once something goes wrong,
the Minister's first instinct is
to rat on his department.
We must nail his trousers to the mast.
- You mean nail his colours?
- No, his trousers.
Then he can't climb down! Come on.
- Welcome home, Minister!
- Hello, Humphrey.
Bernard, didn't you say there were
some press cuttings on my speech?
Yes, I put them in the box, Minister.
Minister, you do realise
the importance of tomorrow's hearing?
Indeed. The press will be there.
It's not just a question of the press.
It's a scrutiny of this department's
future operation.
If it emerged that we were
extravagant or incompetent...
- Are we extravagant or incompetent?
- Of course not.
But there are hostile members,
especially the one for Derbyshire.
- No! Betty Oldham won't be there?
- Yes, alas.
I urge you to master this brief,
and ask if you have any problems.
Another brief? I've only just mastered one.
Really? What was in it?
I can't remember.
So difficult to concentrate on a plane,
all those drinks and movies.
- And they wake you up.
- Of course, Minister.
Frightfully difficult to concentrate
if you keep being woken up.
Seriously, this is the only brief with possible
questions from the committee
with appropriate answers carefully
presented to give our position.
Is it absolutely accurate?
They're carefully presented to give our position.
These committees are important.
I cannot be seen to mislead them.
You will not be seen to mislead them.
- The truth?
- And nothing but.
- The whole truth?
- Of course not.
- We tell them we keep secrets?
- Indeed not!
Why not?
"He that would keep a secret
must keep it secret,
"that he hath the secret to keep."
Who said that?
It was Sir Humphrey.
- Who said it originally?
- Francis Bacon, wasn't it?
Oh, yes.
Why can't we go anywhere without briefs?
In case they get caught with their trousers down.
Trousers down! Pick them...!
Very droll, Bernard.
- Are we going to be interrupted?
- Your diary's empty today.
What was in that submission I read?
More or less a rehash of last year's report.
And the year before? And the year before that?
Yes, ever since 1867.
With appropriate alterations.
Shall we go through it?
Must we? I'm still jet-lagged.
All the press will be there.
Right, let's get down to it.
The fact is that the Department
of Administrative Affairs
is run to a high standard of efficiency
and supports and services
the administrative work
of all Government departments,
as we've said in our submission.
Thank you, Minister. Questions?
- Mrs Oldham?
- Thank you.
Minister, have you heard of Malcolm Rhodes?
No.
He was assistant secretary
in the DAA until he resigned last year.
There are 23,000 people in the DAA.
But he resigned or was eased out.
Became a management consultant
and has just written a book -
this is an advance proof -
in which he makes astounding
allegations of waste of public money,
particularly in your department.
Could I have a word with my officials,
Mr Chairman?
- Know about this?
- Not about the book.
- Who is Rhodes?
- He's a trouble-maker.
- What's in the book?
- Don't know.
- What do I do?
- Stall.
"Stall", meaning avoiding answer.
Yes, I know what stall means!
You've sent me into a typhoon
without even an umbrella!
An umbrella's no use in wind...
Shut up, Bernard!
Have you had sufficient consultation
with your officials?
I...
Let me read you some
scandalous facts Mr Rhodes reveals,
and I quote, "No 4 supply
depot in Herefordshire,
"two former aircraft hangars
used only for stores
"but which are centrally-heated
to 70 degrees day and night."
- What do you say about that?
- I can't answer without prior notice.
- It might not be true.
- It is. I checked.
What reason can there be
for such appalling extravagance?
Some materials deteriorate at low
temperatures, depending on what it is.
Copper wire.
Yes, well... copper wire?
It can corrode in damp conditions.
It's plastic-coated.
Plastic-coated?
I...
Plastic-coated? I'll certainly have it looked into.
He says you insist on ordering all pens,
pencils, paperclips and so on centrally,
then distributing them against
departmental requisitions.
That seems to be quite sensible.
Savings through bulk purchase.
He demonstrates that this is
four times more expensive
than if officers bought what
they want on the High Street.
Very interesting.
If so, we'll change the system.
We're not a rigid bureaucracy.
He said he proposed this change
when he was in your department,
and it was turned down as people
were used to the existing procedure.
- How's that for rigid bureaucracy?
- I'll have it looked into.
- "Looked into"?
- Yes!
You said in your Washington
speech last week
that you conducted a war on waste
and could teach the world a lesson.
How do you reconcile that with
spending £75,000 on a roof garden
on top of the supplementary
benefits office in Kettering?
I'm... I'll...
- Have it looked into?
- Yes! Yes, I will!
The DAA's Permanent Secretary
is due to appear next week.
Isn't he the appropriate person
to answer the questions?
Thank you. See that Sir Humphrey's notified.
Perhaps you might let him see the allegations?
"Allegations of Government waste"?
"Big questions to answer"?
- You've put me in a difficult position!
- What about me?!
The PM's demanding economies,
and we've been wasting all this money!
No one's been saving anything,
you should know that!
They look as though they have.
- Couldn't you have stalled?
- Stalled?
Blurred things a bit.
- You're good at blurring the issue.
- What?
You have a considerable talent
for making things unintelligible.
- I beg your pardon!
- I mean that as a compliment.
Blurring the issue is one
of the basic ministerial skills.
And the others?
Delaying decisions, dodging questions,
juggling figures, bending facts
and concealing errors.
What was I to do?
Make it look like you'd do
something and do nothing.
Like you usually do.
- But if these revelations are true...
- Exactly, Minister, "if".
You could have discussed truth.
The committee isn't interested in truth.
They're all MPs!
- What about a security matter?
- HB pencils a security matter?!
Depends what you write with them!
Why build roof gardens on top of offices?
We took over the office design
from an American company,
and it happens that nobody noticed
the roof gardens on the plan.
God!
It's a tiny mistake anyone could make.
Tiny mistake, £75,000? Give me
an example of a big mistake?
Letting people find out about it!
Why are we heating sheds full of wire?
- You want the truth?
- If it's no trouble.
The staff are using the sheds
for growing mushrooms.
Stop them!
They've been doing it since 1945.
It's the only perk in an extremely boring job.
What about Rhodes's proposals for stationery?
He was a trouble-maker and crank,
unhealthily obsessed with efficiency.
Why didn't we adopt his proposals
and save millions?
- Yes, but a lot of work to implement.
- So?
- Taking on more staff.
- Humphrey!
- Disprove it.
- I can't, obviously.
- Exactly!
- Making it up?
- Of course.
- Why?
As an example of how to handle
a select committee.
Sir Humphrey, let's get down to details.
- This heated aircraft hangar.
- Indeed.
I do understand your concern,
but it gets frightfully cold in Herefordshire.
- Even civil servants...
- We aren't talking about civil servants.
We're talking coils of wire
plastic-coated to keep them warm!
- Staff are in and out all the time.
- Why?
Taking deliveries, making
withdrawals, checking records,
fire inspections...
- They can wear gloves, can't they?
- But it's a staff welfare policy.
I suggest this policy is costing
the taxpayer millions!
Nothing to say?
I can't comment on Government policy.
- But you advise the Minister.
- I can't disclose how I advise him.
- The Minister's responsible for policy.
- All right. We'll ask the Minister.
What about stationery savings?
It would've meant considerable
Government patronage on junior staff.
"Considerable Government patronage"?
Buying a packet of paperclips?
It's Government policy to exercise
strict control over who can spend its money.
It's common sense to let
people buy their own paperclips.
Government policy is nothing
to do with common sense.
Don't you think it's time
the policy was changed?
Well, Sir Humphrey?
I can't comment on Government policy.
Ask the Minister.
The Minister advises us to ask you.
I'm advising you to ask the Minister.
- When does this end?
- As soon as you like.
Let's come to the roof garden.
Yes, with pleasure.
This was part of a wide variety
of roof insulation schemes,
which the Government was testing
in the interest of fuel economy.
But £75,000!
It was thought the sale of vegetable
produce might offset the cost.
And did it?
- No.
- Then why not abandon the garden?
It's there now, insulating the roof,
and we aren't building any more.
But you've wasted £75,000!
All proposals were tested for fuel saving.
At this fantastic waste of taxpayers' money?
You agree it was wasted?
I can't comment on Government policy.
Ask the Minister.
Look, whatever we ask the Minister,
he says is a question for you.
Whatever we ask you,
you say is a question for the Minister!
- How do we find out what's going on?
- Yes, I see there is a dilemma here.
While the Government regards policy
as the responsibility of Ministers
and administration
as the responsibility of officials,
questions of administrative policy
cause confusion
between the policy of administration
and the administration of policy,
especially when responsibility
for the policy of administration
conflicts with responsibility for
the policy of administration of policy.
That's a load of meaningless drivel.
Isn't it?
I can't comment on Government policy.
You must ask the Minister.
- A great help!
- I did my best.
Best for yourself, perhaps!
But your answers solved nothing.
We'll both be there, getting the third
degree from that committee.
We've got to have the same answers!
- Let's establish our position.
- What are the facts?
The facts are neither here nor there!
I see. What's our position?
We choose one of the five standard
excuses to deal with each allegation.
Five standard excuses?
First, the excuse we used
in the Anthony Blunt case:
"There's an explanation for everything,
"but security forbids its disclosure."
Second, the excuse we used
for comprehensive schools:
"Because of budget cuts, supervisory
resources went beyond their limits."
- That's not true, is it?
- But it's a good excuse.
Then there's the excuse for Concorde:
"A worthwhile experiment, now abandoned,
"but not before it had provided
much valuable data and employment."
But that is true, isn't it?
Oh, no, of course it isn't.
Four, there's the excuse
for the Munich Agreement:
"It occurred before important facts
were known and couldn't re-occur."
What important facts?
That Hitler wanted to conquer Europe.
- I thought everybody knew that!
- Not the Foreign Office.
- Five?
- Five...
The Charge of the Light Brigade excuse:
"An unfortunate lapse by an individual,
"dealt with under internal
disciplinary procedures."
- That covers everything?
- Just about, so far.
- Even wars?
- Small wars.
- It's real teamwork from now on.
- United we stand, divided we fall!
Minister, you're due at the House.
The PM's adviser wants you to pop in
for a drink. Sir Mark Spencer.
- Mark Spencer?
- I suggested 5.30?
Fine, yes. Oh, dear. I knew there'd be trouble.
The PM wants to know why
our replies have been so feeble.
Perhaps it's just for a drink.
They don't ask you for a drink
just because you're thirsty!
I'll meet you back here at 6.30,
and we'll cook up a story.
- Agree our position, Minister.
- That's what I said.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Come in!
Hello, Jim.
- Scotch?
- Thanks.
- How are things going?
- Fine.
That select committee was a shock,
throwing the book at us,
but everything's under control
and Humphrey and I can explain it.
The PM shouldn't worry.
I'd like to know where Malcolm Rhodes
got all his information.
And who gave the proofs to Betty Oldham?
The PM must be livid.
It's no fault of mine.
- Why do you think the PM's livid?
- Surely...?
Let's look at the situation logically.
Sit down.
Yes. Of course.
Let me ask you some questions.
What is the PM trying to achieve
in public expenditure?
- Cuts, obviously.
- Why so little success?
- Obstruction from the civil service?
- Are all the Cabinet committed to it?
- I think so. I certainly am.
- But no Minister's made any cuts.
- Rome wasn't built in a day.
- No.
It's because all the Ministers have gone native.
- Surely...?
- The civil service has trained them!
Well, maybe true... Certainly not of me!
If a Minister were really trying to cut expenditure,
how would he react to a book
exposing Government waste?
- I should think he'd...
- Mmm?
It would depend...
What are you trying to say?
Know what the civil service say?
You're a pleasure to work with.
Oh!
Oh...
That's what Barbara Woodhouse
says about her spaniels.
Sir Humphrey said
you're worth your weight in gold.
What does that suggest to you?
That I've failed utterly?
You look as if you need another Scotch.
The PM isn't pleased with my performance
at the committee.
- I failed to cover up the failure.
- On the contrary.
because you're covering up too well.
Don't you see? You're protecting the civil service.
The PM and I are doing our best
to expose why cuts in expenditure
are not taking place.
And you are helping the civil service
to defy the Government.
Am I?
You were wondering where
Betty Oldham got the proofs
and where Malcolm Rhodes
got that inside information.
Can't you guess?
(WHISPERS) You mean... the PM?
Of course not!
Not directly.
(WHISPERS) You mean... you?
What am I to do at the select committee?
There's only one course
open to you. Absolute loyalty.
Who to?
That's your decision.
It was an error that occurred
before important facts were known.
I assure you it is an oversight
that couldn't possibly happen again.
- Wouldn't you agree, Minister?
- Perfectly correct.
The correct official reply.
But I've been thinking very deeply
over the last few days,
and there's no doubt that
this committee is on to something.
Of course there's waste.
And excuses can always
be found in individual cases.
But you have convinced me
our approach is wrong.
Ministers and their civil servants
so often cover up and defend
where they should seek out and destroy.
I've spoken to Mr Rhodes,
author of this invaluable book,
and he'll head an independent enquiry
into the field of administration,
starting with my department.
And how does Sir Humphrey react to this?
Sir Humphrey is in complete agreement with me.
We work as a team. I must say,
he's a pleasure to work with.
But this account of what's been going on
doesn't square with your Washington
speech about a war on waste.
Well, I'm an old-fashioned sort of chap, Betty,
and I believe in a thing called loyalty.
Whatever you say in private
you defend in public, eh, Humphrey?
In that case, aren't you being disloyal now?
No. I believe a Minister has a higher loyalty.
A loyalty to Parliament and the nation.
And that loyalty must be paramount,
however hard and painful that may be.
Of course, one is loyal
to one's department and officials,
until the evidence is overwhelming,
but I must say in public,
that reforms can and will take place,
and I know I shall find
in Sir Humphrey my staunchest ally.
Isn't that so, Humphrey?
(CROAKS) Yes, Minister.
Yes, Minister.
- A big help!
- I did my best.
The best for yourself! This is
your idea of teamwork? Amusing!
- I had to do it.
- Had to do what?
Cravenly admit everything to them?
Don't you realise how calamitous this is for us?
- Not both of us, I hope.
- You hope in vain.
We're up in arms,
with very little confidence in you.
As for Number 10, I shudder to think
how the PM will react
to your public admission of failure.
A personal letter from the Prime Minister.
I did warn you, Minister.
Bernard, you should give some thought
to drafting a face-saving letter
of resignation for the Minister.
"Dear Jim..."
"Dear Jim"?
"We haven't seen enough of each other lately.
"Are you free for lunch at Chequers on Sunday?
"We shall just be the family.
I look forward to seeing you."
I don't think I...?
It has paid off!
A conspiracy! That drink with Mark Spencer!
"...not seen enough... Lunch at Chequers..."
It's hand-written!
Do you realise how much it's worth?
I believe the going rate is thirty pieces of silver!
No, Humphrey. Loyalty and integrity
have received their just rewards.
Loyalty?!
I have backed you up the same way
you have always backed me up.
Isn't that so?
Sorry? Did you say something?
I think he said, "Yes, Minister."
http://episode-heaven.rt.hu