Howard Wolowitz.
Hey, Howard.
Dave Roeger here at NASA.
We need to talk
about your upcoming mission.
Yes, yes, I've been doing
my push-ups.
I'm still stuck at nine, but...
...that's going all the way down
with no one holding me.
That's great, uh,
but that's not why I called.
We've run into a bit of a snafu.
Your Soyuz capsule failed
the pressurization test,
so bottom line,
mission's been scrubbed.
You're kidding.
So what does that mean?
Uh-huh.
Boy, I got to tell you,
I'm really disappointed.
This was my dream
ever since I was a little kid.
Okay, well, uh,
thanks for the call.
Yep, you, too.
Yes! Thank you!
Oh! Oh...
I'm not gonna die in space!
I'm gonna die
the way God intended,
in my late 50s,
with a heart full of pastrami.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x23
The Launch Acceleration
Original Air Date on May 3, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I'm going to need
a larger shirt.
This one's a little tight
under the arms.
Okay.
Do you think maybe it's tight
because you're wearing
long underwear?
Yes, of course
that's why it's tight.
All right, let me
rephrase the question.
Why are you wearing
long underwear?
You're kidding.
Shouldn't the question be:
why aren't you?
No, it should be: why are you?
(sighs) Leonard,
these rental tuxedos have been
worn by hundreds
of sweaty strangers.
I don't like my own sweat
touching my skin,
how do you think
I feel about theirs?
Why don't you
slip this on?
Said the hangman
offering a noose.
Well, that wasn't
as entertaining
as when he rents bowling shoes,
but it was right up there.
Well, that's it.
My orders have been rescinded.
I am officially "no go"
to space.
I'm sorry, Howard,
but I got to tell you,
I'm a little relieved
you're not going.
Why?
Come on, you were
gonna go up in a rocket
designed in the 1960s
by the Russians.
Yeah, so?
When was the last time
you were at Best Buy
and you heard someone say, "Ooh,
check out this Blu-ray player,
it must be good,
it was built in Russia"?
Well, their technology
isn't that bad.
When you come back to Earth
in a Soyuz capsule, you free-fall
from space
at 500 miles per hour,
and the only thing
that slows you down
is a little parachute
that pops out
right before you crash
into the ground.
And the whole thing
was designed
by the same brilliant minds
who were unable to capture
Rocky and Bullwinkle.
All right, well, whatever.
I wasn't worried.
You weren't?
Let me explain the difference
between you and me.
You watch
Star Trek; I live it.
Oh, please. I don't remember
the episode of Star Trek
where the guy
never goes to space
and brags about it
in a tuxedo store.
Make all the jokes you want,
but there's only
one of us here brave enough
to almost do
what I almost did.
Ah, much better.
You must be burning up.
A little. But not more
than your urethras
will be after whatever's
in those pants swims up them.
Well...
I cut quite the dashing,
yet hygienic figure, don't I?
I look like the Flash
about to get married.
Oh! A tissue! A tissue!
Oh, good Lord!
Uh, where's he going?
He keeps emergency
Purell in the car.
Keys! Keys! Keys!
Hey, you.
Before I come in,
you should know, I have gas.
For the record,
not your worst opening line.
Check it out.
It's the gas I use
in my free-electron laser
to support high voltages.
But it also has an
interesting secondary use.
Here. Breathe this in.
B-Before I do it, if you're
a cop you have tell me, right?
Just try it.
Okay.
What's it supposed to...
Oh, my God, that's so freaky!
♪ You're a mean one ♪
♪ Mr. Grinch. ♪
Okay. Me, me, me. Ready?
Leonard, I am your father.
I have never been
more attracted to a woman
who sounds like a man
in my life.
Oh...
Mm.
Hey... you know
how we've been...
taking things slow?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I've been thinking, and...
maybe I'm ready to...
take things a little... faster.
Oh...
great.
Mm-hmm.
And I promise,
after waiting four months,
fast is what you're gonna get.
You know, just-just one thing.
Look, we're in a really
great place right now,
and I don't want to do anything
that will make stuff
all weird again.
So we won't let it get weird.
Okay. Oh, and just a heads-up...
mm, since the last time
you saw me naked,
I got a Cookie Monster tattoo.
The acceptable responses
when you see it
are "awesome" or nothing.
What about...
Cookies!
Amy?
7:00, right on time.
It's not an accident.
I waited outside your door
for 20 minutes.
Well, dinner's almost ready.
I must say,
I was surprised
you chose to spend
our date night
in your apartment.
As I mentioned,
the Pasadena City Council is
debating longer crosswalk times,
and later, the LEGO store is
having a midnight madness sale.
You ask anyone,
that's a hot date.
Tempting choices,
but I have something special
planned for tonight.
What can be more special
than having
an adequate amount of time
to cross the street
on your way to buy
a tiny LEGO Indiana Jones?
With our friends moving forward
in their relationships,
I've decided that we should
make progress in ours as well.
Oh, dear Lord.
Two years ago,
we didn't even know each other,
and now I'm
in your apartment after dark.
How much faster
can this thing go?
I had a feeling
you'd be reluctant,
which is why
I'm going to dip
into my neurobiological
bag of tricks.
Oh, you brain monkeys
kill me. Dip away.
I have devised
an experiment that
I believe will increase
your feelings for me
in an accelerated time frame.
And how do you propose
to do that?
Uh, hope you're not thinking
about some sort
of LSD thought control.
Because there's
only one mind-expanding drug
that this man enjoys,
and that's called school.
Human beings form emotional
attachments as they grow up.
In your case, to your mother,
superheroes, et cetera.
I'm going to attempt
an experiment that will
get you to transfer
those feelings to me.
Well,
seems what's on the menu tonight
is malarkey with
a big side of poppycock.
We'll see.
Let's start with a little
romantic dinner music, shall we?
Super Mario Bros. theme?
Yes.
I see what you're doing.
You're attempting
to build on the work
of Ebbinghaus by triggering
an involuntary memory
of me playing that game--
admittedly the happiest
600 hours of my childhood...
...but it won't work.
Fine. There's no reason
we still can't have
a lovely dinner.
Why don't you have a seat.
Boink! Boink!
May I offer you
something to drink?
You know I don't drink.
Not even...
strawberry Quik?
I love strawberry Quik.
It's my favorite
pink fluid,
narrowly beating out
Pepto-Bismol.
Oh, I know.
I think it will go nicely
with what I have prepared...
for dinner.
Spaghetti with little pieces
of hot dog cut up in it!
Just like your mommy
used to make.
Oh...
yummy, yummy!
We should do this more often.
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry. I did,
I crossed a line.
I didn't mean to!
Who says something
like that right in the middle
of sex?!
I don't know,
it just came out.
People say weird things
during sex all the time.
Okay, well, they
sure as hell don't say that.
It was the heat of the moment.
No,
the heat of the moment is,
"Ooh, yeah, just like that,"
not "will you marry me?"
I'm sorry.
Just-just give me
another chance.
Why, so you can crawl
under the covers and go,
"Hey, baby,
want to go look for houses
in neighborhoods
with good schools?"
Again, I'm sorry.
You know, with Howard
and Bernadette getting married,
I got caught up
in a little wedding fever.
I take it back.
You can't
take something like that back.
I mean, what are we
even supposed to do now?
Okay, at some point,
we'll look back
and this is going
to be a funny story.
Why don't we just
start doing that now?
You're kidding.
No.
Hey, do you remember...
...that time when I proposed
to you in bed?
And you were all, like,
"What are you doing?"
That was so funny.
So funny.
It's not funny.
Give it a minute.
Is that a little smile
I see there?
I should go.
Hey, I was thinking.
For our first dance
at the wedding,
what if we learn the final number
from Dirty Dancing?
You're kidding.
No,
come on.
How cool would that be?
Me running
into your arms...
you lifting me up
into the air.
Oh, you're in a good mood.
Yeah, well, why
wouldn't I be?
You know, I'm marrying
the girl of my dreams,
and I finally got
my mother to agree
not to come on
our honeymoon.
Oh, hang on.
Oh, it's NASA.
Wolowitz.
Oh! Hi, Dave.
What's up?
No kidding. Really?
Well,
that's... great news.
Great, great news.
All right, I'll watch my e-mail
for the details.
Okay, talk soon.
What's so great?
It looks like I'm going
into space after all.
Oh, Howie,
that's wonderful!
Uh-huh, wonderful.
Yay...
What happened?
I thought
they canceled your mission.
Th-They did.
But NASA really wants
my telescope up
on the space station,
so they're putting me
on an earlier launch.
When?
A...
week from Friday.
What? We're getting
married that Sunday.
You're right!
I-I can't go to space.
I have to get married,
and no one can say
that's not a good reason.
I'll call him back.
Wait. I don't want to be
the one who stands
in your way.
Well, too bad, you already did.
It's a done deal.
Oh, well.
But I forgive you.
No. That's not how I want
to start our marriage,
killing your dream?
We'll have the wedding
when you get back.
But wh-what about
all the plans
and the guests?
We'll call them.
Although my dad's
gonna go a little nutso
over losing his deposits.
You're right, he is!
Your dad's gonna be furious.
There's no way he's
gonna let us postpone this wedding.
Well, we tried.
I'll talk to him.
He won't say no to his little girl.
No!
I-I should talk to him,
man to man.
But, Howie, my dad
can be a bully.
He's gonna make you cancel
your space flight.
We can only hope...
that he doesn't.
Bishop to queen four,
level two.
Check.
Sheldon...
knight takes bishop.
You all right?
I'm fine.
Are you?
You left your queen
exposed from above,
you trapped your
knight in the corner,
and you keep sighing
and saying, "Why me?"
Very well.
Can I ask you
a question about women?
We got you that book last year.
Wasn't everything in there?
No, I'm having
a relationship problem with Amy.
And by the way,
that book gave me nightmares.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I screwed things up
pretty good with Penny.
Look at us,
Leonard...
engaging in the social
convention of men bellyaching
about their ol' ladies.
I guess we are.
So, what's going on?
Believe it or not,
Amy has embarked on a campaign
to increase my feelings
for her by making me happy.
I'm sorry, that must be very
difficult for you.
It's awful.
This morning,
she arranged for me
to be an Amtrak junior conductor
for the day.
It-It's usually
only open to children.
She got them
to make an exception.
Shame on her.
They let me
blow the whistle, Leonard.
She's good.
I know.
And it gets worse.
Her efforts are causing me
to have affectionate
feelings for her
at inappropriate times.
You mean, like in bed
or in the shower?
No!
Would you please stop
referencing that infernal book?
For example, this morning,
I was calculating
the random motion
of virtual particles
in a vacuum,
when suddenly
the particles morphed
into an image
of Amy's dandruff...
...gently cascading down
onto her pale,
slightly hunched shoulders.
What has that vixen
done to me, Leonard?
And how do I make it stop?
Well, if you had
a physical relationship,
I'd say propose during sex.
Turns out that's
a real mood killer.
I assume we're talking
about you now?
Yeah.
So, that's
how this works?
I complain,
and then you complain,
and no one offers any solutions?
Pretty much.
Well, no wonder
the women are winning.
Mr. Rostenkowski,
are you busy?
Oh, just looking at some
old pictures. Come on in.
Family pictures,
or...?
H-Holy crap, that's
a dead person.
Last murder case
before I retired.
How many bodies
do you see there?
Careful,
it's a trick question.
I'm not sure.
Nah, you'll never get it.
It's a fraction.
How about that.
Anyway,
sir, I need to talk
to you about something.
Walnut?
No, thank you.
I'm allergic.
Oh, sure.
My partner used to have that.
He's dead now.
From nuts?
Nah, his wife shot him.
But she was nuts,
so in a way...
Nice story.
Anyway,
the reason I wanted
to talk to you is
NASA has moved up
my launch
to the International
Space Station.
Yeah, so?
So...
the date is going
to conflict
with me marrying
your daughter.
Now, I know what you're
going to say-- I made
a commitment to Bernadette
and to your family
and I've got a hell
of a lot of nerve
coming in here and demanding
that we postpone this thing.
Well, message heard
and understood.
Mission canceled.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
I'm sorry.
May I be excused?
No, you may not.
Let me tell you something.
When I first met you...
You just gonna stand there?
I'm sorry, I didn't know,
is this going to...
Well, I should sit...
May I be seat...
Well, I'll just sit.
When I first met you,
I didn't like you.
I'm aware of that, sir.
But then you and I
had some time together.
Uh-huh.
It did not get better.
Right, right.
That silly Beatle haircut
and...
you riding around
on a red Vespa,
and you're still living
at home with your mother.
To be honest, I thought
Bernadette chose you
to punish me.
But then I heard about
your astronaut thing,
and I realized
I judged you too fast.
Maybe you are
the right guy
for my little girl.
Oh, I am.
And just so you know,
I'd still be an astronaut,
even if I didn't go to space.
I've got an I.D. card
and a NASA golf shirt.
No, no, you got to go.
You can't turn down
an opportunity like this.
B-But what about the wedding
and all the money you put
down for the reception?
You let me worry about that.
You go up to that
space station,
and you make me proud.
Um, okay.
You got a problem with that?
All right, look, I'm
gonna level with you.
I'm terrified about
going into space.
What if I don't
make it back?
It's gonna be okay, son.
You really think so?
Of course.
A pretty girl like Bernadette...
she'll find a new guy.
Hey.
Off to work?
Yeah.
Have a nice night.
Okay, you, too.
Penny, just, wait.
I've been thinking
about what I said
when we were in bed
the other night.
Yeah, I've been
thinking about it, too.
I noticed you never answered me.
You're right.
No.
Uh, follow-up.
Are we still dating?
Yep.
Is it still weird
'cause I proposed?
Yep.
I have a couple more
quick questions.
Do you want to call me
from the car?
No!
Think I played that
pretty well.
Hello, Leonard.
What are you doing?
We're playing doctor.
Star Trek style.
I'm in hell, Leonard.
Don't stop.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==