He loves these intimate spaces.
It's where he tries out
all his new stuff.
Le Jean's a genius.
He's bringing them all to a climax.
Holding off hitting that sweet
spot as long as possible.
They all worship him.
You were awesome, babe. Bless ya,
babes, bless ya, but, nah...
No, you smashed it.
It wasn't tight, you know what I mean?
It was. It was absolutely...
I was dropping beats all
over the place, man.
No, it was amazing, baby.
I didn't feel it, it was like...
- Yo. You the guy buying up all the
clubs, right? - Gary Harbinger.
Gary is the owner of the
Shimmers chain.
Nice, man, nice. And you
remember Kelly Sumner?
He's been overseeing
the legal side.
My granddaughters are
your biggest fans.
They download all your records.
Safe, man, safe.
What about somedrinks, yeah?
Good idea, good idea.
Yo, Darryl!
Get these guys some, I don't know,
Jagermeisters or something like that.
We're making history tonight.
Just to let you know your car's here
to take you to the helipad, OK?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Guys,
we have to wrap this up quick.
Are you going somewhere? Am I going
some... What, is this guy for real?
Le Jean plays a set at Pacha on Ibiza
every Tuesday.
- It's a legendary night.
- Everybody knows that, don't they?
You want to attach my
name to your clubs
and you don't know about
my Pacha set?
Well, Marcus here handles the acts
and the day-to-day business...
Whoa, whoa.
See, haul up, haul up.
See...
Are you...
Are you saying that
what I do is an act?
Like, what, like I'm some
kind of mobile disco pig,
available for weddings
and Bar Mitzvahs?
Easy, big fella, easy.
Do you know who I am?
Of course he does, Garry,
of course he does,
he's just, er, he's very
protective of his image, yeah?
It's a credibility issue.
Yeah, it's a credibility issue,
it's all about mystique as well.
Did you see the people down there?
Did you see them?
They don't come to one of my gigs
cos they want to listen to music, man.
It's a pilgrimage, dread.
And because I got that credibility,
those people out there
are my disciples, they worship
at the decks of Le Jean.
And that is what sells.
Do you feel me?
I feel you.
All right, look, I done schooling
you, right? Peace and love.
Let's get down to business, yeah?
One hundred grand in fifties,
as you requested.
It's red. It's my colour.
Gentlemen, enjoy the drinks.
Enjoy the company. Laters, yeah?
We should have stayed a bit longer.
What, anything to do with
the nearly naked girls?
We only booked
them for an hour,
someone should make
sure they get home safely.
The kid's all heart.
Thanks. Drinks are on us.
- You Fisk?
- No, I'm the Easter Bunny.
You got something for me, or not?
My employer would look very
favourably on the individual
that put this guy out of business...
permanently.
Can you do it?
- Won't be easy.
The five grand's a down payment.
There's another 15 when it's done.
sync and corrections by Bellows
www.addic7ed.com
Cor, what's that pong?
It smells like dead, wet dog
in here. Edward.
Hold your horses.
I'm nearly there.
Oh, look, more bags. What, it's not
rancid enough in here?
You sure you got
enough rubbish, Ed?
- It piles up, Sean. You'd be amazed.
- Surely this is a health hazard?
Yes, you'd think so, wouldn't you?
Erm, do you maybe want to explain
what's going on, Edward?
It's a bloody outrage. That's what's
going on. It's a bloody scandal.
The council has started
fining you 200 quid
for leaving your rubbish
out over night.
- Eh? - See, they pick it up between
eight and nine on a Tuesday morning.
Before, you could leave your
bags out on a Monday night.
Now, some jobsworth environmental
officer comes round
and tells me I've got to put them
out just before they get here.
- What do I pay me rates for?
- Well, take it out the back, then.
There's no access.
Now I've got to schlep it
through the bar
where there's customers.
Then this same inspector
comes round
and tells me I can't take the rubbish
through the bar during opening hours.
So you can't leave them out overnight
or bring them through in the morning?
You're a bit stuffed then, ain't ya?
- Exactly. It's a thingy-o
- It's a paradox? - No.
- No, a catch-22? - No
- Chinese puzzle? - No.
- A conundrum?
- No.
- A mystery within a puzzle wrapped up
in an enigma? - Tell you what it is.
It's a downright flamin'
liberty, that's what it is.
- Ooh, I can feel a rant coming on.
- Into the office then.
Ed, when you've finished moaning,
can I have a full English?
Do you lot ever listen
to a word I say?
Yeah, of course we do. Bags,
bleedin' councils, rates, by-laws,
flamin' liberties, eggs over easy,
chunky toast,
mug of tea, and three sugars.
OK, everyone.
Listen up.
Michael Stone, aka Mickey Bricks.
As some of you'll know,
Stone and his crew
have been giving the fraud
squad the run-around for years.
I've had a whisper that their
next big scoop is on our patch.
I'm not having it.
I want them shut down.
Are fraud all right with this, guv?
I'll talk them through it
when Stone and his crew are locked up.
I want round-the-clock surveillance.
Albert Stroller. The Roper.
Been grifting since the Boer War.
He's got contacts all over the city.
Ash "Three Socks" Morgan.
The Fixer.
He knows more tricks
than a cartful of monkeys.
But this is where we start.
Sean and Emma Kennedy.
The newbies.
Stroller found them making
short cons on the street
and brought them into
the fold.
He and Stone are training them up,
moulding them into
their own seedy image.
These two are Stone's
soft underbelly.
If we get to them, we can
penetrate the inner circle,
tear it apart.
That's how we get him.
Read the file, get to know
them, how they operate.
Let's show the third
floor how it's done.
All right, come on,
you heard the man.
- Ma'am. Didn't see you there.
- Who assigned you to this case?
My brief is to catch criminals
and hit my crime target figures.
I wasn't aware that I had to
have every case authorised
before I launch an investigation.
And does the fraud squad know
you're going after Stone?
The information I've been given
is that they're planning a job,
I can't to this stage determine
whether it's fraud or not.
Don't play games with me, lnspector.
I'm just an old-fashioned copper.
Find the bad guys. Put 'em away.
Some of us have to get
our hands dirty.
And that's how you intend to conduct
the case, is it? Get dirty?
If I have to.
I will not have this department
brought into disrepute.
Everything gets done by the
book, the same book I'll be
throwing at you if I find out
you've been cutting corners.
Yes, Ma'am.
I mean it, lnspector.
You have to catch him
with the cash in his hand.
Any room for doubt and you'll end up
embarrassing us all.
Oh, I'll catch him, Ma'am.
I guarantee it.
OK, so our new mark is
Linda Runcorn.
The story is that she's the CEO of
an online restaurant and hotel guide.
It's got a huge tourist readership,
so it's very influential.
However, excellence is not the best
way to guarantee a good review.
The larger chains escape, but
she tells the smaller hotels
and family restaurants that if they
don't make it worth her while,
she'll put them out of
business.
- Worth her while by handing
over cash? - Precisely.
The smaller hotels and restaurants
survive on reputation.
She operates on fear, and once she's
got hold of you, she bleeds you dry.
Character traits? A bully.
She sucks up to the bigger chains,
while bullying the smaller clients
who can't afford to fight back. Nasty.
- What's our way in?
- Her mum's family, the Toppings.
Had a bit of land and a noble
line going back centuries,
but they cut off her grandmother,
Helen Topping, without a penny
when she married a builder.
Seems the family thought
he was beneath her.
But to this day, Linda wears
a bracelet given to her
by her Grandmother which bears
the Topping family crest.
So what's the game?
An inheritance scam?
Yeah. We use a long-lost relative
Linda's never heard of.
One of the Toppings. A maiden aunt
who died without making a will,
leaving behind an estate which
Linda is the sole heir to.
Which just happens to be worth
a small fortune. Exactly.
Yeah, I'm here.
I'll call you when I'm done.
- Miss Runcorn?
- Yes.
Hello. I'm Holly Patterson,
Greyshot Genealogy.
I was rather surprised
to get your letter.
- Oh?
- How did you find me?
- The voting register.
- Did I ask for water?
For heaven's sake, just put it down.
We'll call you when we want something.
They fuss all over you, then when
you actually want something,
when you want to actually
order something,
they're nowhere to be bloody seen.
Quite.
So, what's this potentially
exciting news exactly?
Well, every few months,
the Treasury releases
a list of estates that are intestate.
- That means... - People who died
without leaving a will. Yes. Yes.
You're one of those bloody
heir hunters, aren't you?
Oh, well, we prefer
probate investigators.
All the same thing,
like ambulance chasers.
I can't imagine what you
found on my father's side,
they didn't have two
pennies to rub together.
What is it?
A tin bath?
Well, actually, it's a relative
on your mother's side.
- Oh. My mother's side?
- Yes, the Toppings...
Now, this is your great-aunt Irene.
Irene Topping. Excuse me.
Sorry, I just need to check this.
She's the sister of your
maternal grandmother.
Now, your great-aunt passed away.
She was childless, she never married
and she didn't leave a will.
So her estate passed to
the next in line.
- Which is you. -Me?
- Yes. It appears so.
Well, I don't suppose there's
anything to get too excited about.
I never really believed
all those rumours
about my mother's
aristocratic family.
The old bag probably left me a
tatty old armchair and some cats.
Well, she actually left you
jewellery and property
worth in the region of £4.7 million.
And, as far as we can tell,
you are the sole heir.
Well, that's different.
I mean, obviously, I am devastated
about poor old Great-Aunt Irene.
But... Sorry,
did you say 4.7 million?
- I did.
- O-M-G.
Well, it was a
pleasure to meet you.
You'll be hearing from us soon.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, it's me. Done.
- Hook, line and sinker.
- OK, good. See you back here.
Well?
Some old rubbish about an old
aunt leaving her a fortune.
All right, stay on it.
Katherine Farmer.
We haven't seen you for a while.
Still picking pockets?
No idea what you're
banging on about, mate.
Really?
You going to tell me what I'm doing
here, or what? You know this man?
Don't ring any bells. Sean Kennedy.
Never seen him before.
Really? Let me jog your memory.
We found this with your stuff.
That ain't mine.
Intent to supply Class-As.
You can't stitch me up like that.
Can't I? I want to see a brief.
This isn't your first
offence, is it, sweetheart?
It's not going to be three
months, out in a fortnight.
You'll do serious time for this.
Now look at the picture again.
Sean Kennedy.
All right.
I may have seen him knocking about.
It was more than that, wasn't it?
Used to run around together,
get into scrapes.
We was just kids.
I don't see him any more.
What happened?
His sister put a stop to it?
Didn't want a nasty little pilferer
like you horning in on their double
act? It weren't like that. Whatever.
I think it's time you and
Sean got reacquainted.
Why? I'm going fishing,
and you're my bait.
Do I look like a maggot? You'll
infiltrate this gang he's joined
and report back to me.
No. I ain't no grass.
I see you've had a little girl.
What is she now?
Two?
Be a shame. Drug-dealing mum
locked up, kid put into care...
You leave her out of this.
She's be a teenager
when you got out.
Wouldn't even know you.
She'd be with a new mum.
- You can't do this.
- I'm a police officer, sweetheart,
I can pretty much do anything I want.
Now, you do what I'm telling you,
or your brat will be in a foster
home in time for her tea.
What's this here, a family crest?
The Topping family.
We need an exact match.
By tomorrow, you said?
- Can it be done? - It's not easy.
You have to get the stone right.
The shape and the clarity, and the
way the light dances off the...
- Hmm. That's odd.
- Something wrong?
Not at all, but you might
want to rethink a replica.
- Why? - Because if
this is what I think it is,
a replica won't stand up to any
serious scrutiny.
It's fine with the naked eye, but if
she gets it authenticated...
What?
- What is it, Bob?
- Cushion-cut, 20-carat, azure stone.
If I'm not mistaken,
we are looking at a
150-year-old Kashmir sapphire.
Well, that sounds expensive.
It's hard to tell from a snap,
but if this is the real thing,
it could be 20-30 grand.
It won't stand up to close scrutiny,
but I'll get you the replica
by tomorrow, all right?
Cheers.
Bloody hell. You spilled my shampoo,
you clumsy....
Oh, I'm so sorry. Watch the suit,
will you? It's a nice one, then?
I said get your grubby
mitts off my threads.
Now tootle off back to your caravan.
There's a dear.
Get me another bottle.
She's stolen my wallet.
Stop that girl.
Police. What you talking about?
I ain't done nothing.
Hey. What's going on here?
City of London Police.
- What seems to be the problem?
- This geezer is sexually harassing me.
I wouldn't touch you with
a jack hammer, love.
Both of you calm down. Sir, why don't
you explain to me what's happened?
This grotty little chav
stole my wallet.
Do you want a smack,
cheese breath?
I want her to turn out
her pockets right now.
I want my money back.
And I want you to calm down.
I'm not going to warn you again, sir.
Do as he says.
Empty your pockets.
- It's not there.
- Well, are you sure it's missing, sir?
Yes. I keep it inside my jacket.
Why don't you check
your other pockets?
I don't see why, I don't keep...
I think you owe this young lady
an apology, don't you?
- I'm sure she...
- Oh, come on, then, apologise.
Sir.
- I'm most terribly sorry.
- Yeah, well, up yours, creep.
No, seriously, did you
see that guy's face?
When I accused him of
sexually harassing me,
I thought he was going to puke.
What happened to you? Kat Farmer
used to be the best in the business.
Used to be able to
steal anything, and you
got caught nicking a wallet.
Come on, girl!
Who says I wanted his wallet?
Whoa, nice.
Shit.
- You know, I never thought
I'd see you again. - Why's that?
You're in this fancy new crew now.
I'm still nicking watches.
I might have moved on,
but I haven't changed.
I'll never forget
what you did for me.
Yeah, well, I ain't a grass.
I know.
I was worried about you in there.
It weren't that bad. Regular meals
every day. A roof over my head.
It's good that you
were worried though.
You ain't done so bad for yourself,
have you? Well, you know...
I got a little girl now.
What?
Yeah, she'll be three next month.
I can't believe you're a mum.
Dad's a bit of a waste of space
though, I ain't seen him in two years.
I'm sorry to hear that. Don't be.
Like I said, he's a waste of space.
Look, Sean, now you're all sorted,
I could really use a leg up.
Uh?
There must be some little job I can
do in that fancy crew of yours?
Sweep up? Make the tea?
Stand there and look pretty?
Kat, it's not really that...
I'll get Mum to look
after Laurel for a bit.
Truth is, Sean, I'm really skint.
Oh. No. I don't want your charity,
you know me better than that.
I want to work for it.
Ash sent these over
from the printers.
These are fake title deeds to a
30-acre pile in Northumberland.
Great.
And documents showing all the debts
still owed to the estate.
Fantastic.
Hey, guys.
- Sean, what the hell are you...?
- I see you've brought company.
All right?
I'm Kat.
Like your gaff.
This all from grifting then?
- All right, Emms?
Long time no see. - Kat.
- Wow. Look at you, all glammed up.
- Look, she's an old friend, OK?
I said she could help out with a job.
She used to hang around with me
and Emma back in the day.
She just needs a leg up, that's all.
It's one job, and I'll
pay her from my share.
Are you serious? I mean, I'm sorry,
this is nothing personal...
I can vouch for her
and so can Emma.
That aside, I owe her.
She kept me from going to prison.
- That was a long time ago, Sean.
- That's what I said.
It makes no difference.
I was 15, and she could
have seriously reduced
her sentence if she'd grassed
me up, but she didn't.
You two, of all people,
should respect that.
How many of your old
friends have turned up?
And we've taken care of
every single one of them.
Kid's got a point.
- Emma?
- Oh, she's a train crash.
But she's all right.
OK.
We'll work her into the con.
- Looks like she's in, Guv.
- All right. Stay on it.
OK. So tomorrow, Emma
goes to see Linda
and reveals the news about
the debts owed on the estate.
But before she starts asking
questions, show her the bracelet.
Yeah, there might be
an issue with that.
An issue?
Seedy Bob says the sapphire
on the bracelet might be
a rare Kashmir sapphire,
and very hard for Bob to forge.
- So if she gets it authenticated...
- Yeah. They'll spot it.
What if we do a switch?
What, swap Linda's bracelet
for Seedy Bob's replica?
Yeah. So she gets her own
bracelet authenticated.
What if she compares the two?
No, no, apparently, the replica will
look the same to the naked eye.
It's only if she gets it examined
that there's a problem.
Even if that's true, it's
still a tricky manoeuvre.
Not for Kat. She could easily swap
the fake bracelet for the real one.
Seriously, guys. It makes perfect
sense. It's what she specialises in.
She could do that switch with her
hands tied behind her back.
Well, it is what I do. Kat can go
along as Emma's assistant,
Emma can distract Linda and
Kat can move in for the kill.
It makes sense.
Lovely morning.
It was.
And there was me thinking this was the
beginning of a beautiful friendship.
Yeah, well, think again.
So what have you got for me?
They're conning some bird.
Linda Runcorn.
An inheritance scam, I know all that.
Tell me something I don't know.
They've got this fake bracelet that
proves it's legit, or something...
Except there's a snag.
They think that the sapphire in
the bracelet might be from Kashmir.
Could be worth a few quid.
Maybe more than a few quid.
So they're worried this Linda
might get it valued?
Yeah. They want me to
help Emma do the switch.
I nick the real one and put
the fake one back on her wrist.
So, Runcorn gets her own valued,
thinks the whole thing's kosher.
All right.
Do what they want for now.
Keep reporting back to me.
And one other thing.
I want you to slip this in
Emma Kennedy's case. No way.
They've been all right by me so far.
I'm not doing that.
OK, no? If you don't want
to do it, that's fine.
- If you don't feel like it.
- I've done what you asked.
But we're not finished, are we?
I make one call to Social Services,
tell them you've been arrested
for dealing in Class-A drugs, they'll
pick your kid up within the hour.
You want me off your back?
Then do as you're told.
At the end of this, you'll never
have to set eyes on me again.
Well, here are the deeds
to your aunt's estate.
And here's a picture of the
house in Northumberland.
- It's a nice gaff.
- Yes. Thank you, Miss Hunter.
I've just got to tell you about a
slight problem before we continue.
Problem? Well, as you can
see from the house there,
it's a couple of centuries old,
and a few years ago,
- it started suffering rom subsidence.
- Nasty. My nan had that.
Yes.
Your great-aunt Irene,
she had to get builders in,
and apparently, now, they're claiming
that they haven't been fully paid.
Can I, er, get some water? Hmm?
A glass of water.
I'm not being funny, but
it feels like a family of
badgers just moved in.
- How much are they owed?
-Sorry? These builders.
- Oh. Yes. Er, 100,000.
One hundred grand?
For subsidence?
Well, it is a massive house.
And very old.
And as the builders are
threatening court action,
they will need to be paid before
the transaction can be completed.
Why? Sorry?
I mean, why before? Can't the debts
be absorbed by the estate?
Well, it could be, I suppose,
but time is of the essence.
The builders are threatening
to force the estate
into administration over
these unpaid bills.
You can't imagine how complicated
that would make things.
The legal fees alone would treble
what you owe the builders
and it could mean that you wouldn't
see your inheritance for five years.
I see.
And you're sure it's my aunt?
Sorry, am I sure? I'm not going to
suddenly find there's been a mix-up?
Not if I've done my job
properly, no.
I don't remember having
a Great-Aunt Irene.
And I don't want to
fork out 100,000
and then find out I'm paying
somebody else's bloody bills.
I am quite sure that it is
your aunt.
Actually, one of the items that she
left was a sapphire bracelet,
very much like the one
you're wearing. A bracelet?
Have you got it?
Yes. Show me.
If you could...
It's just somewhere down here...
Oh. Oh, my God. Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's fine.
I'm always doing this.
Mum says I could start World
War III, I'm so accident prone.
It's fine. I can manage.
Miss Hunter, why don't you give
Miss Runcorn the bracelet now?
Well, it certainly looks authentic.
Yes, and it has the crest,
and everything.
I'll have to get it authenticated.
But if it's all above board, I'll
sign the papers and pay the debts.
That's great. Great.
You won't regret it.
You said we have to move quickly.
Yes. How quickly?
Well, it would help if you paid
the debts in cash.
Cash? I'm not sure.
They are builders.
Well, if it'll oil the wheels
a little, then so be it.
Great. Great.
That was good work.
Thank you.
Leg it. Leg it.
Kat.
Can I help you, officer?
Oi.
Guv.
Put her in the car.
That's not mine.
I can walk there myself...
No.
I don't know what happened,
they just came out of nowhere.
How did she get drugs on her, Kat?
Emma doesn't even do drugs.
They weren't mine, if
that's what you're asking.
I went with her, I did what
you asked me to do,
and then we went outside and...
Kat's right. It's not her fault.
Something else must be going on.
The cops must have planted the gear
on Emma. I'm so sorry, Sean...
She's at the Barber Street station.
She was arrested by
Detective lnspector Fisk.
Sid Fisk? You know him?
Yeah, he's bent as a nine bob note.
This is how he operates. He frames
people and then bangs them up.
Well, it's ridiculous.
What does Fisk want with Emma?
This can't be just about Emma.
It's about all of us.
I'm going to see her. On my own.
Meet me at Eddie's in an hour.
Ahem...
Excuse me. Roger Wyles, senior
partner, Wyles, Clark and Foster.
I'm representing Emma Kennedy.
If I am delayed from seeing my
client in any way whatsoever,
there will be a serious complaint
made to the IPCC.
- Take this gentleman down to cell
four, please. - Thank you.
- Fisk.
- 'Sir, Stone's come to see her.'
- Miss Kennedy. Roger Wyles.
Your solicitor. - Yeah, of course.
I have no idea what happened.
It's all right. It doesn't makeany sense.
It's OK, it's OK, we'll work it out.
How's Sean?
He's OK. Except he wants
to drive a JCB into the building.
Good plan.
Needs fine tuning.
Yep. I'll get you out of here, OK?
I'll think of something.
- We won't go further with the con on
Linda, we'll figure it out. - No.
- Emma... - No, I don't want you
to do that, right?
We've come too far. When she
gets the bracelet authenticated...
No, no, no, no, stop, stop.
Think a minute.
Look at what happened.
Look at where you are.
Yes. And it would feel a whole lot
worse if it was all for nothing.
We've done the switch.
We've shown her the paperwork.
All that's left to do now is collect.
It'd be crazy to back out now.
I'll keep.
He's got some front coming
in here, I'll give him that.
You want me to nick him, Guv?
- For what?
- Impersonating a brief?
Nah. I'm going to make him
an offer he can't refuse.
For the girl?
You're learning, sergeant.
I thought you wanted Bricks banged up.
At all costs, you said.
He will be.
The thing is, he's a clever boy,
that's why no-one's got him in the past.
You can't beat him at his own game.
So I'll play him at mine.
Nice and simple, no way out.
When he accepts my offer
and hands over the cash,
I'll get him for attempting
to bribe a police officer.
Time's up.
Hello, Michael.
Fancy a coffee?
She's doing my nut in.
Emma's a tough cookie.
She'll be OK.
She's not going to be OK.
Not unless we do something.
Like what? Boost her
from the cop shop?
Let's just wait until we
hear what Michael says.
Try not to think about it
until we hear from him.
- I sorted out the bin problem.
- Not now, Ed.
They're refurbishing
the block next door,
so they've got a skip, so I just
bung the bags over the wall.
It's not permanent, but a bloke
thinks it'll be there six months.
It's not a great time, Eddie.
Sorry, mate. I thought you might be
interested, you know, as mates.
Yeah, well, we just hit a bit of
a bump in the road. Oh, right.
Where's Em?
- It's Kat, isn't it?
- Yeah, that's right.
So what are you, like, a new
member of the crew, or what?
I'm not helping here, am I?
Not really, but we'll be OK,
we'll think of something.
Yeah, mate, yeah, sure.
Of course you will.
Yeah, sure.
Emma Kennedy had cocaine
with a street value of
five grand in her bag.
She's looking at intent to supply
and a pretty hefty sentence.
It's funny how you know
the exact value.
Pay for it yourself, did you?
I'm sure I don't know what you're
suggesting, Michael.
Do you know, I have a lot of
respect for the police. I do.
They have a job to do and I'm fair
game, and if they can catch me, then
no hard feelings.
But a bent cop?
Someone who's not interested
in catching criminals,
just lining his own pocket.
That's got to be the
lowest of the low.
Spare me the honour amongst
thieves bullshit, Stone.
I couldn't be less interested
in what you think of me.
Then what are you interested in?
They told me you were a bright boy.
Spell it out for me.
Fifty grand and the girl walks.
- 50 grand cash. - Shouldn't be too
steep for you. The great Mickey Bricks.
How do I know I can trust you?
You don't.
But as far as I can see, you
don't have much choice, do you?
You've always got a choice.
And my grandmother always told me,
never make deals with fools
or bent cops.
You're making a big mistake, Stone.
How is she? She's a little
shaken up, but she's coping.
- Is she angry with me? - No, mostly,
she's angry with herself.
I think we've sat here like
lemons for long enough.
- Let's go and help her. - I'm working
on it. - Not hard enough. - Sean.
No, I'm sorry, Albert, I just want
to do something.
This is what Fisk wants,
us losing our focus.
That's why he planted
the coke on Emma.
We have to keep our heads
in what we're doing.
Not get distracted.
- Carry on with the con?
- Yes, all the ground work's been done.
We can wrap it up quickly.
- We may even need the money
to get Emma back. - He's right.
Now, we just have to be
extra vigilant.
Cover our backs every possible way.
If Linda's on, we can
arrange a time and a place
for the money exchange
that we control.
It's what Emma wants us to do.
She said that, did she?
Yes. She's got Linda
exactly where we want her.
Agreed?
Yeah, agreed.
Yeah.
Sean?
Fine.
Hello, Linda Runcorn?
My name is Sheldon Greyshot,
Greyshot Genealogists.
Yes, I'm afraid Miss Patterson
has been taken ill,
so I'll be dealing with
your case from now on.
We need you to sign some paperwork,
at your earliest convenience.
Are you going to let Emma go?
What's it to you?
She's my friend.
You're breaking my heart.
Now, are you going to tell
me what I need to know,
or do you want to share
a cell with her?
- They're arranging a meet.
- Which will be where?
I don't know. They won't tell me.
They've all clammed up.
You nicking Emma
has freaked them out.
What about the woman? Linda Runcorn.
They must be telling her.
Yeah, but she ain't going
to tell me, is she?
No, she isn't.
Detective lnspector Fisk.
This is DS Loach.
Can we come in?
Con men?
Did they suggest there were any
outstanding charges
on your aunt's estate?
Mortgage payments, legal fees?
Yes.
One hundred thousand
for subsidence.
I was about to give it to them as well.
In cash.
I don't believe it.
- So there's no estate? - No estate.
No dead relative. - No nothing.
- And I'm afraid the bracelet
they gave you... - What about it?
Well, we're going to
have to take it with us.
It's evidence.
I spoke to them yesterday.
They said they were
going to come and
collect me later today.
- Did they give you an address?
- No. I didn't think to ask.
- Did they say what time you were
being picked up? - Two o'clock. - Great.
- We'd like you to keep that
appointment. - Excuse me?
I want you to go along,
sign the papers,
and hand Michael Stone
the money, just as planned.
- Are you mad? - It is essential that
we catch him with the cash in his hand.
- My cash? - Yes.
- Have you lost your mind?
There'll be a team of
police officers with us.
We'll be with you every step of the way.
There's no risk at all.
No risk to you, no.
It's not your money, is it?
You don't even know where they're
bloody taking me, do you?
No, but I can assure you...
And I can assure you the £100,000
is going back into my bank.
I'm sorry, I don't mind helping
you catch these people,
but I will not risk my life savings.
And you have no right
to ask me to do so.
You've got two minutes.
Thanks.
Sean, what are you doing here?
Fisk.
- Her brother's turned up.
Look, you shouldn't have come.
Well, I had to.
Nobody else is doing anything.
Mickey's acting like it's just a little
inconvenient hitch in his master plan.
That's just the way
he deals with stuff.
He doesn't let his
emotions get in the way.
That's because he doesn't
have any emotions.
Oh, Sean, come on.
Don't be stupid.
I'm not being stupid, when are you
going to realise you're in trouble?
You have to trust Mickey, OK?
We both do.
He'll come up with something.
He always does.
Yeah?
What if he doesn't this time?
Little family reunion, Seany?
Excuse me?
Detective lnspector Fisk.
My pals call me Sid. How is Emma?
Still acting tough?
Are you the copper
that set my sister up?
Yeah, I am.
And I can make it stick too.
I have this network
of people, you see,
all willing to state that they bought
Class-A drugs from your big sister.
Come on, then. Come on.
I'm not entirely sure how
it would help your sister,
but it might be fun all the same.
Come on.
No?
Smart boy.
See, what I don't understand is
why Mickey wasn't interested
in the deal I offered him.
- What deal? - When he was here
posing as her brief.
- You spoke to Mickey?
- Like I said, I offered him a deal.
Fifty grand and she walks.
Didn't seem too much, not for
a big crew like your lot.
He turned me down.
You're lying.
Oh, what, he didn't tell you?
I'll get you fifty grand.
Sorry, that deal's closed.
I've got another one though.
Yeah, and what's that, then?
Linda Runcorn gets picked up at
two o'clock to finish a deal.
I want to know where
you're taking her.
Ten minutes after you tell me,
I have Emma released.
You have my word on that.
If you don't tell me, I'll make sure
she gets ten years. Minimum.
Time to find out if blood's thicker
than money, Seany.
Need some company?
I'll have what he's having. Sure.
You worried about Emms?
Yeah, but she'll be fine, we've got
out of worse scrapes than this.
Yeah, you have.
I used to love you and Emms,
back in the day,
always looking out for each other.
I never had that.
I had a sister who hated my guts
and a mum who was only happy
when she was off her face.
You've got your little girl now.
Yeah. Mum's better too.
It's funny how something so little
can turn two people's lives around.
It's hard though...
looking out for her, making sure
she's got what she needs,
things that I never had.
I'm sure you're a great mum.
Well, I try my best.
That's the thing about family.
You do whatever you have to to
take care of them, keep them safe.
Yeah, you do.
And there ain't nothing wrong
with that, is there, Sean?
No, there isn't.
Inspector Fisk?
It's Sean Kennedy.
'I'll tell you what you want to know,
but I need to see Emma's free first.'
You won't regret this, kid.
'Yeah. I'd better not.'
You know what you have to do?
Just go along with everything
until you turn up. Exactly.
Afternoon. Hello.
I need to speak to Mr Gayhorse.
I'm sorry, we don't have anyone
here by that name.
I'm Sheldon Greyshot.
Who are you?
Oh. I've got it down as...Gayhorse.
What does that look like to you?
Er...Playhouse.
Look, it's Greyshot.
It's obviously a mistake.
We don't make mistakes.
We can't afford to.
We're from Her Majesty's Treasury. My
name is Farrow and this is Whitman.
You're investigating the estate of
Marcus Hambury.
Is there a problem.
He's wanted for tax evasion.
As you know, any probate
investigator's at liberty to
track down the heirs to intestate
assets of the deceased,
whatever their misdemeanours
when living.
Except in this case, the deceased is
alive and well and living in Hove.
Hove? Yes, we're afraid he might have
faked his own death to avoid capture.
So, we'll need a room and all the
documentation you have on the estate.
Jennifer, get the
Hambury file, will you?
And show these gentlemen to
meeting room one.
I've two more associates coming.
Please alert me when they arrive.
Do give their names to
the receptionist.
Here for the Hambury meeting. Ah,
yes, upstairs. Thank you.
Fisk. It's Sean.
Miss Runcorn. Let me take you
upstairs. We're on the second floor.
Get her out.
I want to see her.
You. Out.
Get off me. Where are they?
Fordham Road. Second floor.
You've done the right thing, Seany.
What have you done? Sean?
- What did you do?
- What I had to.
All units. All units.
Fordham Road. Now.
- Second floor?
- Up here. Is everything OK?
Michael Stone, I'm arresting you
on suspicion of probate fraud.
Are you going to paint
my portrait later?
Just making sure it's real.
What's real?
That we just collared the biggest
grifter in London red-handed.
Oh, dear, not looking
great, is it, Mickey?
Any advice from your
grandmother on what
to do when you're
caught bang to rights?
- Can we just get this over with?
- Should have trusted me.
You should have accepted my
deal when you had the chance.
Then I wouldn't have had to get
your boy to betray you.
- Sean? - That's right. He's the
one who told me where to find you.
No, he... Why would he do...?
Emma's freedom.
So you see, I am a man
of my word, after all.
Make a deal with me, I stick to it.
So?
What do you say, Michael?
One hundred grand and you can walk.
One hundred?
It was 50 before.
I double it for a big cheese like you.
You see, someone offered
me 20 grand to put you away,
so I need the right
incentive not to do that.
You get me the cash,
this will all just disappear.
- How? - I'll do what I always do when
I'm paid to make a case go away.
Pollute the evidence, a couple of
schoolboy errors in the paperwork,
and tell your brief what to look
for. You'll be out in an hour.
That's got to be worth
a hundred grand.
That's just what I wanted to hear.
What are you smiling about?
Ma'am.
This is Michael Stone...
- Mickey Bricks. - How are you, Michael?
I trust we've made you comfortable?
Well, it's certainly
been interesting.
Hard to get the staff these days.
What's going on here?
Michael and I had a little deal.
You know about deals, don't you,
Sidney? You'll appreciate this one.
It's very nuanced.
Michael was in no position to
refuse this offer.
I've been brought in to
clean up this department,
by any means necessary.
Starting with a certain
diseased apple called Fisk.
OK.
So, what do you want from me?
Simply to do the thing
you're best at.
You're a bit stuffed then, ain't ya?
Exactly. It's a...a thingy-o...
It's a paradox?
No, no. No, a catch-22?
No. Chinese puzzle?
A conundrum?
No. A mystery within a puzzle
wrapped up in an enigma?
So, what we going to do about Fisk?
Hang on. I know that face.
He's got something.
Michael?
Don't keep us in suspense.
A mystery within a puzzle
wrapped up in an enigma.
We're going to set Fisk a trap.
One he'll fall headfirst into.
So, Linda Runcorn.
The story is she's the CEO of an
online hotel and restaurant guide.
It was a straightforward
probate con, really.
Albert look into the kind of extras
you'd have to pay on an estate like that.
You know, bills for maintenance, loans
to fix the roof, that sort of thing.
So, what do you think?
Yeah, I can make that work.
We got Jean Kirkpatrick,
one of the best grifters north of
the Watford Gap to help us out.
We ensconced her in a Chelsea
apartment and gave her a dossier
briefing her on the character she
was supposed to play for us. Linda.
Nothing worse than a bent copper.
Now remember, Fisk will have us
under surveillance round the
clock, so we play this for real.
Old bag probably left me a tatty
old armchair and some cats.
Well, actually, she left jewellery.
And property worth in the
region of £4.7 million.
We knew your team were watching us.
No. There's no way you would've
known I was tailing you. No way.
Oh, we knew.
We knew you were coming after us
the moment you took our five grand.
Your five grand?
The five grand's a down payment,
there's another 15 when it's done.
The guy who paid you in the bar, Domino
Derek, an old poker friend of Albert's.
All this. Why?
I'm a good cop.
- Excuse me? - OK, I take the occasional
backhander, but who doesn't?
I'm old school. Do you know how
many villains I've put away?
The ones who didn't pay you?
So you call me a rotten apple, a
disease that needs to be rooted out,
then you do deals with con men?
That makes you the scab. The Judas.
Coppers like you were
extinct years ago.
I'm trying to do honest police work
with both my hands tied behind my back.
Honest? Planting drugs on people.
Taking bribes to let them go.
We know you threatened Kat Farmer
if she wouldn't spy for you.
That's the trouble with
being predictable, lnspector.
It meant we could
read you like a book.
- Yeah.
- Wainwright here.
- I've got something for you.
- Thank you.
You using Kat actually
made our life easier.
Really?
Well, delighted I could help.
Emma? Oh, she's a train crash.
But she's all right.
It meant we could feed
you the information
we wanted you to have
more easily.
What's this, here?
A family crest?
The Topping family.
We need it exactly the same.
By tomorrow, you said?
Can it be done?
It's not easy.
You have to get the stone right.
Sean and Emma Kennedy.
The newbies.
These two are Stone's
soft underbelly.
If we get to them, we can penetrate
the inner circle and tear it apart.
That's how we get him.
We knew you were targeting Sean
and Emma, so we played along.
It's Sean Kennedy.
I'll tell you what you want to know,
but I need to see that
Emma's free first.
- You won't regret this, kid.
- Yeah, I'd better not.
We told you the bracelet
was valuable
because we knew you couldn't
resist getting your hands
on the extra cash
we said it was worth.
I'm afraid the bracelet
they gave you...
- What about it? - Well, we're
going to have to take it with us.
You stole a bracelet you
thought was worth 50 grand,
and used your own money
to try and entrap us.
You know what you have to do?
Just go along with everything
until you turn up. Exactly.
He's dropped off the cash.
Ash made up an identical
package, with fake money
and a recording device.
All we had to do then was switch the
envelopes and wait for you to arrest me.
'So? What do you say, Michael?
'One hundred grand and you can walk.
'A hundred?
It was 50 before.
'I double it for a
big cheese like you.
'You see, someone offered me
20 grand to put you away,
'so I need the right incentive
not to do that.
'You get me the cash and this
will all just disappear.
'How? I'll do what I always do when
I'm paid to make a case go away.
'Pollute the evidence, a couple of
schoolboy errors in the paperwork
'and tell your brief what to look
for. You'll be out in an hour.
'That's got to be worth
a hundred grand.'
I was doing my job.
Sidney Fisk. I'm arresting you on
suspicion of corruption.
Hang on a minute,
I'm not the villain, here.
- I'm not the scumbag.
- You do not have to say anything.
It's OK, I know.
Know what?
Everything. Fisk,
what he made you do.
It's all right.
No, it ain't.
Yes, it is, listen,
we've taken care of it.
He won't be bothering you again.
You must think I'm such a skank.
No.
He said he was going to...
I know.
She's all I've got, Sean.
Listen, this is about
what Fisk did, not you...
I know more than anyone,
people like us,
where we're from, you know,
we take care of our own.
So we're all good. OK?
In fact... In fact,
we're better than good.
- What's this?
- It's your cut.
What?
From the con we were working
on, the bracelet switch.
- But...
- It's not charity, OK? You earned it.
Sean, I can't take this.
I don't deserve it,
not after what I did.
Yes, you can.
- I owe you.
- Call it even.
Mummy. Hello.
Laurel, this is Sean, say hello.
Hiya.
Take care of yourself, Kat.
You too, Seany...
Michael.
Come to wave me off?
You took a hell of a risk
carrying on with the con...
You should've accepted
Fisk's offer in the pub.
You could have ended it there and
then. Well, I was having so much fun.
You saw an opportunity to relieve
Fisk of his cash and you took it.
That's what I do.
That's dirty money.
Made from bribery and corruption,
and by rights, it belongs to
the Metropolitan Police.
Yeah, maybe, but we'll put
it to much better use.
What makes you think I won't
just arrest you for it?
You won't do that.
Won't I?
Because then, you'd have to
explain to your superiors how you
blackmailed a group of con artists
into helping you catch a bent cop.
Well, they did say
by any means necessary.
We could go and talk them
through it now, if you like,
you know, while I'm still here?
Goodbye, Chief lnspector.
Michael.
This was a one-off.
Starting now, the slate's clean.
I'm the law enforcer
and you're the criminal.
If I can catch you, I will.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
- So, how was she about us keeping
Fisk's money? - Fine.
- Fine? - Yeah, well,
she moaned for a bit,
then I convinced her
it was for the best.
How was Kat?
OK, yeah.
Can we get back to normal now, please?
It didn't feel right
working for the police.
Give me tinkers and tricksters, and
gamblers and fraudsters any time.
At least you know where you
stand with them.
Ain't that the truth?
sync and corrections by Bellows
www.addic7ed.com