Do I have 70?
Seventy. Seventy-five.
Eighty.
Eighty-five.
Ninety.
Ninety-five.
One hundred.
Drawn in 1934 by Leonard Wright.
The original artwork for the cover
of Black Storm, Issue One.
At £100,000.
Any more bids?
One-ten.
At £110,000.
Going once, going twice.
Sold.
I can't believe we just did that.
Hello, Eddie.
I need more time.
-Time's up, I want my £10,000.
-I haven't got it.
It's these bloody grifters,
they don't pay for anything.
Then you shouldn't let them gamble
in your bar, should you?
I mean, I am a police officer.
I've got to report it.
-You're gonna lose your license.
-But you can't.
This place is all I've got.
You ever been to prison, Eddie?
What's that?
That's counterfeit money you've
been laundering through your till.
Please.
I tell you what, I will settle
for some names. I want the big fish.
No. No way. I am not a grass.
Wrong answer, Eddie.
Okay!
There's this crew that drink in here,
they play the long con.
Names.
Mickey Bricks.
Maybe I am missing something here.
Only, I thought we were grifters.
-I mean we could've lifted this.
-And then what?
I don't know. Do our thing, don't we?
Work the magic.
Great plan, Danny.
It's wiped out our working capital.
We will have to raise some cash.
Think of it as an investment.
Black Storm was one of
the original superheroes, and this...
is the Mona Lisa of comic book artwork.
That's why we had to pay £110,000 for it.
They say you have
to speculate to accumulate.
No, you know, it feels all wrong.
We should be really proud of ourselves.
For once, we did not break the law.
Ash, how are the auction house
blueprints looking?
It won't be easy, but it's definitely doable.
Right, we've got two weeks until
the next auction.
Meantime, we'll need
to raise some working capital.
But the beauty of it is, our guy can delay
the currency movement...
just long enough for us
to place a spread bet.
We've been clearing 300,
400% profit, easy.
Wow!
-That's beautiful.
-That's beautiful, but illegal.
-But foolproof?
-Completely.
I'm in. Definitely. Let's do it.
Right.
You'd have to be an idiot not to. £25,000.
Thank you.
Let's see what we've got here.
Yeah. Thank you.
Beats working for a living.
Can I help you?
I am arresting you for fraud.
You don't have to say anything...
but it may harm your defense
if you do not mention when questioned...
something which you later
rely on in court.
You can go for now.
I will contact you, take a statement.
Turn around.
Okay, here's the deal.
You two can go to prison,
or I can walk out of here...
with the money
and we all forget this ever happened.
A bent copper.
-So much for ''Protect and Serve.''
-Brilliant.
You think for one second
that we are going to let you...
swan out of here with £25,000?
You're dreaming, missy.
I think that's exactly
what you're going to do...
unless Mickey here fancies
another spell inside.
Not particularly.
People like you, yeah,
they give the police a very bad name.
I take it we have a deal. Now, okay.
Do anything stupid, he testifies,
you two go to prison.
Got it?
You know what they say,
what goes around comes around.
Then I'd be seriously worried,
if I were you.
-Yours?
-Yeah, I like to draw.
-You are very good, aren't you?
-That's what my art teacher said.
Now, what would a couple
of grifters be doing...
with artwork worth £100,000?
Like the catalogue says,
we're auctioning it.
Yeah, I mean it's completely legit.
We got receipts, we got everything.
What's she doing?
What are you doing?
Basically you've got five seconds
to tell me the score or I torch it.
We told you. There's no score.
Yeah, we're auctioning some artwork.
No law against it.
-There's no score.
-You wouldn't dare.
All right! We will tell you! Put it out!
Now, you tell me everything...
or this time, it won't be a beer mat.
We're auctioning
the artwork this afternoon.
We needed a genuine piece because
the auction house like to authenticate...
the artwork before they sell it.
While it's on display at the viewing...
we switch the authentic artwork
for a forgery.
It's the forgery that gets auctioned.
And then on the side...
we sell the authentic artwork
to a rival collector.
Yeah, and we clear £100,000 profit.
You clear £50,000 profit. I get the other 50.
Fifty?
One phone call to the auction house,
you don't make a penny.
Now, we need the £25,000
to pay the forger.
Fair enough.
Don't worry, we will meet you
back here after the auction.
You know what? I think I will tag along
for the ride.
One condition.
Once you get your money,
tell us who sold us out.
What makes you think
someone sold you out?
So, where to?
We need to pick up the forgery.
Bye, Eddie.
-Everything all right, Mick?
-Absolutely fantastic.
This is great. What do you think
we should do? Tell the others?
No, they've got their jobs to do. So--
Did anyone ever tell you
it's rude to whisper?
-Do you think she's fit?
-Don't...
-What?
-...even think about it.
You know, would you have a few,
you know, if you could?
What do you mean, if I could?
-What are you doing?
-Danny, get in the back.
-You get in the back.
No, I am not getting in the back.
Is there a problem?
The two collectors we outbid at the last
auction won't want to lose out again.
The higher they bid,
the more profit we make.
-A little encouragement goes a long way.
-Absolutely.
You have any preference?
I'll take the geek.
Be gentle.
As a kitten.
Morning. Landlord's gas safety checks.
I need to inspect the gas appliances.
It's actually not a very good time.
I've got to leave for work.
Well, that's your problem, you see.
You're out all day, you get a buildup
of gas from a faulty appliance.
You come home,
flick on a light switch, bang!
Next thing you know, they are scraping
your brains off the pavement.
Right. Let's start with the cooker.
It's electric.
-Boiler?
-In there.
Okay, I need you to turn the hot tap
on in the bathroom while I check it.
Sad.
Excuse me.
I love Superman.
Although, I've always preferred him
more as Clark Kent, you know.
Strong, but vulnerable, you know...
those glasses.
My little nephew,
he's crazy about him as well.
Actually, I wanted to get him a present.
Could you help me find some other stuff,
if you are not too busy?
No, I mean, yes, I can help you.
No, I'm not too busy.
I'm Neil.
It's my shop.
What do you know about that?
Excuse me.
Yeah?
I couldn't help noticing
your auction catalogue. Snap.
You must be here for
the pop-art exhibition.
Yeah, I am a sucker for Lichtenstein.
-Are you a collector?
-I've been known to dabble.
Perhaps you could clear
something up for me.
What do you make of the idea...
that Lichtenstein is mocking his subjects
in his paintings?
A common misconception. May I?
Please, yes, of course.
What Lichtenstein's comic book
paintings show is a grown man finding...
meaning in junk he's supposed
to have thrown away.
They are about the energy
of adolescent fantasy.
Yes.
So, why comic books?
Mickey was into them when he was a kid.
Because there's too much security
in the traditional art world.
He was one of those specky kids.
You know, a lot of crying.
-''Please don't bully me.''
-Plus, the artwork is easier to forge.
Yeah, that's right, Mickey.
You keep telling yourself that, mate, yeah?
Who would have thought it, the great
Mickey Bricks taking the easy option.
Yeah, that's good,
coming from a parasite like you.
It's just down here on the right.
It's perfect. Tim will love it.
-Thanks for all your help.
-No, it was a pleasure.
Bye-bye, then.
Three, two, one.
Are you doing anything later?
There's an auction, comic book artwork.
Maybe you and your nephew
would like to come?
-We'd love to.
-Great.
Great.
It's the same energetic style,
bold primary colors.
The same single-mindedness
you later find in Warhol's work.
The comics inspired
the pop-art movement.
I'd sell my soul to own an original piece.
I'll let you in on a little secret.
I'll be bidding for some original artwork
at the auction.
Really? Which artist?
Black Storm, the Mona Lisa
of comic book artwork.
We could go to the auction together.
Right, we'll need the £25,000.
-I'm coming in with you.
-No, that might not be such a good idea.
-You know what these artists are like.
-Yeah, you know, very sensitive.
Say the wrong thing and you'll crush him.
Don't say we didn't warn you.
For £25,000,
this forgery had better be good.
Danny, you handsome little prick.
Come here.
Not the bear hug.
-Hey, Mickey.
-How you doing?
Hello, gorgeous.
Max, we are in a bit of a hurry.
Max, we are really in a hurry.
Ladies and gentlemen, walk this way.
He's very up and down.
Okay. Let's play Spot the Forgery.
-Is that the dog's bollocks, or what?
-Which one is it?
Wow, that's brilliant.
-Max, you've excelled yourself.
-That is spot on.
Are you sure the auction house
won't spot it?
The auction house spots it,
Mickey can have his £15,000 back.
-Fifteen?
-Cheap at half the price.
Any more stunts like that,
and it won't be the dog's bollocks...
that you have to worry about.
-You two want to get a room?
-To do what?
-I think he's jealous.
-Somehow I doubt it.
Now, what happens to the other £10,000?
Take a wild guess.
Well done, Romeo.
Okay, what's next?
There are some things I need to do.
Why don't you take him
and the artwork back to the bar?
''Him''? I am here, you know.
What can I possibly do
without the artwork?
Yeah, you tell me.
I tell you what, why don't you stay
with her, yeah?
I'll go and pick the stuff up.
Okay, watch my lips.
We stick together. You got it?
Anyway, I am really not in
the mood for Eddie's whining.
Eddie?
Wait. Eddie put you on to us.
Eddie? Eddie, Eddie's Bar, Eddie?
Eddie did this. I'm gonna kill him,
I will kill him.
Get over it.
Eddie's just saving his skin, like you.
He's nothing like us.
God, you really overdo the whole
''honor among thieves'' business.
I mean, want to do
the honorable thing, go straight.
That's good, isn't it? That's good,
coming from a bent cop.
-I don't pretend there's any honor in it.
-That's because you can't.
I'll just check if there's any mail for me.
You running a bit late, ain't you?
How's Max?
-The forgery okay?
-Ash.
-Who's she?
-Detective Inspector Phillips.
-Eddie sold us out.
-Eddie? Who told you that?
No, she's lying. He wouldn't.
I mean, not Eddie.
Are these the blueprints
for the auction house?
Think of me as your silent partner.
How are you handling the CCTV?
Security system's due
for its quarterly service.
That includes the CCTV.
I'll rig the tapes so they will be running,
they just won't record anything.
Is that the modified case
for switching the artwork?
Yeah. It's good to go.
The back of the frames match the case.
Now, while Mickey distracts everyone...
you press the other side of
the case against the original...
you clip it on, you flip the case over...
the forgery releases, and off you go.
Yeah, piece of cake.
Piece of cake.
You will have security down on you
like a ton of bricks.
Listen, maybe you should do it.
Yeah, does everyone want to chill out,
okay? I'll do it, okay? I'm going to do it.
-You just look after your end.
-No one's worried about my end.
Mickey, maybe you should find yourself
a nice girl and all that will change.
Been a while, has it, Mickey?
Yeah, what can I say? I'm very choosy.
You need to get down
to the auction house.
Yeah. I will call when I've rigged the CCTV.
You don't want to set foot
in there before then.
Keep practicing, Danny.
Next time. Go straight on, all right.
It's not a problem.
And distraction.
Like I said, Mickey, it is a piece of cake.
Okay, we got to go.
Yeah, hang on a minute, a little bit of
appreciation for that wouldn't go amiss.
You pull this off, I'll give you an ice cream.
You all right in the back, Mickey?
Got enough room for your little legs?
-Take the next right.
-Right. You mad? It's straight on.
Turning right avoids the one-way system.
Take a right.
Don't listen to him, love, straight on.
-Actually, where are we?
-Manor Road.
Right, yeah, it is right. Take the next right.
Danny, shut up.
-Why are we stopping?
-I'll be two minutes.
-Doing what?
-We don't have time for this.
Okay, here's the deal.
We keep one set of artwork each
as security.
-Are you having a laugh?
-Why don't we just come with you?
You wait here.
I will take the genuine piece.
Like you said, we don't have time for this.
Great, thank you.
Weren't planning on going anywhere,
were you?
No, the thought
hadn't even crossed my mind.
Has anyone ever told you you're paranoid?
Yep, I will take your phones, too...
just in case you were tempted to make
any arrangements behind my back.
I would give it, but I mean, me Nan said
she might call today. She gets very Ionely.
Yeah, if me Nan calls...
just tell her I'll come
and see her tomorrow.
Did you get what you needed?
It's still there, Danny.
So, your boyfriend work round here,
does he?
You got a boyfriend? No?
What, you're more of a cat person?
Hey, stop them !
Give our bag back, pricks!
Hey, stop that car!
Great.
-You call that running?
-Yes, I call that running.
-Where were you?
-Right behind you.
-lf I knew you were going to slow down--
-Look, it's not my fault.
-Do not make this my fault.
-It is your fault!
You let some idiot take the case
and it's my fault?
-Shut up!
-I've had it up to here with you.
-Always got to have things your own way.
-Let's sort it out now!
Shut up, Danny, and get in the car!
Is that supposed to mean something?
We just got screwed, all right?
That was the real artwork.
Do we really have to go through
the whole me phoning the auction house...
you stopping me at the last minute thing?
I mean, we can if you like.
Told you she wouldn't go for it.
I didn't see you coming up
with any better ideas.
When exactly did you arrange it?
I left a note for Ash at the hotel,
when I checked my mail.
You can't blame us for trying, can you?
Yeah, well, I'd probably be more worried if
you weren't trying to ditch me, I suppose.
Here you go.
Where's he taking the artwork?
Did you really think we wouldn't find out?
What's that? You're sorry?
Well it's too late, son, isn't it?
Did she buy it?
Let him go.
I said, let him go.
Mickey, I'm sorry.
She was trying to blackmail me.
She planted some counterfeit money.
She told me I was going to prison.
You'll wish you had
when we get through with you.
Mickey, please. How long have we
known each other?
I didn't have any choice.
Danny?
Jesus, Eddie, you're making me want
to kick you.
I believe we have an auction to go to.
What about him?
What you do after I get my money,
that's your business.
We had a deal.
-You can't do this!
-Later, Eddie.
I slipped.
-A slice of history.
-And where is it?
It's not arriving till later this afternoon.
I didn't expect to get another shot at it
so soon.
-Are you expecting much competition?
-Only the geek.
Neil Davis. Comic book collector.
Thinks it's all about
the mythology of the characters.
No appreciation of
the artistic significance.
I mean he couldn't even spell Lichtenstein.
Then it would be a tragedy
if he acquired such an important piece.
I will just have to make sure
that he doesn't.
Hi. You made it.
Here.
-You didn't have to do that.
-Yeah, I wanted to.
And who's this?
Is it a bird? Is it a plane? No, it's....
This is Tim. Say hello to Neil, Tim.
He absolutely loves his costume.
Wouldn't take it off.
I wish I'd got one.
Maybe some other time?
-Shall we go in?
-Yeah.
He's really excited.
Right, he'll be a while.
So let's take the weight off.
So, what is it we are looking at?
The original artwork for the cover
of Black Storm, Issue One, when it arrives.
And I take it this is a big deal?
Yeah.
He was one of the very first superheroes.
Massively influential.
Shaped the future of comics
as we know them.
-Wow.
-I'm bidding for it.
And who's that?
Gideon Sturock. The competition.
Looks like a pretentious little prat to me.
He calls himself an art collector.
He doesn't care about the characters
or the mythology.
It's just another trophy to him.
I hope you are not going
to let him buy it, then?
Not if I can help it.
-The geek.
-Really?
Who's that rather attractive
young woman with him?
If she's with a loser like that,
probably a hooker.
I'm very much going to enjoy seeing
the look on his face when you outbid him.
Good work, Ash.
CCTV's rigged. We're on.
You two go ahead, all right?
Is there a problem?
You are about to commit a crime.
Obviously I can't be associated with that.
Okay.
Get yourself a nice a cup of tea,
yeah? Sticky bun, all right?
Danny, I will be right behind you.
Now, you don't talk to me...
you don't acknowledge me,
you don't know me...
but you stay in sight. Clear?
What time does it start, 3:30?
Okay, is that any good?
Colossal.
-What's he doing here?
-How the hell am I supposed to know?
-What is going on?
-Master planner here screwed up.
The auction house
usually have an expert...
come in and authenticate the artwork...
-before they put it up for auction.
-Yeah, you knew that.
Yes, I did, but this is not their usual guy.
The guy they've brought
in rumbled us six months ago...
when we tried to sell
a forged Andy Warhol print.
Yeah, we had these tins of Spam.
We'd had them all stacked up.
They were cute.
We cannot put the artwork up
for auction with him there.
We are going to have to postpone.
Just till I'm out of the way.
Deeply convenient.
Would you like us to step outside
and prove it to you?
All right, what about Ash? Yeah.
We will get him all, you know,
disguised, he can do it.
No, he's been servicing their CCTV.
-We'll have to get someone else, then.
-Danny, there is no time. Sorry.
-I'm calling it off.
-No, we can't rig the CCTV a second time.
Buyers are ready. Everybody's in place.
Got to go now.
-I could do it.
-Yeah, right. I don't think so.
Yeah. She can do it.
And watch her disappear
with the money afterwards.
Are you out of your mind?
We still make the switch. Yeah?
We still got the original.
I mean, that could work.
I guess you're gonna have to trust me.
All right, the auction house
are expecting a Mr. Henshaw.
I'll call and tell them that my PA will
be delivering the artwork instead of me.
Wait until I am back in the foyer
before you make the switch, all right?
I don't want to be anywhere
near you when you do it.
Mr. Williams, please.
Hello, I'm Mr. Henshaw's PA.
I think you are expecting me.
So, I understand your own expert
isn't in today?
Paul? No, he called in sick this morning.
We had to get David in here
at the last minute.
-It's authentic.
-Best get this on display.
I know Mr. Henshaw has a plane to catch,
so I will issue you with a banker's draft...
-immediately after the sale.
-Great. Thank you.
Something tells me you are going
to be horribly disappointed.
We'll just have to see
about that, won't we?
Pretty girl.
How much does she charge?
Yeah.
We're on.
Mama !
Kids. Who'd have them?
I've got four.
Great, I love them.
They as good-Iooking as their mom?
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you could please take your seats...
we will get today's auction underway.
We start with the resale of a piece
that was purchased two weeks ago...
at this very auction house.
Lot Number One is the original artwork...
for the cover of Black Storm, Issue One.
Drawn in 1934 by Leonard Wright,
it's a landmark piece...
both culturally and artistically.
I'll open the bidding at just £60,000.
Sixty. Sixty-five.
Seventy.
Seventy-five.
Eighty. At £80,000.
Eighty-five.
Ninety.
Ninety-five.
At ninety-five.
One hundred.
At £100,000.
One-five.
One-ten.
One-fifteen.
Regret is a terrible thing.
One-twenty.
At £120,000.
Any more bids?
Going once.
Going twice.
Don't bid.
Sold!
Minus our commission, that's £108,000.
Did you get it?
-You little beauty.
-I will cash it and give you your half.
You know what?
That doesn't really work for me.
Excuse me?
Did she just say what I think she said?
Fraud, deception, assaulting a bartender.
I mean you two have racked up
quite a charge sheet, haven't you?
Don't forget you've been
with us every step of the way.
Me?
I am an undercover police officer.
Of course I've been
with you every step of the way.
I mean, how else would I obtain evidence?
Why don't you just be
a good little girl, yeah?
Hand it over?
Play nice, Danny.
Now, same deal as before.
I keep the money or you go to prison.
What's it to be?
I tell you what, you keep
the original artwork, cover expenses.
Are we supposed to be grateful?
I really don't care what you are.
Now I am going to walk out that door,
you are going to leave it...
ten minutes, then you're free to go.
What, and you really think
that's going to happen?
Trust me, Danny, you really
wouldn't suit prison overalls, mate.
Me? I look good in anything.
You, I will see around.
That's a very, very bad move.
Simply magnificent.
Excuse me.
-That's rather odd.
-What's that?
Black Storm's wearing a signet ring.
I don't recall seeing that before.
Max, we need one identical copy
and then another copy with a small flaw.
A flaw?
What sort of thing did you have in mind?
Oh, my God.
-Wait a minute, where are you, hello?
-Sorry.
-Right. Okay.
Miss Jackson.
It appears that the artwork
you put up for sale is, in fact, a forgery.
The police are on their way.
Right. D.I. Phillips.
I am working undercover.
The suspects are still inside, all right?
We've worked with the police before.
They've always notified us in the past.
-We couldn't, for operational reasons.
-We? Where's your backup?
I'm working on my own today.
Why don't we discuss this inside?
What are you doing? I am a police officer.
Feel good, big man, does it?
Get your hands off me!
D.I. Cole, this is D.S. Martin.
I've been working the inside with
this crew for the last couple of months.
Tell us why you put
the artwork up for sale.
The art expert knew them.
It was the only way I could get
them to go through with it.
Look, their names are,
just remember this, all right...
Michael Stone, Danny Blue,
and Ash Morgan. Check Mickey's record.
Okay. She checks out. Sorry.
Thanks to you, they've got away,
and my cover's blown.
How was I to know?
The ID and artwork could've
both been forgeries.
So, what's the scam?
Look, they switched the authentic artwork
for a forgery while it was on display.
-I take it you have CCTV here?
-Won't help.
Ash Morgan posed as an engineer.
He rigged the CCTV,
so it recorded absolutely nothing.
We haven't had an engineer here today.
I personally authorize all maintenance.
I would've known if we had.
Why don't we take a look at it?
Like I said, it's working perfectly.
This guy Ash didn't leave
the auction room.
Look, he prepared a fake ID.
I mean I saw it, so....
Even with a fake ID...
there is no way he would've got
anywhere near the CCTV system.
There you go. That's them.
Mickey, the black guy.
He was using the name Henshaw.
He bought the artwork from you,
like, about two weeks ago.
That's not Mr. Henshaw.
Mr. Henshaw's white.
One-ten.
It's not the other guy, either.
There, now, I follow them, okay.
Go to the camera in the stairwell.
There are no cameras in the stairwell.
If the CCTV's working,
you will see them switch the artwork.
Nope, they didn't go anywhere near
the Black Storm artwork.
Wait, you know, they must have.
I can see you near it.
-What's happening now?
-That's nothing.
Some kid let go of his balloons.
So the only time we lose sight of the
artwork, you're standing right next to it.
-What's in the case?
-Nothing. It was empty.
I still had it from when I delivered
the artwork for them.
So, I understand your own expert
isn't in today.
Paul? No, he called in sick this morning.
Okay, I need you to turn the hot tap
on in the bathroom while I check it.
Sorry, pal.
Where's the case now?
I gave it back to Mickey and Danny.
Where were Mickey and Danny
when we lost the picture?
In the foyer, nowhere near
the Black Storm artwork.
You do still have
the banker's draft, don't you?
Yeah, of course.
The woman and the kid with the balloons.
So, what's this?
Maybe we should check this out.
I've got other evidence.
Listen, they were running a con
on some estate agent. Here you go.
Richard Shaw, all right?
That's the guy they were conning.
He will totally back up my story.
You'd have to be an idiot not to. £25,000.
Richard Shaw. Estate agent?
I don't think so.
Look, I can take you to the forger's studio.
Okay. Let's play Spot the Forgery.
I told you, they planted the key on me.
How come the safe deposit box
is registered in your name?
Blueprints for the auction house.
Research on Black Storm.
And there's got to be £10,000 here.
What happens to the other £10,000?
Take a wild guess.
They steered me here.
But it's your safe deposit box.
It's registered to you.
Yeah, but they knew I'd see
the safe depository when we drove past.
-Actually, where are we?
-Manor Road.
Right, yeah, it is right. Take the next right.
They must have known I had a box here.
And how would they get
inside your safe deposit box?
It's counterfeit.
What's this, then?
Eddie.
She's this bent D.I.
She caught Billy and his crew
gambling down here, you know...
they were playing poker.
She wants £10,000, or I lose me license.
And I could lose everything, Mick.
-Are you thinking what I am thinking?
-Yup.
Is she fit?
-Okay, I can take you to their hotel.
-It's not illegal to stay in a hotel.
-Yeah, but we can get a search warrant.
-On what grounds?
Mickey and Danny didn't put
the artwork up for sale, you did.
You collected the banker's draft.
As far as we can tell, they didn't switch
the artwork, either, whereas you....
-There's CCTV footage, witnesses.
-Look, all this. Everything, the lot, okay?
It's all Mickey and Danny.
There's no evidence you
even spoke to them.
There's no Max the Forger.
There's no Richard Shaw.
This Mickey and Danny don't appear
to have done anything illegal.
At least not today, anyway.
-Where did all this come from?
-They planted it.
-They are setting me up.
-Can you prove it?
I don't have any choice. I'm sorry.
Samantha Phillips. I am arresting you
on suspicion of theft, fraud, and deception.
You do not have to say anything...
but it may harm your defense if you do
not mention when questioned...
something which you later
rely on in court.
Come on, cards on the table.
Would you have a little knock-about
with her?
Like I said, Danny, I'm very choosy.
Yeah, but choosy ain't
getting you nowhere.
When she got that truncheon out,
did it for me.
Women are your kryptonite.
What are you on about, what are you on?
Are you tripping or something?
I'm their kryptonite. Albert, I.... Listen.
-Women are powerless to resist me.
-Yeah, dream on.
-Right, I'll drive you.
-No, I'm driving.
Let me drive.
Would you open the door for me, please?
-Want us to do everything, yeah?
-Thank you.
I didn't want to drive, okay?
So I tricked you, so I won.
You drive, I am not driving. Forget it.
But, Dad.
-Always a pleasure.
-Here you go, your first score.
-Is that all?
-Shut up.
-He's learning fast.
-I'll see you around, guys.
-Thank you.
-Nice working with you.
Come on, let's get you home.
-Eddie, what happened?
-I slipped.
Yeah, I didn't have time to fit
the padding before you got to the bar.
Yeah, I couldn't exactly
say anything, could I?
Grifting's a dangerous game, Eddie.
But look on the bright side...
at least D.I. Phillips
won't be bothering you anymore.
Yeah, nice one. Thanks, fellas.
So, I cashed the banker's draft
we got from the auction house.
The money's in here, along
with the £80,000...
that Neil very happily paid for the original.
Dangerous, but lucrative.
So does this mean you lot
are going to settle your tab?
-Eddie.
-Charming.
-Where's the gratitude?
-No appreciation.
Makes you wonder why we bother.
All right, then, here.
Okay then, I'd better be off.
Hold on.
Where are you going all dressed up?
I don't think that's,
any of your business, Danny.
-She's got a date.
-A date? Who with?
I don't think that's any
of your business, either.
-Neil.
-Neil. Neil?
You are going out with some
specky comic-book geek, when...
a beautiful, friendly, funny,
sensitive, creative guy...
like me doesn't even get a look in?
Looks that way. Doesn't it, Danny?
Okay, guys, don't wait up.
Cards, gentlemen?
Cards? Yeah, brilliant.
I can hardly handle the excitement.
What?
Shall we say, a tenner a hand?
-No. No way.
-Eddie, come on.
Just a bit of fun.
Besides, you're one of the crew now.
So, Eddie, what do you got?
Like I'd tell you lot.
English