Lizzy! Jane!
What do you think? Mr Collins has made
an offer of marriage to Charlotte Lucas!
She's accepted him!
Charlotte?
Engaged to Mr Collins?
Impossible!
The fireplace in the great room at
Rosings would be much larger than that.
A fireplace of truly
prodigious dimensions.
But why should you be surprised,
my dear Lizzy?
Do you think it incredible
that Mr Collins could procure
any woman's good opinion,
because he didn't succeed with you?
Charlotte, I didn't mean...
I was surprised.
Charlotte, if Mr Collins has been so
fortunate as to secure your affections,
I'm delighted for you both.
I see what you are feeling.
I'm not romantic, you know.
I never was.
I ask only a comfortable home.
And, considering Mr Collins' character
and situation in life,
I'm convinced my chance
of happiness with him
is as fair as most
who enter the marriage state.
(COLLINS): My dear Charlotte!
Cousin Elizabeth, you can see before you
the happiest of men!
Jane, it was such a
humiliating spectacle!
She knows she's marrying
one of the stupidest men in England.
I never believed her capable of that.
Lizzy, you do not make allowances
for differences of situation and temper.
Our cousin Mr Collins is not the
cleverest of men, perhaps,
but he is respectable.
He is not vicious, and as far as
fortune goes, it's an eligible match.
Very eligible! You wouldn't think of
marrying a man like that,
simply to secure your own comfort.
No, but Lizzy, not everyone is the same.
Dear Jane!
I doubt that
you will have to make a choice
between marrying for love and marrying
for more material considerations.
Though you may, perhaps?
(THERE IS A KNOCK ON THE DOOR)
This came just now
from Netherfield, ma'am.
Thank you.
It's from Caroline Bingley.
She writes...
..that the whole party will have left
Netherfield by now, for London.
And without any intention of
coming back again.
(MISS BINGLEY): Charles first thought
that his business in London
would only take a few days,
but we 're certain
that this cannot be so.
I am convinced that when Charles
gets to town,
he will be in no hurry
to leave it again.
I do not pretend to regret
anything I shall leave in Hertfordshire,
my dearest friend,
except your society.
Mr Darcy, of course, is impatient
to see his sister.
And to confess the truth,
I'm scarcely less eager
to meet her again,
from the hope I dare to entertain
of her being hereafter... my sister.
Am I wrong, my dearest Jane,
in indulging the hope of an event
which would secure the happiness
of so many?
Is it not clear enough ?
Caroline Bingley believes her brother
is indifferent to me, and
she means to put me on my guard.
Can there be any other opinion
on the subject?
Yes, there can!
Miss Bingley sees that
her brother is in love with you, and
she wants him to marry Miss Darcy.
She hopes to keep him in town, and
persuade you that
he does not care about you.
Indeed, Jane, you ought to believe me.
No one who has seen you and Bingley
together can doubt his affection.
I cannot believe Caroline is capable of
wilful deceit.
All I can hope for is that
she is deceived herself.
Believe her to be deceived,
by all means,
but she can hardly convince a man
so much in love
that he's in love
with someone else instead!
If Bingley is not back by your side and
dining at Longbourn within two weeks,
I shall be very much surprised.
I don't envy Charlotte in the slightest!
F ancy marrying a clergyman!
He'Il read from Fordyce's sermons
every night.
Before they go to bed!
Look at that hideous cloth!
It would do very well for Mary.
Look! There's Denny and Carter.
And Wickham!
I suppose you'Il keep him
all to yourself again?
Of course.
She's violently in love with him!
For heaven's sake, lower your voice.
Good afternoon to you, Ladies!
How fortunate! We were
going to Longbourn in search of you.
We came into town in search of you!
We hoped we would see you
at the Netherfield ball.
I was very sorry to lose the pleasure
of dancing with you.
But fate, it would seem...
No. With you I must be entirely open.
I decided that it would be wrong
for me to be there.
I found that I had better not meet
with Mr Darcy.
Scenes might arise
unpleasant to more than myself.
I understand and admire
your forbearance.
Not that it would give me
a moment's concern
to see Mr Darcy publicly set down,
but in Mr Bingley's house...
It would grieve me
to see him embarrassed and discomfited.
And through him, your sister.
Yes.
I hear Mr Collins
is engaged to be married.
Yes, to my good friend Charlotte Lucas.
I had thought that his intentions
tended in another direction.
Perhaps they did, but they took a little
turn, to everybody's satisfaction.
And relief.
I hope that you will stay and
take tea with us.
I should like to introduce you
to my mother and father.
Thank you.
Denny!
Oh, young George Wickham is such a
charming young man, is he not, my dear ?
What? Oh, indeed he is.
It was very good of him
to entertain us so eloquently
with stories about his misfortunes.
With such narratives to hand,
who would read novels ?
But I believe he has been treated
contemptibly by Mr Darcy, father.
I dare say he has. Though Darcy may be
no more of a black-hearted villain
than your average rich man,
used to his own way.
It behoves us all
to take very careful thought
before pronouncing an adverse judgement
on any of our fellow men.
Lord!
I feel very sorry for poor Mr Wickham.
And so becoming in his regimentals!
I remember the time when I liked
a red coat myself well enough.
And I do still in my heart.
And there's no need to smile like that,
Miss Lizzy!
Though Mr Wickham
has taken a fancy to you,
I'm sure you've done nothing
to deserve it,
after your dealings with Mr Collins!
Well, it is all in vain,
it will all come to nothing!
The poor young man!
If only he had five or
six thousand a year,
I' d be happy to see him marry
any of the girls!
But nothing turns out the way it should.
And now Mr Bingley, of whom we all had
such expectations, is gone off forever!
What?
I've heard again from Caroline Bingley.
It's now definite that they will stay
in town for the whole winter.
I cannot believe it.
It is true.
Come now, Jane, take comfort.
Next to being married, a girl likes
to be crossed in love now and then.
When is it your turn, Lizzy?
You can't be long outdone by Jane,
when here are officers enough in Meryton
to disappoint all the young ladies
in the country.
Let Wickham be your man.
He's a pleasant fellow.
He would jilt you creditably.
Thank you, sir,
but a less agreeable man would do.
We must not all expect
Jane's good fortune.
True, but it is a comfort to think...
that whatever of that kind
may befall you,
you have an affectionate mother
who will always make the most of it.
I don't know what will become of us all,
indeed I do not!
And I cannot bear to think of
Charlotte Lucas
being mistress of this house!
That I should be forced to make way
for her, and see her take my place!
My dear, don't give way to such gloomy
thoughts. Let us hope for better things.
Let us flatter ourselves
that I might outlive you.
You mustn't be anxious for me, Lizzy.
He will be forgot,
and we shall all be as we were before.
But, I may remember him as...
..the most amiable man
of my acquaintance.
That is all.
I have nothing either to hope or fear...
..and nothing to reproach him with.
At least I have not had that pain.
My dear Jane.
You're too good. Your sweetness and
disinterestedness are truly angelic.
- Don't tease me, Lizzy.
- Indeed I do not tease you.
There are few people whom I really love,
and even fewer of whom I think well.
The more I see of the world,
the more I am dissatisfied with it.
Jane, what if you were to go to town?
Aunt and Uncle Gardiner
would gladly take you
with them to Gracechurch Street
after Christmas.
Why would you have me
go to London, Lizzy?
No reason.
A change of scene and society?
Why are you so late?
I'm sure I feared your coach
had overset itself,
or you had been attacked by robbers!
Nonsense, we made good time.
How do you do, F anny?
Very ill, Edward. No one knows
what I suffer with my nerves.
But then I never complain.
That's the best way, F anny.
You're very good.
- Have you brought us some presents?
- I see you've not changed, Lydia.
- Why, have I not grown?
- Aye, in everything but good sense.
Lizzy!
Get yourselves in, get yourselves in,
for you have barely time
for a change of clothes!
We are bidden to the Philips'
this evening.
I have no desire to be going
here and there at night.
I should much rather sit at home
and rest my poor nerves.
# God rest ye merry gentlemen,
Let nothing you dismay,
# Remember Christ our Saviour
Was born on Christmas Day,
# To save us all from Satan's pow'r...
(SONG CONTINUES IN THE BACKGROUND)
Aye, poor Jane. I would not have you
think I blame poor Jane at all!
Who could blame poor Jane
for the matter ?
She is the dearest girl in the world!
I was telling our dear sister,
Mrs Gardiner, she did her best.
She would have got Bingley if she could.
She did her best,
and no one could do more.
But, oh, sister,
when I think about Lizzy!
- It must be very hard, sister.
- It is very hard.
She could have been
Mr Collins' wife by now!
That would have given you such comfort!
Oh, those Lucases are
such artful people indeed.
They are all for what they can get!
However, your coming just at this time
is the greatest of comforts.
And we are very pleased to hear
what you tell us about
the latest fashions for long sleeves.
May I present Mr Wickham to you, Aunt?
I understand you come from Derbyshire,
Mr Wickham.
Indeed I do, ma'am.
Do you know the country?
Very well.
I spent some of the
happiest years of my life at Lambton.
Not five miles from where I grew up,
at Pemberley!
Pemberley! Surely it is the most
handsome house in Derbyshire,
and consequently in the world!
I see you take my view of things, ma'am.
- Are you acquainted with the family?
- No.
I had the good fortune
to be the protégé of old Mr Darcy.
He was the very best of men.
I wish you' d known him.
And a four on yours, and I'm out!
Lord, I've won again!
Let's have some dancing now.
I long for a dance!
Mary!
Mary, play Grimstock.
Capital! Capital!
- Fine girls, are they not, Mr Gardiner ?
- Indeed they are, Sir William.
- The two eldest in particular, perhaps ?
- Indeed, indeed.
They would grace
the court of St. James itself!
But let's not forget
the younger Miss Bennets!
Aye, they have arms and legs enough
between them,
and are three of the silliest girls
in England.
When do you go into Kent?
We shall spend the wedding night
at Lucas Lodge,
and then travel to Hunsford on Friday.
You will write to me, Lizzy?
I believe I am not likely to leave Kent
for some time.
I shall depend on hearing from you
very often.
That you certainly shall.
My father and Maria
are to come to me in March.
Lizzy, will you promise to be
one of the party?
Y ou will be as welcome
as either of them.
Then how could I refuse ?
But I'Il only come if you guarantee me
a glimpse of the famous chimney piece
at Rosings Park!
That you could scarcely avoid,
even if you wished to!
(MARIA): Charlotte!
Have you asked her ?
Is she to come to Hunsford with us ?
- Yes.
- Good!
I shan't be half so frightened
of Lady Catherine
if you are with us, Lizzy!
Who is that girl
dancing with Mr Wickham?
Her name is Mary King.
She's come to stay with her uncle
in Meryton.
- She's not very pretty, is she?
- Beauty is not the only virtue, Maria.
She's just inherited a fortune
of 10,000 pounds, I understand.
Now that is a definite virtue!
(MOTHER): It is very hard.
And I feel sorry for Lizzy,
because she's done little to deserve it.
(LYDIA): For Wickham to pursue Miss King
all the way to Barnet,
just for her 10,000 pounds!
(KITTY): I wish someone would die
and leave me 10,000 pounds.
(KITTY): Then all the officers
would love me!
(MOTHER): I'm sure they would,
Kitty dear.
(KITTY): Did you think
her pretty, mamma?
No indeed,
she has nothing to any of you.
(LYDIA): A little short freckled thing!
Poor Wickham. How he must be suffering.
(JANE): January the 12th.
My dearest Lizzy,
here we continue at Gracechurch Street
to be quiet and comfortable.
Aunt and Uncle could not be kinder
or more attentive.
All I lack here, dear Lizzy, is you,
to make me laugh at myself.
Three weeks ago, when our Aunt
was going to that part of town,
I took the opportunity of calling on
Miss Bingley in Grosvenor Street.
I was very eager to see Caroline again.
And I thought she was glad to see me,
though a little out of spirits.
She reproached me for giving her
no notice of my coming to London,
and I thought it very strange
that both my letters
should have gone astray.
Very strange indeed.
My visit was not long, as Caroline
and Mrs Hurst were going out.
Goodbye, Miss Bennet.
They promised to call at
Gracechurch Street in a day or two.
I waited at home every morning
for three weeks,
and at length, today she came.
I know, my dear Lizzy,
you will be incapable
of triumphing at my expense,
when I confess I have been
entirely deceived
in Miss Bingley's regard for me.
She made it very evident
that she took no pleasure in seeing me.
When I asked after her brother,
she made it clear
that he knows of my being in town,
but is much engaged at present
with Mr Darcy and his sister.
I must conclude then,
that Mr Bingley
now no longer cares for me.
Lizzy! Come quick!
Denny and Carter are here.
And guess who else? Wickham!
I heard you were going into Kent.
I felt I could not let you go
without calling to see you once.
I'm very glad you did.
I've missed our conversations.
I hear I am to congratulate you
on your forthcoming betrothal
to Miss King?
You must despise me.
Indeed I do not!
I understand, as my younger sisters
are not yet able to,
that handsome young men must have
something to live on,
as well as the plain ones.
Miss Bennet...
..I would wish you to believe me that...
had circumstances been different...
Had old Mr Darcy never had a son.
Oh, yes.
But life is full of these trials,
as my sister Mary reminds us daily.
I sincerely wish you
every happiness in the world.
- You are very forbearing.
- I flatter myself I am!
I think Jane would be quite proud of me.
I hope you and I, at least,
will always be good friends.
I'm sure we shall, Mr Wickham.
(FATHER): Well, Lizzy,
on pleasure bent again.
Never a thought of what your poor
parents will suffer in your absence?
It is a pleasure I could well forego,
father, as I think you know.
But I shall be happy to see Charlotte.
What of your cousin Mr Collins
and the famous Lady Catherine de Bourgh ?
As a connoisseur of human folly,
I thought you impatient
to be savouring these delights.
Of some delights, I believe, sir,
a little goes a long way.
Yes. Well, think of me, Lizzy.
Until you or your sister Jane return,
I shall not hear two words of sense
spoken together.
You'Il be very much missed, my dear.
Very well, very well. Go along then.
Get along with you.
Aye, Maria. All that land to the left
of us belongs to Rosings Park.
All of it? Oh, Lady Catherine must be
very rich indeed!
I believe so, I believe so!
And she has many favours in her gift.
Y our sister has made
a fortunate alliance!
(SIR WILLIAM): Yes, well,
I believe the next turn
takes us on to Hunsford.
Sir William! Maria!
Cousin Elizabeth.
I am truly honoured to be able
to welcome you to my humble abode!
- My dear Sir!
- My dear Mr Collins!
I am deeply honoured to make
a humble welcome to the Parsonage...
- I am happy to see you, Elizabeth.
- And I you.
The staircase, I flatter myself,
is eminently suitable
for a clergyman in my position,
being neither too shallow nor too steep.
As serviceable a staircase as I've ever
seen, sir. At St. James' Court...
Though it is nothing to the staircases
you will see at Rosings.
I say staircases,
because there are several,
and each in its way very fine.
And here, if you would permit me,
cousin Elizabeth.
This will be your bedchamber,
while you are with us.
And I trust you will find it comfortable
and convenient.
- Indeed it is a very pleasant room.
- Observe that closet, cousin Elizabeth.
- What do you say to that?
- Well...
Is it not the very essence
of practicality and convenience?
Lady Catherine de Bourgh herself
was kind enough to suggest that
these shelves be fitted.
Shelves in the closet...
Happy thought indeed.
She is kindness itself.
Nothing is too small to be
beneath her notice, is it not, my dear ?
She is a very attentive neighbour.
We dine at Rosings Park
twice every week!
And are never allowed to walk home.
That is generosity itself,
is it not, Maria?
Her ladyship's carriage
is regularly ordered for us.
I should say one of her ladyship's
carriages, for she has several.
And now, Sir William,
you were kind enough
to express a wish to see my gardens.
Mr Collins tends the gardens himself,
and spends a good part of every day
in them.
- The exercise must be beneficial.
- Oh, yes.
I encourage him to be in his garden
as much as possible.
And he has to walk to Rosings
nearly every day.
So often? Is that necessary?
Perhaps not, but I confess
I encourage him in that as well.
- Walking is very beneficial exercise.
- Oh, indeed it is.
When he's in the house,
he is mostly in his book room,
which affords a good view of the road,
whenever Lady Catherine's carriage
should drive by.
- And you prefer to sit in this parlour ?
- Y es.
So, it often happens
that a whole day passes
in which we haven't spent more than
a few minutes in each other's company.
I see.
I find that I can bear the solitude
very cheerfully.
I find myself...
..quite content
with my situation, Lizzy.
- (COLLINS): Charlotte, come quickly!
- (CHARLOTTE): What is it?
(MARIA): Lizzy! Lizzy!
Come into the dining room.
There's such a sight to be seen!
Make haste!
Look, Lizzy, look!
Is this all? I expected
the pigs had got into the garden!
Here's only Lady Catherine and
her daughter.
No, that's old Mrs Jenkinson.
With her is Miss Anne de Bourgh!
She's rude to keep Charlotte
out in this wind!
- What a little creature she is!
- I like her appearance.
She looks sickly and cross.
Yes, she will do very well.
She'Il make him a proper wife.
Who, Lizzy?
(COLLINS): Mark the windows.
There are 64 in all. 64!
And I have it on good authority
that the glazing alone originally cost
in excess of 600 pounds!
It's a very handsome building,
and prettily situated, sir.
And by no means lacking in windows.
Do not make yourself uneasy,
my dear cousin, about your apparel.
Lady Catherine is far from requiring
that elegance of dress,
which becomes herself and her daughter.
She won't think the worse of you
for being simply dressed.
She likes to preserve
the distinction of rank.
Thank you, Mr Collins,
that is a great comfort.
(LADY CATHERINE): An apothecary
will serve your needs quite adequately.
Make sure it be no one but Nicholson,
Mrs Collins.
I shall be extremely angry
if I hear you have gone elsewhere.
I have no intention to, Lady Catherine.
No indeed. No intention at all.
Well.
Your friend appears to be
quite a genteel
pretty sort of girl, Mrs Collins.
Her father's estate is entailed
on Mr Collins, I understand.
Yes, ma'am, and I am, believe me...
Do you have brothers and sisters,
Miss Bennet?
Y es, ma'am,
I am the second of five sisters.
Are any of your younger sisters out?
- Y es, ma'am, all of them.
- All?
What? All five out at once ?
The younger ones out
before the older are married?
Your youngest sisters
must be very young?
Yes, ma'am, my youngest is not sixteen.
Well!
She is full young
to be out much in company.
But really, ma'am, I think it would be
hard upon younger sisters,
that they not have their share
of society and amusement,
simply because their elder sisters
have not the means or
inclination to marry early.
Sir William, wouldn't you agree?
- Well...
- (LADY CATHERINE): Upon my word!
You give your opinion very decidedly
for so young a person!
Pray, what is your age?
With three younger sisters grown up,
your ladyship can hardly expect me
to own it.
Miss Bennet, you cannot be
more than twenty, I am sure.
Therefore there is no need
to conceal your age!
I am not one and twenty.
Mrs Collins, did I tell you of
Lady Metcalf's calling on me yesterday
to thank me for sending her Miss Pope?
''Lady Catherine, '' said she,
''you have given me a treasure. '' Yes!
Yes.
It is beautiful.
I could grow almost as fond
of these woods and hills as you have.
Lizzy?
We have been here three weeks,
and already we have dined
at Rosings Park six times!
I would never have expected it
to be so many!
No, nor I.
(COLLINS): My dear!
Maria! Cousin Elizabeth !
Mr Darcy is arrived at Rosings!
And with him his cousin,
Colonel Fitzwilliam!
The younger son of the Earl of Matlock!
They have vouchsafed us
the greatest honour.
They are coming to call upon us!
- When, my dear ?
- Even now, Mrs Collins!
They're hard upon my heels! Make haste!
This must be due to you.
Mr Darcy wouldn't come so soon
to wait upon me.
Y ou're mistaken, for he dislikes me
as much as I do him.
Make haste! Make haste!
Delighted to make
your acquaintance at last!
At last, sir ?
I've heard much of you,
and the praise hasn't been exaggerated.
I can well believe that.
Mr Darcy is my severest critic.
I hope we shall see you
frequently at Rosings.
- I'm fond of lively conversation.
- This you do not find at Rosings Park?
My aunt does talk a great deal,
but seldom requires a response.
My friend speaks hardly a word
when he comes into Kent,
though he's lively in other places.
Nobody plays, nobody sings.
- I believe you play and sing?
- A little, and very ill.
I wouldn't wish to excite
your anticipation.
I'm sure you're too modest.
Any relief would be profoundly welcome.
Can you tell me why Mr Darcy
keeps staring at me?
What do you think offends him?
- I hope your family is in good health.
- I thank you, yes.
My sister has been in town
these three months.
Have you not seen her ?
No.
No, I have not had that pleasure.
Mr Darcy and I
are not the best of friends.
I'm surprised.
Why should you be?
I always believe in first impressions,
and his good opinion once lost,
is lost forever.
So you see, it is a hopeless case,
is it not, Colonel Fitzwilliam?
You will never play really well,
Miss Bennet, unless you practise more.
(LADY CATHERINE): You may come
to Rosings as often as you like,
and play on the pianoforte
in Mrs Jenkinson's room.
She would be in nobody's way
in that part of the house.
Thank you, ma'am.
There are few people in England,
I suppose, who have more true enjoyment
in music than myself.
(LADY CATHERINE): Or a better taste.
And if I had ever learnt,
I should be a true proficient.
(LADY CATHERINE): And so would Anne.
Do you mean to frighten me, Mr Darcy,
by coming in all this state to hear me?
I won't be alarmed.
My courage always rises
with every attempt to intimidate me.
I know you find great enjoyment
in professing opinions
which are not your own.
Your cousin would teach you
not to believe a word I say,
Colonel Fitzwilliam.
- That is ungenerous of him, is it not?
- It is indeed, Darcy!
Impolitic too,
for it provokes me to retaliate
and say somewhat of his behaviour
in Hertfordshire,
which may shock his relations.
- I'm not afraid of you.
- What can you accuse him of?
I should like to know how he behaves
among strangers!
The first time I ever saw Mr Darcy
was at a ball,
where he danced only four dances,
though gentlemen were scarce,
and more than one lady
was in want of a partner.
- I'm sorry, but so it was.
- I can well believe it!
I fear I am ill qualified
to recommend myself to strangers.
Shall we ask him why?
Why a man of sense and education,
who has lived in the world,
should be ill qualified
to recommend himself to strangers?
I...
I have not that talent
which some possess,
of conversing easily with strangers.
I do not play this instrument
so well as I should wish to,
but I have supposed that
to be my own fault,
because I would not take the trouble
of practising!
You are perfectly right.
You have employed your time much better.
No one privileged of hearing you
could think anything wanting.
We neither of us perform to strangers.
(LADY CATHERINE): What are you
talking of?
What are you telling Miss Bennet?
I must have my share
in the conversation!
As for the daughter,
she is a pale sickly creature
with little conversation and no talent.
I'm sorry to be hard
on any of our sex, but...
Mr Darcy shows no inclination for her,
and treats her with the same
indifference he shows everyone,
but Lady Catherine is determined
to have him for a son-in-law,
and she is not a woman to be gainsaid.
(THE DOORBELL RINGS)
Mr Darcy.
Mrs Collins and Maria
are just now gone into Hunsford village
with my cousin.
You find me all alone this morning,
Mr Darcy.
I beg your pardon. I would not wish
to intrude upon your privacy.
I was just writing a letter
to my sister Jane in London.
Mr Bingley and his sisters were well,
I hope, when you left London?
Perfectly so, I thank you.
I understand Mr Bingley has not much
idea for ever returning to Netherfield?
It is probable that he may spend
little time there in the future.
If so, it would be better for the
neighbourhood that he give up the place.
I should not be surprised
if he were to give it up,
as soon as any eligible purchase offers.
This seems a very comfortable house.
Lady Catherine, I believe,
did much to it when Mr Collins came.
I believe she did.
And she couldn't have bestowed her
kindness on a more grateful recipient.
Mr Collins appears extremely fortunate
in his choice of wife.
Yes, indeed he is.
Though seen in a prudential light,
it is a good match for her as well.
It must be agreeable to her to live
within easy distance of her family.
Easy distance? It's nearly fifty miles!
What is fifty miles of good road?
Yes, an easy distance.
Near and far are relative terms.
It is possible for a woman
to be settled too near her family.
Yes, exactly.
You would not wish to be always
near Longbourn, I think.
I shall trespass on your time no longer.
Please convey my regards to
Mrs Collins and her sister.
No, no, please don't trouble yourself.
- Miss Bennet!
- Colonel Fitzwilliam.
I've been making the yearly tour
of the Park.
Shall we take this way together ?
With pleasure.
Do you know Mr Bingley and his sisters?
A little.
Bingley is a pleasant,
gentleman-like man.
He's a great friend of Darcy's.
Yes. Mr Darcy is uncommonly
kind to Mr Bingley,
and takes a prodigious
deal of care of him.
Yes, I believe Darcy
does take care of him.
I... I understand
that he congratulates himself
on having saved Mr Bingley
the inconvenience
of a most imprudent marriage.
Did Mr Darcy give his reasons
for this interference?
I understand there were some very strong
objections to the lady.
And why was he to be the judge?
You're disposed to think
his interference officious ?
I don't see what right Mr Darcy had
to determine and direct
in what way his friend was to be happy.
But, as you say,
we know none of the particulars.
- Perhaps there was not much affection.
- Perhaps not.
But if that were the case,
it lessens the honour of my cousin's
triumph very sadly, don't you think?
- Miss Bennet, are you unwell?
- A sudden headache.
Perhaps I have walked too far today.
Let us take the shorter way back.
Y ou're sure ?
I would willingly stay at home with you,
and brave
all Lady Catherine's displeasure.
My dear Charlotte,
I beg you to consider...
I shall be quite all right.
It's only a headache.
It will pass, and more speedily
in quiet and solitude.
I am quite sure,
when all the circumstances
are explained to Lady Catherine,
she will not be angry,
for she has indeed
such Christian generosity of spirit...
- My dear, the time!
- My dear! Why did you not say before?
I cannot begin to count the occasions
on which her ladyship has impressed
upon me the importance of punctuality...
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Forgive me.
I hope you are feeling better.
I am, thank you.
Will you not sit down?
In vain I have struggled.
It will not do!
My feelings will not be repressed.
You must allow me to tell you
how ardently I admire and love you.
In declaring myself thus I'm aware
that I will be going expressly against
the wishes of my family,
my friends, and, I hardly need add,
my own better judgement.
The relative situation of our families
makes any alliance between us
a reprehensible connection.
As a rational man I cannot but regard it
as such myself, but it cannot be helped.
Almost from the earliest moments,
I have come to feel for you...
..a passionate admiration and regard,
which despite my struggles,
has overcome every rational objection.
I beg you, most fervently,
to relieve my suffering
and consent to be my wife.
In such cases as these,
I believe the established mode
is to express a sense of obligation.
But I cannot.
I have never desired your good opinion,
and you have certainly bestowed it
most unwillingly.
I'm sorry to cause pain to anyone,
but it was unconsciously done,
and I hope will be of short duration.
And this is all the reply
I am to expect?
I might wonder why, with so little
effort at civility, I am rejected.
I might wonder why,
with so evident a desire to offend me,
you chose to tell me that
you like me against your will,
your reason, and
even against your character!
Was this not some excuse
for incivility if I was uncivil?
I have every reason in the world
to think ill of you.
What could tempt me to accept the man
who has ruined the happiness
of a most beloved sister ?
Can you deny that you have done it?
I have no wish to deny it.
I did everything in my power
to separate my friend from your sister,
and I rejoice in my success.
Towards him I have been kinder
than towards myself.
It's not merely that on which
my dislike of you is founded.
Long before, my dislike was decided
when I heard Mr Wickham's story
of your dealings with him.
How can you defend yourself
on that subject?
Such interest
in that gentleman's concerns!
Who that knows of his misfortunes,
can help feeling an interest?
His misfortunes! Yes, his misfortunes
have been great indeed!
And of your infliction!
You have reduced him
to his present state of poverty,
and yet you can treat his misfortunes
with contempt and ridicule!
And this is your opinion of me?
My faults by this calculation
are heavy indeed.
Perhaps these offences
might have been overlooked,
had not your pride been hurt
by the confession of the scruples
long prevented my forming
serious design on you.
Had I concealed my struggles
and flattered you.
But disguise of every sort
is my abhorrence.
Nor am I ashamed of the feelings
I related. They were natural.
Did you expect me to rejoice
in the inferiority of your connections?
To congratulate myself
on the hope of relations
whose condition in life
is so below my own?
You are mistaken, Mr Darcy.
Your declaration merely spared me
any concern for refusing you,
had you been more gentleman-like.
You could not make me
the offer of your hand in any way
that would tempt me to accept it.
From the beginning, your manners
convinced me of your arrogance,
your conceit, and your selfish disdain
for the feelings of others.
Within a month, I felt you were the
last man whom I could ever marry!
You've said quite enough, madam.
I perfectly comprehend your feelings...
..and now have only to be ashamed of
what my own have been.
Please forgive me
for having taken up your time...
..and accept my best wishes
for your health and happiness.