Previously on "The Originals"...
Hayley: If we can't create
some sort of community,
then what's the point?
Kill each other and get
it all over with.
Elijah: If there is
no peace between us,
then how can you expect
others to follow suit?
Klaus: The city's inhabitants will
not adhere to this agreement.
Aah!
The guy on the bike, the bomber,
owed money to the casinos.
More importantly,
to the humans who run them.
The ancestors told me to let you live.
Whatever it is they want,
I will make sure they get it.
They want us to kill Klaus' child.
I've been hexed, and I
don't know how long I have.
Klaus: I'm calling to let
you know the priest is dead.
Your exile is suspended
for the next 24 hours.
You may return to the quarter
to bury your friend.
[Music playing]
[Baby talk]
Hi.
[Stake pierces body]
Greetings, boy.
[Gasping]
Genevieve: New Orleans
is full of ghosts.
Our dead are always here hovering.
When supernatural creatures
die, they're doomed
to spend eternity alone watching
the world go on without them.
Of course, that's not the case
for the ancestral witches.
We linger in a different way...
Consecrated in the earth,
replenishing its power.
What about humans?
Some find peace.
Some... don't.
I have to make an appearance
at the priest's wake.
You three head back to the lycee.
Take some time to think
about those spirits
who might still be
walking alongside you.
I don't know why we're
supposed to care
about Kieran O'Connell.
We care because when a pillar
of our community passes,
Monique, you call
a cease-fire and pay respects.
Or you just want to see Klaus.
You two are getting cozy.
I need the Mikaelsons to trust
me so I can get close enough.
To kill their baby?
To fulfill my obligation
to our ancestors.
Go home, Monique.
[Heavy sigh]
[Music playing]
Hey, earth to you.
Your face...
Will heal.
Listen, I wanted to thank you.
Unless you come equipped
with the means to fill this,
no additional platitudes
are necessary.
Ok. I'm in a crap mood
because my Uncle just died
and people are partying
like it's Mardi Gras.
What's your excuse?
Klaus, seriously, what's going...
I've been having these
dreams about my dead father.
No diagnosis necessary, love.
I've already got this one covered.
My fears of fatherhood,
of scarring my child
as my father scarred me are
manifesting as nightmares.
So horrifically cliche.
Truthfully, I'm just surprised
to hear you acknowledge out loud
that you're going to be a dad.
Your baby mama's been living
in the bayou for months.
It's not exactly what to
expect when you're expecting.
I know more about
the trials of fatherhood
than you might imagine, Camille.
And it worked out so well
for you the first time.
Why change a thing?
Well. I see you've come to
return some stolen property.
On the contrary.
I've decided the boy
shall remain with me.
Man: Unfortunately, he's not for sale.
Well, I do not wish to buy him.
You will grant him his freedom.
And if I say no?
You seem to have misinterpreted
the matter as up for debate.
[Hoarsely] Fine. Take him.
He wasn't worth...
A damn to me anyway.
They told me he is your father.
Is it true?
You know, my father hated me, too.
The truth is, Marcellus, family
can be more than just those
with whom we share blood.
We can choose.
[Music playing]
[Clink clink]
[Music stops]
I know I haven't been around
these parts lately.
It's a testament to father Kieran
that we could come together
and share a drink and a story or two.
Kieran rolled into town
on a rusty old cruiser
after his daddy died 25 years ago.
And, damn it, that guy could party.
[Laughter]
That was, of course,
before he took his vows.
But even then, he was
committed to the quarter.
He knew that this town needed him.
And we still do.
To father K.
All: To father K.
[Music resumes]
[Sighs]
Looks like we had the same idea.
It's Cami, right?
I've been informed that
Kieran's necklace is missing
and the key that he always wore,
I assume he left it for me.
Excuse me?
How rude of me.
[Places glass on table]
I'm Francesca Correa.
I took over your Uncle's position
as faction representative
when his mental faculties
were compromised.
His faculties weren't compromised.
He was hexed.
Hexed by one of our enemies.
Look, I'm invested in protecting
the people of this city.
And to do that, I need the key.
It must have fallen off
during the events that led
to his untimely death.
I'm so sorry.
Seems rather uncivilized...
To laugh and dance around
the body of a loved one.
Yes. Far better to practice
your process of grief,
isn't it, Klaus?
Denial, rage,
and hoarding coffins in basements.
I'll warn you, Hayley,
Niklaus is in a spectacularly
foul mood today.
Sod off.
What's the deal with
these moonlight rings?
Oliver's trying to start a
revolution every 5 seconds.
People are scared, angry.
And, frankly, I'm tired of stalling.
It's a day of peace,
Hayley. Try and enjoy it.
In the meantime with all
manner of unknown enemies
conspiring against our family,
you'll move back in with us.
[Sarcastically] Awesome.
Then we can do that thing where
you lock me in the tower,
I escape, there's drama,
and then you two both
realize that I'm very
capable of looking after myself.
The rings are in progress.
I will live up to my word.
We will find and punish
whoever launched the attack
on the bayou.
And you will return to the
compound for your own safety.
But right now, I'm gonna
finish this bottle...
And the next in the hopes
of drowning the demon
that has chosen today to haunt me.
Cheers, Mikael.
Impeccable Freudian timing.
Elaborate.
Have you dreamt of our father?
Go ahead. Have a good laugh.
I can assure you there
isn't a piece of this
that I find even remotely
amusing, Niklaus,
especially considering I've
been dreaming of him, too.
What?
If you are also seeing him...
Perhaps our elusive, unknown enemy
is orchestrating a further attack.
Well, then what better way to
punctuate a day of peace...
Than by killing someone?
[Bell rings]
[Indistinct whisper]
[Chuckles nervously]
You disappeared from the party.
Would you care to explain why
you would choose to torment us
with visions of our father?
Your father?
Mm-hmm.
I didn't.
I-I wouldn't.
Of course.
How foolish of me.
It must have been that other witch
that's been parading throughout
our house in scraps of lace.
I know how talented you are
with your tongue, Genevieve.
Might I recommend you use
it to provide answers?
I would so hate to tear
it from your mouth.
As much as I enjoy these
repeated accusations
of wrongdoings, I don't know
what you're talking about.
But if you've both been seeing
your dead father, I can
try to get you answers.
Fine. Go.
Niklaus, don't you dare...
Go.
[Bell on door rings]
You don't trust her.
And you're right not to.
Only a fool would,
but she certainly wants
us to, doesn't she?
Let me guess. There's
something of benefit
for you in all of this, isn't there?
I need a witch to make those
rings for the wolves.
Perhaps we'll get both
answers and cooperation...
I don't know if the ancestors
would like us messing
around in the spirit world.
It's just a simple seance.
Phony witches do seances
to impress tourists.
They're not real.
Abigail: What's that for?
It was my friend Tim's.
Come on. What's the point
of being a witch
if we can't use our magic
for stuff like this?
Both: Elikopte fantomes,
soliter mouri, vous reveler...
[Wind]
Tim?
[Violin music]
[Chimes ringing]
What a delightful tune.
[Exhales sharply]
So Klaus gives you 24 hours
in the quarter, and you're spending it
coffin sitting with me?
No preparations for war?
No chess pieces to move?
We're honoring Kieran.
Even us bad guys
can take the night off.
Maybe you can.
Not sure the humans are
on their best behavior.
This Francesca person
cornered me earlier,
asking about some key.
What'd you tell her?
It doesn't matter.
I don't have it.
But you know or you would
have asked, "what key?"
[Chuckles softly]
I had Josh lift it for me.
Off my Uncle's sick and dying body?
I'm trying to do you a favor.
Trust me, you don't want to
be a part of any of this.
Trust you?
Are you kidding me?
Cami, this is bigger than you.
Don't patronize me, Marcel.
Do you know what's bigger than me?
My Uncle lost his mind,
beat the crap out of me,
and then died.
And now I have to sit
by his body all night.
I'll sit with you.
I'm not trying to lie to you.
I'm trying to protect you.
You need to leave, like, now.
I will tell you about the key.
I don't want to know!
I don't want to know any of it.
[Puts glass on table]
[Chatter in adjoining room]
Genevieve.
I asked around.
It's not just your father.
The purgatory, where
supernatural souls are trapped,
is disintegrating.
What do you mean, disintegrating?
She's right, more or less.
It's actually imploding.
I made a call to a rather
reluctant Bennett witch
in Mystic Falls, who said
the same thing...
The dead are being torn
away into nothingness.
And they're not interested
in going quietly.
So you're saying that our father,
faced with permanent extinction,
has decided to spend his
remaining time tormenting us.
How delightful.
Well, on the plus side,
we'll soon be rid of
his abhorrent soul forever.
And what a good riddance that will be.
So am I in the clear, Elijah?
Or is there a new conspiracy
you two would like
to threaten me over?
Nothing springs to mind
at this precise moment.
Oh, gee, thanks.
I have to get back to the girls.
Perhaps tomorrow after the funeral,
you and I could spend
some time together...
Alone.
I suppose we'll have to see.
[Scoffs]
Please tell me you've designed
a stronger method to control the witch
than playing hard to get.
Klaus: Well, I've always been
partial to the classics.
Ah. Hayley, right?
I'm guessing you're not here
because you want to make a new friend.
I don't count terrorists as friends.
Wow.
I've been accused
of everything from grand
larceny to blackmail.
But terrorist, that's new.
A human pulled up
to our home in the bayou
on a motorcycle and blew himself up.
I heard. Awful.
Good night.
Word on the street is
he owed 100 grand
to the palace royale casino.
And then after he died,
the debt was erased.
Just like magic.
Jeff was a fixture
at my roulette table.
Sometimes he was up.
Sometimes he was down.
I absolved his family
of the debt he owed
out of the goodness of my heart.
Feel free to sniff around.
My hands are clean.
And I'd advise you
to mind your manners.
It's lucky you're still alive.
You're the one the wolves all
whisper about, like royalty.
If I was interested
in hurting the wolves,
you'd be my target.
And when I go after
someone, I don't miss.
Monique: Purger l'interieur,
etiendre la lumiere
dans cette f...
[Bell ringing]
Your reading was beautiful.
Sneak attack. Not fair.
I'm still pissed.
Tell me about the key.
I thought you said
you didn't want to know.
I'd like to say I slept on
it, but I didn't sleep.
I stayed awake all night next
to the body of a hexed priest
only to attend a funeral
filled with vampires.
So I'm thinking you should
tell me about the key.
Kieran told me that
the key leads to something
that can be used against
the supernaturals
if we ever get too far out of line.
Kieran and I had our ups and downs,
but we trusted each other.
So I let it be.
Because I knew if he had to
use whatever Pandora's box
that key opens, it'd be because
he didn't have a choice.
You could've just asked me for it.
Would you have just handed it over?
So what does it open?
I don't know. I turned
the city upside down
last night trying to find it.
The church, the rectory.
I even searched your family's tomb.
It's hard to find
a needle in a haystack
when you don't even know
what the needle looks like.
And you want to know
if I have any ideas.
That's why you're here.
I'm here because my friend died
and my other friend is grieving.
You can question my
intentions all day long,
Cami.
I'm here for Kieran.
And I'm here for you.
[Music playing]
[Coughs]
You all right?
You look...
A hundred months' pregnant
and pissed off at the world?
I was going to say, "you look lovely."
Do you think I was the
target of those bombings?
Of course you were the target.
Were I to wage a war on the
wolves, you'd be my first kill.
I would string you up for
all your worship.
I believe that was
my brother's way of telling you
he'd like you to return home with us.
Perhaps try a different approach,
Niklaus,
with fewer references to murder.
As much as I would hate to throw you
over my shoulder and drag you
kicking and screaming to the compound,
we both know I will
for the sake of my child.
One bad dream,
and suddenly you want to be
a responsible daddy.
Let me put this in perspective.
My father lived to torment me.
It is not my intention to become him.
This cycle of misery
ends with my child.
[Chuckles softly]
You forgot one thing in your
attempt to plead your case.
She's not your child.
She's ours.
Very heartfelt, Niklaus.
I bloody hate funerals.
Cami...
[Clears throat]
Hayley, hi.
Hi. I know you don't know me.
I just wanted to say that I...
I'm sorry about your Uncle.
He was really good to people like me
during the storm, and I
really appreciated that.
Thank you.
You want something, don't you?
I'm sorry about the timing.
I was just wondering
if before he died,
he said anything weird
about Francesca Correa.
I think that she may
have been involved
in an attack on the bayou.
If you hear anything...
Look, Hayley, I'm tr
mostly failing...
To stay out of all this stuff,
but she's a real bitch.
So, yeah, if I hear anything,
I'll let you know.
Thanks. Um, again, sorry
about your Uncle.
Me, too.
[Coughing]
Klaus!
Hayley!
Genevieve: I can help.
Don't you touch her.
Let her be, Elijah.
She was a nurse.
There's a spell I can do.
Klaus, get chamomile from the pantry.
Genevieve: She's trembling.
Your jacket, Elijah.
She's not breathing.
[Muffled] I can hear the baby's
heartbeat, but not hers.
[Gasping]
Who are you?
I suppose...
I'm family.
In the beginning was the word.
And the word was with God.
He was with God in the beginning.
In him was life.
And that life was
the light of all mankind.
The light shines in the darkness.
And the darkness has not overcome it.
Cami...
Sean didn't have a funeral.
Our parents wanted
nothing to do with him,
so the city had him buried out here
with the criminals
and the John does...
The great unloved.
You said you checked my family's tomb,
but I've been thinking.
All this time, I wondered why Kieran
didn't have Sean interred,
where he belonged, with the family.
But then I realized, what if he saw
an opportunity to hide something
he didn't want anyone else to find?
Cami, we can do this another time.
Bad timing is the theme of the day.
I'm going to need a sledgehammer.
Coeur blesse, battre avec mwen...
Come on.
Elijah: She's still not breathing.
It's not working.
I assume my reputation precedes me.
This is a nightmare.
I'm dreaming.
On the contrary, my darling.
This is very real.
Welcome to my hell.
Stuck in an eternity of watching over
that hideous creature
my children call brother.
You're dead.
How can I be here?
Oh, my God.
No! No! The baby!
The baby?
Aah!
That kid never had a chance!
And as if your bloodline
isn't filth enough,
you poison it by merging
it with Klaus'?
[Chuckling]
The deathless vermin
fancying himself a daddy.
[Screaming]
Aah!
She's not dead.
I'm not dead.
If I was dead, you wouldn't
be trying to kill me.
[Chanting continues]
I'm taking her to a real doctor.
If you move her from here,
my spell will break.
There won't be enough time
to get her to a hospital.
Will the baby survive
if delivered now?
I'll rip it out of her myself.
Hayley will bleed to death.
I won't lose that baby.
I won't lose either of them.
[Genevieve's chanting resumes]
[Distorted chants]
I know what to do.
Get my bag...
The gris-gris pouch.
Now!
You're dead, Mikael.
Your son already beat you.
He is not my son!
He's a scourge, a walking
symbol of weakness.
There is no saving that atrocity
festering in your womb.
Klaus will destroy it
one way or another.
Better he dies now
and you along with it.
Aah!
My daughter has an
advantage Klaus never had.
She will never, ever know you.
[Gasping]
Hayley.
You're all right, love.
You're all right.
I saw him, and he tried to kill me.
I saw Mikael.
[Knock knock]
You've proved quite
resilient, little wolf.
Fighters, both of you.
I guess we've had to be,
especially lately.
I've decided that I'm
going to move back in.
Well, I'm relieved to hear it.
But no mouth-breathing bodyguards,
no telling me what to do.
All I ask is that
the child is kept safe.
And what about me?
What happens after she's born?
If you try to take her
away from me, I...
Come with me, hmm?
Please. I want to show you something.
Believe it or not, Hayley,
I would actually like you to be here.
Our daughter should be
raised by her parents
in her family home.
You, me, Elijah, and the miracle
baby all under one roof.
Sounds like a bad reality show.
[Chuckles]
You said you saw my father.
Why do you call him that?
He's not your real dad.
He's done damage
only a father could do.
What did he say to you?
Nothing true.
[Music playing]
Hayley and the baby are fine.
I'd take her to a doctor when she's
gotten some rest, if you want,
but she's in the clear.
I'll see myself out.
Genevieve...
Thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
You tore my sister from my family.
I cannot forgive that.
However, I may be inclined to
show a degree more of kindness
if you were to help me
with a slight issue.
Anything.
When the baby arrives,
Hayley will once again
transform with a full moon.
Now, I would like
to create for her a gift,
a ring of empowerment, something
to control this curse.
What kind of spell would...
A spell of my mother's,
from her grimoire,
which, as I understand,
you have been rather eager to obtain.
Someone must have gotten to it.
I don't think so.
My brother taught me
this code 15 years ago.
I never knew how he learned it.
You can tell me what that says?
I can...
But I won't.
I'm sorry.
Cami, this is too...
Dangerous. Yeah.
I got it.
But if Kieran taught Sean this...
My brother was meant to be
brought into it all along.
That makes it my responsibility now,
whether I like it or not.
What the hell did you do to Hayley?
I was trying to do what
the ancestors asked.
That baby is part witch.
The ancestors want her
consecrated to the earth
so her magic can fuel our community.
She has to be born first
before she can die.
Leave.
I don't want to look at you.
Allumez le feu dans cette femme...
Misericorde.
Don't make me do this.
[Sobbing] She's a baby.
Don't make me a monster.
Please.
No.
[Screaming]
Uh! Aah...
N... no.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'll do it.
I'll do whatever you want!
Hayley has agreed to
return home to us...
Of her own freewill.
When Mikael is truly gone,
do you think then I'll find peace?
I certainly hope so.
Although it's not only our
father that haunts you, Niklaus.
You might want to make
peace with the living.
Marcel: I demand to know
why their freedom
has not been granted.
All necessary authorities
have ruled in their favor.
You think I don't remember you, boy?
Have they turned you
into one of them yet?
[Chuckling]
I thought not.
[Screaming]
[Woman groans]
[Gunshots]
Ugh!
Here. Let me heal you.
No.
You've always said we'd
choose our family.
So what am I to you, Klaus?
You made me a promise when
you daggered your sister.
It's finally time to make a choice.
Turn me now...
Or let me die.
You do not know what you ask of me.
Becoming like me...
It would Rob you of all
that makes you good.
I know what you are...
Who you are.
This is what I want.
Please.
[Labored breathing]
[Crack]
Your furlough ends
when the clock strikes.
I'm aware. Don't worry.
I intend to be far away
from here by then.
But just because I'm across the river
doesn't mean I'm out of the game.
A full moon's coming.
I know you're up to
something with the wolves.
And I've been racking my brain,
trying to figure out what.
And any way I do the math, it
ends with me and my guys dead.
Or maybe we're supposed
to fall in line,
pledge our allegiance
to you all over again.
So if we get bitten, you
might deign to cure us.
Is that what you're after?
Because it's not gonna happen.
Well, that will be your
choice, just as you chose
to bring my father to town...
You, who knows better than
anyone the specific agony
of a father's hatred.
Klaus...
I spent decades trying to make up
for what your father did.
How did I fail?
Maybe the scars just ran too deep.
Good night, Marcellus.
You didn't fail me.
You raised me.
You taught me everything that I know.
You taught me that I
can't afford to be weak,
not when my enemies are stronger.
So whatever it is you got
coming with the wolves,
just know that I'm gonna
fight for my guys.
I'm gonna fight for my city.
And I will fight until I am dead.
I would expect nothing less.
[Music playing]
If I died and someone threw a
party, I would be so pissed.
You almost did.
In a thousand years,
I can't recall a time
I've felt so frightened.
Elijah...
[Chimes ringing]
Tim, is that you?
Who are you?
Your friend Timothy
has moved on, Davina.
I'm truly sorry for
what my son did to him.
You're Klaus' father.
And I'm the only one who can
rid you of him forever.
[Speech echoing]
But first, my little witch...
I need you.
What can I do?
You can bring me back to life.