Now, you don't have to
search the world for the perfect gift.
Handmade in the tradition
of ancient artists.
¶ Ch-Ch-Ch-Chia! ¶
It's new Chia Pets.
Chia elephant,
Chia cow and Chia lion cub.
It's easy. Soak your Chia
overnight, spread the seeds...
call roll.
Mr. Akaka.
Resident of
a Sandpiper Crossing facility
or similar retirement community,
you may be eligible to
receive compensation.
Residents of some
Sandpiper Crossing
or similar
retirement communities
may have been overcharged
for goods and services.
In partnership with the law offices
of Hamlin, Hamlin & McGill,
the law offices of Davis & Main
are working to help those
who have been overcharged by
their retirement communities.
For your free consultation,
call Davis & Main
at 505-242-7700.
That's 505-242-770...
You've reached Kim Wexler.
Please leave a message.
¶ Someday you'll see me
¶ Floatin' in the sunshine
¶ My head stickin' out
from a low flyin' cloud
¶ You'll hear me call you
¶ Singin' through the sunshine
¶ Sweet and clear as can be
¶ Bali Ha'i will whisper
¶ On the winds of the sea
¶ "Here am I,
your special island!"
¶ "Come to me, come to me!"
¶ Bali ha'i
¶ Bali ha'i ¶
All right. There you go.
That completes our week-long
tour of South Pacific.
You're welcome.
Tomorrow we
begin our exploration
of the Carpenters' catalog.
Of course,
I am open to requests.
That's right.
All you gotta do is call me.
Anytime.
All right?
Bye. Call me.
Boundaries, Mrs. Nguyen.
Boundaries.
Why are you here?
You lose that job already?
I should be so lucky.
You don't like your job?
Boo-hoo. Poor baby.
You know, some people work for a living.
No one gives us free cars.
So why you here?
This place is paid up. I'm within
my rights as your legal tenant.
That's all you need to know.
Do I smell coffee?
Have you got a pot on?
Why?
How about a fill-up?
You can afford to buy your own!
Faster I get coffee,
the faster I'm out of here.
Chao cac co, ladies.
Son of a...
You haven't unpacked yet?
Kevin and Paige are here.
Absolutely.
I don't know exactly what
Chuck may have said to you,
but just so you know, I did not
ask him to step in on my behalf.
Hi, guys! Sorry for the wait.
Not a problem. Hi.
So good to see you again.
Howard.
Hi, Kim.
Good to see you, too!
Hi, Paige. Hi, Kevin.
Kim, great to see you.
Please have a seat. Thank you.
Kevin, how's your grandson?
Out of control. Just running
circles around all of us.
Hello. Can I help you?
You know why I'm here?
He needs an answer.
Respectfully,
I'm gonna have to say no.
You sure about that?
I am.
Your Honor, the defense has made
the very reasonable request
that the plaintiffs produce their
medical records, or barring that,
a signed HIPAA release so that we
can examine the records ourselves.
Your Honor, our clients'
medical records
have no bearing on
the merits of this case.
The medical records
are plainly relevant
as they bear directly
on our contention
that the plaintiffs are not
adequate class representatives.
This is a transparent attempt
at intimidation, nothing more.
How so?
Many of our clients have information
in their medical records
that they prefer
to keep private.
They're fearful,
as any of us would be,
at the thought of
a bunch of strangers
poking around in
their personal files.
And by forcing them
to reveal this information,
the defense is banking on them
simply dropping out of the case.
Your Honor, this is about class
certification. That's all.
If the named
plaintiffs are suffering from
dementia or other
mental deficiencies...
You're saying
they're incompetent?
I'm saying we have
a right to any record
that would speak
to their competency
as regards this class
certification issue.
Your Honor, it seems like the
defense wants it both ways, then.
If our clients are
suffering from dementia,
then the residency
contracts they signed
with Sandpiper couldn't have
been entered into knowingly.
No. No,
that is not what we...
The defense wants to claim that
their residents are competent enough
to be held to their contracts,
but too incompetent to sue.
So which is it?
Many of the residents signed
their contracts years ago.
And at the time, they
were perfectly competent.
But that can change,
especially when we're talking
about elderly individuals.
Or maybe Sandpiper preyed on
mentally incompetent seniors
and bilked them
out of their money.
Ms. Wexler...
I am simply trying to defend our
clients from bullying by the defense.
Your Honor, as stated in
the brief in front of you,
this is a standard request granted
in every case of its kind.
This is not about bullying.
Granting this
invasion of privacy
allows our clients to
be doubly victimized.
I ask that you deny the
defense's motion, Your Honor.
I'm leaning toward
granting the motion,
but I would like to review the
pleadings and briefs again.
I'll have my
decision for you shortly.
Adjourned.
I'm gonna meet you
back at the office.
Ms. Wexler?
Hey.
I just wanted to say,
good work in there.
Thanks. But I'm
pretty sure I lost.
Of course you did.
It's an unwinnable position.
That's why your boss
didn't bother showing up.
But you went down swinging,
and I admire that.
Thank you.
What are you doing for lunch?
Probably just grabbing something
from the vending machines.
Oof.
We can do better than that.
Mr. Schweikart.
Good to see you, sir.
How you doing, Sean?
Very well.
Can I get some drinks for you two?
Your usual Moscow Mule?
Absolutely.
You want one? Best
Moscow Mule in the city.
Fresh ginger, real
copper mug, the works.
That's very vintage.
But I'm good.
Just an iced tea. You sure?
All right, then.
I'll be the sole degenerate
who's drinking in
the middle of the workday.
That, too, is vintage.
I'll get those started.
So, you've been with HHM,
what? Ten years?
Yeah. Last August.
And you started
in the mail room?
I did. I was six years there.
How did you know that?
I asked around.
It's a small town.
It sounds like you
certainly paid your dues.
I was very fortunate.
HHM put me through
law school while I worked.
That's great that they
foster talent like that.
And I imagine you're paying
it off as part of your deal?
Yeah, happily.
It's a pretty
standard arrangement.
I have to say,
watching you in court today,
it sure did bring back
some old memories for me.
One in particular, anyway.
Yeah? I was a year
out of law school
at this firm in Boston, and I was
finally put on my first big case.
This huge employment
discrimination suit.
That thing kept us in
billing for a decade.
Anyway, we landed this monster,
and I find out I'm
second chair to one of
the partners on
the preliminary hearing.
And I think, "This is it!"
"This is what will define
the rest of my career."
So, the hearing's
getting closer and closer.
I even get this new
suit that I can't afford.
I split it over
three credit cards.
I'm probably still
paying it off to this day.
So, I go in bright and early, I'm
wearing my new suit, prepping my table,
and in walks
the opposing counsel.
There's four of them.
One senior partner and three
high-level associates.
These guys have been litigating
longer than I've been alive.
But I think... ""
"I'm good, I've got my boss
coming, it'll be fine."
So I'm sitting alone at my table,
waiting for my boss to show.
And I'm waiting.
And then suddenly they're calling
us to order, and I realize
that no one from my firm is coming.
It's just me.
So I think, "All right, then.
This is the moment."
And I get up there and I argue
like my life depended on it.
I'm sweating and I'm citing
statutes left and right.
And I'm doing okay.
Respectable.
But I'm just a BB gun
to these four howitzers.
And I lose, of course.
It was inevitable.
But later, it hit me that my
boss never intended to show.
And they all laughed about it.
They patted me on the back,
said it was my trial by fire.
And I laughed with them.
But, you know,
it never really
sat well with me.
You want them to have your back.
Because at the end of the day, it
wasn't about proving my mettle.
My boss had a tee time
that he didn't want to miss.
I wasn't there long.
Could I ask why we are here?
You know, I've had my
eye on you for a while.
Since that Kettleman thing. It was
an excellent deal you got for him.
And I'm wondering why someone who
can put together a deal like that
is arguing a losing
position with no backup.
I have no complaints about HHM.
That's great. However,
if on the off-chance
you're pondering a change,
Schweikart & Cokely
would be more than happy
to put your talents to good use.
I...
Of course we'd have to have
a more formal meeting,
work out specifics, but we think
you would be a great fit.
Well, I'm flattered, but there's
clearly an ethical issue here.
Well, of course,
we'd take you off Sandpiper.
And rest assured,
we wouldn't be expecting
any information
about HHM's strategy.
Look, we're a large,
diversified firm.
And just think what you
can do with our resources
and the freedom to
really spread your wings.
That's...
I owe a lot to HHM.
Your tuition debt?
We could take care of that.
That's very generous.
Well, give it some time,
you think about it.
And you give me a call,
and we'll set up a meeting with
the rest of the senior partners.
And, to be clear,
I'm talking partner track.
Jesus, Sean, did you have
to send to Moscow?
Sorry for the
wait, Mr. Schweikart.
Are we ready to order?
For the gourmet Quick Chop.
It's the fastest,
easiest and safest way
to chop, mince or dice
any vegetable. Guaranteed.
Here's how it works.
Just place the vegetable on
the board, give it a tap,
and you've got finely
shredded cabbage in seconds.
For crunchy coleslaw.
Tap again and chop celery...
for a delicious stir-fry.
It even works on
your tougher vegetables.
Like potatoes.
Make home fries
with just one tap.
Get down.
Quick Chop peels and chops it
with just a tap.
Keep tapping for freshly minced garlic.
The secret's the six
carbon steel blades,
combined with
the rotating action.
Each time you tap, it rotates
and chops on a different angle,
and never misses a thing.
One tap, and you've got
sliced onions for burgers.
A few more taps,
and you've got...
What's the message?
Take the $5,000.
It took two guys
to tell me that?
We were just supposed to scare you.
That's all.
Then try harder next time.
Get out.
It has the power to chop nuts.
Almonds, walnuts, pecans.
The Quick Chop even has
the muscle to crush ice.
Get out.
Call now and
you'll get Quick Chop
for $14.99. But that's not all!
We'll also include the grater
and the gripper free.
Remove the blades
and it instantly converts...
Hey, Julie. Come on in.
I've got those
Sandpiper documents.
Great, just put them anywhere.
Howard asked if you could
go through them now.
It's 1:15. I was just
about to grab some lunch.
Yeah. He needs them done by
2:30 so he can draft a letter.
I brought these. Figured I could
petty cash a lunch order for you.
I got accounting to approve
that new fancy salad place.
Kaylee.
Kaylee, come on.
Not too far from the side.
Throw the ball, Pop-Pop.
When are we going home?
What?
You don't like it here?
It's okay.
"It's okay"?
You've got a pool.
What more do you want?
I guess.
You guess? You guess? Well...
You want to come out of there?
No! I'm staying.
Well, you want me to come
in there and get you?
I can't have you in
a pool that's only "okay."
It's good! It's good!
You sure? You sure?
I'm sure!
Kaylee, honey,
it's time to come out now.
Just a few more minutes!
No. You do what Pop-Pop says.
Come on, baby, before
you turn into a prune.
Miss?
The gentleman
would like me to let
you know that your
next drink is on him.
Just let me know
when you're ready.
I'm ready.
I wasn't sure that was gonna work.
Don't tell me that's the
first time you've done that.
So, what kind of
return on investment
are you getting on these drinks?
None as pretty as you.
Man.
I'm Dale, by the way.
Giselle.
Okay, item number 44,
what do we have?
Residency contract
for Abigail Hildreth.
"Abigail Hildreth."
And what's the date on that?
Dated August 1st, 1999.
August 1st, 1999.
And do we have the corresponding
deposition for Mrs. Hildreth?
Yes.
Have you ever heard the expression,
"A watched pot never boils"?
Here it is.
Thank you. See?
I've got her down as item 12.
Date of depo, September 15th.
September 15th.
Fifteenth of September.
Or yeah, September 15th.
Thank you.
Okay, item number 45.
Jimmy?
It's my grandma. She's old.
I'll be right back.
Kim?
How fast can you get downtown?
Santa Fe downtown?
Albuquerque.
Why?
I'm at the bar at Forque.
And I've got a live one on the hook.
I'm on my way. What's the shot?
Definitely two or three.
You don't think they do?
They could.
I know, but they don't have to.
That's possible, but I don't
understand why that's an issue.
You can always go back.
Yeah. Yeah.
Viktor! There you are!
So sorry I'm late.
I had to put out a few fires.
No problem.
I made a new friend.
Dale, my brother Viktor.
Hey, how you doing?
Nice to meet you, Dale. Thanks
for keeping sis company.
My pleasure.
You need a drink.
Let's get you a drink.
So, what do you do, Dale?
I'm an engineer.
Like Casey Jones, with the hat?
No, idiot.
An engineer-engineer.
Not an "engineer."
Dale builds things.
I design things. Spillways
and drainage fields, mostly.
I don't actually build them.
Well, that's cool. Yeah.
But you could still wear the hat, though.
Right? Nothing stopping you.
Yeah, I guess I could.
I'm just saying there's no rule
about that, as far as I know.
You are such a brat!
Why the good mood?
Did it go well today?
Please tell me it went well.
Yeah, it went well.
Very well? Like, very, very?
Beyond our wildest... Yeah.
Whoo!
How many of these has she had?
I'm just getting started, baby!
Remember these faces, Dale!
Giselle.
They're gonna be on the cover of
Fortune Magazine, January issue.
Giselle. Please.
Dale's a good guy.
He's not gonna do anything.
You're boring the man.
No, no, not really.
Thank you.
All right, I'm off to
the little girl's room.
Say only nice things about me
while I'm gone, okay?
She's something.
Yeah.
So, Giselle was telling me you
two are starting a business?
What exactly did she tell you?
Nothing much.
Just something about a dotcom.
Some way for people to hook up with
each other using the Internet?
Look, I'm sure
you're a nice guy,
but she was
talking out of school.
We're full up on this thing.
Okay.
We sign one more investor,
we gotta go public.
And I'm just... No.
We cannot take anyone else on.
No offense.
It's okay. Yeah.
No worries.
Spread your arms.
No.
He's got a gun.
I don't care about the gun.
Tomorrow, you go to
the district attorney.
And you explain to him that
my nephew's gun was yours.
The DA will ask you, "Why you
didn't say anything before?"
You tell him you forgot.
You were rattled.
Make up anything you want,
I don't give a shit.
But it's your gun.
Let's discuss my payment.
That time has passed.
No $5,000 for you.
The price is $50,000.
How about your
payment is you get to live?
Not enough.
You think you can
negotiate with me?
I say the word, my nephews
go to a certain motel.
Pay a visit to
your daughter-in-law
and your little granddaughter.
What do you think happens then?
Consider your
position carefully.
I get my money,
or neither of us
walk out of here.
You're willing to die for this?
Maybe I need the $50,000
more than you do.
How you manage to live so
long with a mouth like that?
$50,000.
And the gun is yours.
He sent you?
I volunteered.
Only safe way for us to talk.
You really pushed it in there.
That thing we did?
He finds out, we're both dead.
You get that, right?
What thing we did?
What's this? $25,000.
What for?
We made a deal.
I didn't hold up my end.
Your problem is coming back
sooner than we expected.
You gonna cash that? I might
know a guy who can help.
It's better as a souvenir.
I figured you'd be,
maybe, I don't know,
a touch happier this morning.
Maybe a smidge? Possibly?
I am. I'm totally happy.
Why wouldn't I be?
I...
I had a job offer.
Really? From where?
Schweikart & Cokely.
Seriously?
Rich Schweikart
said that they would
even pay off my
law school loans.
That's great!
Please let me be there
when you tell Howard.
Please.
So why the sad puppy eyes?
What, you don't want that job?
No, no, of course I do.
I mean, who wouldn't, right?
It's a huge firm. You get
out from under Howard's thumb.
Right. Exactly.
Besides, HHM is looking more and
more like a dead end for me anyway.
Exactly. So what's the problem?
I just...
I don't know.
I keep thinking of you
floating in that pool.
You knew what you wanted,
but I got in the way.
What are you talking about?
You took the Davis &
Main job because of me.
I took that job because it
was the right decision.
A steady pay check? Done.
A place to live that's more than,
five square feet? Boom.
A car that's all one color?
Nailed it.
I'm good.
I got what I wanted.
And you?
With this Schweikart thing?
You could have
everything you ever wanted.
What's not to love about that?
Yeah. What's not to love?