Previously on "The Originals"
This town was my home once,
and in my absence,
Marcel has gotten everything
that I ever wanted.
I want it back.
I hereby pledge my allegiance to you.
You have the keys to my kingdom.
You're choosing him over
me, aren't you, again?
The only reward anyone ever
gets from loving Niklaus
is suffering and death.
Niklaus, the girl is carrying your child.
You're coming with me, little wolf.
I've been deemed under protection
by the almighty Klaus.
I believe it is time for my
niece Cami to leave town.
Leave New Orleans. Forget everything.
Do I know you?
You've been compelled.
It's ok. I can fix you.
For centuries, people
have come to New Orleans
looking for a fresh start,
hoping to find fortune,
adventure, even love,
young society women imported
from France with the promise of
marrying a proper New Orleans gentleman,
Like the legendary Casket Girls.
Little did they know that the men
who awaited them were far from proper
and not at all gentle.
Get them out. We want to see the women.
Come out. Come out here.
Come on. We want the women.
Oh, there, there, little lambs.
All the bad men have gone away.
Us girls have got to stick together.
Now, is there anything you
want to take with you?
The Casket Girls' legend lives on,
now celebrated in typical
New Orleans fashion
with stylish costumes
and supernatural flair.
It's a yearly reminder of how women
can be oppressed by selfish men
and how they can triumph
when brave enough to fight for themselves.
Oh, god, it hurts!
I'm sorry, Cami.
It's the only way to break
all of Klaus' compulsion.
Believe me, I know what it's like.
You're ok, and, hey, all
these notes that you made,
It's very "memento" of you.
Nice work.
We've been at this all night.
I don't understand what's happening to me.
I don't understand any of this.
But you will.
I will unlock every stolen memory,
undo every piece of mind control
that any vampire has ever done to you.
When I am done, you will
understand all of it,
and you'll be free.
I can stop if you want me to.
No. Don't stop.
I want to remember everything.
Would you like some help?
You might need to use all
your vampire strength.
Allow me.
Thanks.
Not too many pregnant
Casket Girls, I guess.
I think you look lovely,
only I would...
I know, keep the freaky
werewolf birthmark covered.
Well, I don't suspect any
of the riffraff here
would dare lay a hand on you
knowing that you're under the
protection of my family.
Still, we shouldn't take any chances.
All knocked up and nowhere to go.
You know...
If you wanted to attend
the festivities tonight,
I'd be more than willing to take you.
You and Klaus are barely on speaking terms.
Let's not rock the boat, ok?
Of course.
Elijah...
Do you mind?
Not at all.
Dull, dreary, hideous.
Talking about the clothes
or something else?
Why, feeling insecure?
This festival might as well be in my honor.
I need a proper costume, so bugger off.
-Bekah...  -Don't.
You made your choice.
You and Klaus are best friends again.
You've relinquished your right to touch me.
Wonder who that could be.
What's up?
Bit of an issue.
Seems our little bird has flown the coop.
You should start to feel
it, like a weight lifting.
And your cheat sheets are about
to make a lot more sense.
I promise, as soon as the
world stops hunting me,
I will find the daylight ring spell.
I know. Just don't worry
about that right now.
I remember why I wrote this.
I found a picture of
Klaus and Marcel from 1919.
Klaus compelled me
to go out with Marcel to spy on him.
That's what he said yesterday
before he told me to forget.
I'm remembering.
Let's take you back more.
Leave New Orleans. Forget me.
Put your number in Cami's phone.
Most of the quarter is shut down right now.
We'll have to walk,
and the sun is taking forever to go down.
Hey, no tears.
Promise you'll meet us as
soon as it gets dark out.
Yeah, but don't worry about me.
Just don't let them find you.
I know Klaus told you to follow me,
but does it really mean you have
to follow me to the bathroom?
Just give me two minutes.
It's my gynecologist.
What the hell do you want?
I know you don't trust me,
but you need to listen.
Everything is about to change.
Davina is on the loose.
Figured that out on your own, huh?
Remind me again why I should give a damn.
I need something from you
so that the witches can
complete the harvest.
On what planet
would I help you witches get more power?
All you've done is hex me left and right.
You'll help me because if we
don't complete the harvest,
our access to magic will fade for good,
which doesn't bode well for your family.
What do you know about my family?
You're from the crescent wolf bloodline.
Marcel forced a witch to curse them
so they'd be trapped in wolf form.
And I should keep listening
to you because--
Because my bloodline executed that curse.
Help me complete the harvest,
and I'll undo the curse for you.
But what can I do?
I need to consecrate the
remains of a powerful witch
so I can absorb their magic.
I know of one whose body was never found.
Her name is Celeste Dubois.
I believe you and she
have a friend in common.
Elijah.
Story goes that when she
died, he buried her
in a secret spot at her request.
All you need to do is find out where.
There's people everywhere.
Just keep walking. No one knows it's you.
Cami...
We have to get off this street.
Kieran is gonna call me
first if he hears anything.
Ah, you two look rather cozy.
Hardly. I was just telling
Elijah how we're wasting time.
You don't like festivals?
I don't see why not?
Who doesn't love a street fair?
Sister, come to help us find our stray?
We can't let your secret weapon
get in the wrong hands, can we?
For the record, we are moments
away from retrieving her.
Recognize that tone of voice, Niklaus.
Clearly, you have some
diabolical machination.
What is it?
Timothy...
Might I have a word?
Cami, hey, it's me... again...Stalking you.
Heh. Look. Just really need
to know where you guys are
so I can meet you before
the sun comes up...Again.
Uh, hello?
Joshua, my most disappointing minion,
I suspected you wouldn't answer the call
were it from me.
Klaus, hey, what up?
Guess what. I just moved to Turkey.
Weirdly, they don't eat turkey here.
- Go figure. - You're lying.
In fact, Marcel and I were just chatting
about your failed double agent status,
and we've surmised that
you're likely still in town
and in the company of a friend--
A young, angry witch.
Nope. Nope. No witches here.
Totally digging turkey, though.
Are you really gonna leave Davina's
fiddler soulmate Timothy alone with me?
Oh, Josh, what would she think of that?
I assure you, I just want to talk to her.
Tim and I will be at the compound.
I really do hope she comes home soon.
We should keep moving. How
long do we have to wait?
Give it a few minutes.
Then I'll check to see
if the coast is clear.
Josh, sorry I missed your calls.
What?
I didn't want to tell
you, but I know Klaus.
If Davina doesn't show up, he'll kill Tim.
We'll think of something.
Make your way to the quarter. Stay hidden.
We'll text you when we have a plan.
- I have to go. - Davina, wait.
I can't let Tim die.
What's wrong?
The witches.
Gadyen nan balans. Gadyen nan la foi.
Se pou nou fe sa yo dwe fe.
No!
Cami?
I'm just grabbing some clothes.
Give me two minutes, please.
Your brother was ill.
There's no reason to stay.
You don't have to be Sherlock
Holmes to know the obvious.
Our secret weapon has escaped.
She wouldn't just leave.
She knows the witches want her back.
Her violin is missing.
She may have left of her own volition.
What did you say to her in the attic?
She lied to my face so
she could stay up there
thinking that you'd help
her control her magic.
How do we know that you didn't take her?
I have no idea where Davina
is or why she ran away.
Can I suggest you take a step back?
I can assure you, I have
absolutely no desire
to see that child come into harm's way.
She's suffered enough with
this harvest ritual nonsense.
That child to whom you
refer so affectionately
is the most powerful witch in New Orleans.
If she's fled, what's to
stop her from destroying us,
in fact, destroying all we've worked for?
No. If she's not a friend to this family,
then she is our enemy.
She is a friend, Klaus.
Well, let's hope so.
Lucky for you, I know how to get her back.
Follow my lead.
You know how Niklaus operates.
If he perceives a threat,
he can become quite ruthless.
This would not bode well for Davina.
I'm not gonna let anybody
lay a finger on her.
Nor will I.
So the witch is missing, huh?
Walked right out the
front door, apparently.
Know anything about it?
No,
although I did tell her
that the witch elders were dead.
Well, why would she care when the witches
tried to kill her in their ritual?
I think it was more that
Marcel didn't tell her
that the one thing preventing
her from being free
had been eliminated.
So you are the reason she's run off.
Hey, I was just telling her the truth.
She's the one who realized
they were just using her
to keep their control over the witches.
Well, I've never been a
fan of the boys club.
Just wait. Elijah will join them,
and the three of them will be impossible.
Used by the witches, lied to by Marcel,
manipulated by Elijah,
threatened by Klaus...
She's like a modern-day casket girl.
Are you talking about Davina or yourself?
Does it matter?
Either way, us girls have
got to stick together.
Sorry to interrupt.
Been calling you for like an hour.
I thought you'd have taken the hint.
You've been acting like this
since Agnes was killed.
Yeah. Can you blame me?
It's not like I have a lot
to keep me going these days.
Well, while you've been
drowning your sorrows
by nailing everything that walks,
I've been doing my tours,
keeping my head down my ears open.
Marcel's daywalkers are
scouring the whole town
looking for a girl-- brown hair, blue eyes.
Sound familiar?
If Davina is not with Marcel,
he won't know if we're practicing magic.
And if we can actually get her back,
we can fix everything.
Sun goes down,
vampire search parties quadruple.
I got this from her family's old house.
Feel like a locator spell?
Keep drinking.
You need the vervain in your system
so you can't be compelled again.
Hey, Cami,
you don't have any human blood
in your fridge, do you?
For crying out loud, here.
Davina?
Someone is practicing magic.
They're trying to find me.
Then we have to run.
There is no way to sneak
me out of the quarter.
By now, everyone is looking for me--
The witches, Marcel, Klaus.
My uncle will know what to do.
- Cami...
- I mean, he has to know somewhat of
- what's going on in this town, right...
- Cami, stop.
Unless he's been compelled.
He knows.
What are you talking about?
He works with Marcel.
They're practically friends.
I hear them talk.
He knows everything.
No.
He would've told me if he knew
the witches put a hex on my brother.
He knows?
Cami...
Oh, my god.
He knows.
Hey, you guys seriously
need to go, like now--
Plane, train, automobile, whatever.
Take my car. It's parked down at the docks.
I'll text you the where.
Celeste entrances me.
She is perfection.
She is dead.
Even as the sun rises, I see only night.
But for the promise I made to her
that in death, I would bury
her far from the mayhem
of witches, vampires, and men.
I'm so sorry, Elijah.
Hey. It's just me. Don't, like, melt me.
What are you doing?
You're supposed to be hidden.
Yeah. So are you, remember,
but you're kind of working that
whole "girl on a mission" Look
that makes me nervous.
Are you sure that you really want to mess
with the baddest dude in all of history?
He messed with me when he took Tim.
I'll kill him, all of them.
Davina, originals can't be killed.
Maybe they can.
I have so much power,
I've never felt anything like it before.
It's growing, gathering inside me.
I'm strong, Josh.
If you kill them, then--
What?
If you're gonna do it,
don't hold back.
You hit them with all you got.
That was very sweet,
not telling Davina that if she kills Klaus,
You die, too, very noble.
Problem is, she goes after my brother,
she'll be the one who ends up dead,
A very unnecessary end
to an already-tragic story.
Perhaps you'd like to help me help her.
Where's Rebekah gotten off to?
It's not Rebekah that I'm concerned about,
and how are you be so certain
that Davina will come?
One might think you've
forgotten what it's like
to be in the grip of an
all-consuming infatuation.
She'll come.
Are the maudlin theatrics
absolutely necessary, Niklaus?
Ha! It's a fair point,
Timothy, play something a
little more upbeat, please.
That's a good lad.
Took you long enough to spread the word.
Have you met his nightwalkers?
Not the brightest assortment.
All that matters is, I got it covered.
When Davina gets here, you two need
to let me do the talking.
Well, I'm sure you'll have your chance.
Hello, luv.
Silence is golden, Timothy. Thank you.
Davina?
You got me here. Now let him down.
Well, first, we have to have a little chat
about you returning to the fold.
What did I say, Klaus?
I got this. D., what happened?
Why'd you run? Talk to me.
Hey, I can make it right.
How, by threatening my friend?
Actually, that was my idea. Apologies.
I've been known to go too
far to make a point,
But I do always get results.
You pretend to be so confident,
but I know the truth.
you're afraid everyone can
see what you really are--
an animal...
a beast.
Why don't you show us your real face?
That's enough of you.
Davina, you don't have to do this.
You--
You looked me in the eyes
and lied to my face,
pretended you wanted to help me.
Listen to me.
You call yourself the noble one,
but you're a killer just like your brother.
For 1,000 years, you fed on innocent blood.
Why don't you choke on it?
And you--
I trusted you.
I loved you,
but you were just using
me to stay in power.
You don't care about me.
You're wrong.
When you lost to Klaus, you
handed me over like some trophy.
Maybe I should boil you in bronze.
I care.
I took you in like you were my own blood.
Come on now, luv.
Don't tell me you were falling for that.
Isn't it time for us girls to have a chat?
Now, that is impressive,
and well-deserved, in my opinion.
Now, before you turn on me,
I have a surprise for you.
Josh, what are you doing? Get out of here.
What are you doing?
Now, if I were Klaus, I would rip
Josh's head from his neck,
feed it to a nightwalker,
and that would be the end of your friend...
But hurting people is such
a boyish thing to do,
like how Klaus compelled
your fiddler on the roof,
and, while I am many things,
I'm certainly not my brother.
It's ok, Timothy. You can come down.
No one is gonna hurt you.
He told me I couldn't
climb down off this beam.
Then don't climb, silly.
Am I the only smart one in the room? Jump.
Davina, how did you do all that?
How did I even get here?
I'll explain everything, I promise.
Why are you doing this?
Seems to me that you're the
one holding all the cards,
but you don't know who to trust.
I've just proven that you can trust me.
Now I'd like to show you one more thing.
Won't take long.
You can bring your friends.
Oh, Sophie, I told you
everything that I found.
You said he buried her
between two lovely oak saplings.
News flash-- that was 200 years ago.
They're all just trees now.
You want to be the all-powerful
witch, keep looking.
Say a prayer. Have a little faith.
You can do this.
Ok.
Soeurs et freres, mwen rele sou nou.
Mennen me sa me chache.
Please, please help me.
I'm trying to do the right thing.
Oh, don't worry.
They're not really dead,
just really hungry,
and I'm not helping.
You think my brother Nik is awful?
Marcel learned from the best.
This is how he treats his so-called friends
who betray him.
Most of what these poor souls did
is no worse than what Josh did.
Take Thierry, for example.
He was Marcel's most trusted friend.
Klaus tricked him
into breaking one of Marcel's rules.
Marcel knows this, and yet he keeps Thierry
locked in here day after day suffering.
This is insane.
Why are you telling me this?
Because you need to know
who you're dealing with,
who you can trust.
Hey, hey, it's gonna be ok.
I mean, you're gonna be all right.
Here. Drink something.
Davina, both you and I have been lied to
and taken advantage of by Marcel and Klaus.
Maybe together, we can
get a little payback.
Uh, guys?
Tim?
It was Klaus. He made me do it.
I didn't even know what I was doing
until I made you--
Made her what?
Drink.
Tim?
Klaus poisoned the water.
Davina?
Oh, no.
Cami, are you all right?
Did you eat today?
Oh, you must have fainted.
Yeah, or I got mystically
cold cocked by 3 witches.
Where's Davina?
Does your friend Marcel know she's here?
Cami, I can explain.
Vampires? Witches?
My brother, your nephew, hexed by a witch.
How could you not tell me?
It's complicated.
There's a lot you don't understand.
You hid the truth from me.
You let me believe that Sean was crazy,
that I was crazy,
instead of telling me the truth.
I was protecting you.
You saw what happened to Sean.
Cami, please--
Get the hell away from me.
You are every bit as bad
as the other monsters in this city.
Oh, isn't this monumentally awkward.
Rebekah, where are you?
I'm with Davina, and she's dying
because of your treachery.
Well, I tried to talk to her
out of respect for Marcel,
but she made it quite clear
she is not our friend.
My apologies is you thought she was yours.
Just tell me how to cure her.
Vampire blood isn't working.
No. It wouldn't.
You see, the poison I
compelled Timothy to feed her
is quite potent.
It's just a matter of time for her.
For both of them, you diabolical bastard.
They're children.
We could've dealt with her fairly.
There is no dealing with
those who threaten us.
Davina sealed her fate
when she stood against me.
This was her choice, not mine.
Oh, come on.
The stench of your
judgment is overwhelming.
Need I remind you that Davina
just bested the lot of us?
I did what had to be done.
Don't worry, Elijah. I remain
as redeemable as ever.
So you compelled that boy to poison Davina
without consulting Marcel or myself.
You know what the worst part is?
Is that you're so predictable,
I had to make an alliance
with your brother,
who I don't even like.
Judging by your expression,
you have something you'd like to share.
Damn straight, I do.
I got a call from Kieran earlier,
right after Sabine and some witches
almost got their hands on Davina first.
Oh, hello.
Let me guess, protection spell?
You think I'd let a day
where witches can do magic
pass by without one?
They all should've done the same.
You broke one of my rules, Sabine,
and I'm guessing that spell of yours
is probably a one-time deal.
I'll give you two choices--
an immediate reunion with
your dearly departed friends
or you can do that same spell
for a young witch friend of mine.
Yeah. You probably know which
one I'm talking about.
So when you slipped away to allegedly
check on your nightwalkers,
you were, in fact, colluding with a witch.
That's very clever.
I suppose I should be proud.
Eh, I just wanted to make sure
I had a failsafe just in case,
as Elijah expected, you
started acting like you.
Except that now you've
involved the witches,
who, last time I checked,
were enemy to us all,
to everything we have,
and to our family.
Davina is Marcel's family, Niklaus,
or did that somehow slip your mind
as you tried to take her life?
You will call Rebekah.
You'll tell her that Davina will recover.
Do wish the same could
be said for that boy.
Tim.
Tim? Tim?
Tim, Tim, wake up. Tim, please wake up.
Open your eyes. No, no.
Please wake up.
Please don't leave me alone.
Is she ok?
She's devastated and exhausted.
Where's her room?
No. I got her.
I got her.
It is said that this is a man's world,
and sometimes it is.
For every Casket girl that was saved,
countless others were not...
She'll never trust me again.
Perhaps.
You must never surrender the
fight to reclaim that trust.
But women are more resilient
than given credit for...
These drawings, what are they?
She drew those the whole
time she was in the attic,
said they're different than what
she draws when she senses magic.
These ones, she called them evil.
And some women, well,
let's just say, their oppressors
had better watch out.
Surprised to see me?
After all, you did compel me to leave town.
You remember.
Chalk one up for decompulsion.
Hurts like hell, but it's worth it,
Made me realize exactly why
I want to stick around,
Oh, and, Klaus, if you hurt Davina
or Josh in any way, I'll
expose you to the world,
and then you can kiss the
french quarter good-bye
forever.
Have a nice night.
I, too, am resilient,
and I'm tired of being oppressed.
For 1,000 years, my brother
has taken what he wants
in whatever way he wants,
regardless of the consequences.
Marcel seems determined to allow it,
and Elijah stands right by his side
futilely awaiting the
day that he'll change.
So men suck.
What do you want me to do about it?
Despite your dire warnings to Marcel,
he just can't seem to quit my brother.
The two of them stand side by side
ruling this city whilst
you're left in here to rot.
I want you to help me take New Orleans
right out from under all of their noses,
and I have something they won't see coming,
someone on the inside.
She's quite the resilient girl herself.
You ok?
I'm better now.
How was your day?
Killer.
What's with the artwork?
Davina's sketches.
I wonder if they represent
some kind of premonition.
They seem to suggest something is coming...
Something sinister.
Oh, my god,
isn't that--
Hello, Celeste.
Come on, Sophie. Pick up. Pick up.