Max, did you pick up
the tip from table two?
No, but I'm pretty sure
I picked up a staph infection.
So they literally gave me
their two cents worth.
This is so embarrassing,
even Abe Lincoln won't make eye contact.
Girls, I need you to
do something for me.
You know the rule: nothing for you,
on you, near you, or in us.
I'm going to restroom.
Keep eye on the kitchen.
I have a four-minute egg
and a five-minute date
with the Sports Illustrated
Swimsuit Issue.
Hey, do you see what I see?
A fire?
No, a way out of this job.
Lord Jesus, there's a fire.
You two gonna do anything about that?
'Cause I'm not.
I don't mess with fire or Presbyterians.
Fire, fire!
I smell fire!
Well, don't just stand there.
Do something!
We are.
S'mores!
You'd think you want this
place to burn to the ground.
You'd think that.
Caroline, do something.
I'm on it. Chocolate?
(Caroline) Han, not too close.
You know you can never get
the smell of Korean barbecue
out of your clothes.
[shouting]
[shouts weakly]
Either he put the fire out,
or that little robot just had an orgasm.
(Peter Bjorn and John)
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
[cash register bell dings]
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
Welcome to The High dessert bar.
I'm the hostess slash quasi-manager.
First day in, got a huge promosh.
I hate to brag,
but the word “dazzling” was used.
Yeah, by you.
Little to no power has
really gone to your head.
It has.
She's like the Putin of pastry.
But doesn't it feel good
to not just be working at the diner?
I haven't slipped on one
used baby diaper all day.
Speaking of babies,
look, there's Han.
That's, like, the third time
I caught him spying on us.
Why would he stalk two
of his worst employees?
I know.
It's like Where's Waldo?
when you don't want to find Waldo.
Not seeing a hostess up in here.
She meant quasi-manager.
If Marty Scorsese walks in here,
do you want him to seat himself?
He'll be lost. Lost.
Sorry, Joe, I was just
over there giving Max...
Honey, I'll download an audiobook
if I want to hear a story.
I want you to meet someone.
Me too, and I'm sure I will
when the time is right
and I'm open to it.
Kind of focusing on me right now.
Stop.
Learn to read faces.
I'm not talking about you.
I'm talking about him.
[with Irish accent] Hello,
pleasure to meet you.
I'm Nashit.
Nashit's an Indian name,
and isn't that an Irish accent I detect?
Or have I just lost consciousness
from how white your teeth are?
Yes, it is.
My father's Indian. My mother's Irish.
He's Irish. He's Indian.
He's East meets West.
He's everything
in a hot Irish coffee, boy band package.
I found him on the street
next to a dirty chair.
Hi, I'm Caroline, the hostess
slash quasi-manager
at The High.
Are you high?
'Cause that was a lot of talking.
Who is this, and where can I get one?
This is Nashit, our new waiter.
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
[gasps]
Can you say “magically delicious”?
I really want Nashit to work out.
I like it when good-looking
people succeed.
Well, I guess that's good news for me.
Is it?
Hi, honey.
(Joe) Have you met the new waiter?
I love him. He's my favorite.
If I did men, he would've
been done by now.
Hmm, so you think you're pretty.
Well, I do too.
Okay, Nashit, pay attention.
These are the tables.
This is the dessert bar.
And these are my boobs.
Max, be professional.
These are my boobs, sir.
Please, I have to make him a waiter.
Fine, you make him a waiter,
and I'll just make him later.
Here you go. This isn't yours, is it?
No, because they already have dessert.
Damn it.
You asked for water, like,
an hour ago, didn't you?
I'm so sorry.
Oh, don't you worry those lips.
And what's an hour when we have
our whole lives ahead of us?
Max, I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I stink as a waiter.
This is desperate.
Well, desperate times
call for us making out.
Hey, I have a question for you.
Your skin is so creamy and white.
You must have a little Irish in you.
I've had a lot of little Irishes in me.
That's meant to be dirty, right?
Well, I just mean that I think
you're quite beautiful.
Oh, well, then I just
mean we're doing it.
I did not think there was somebody
who had a prettier nose
or was worse than me
waiting tables, but here we are.
Nashit, there's not a fork
in the mix out there.
Now, get out there and fork those women.
Take it easy on him.
I don't want him to be all forked out
by the time he gets to me.
I'm gonna have so much sex
on my bed with Nashit
that I'm gonna need a new sheet.
Aren't you too old for him?
Yeah, but that test said mentally I'm 14,
so we can totally do it.
Well, I'm off to Chinatown
to have someone
put needles in me.
Oh, my God. I love your coat.
You look gorgeous.
I mean, the way it flows.
Okay, so I can see you're a kiss-ass,
so here's the thing.
As my quasi-manager,
or whatever nonsense
you're telling people,
I need you to tell Max
and Nashit to cool it.
There are no hookups here at The High.
Done, and we can stop staying “quas”"
if we're both on board
with the manager thing.
We're not.
The High is about fine pastry,
not someone's sordid love life.
And in an ironic twist,
I need you to kick
my girlfriend's hot ass out of here
if she comes in.
Here's $100.
That's $100.
Consider her hot ass out the door.
We're in a fight.
She got drunk, stole my Black Card,
and bought 90 people soup
at Barney Greengrass,
and the soup isn't even good there.
Do not take this as a no,
because I want the money,
but why can't you
just tell her yourself?
I can't tell her myself.
She's younger than me,
and everyone knows
the mommy thing just isn't sexy.
Make sure she eats something
and gets home safe.
Caroline, I have a question for you.
What do I do with the
notes the women give me?
You've gotten notes?
Just a few.
[gasps]
How could women be this desperate?
Max, this one's from you.
They're mostly all from me,
except the business card.
I don't need no damn card
to let him know I'm all business.
Max, Joe just told me there
are no hookups at The High,
and judging from this very
detailed picture you drew,
that's exactly what you're planning.
Oh, I was planning more.
I just ran out of paper.
We can't lose these jobs.
I have two $100 bills,
and I'm this close
to pulling the trigger on
an Amazon Prime account.
Amazon Prime?
You have been driven mad with power.
Fresh, flakey pastry.
And speaking of flakes,
there's Joe's flakey girlfriend.
Can someone help me get
my chair off my coat?
How did she get in here?
Probably floated in
on a cloud of Valium.
It's go time, as in she's got to go.
You have a better chance
moving an actual train wreck,
but good luck.
- Allie, hi, you...
- Shh.
[whispering] Allie, hi.
- You need...
- Sorry.
But I am hungover, and
I have a headache.
Could I get a latte with a side of weed?
No, because this isn't Amsterdam
or Bill Maher's house.
Now, you need to leave.
You know Joe doesn't want you in here.
Well, I'm not leaving.
My legs won't move
because my muscle
relaxers just kicked in.
John, can you do me a favor?
Walk Allie outside,
and by that, I mean pick her up
and carry her outside.
I went to pastry school.
I'm not Shrek.
Of course not. You're much more Fiona.
Girl, that's good.
I was gonna say the donkey,
'cause I have a fine ass.
(Allie) Okay, fine.
Driver, two stops. Barney's and Fro-Yo.
(Max) Earl, we're late again.
Did you keep us alive?
Max, I can barely keep myself alive.
This morning, I had to
jump-start my heart
by putting my finger in the socket
Tom and Jerry style.
Oh, hello.
So what did you girls do today?
I haven't seen you since
right here last night.
Oh, really, Han?
'Cause I swear I saw you lurking around
outside The High.
It was either you,
or Pikachu is visiting New York.
That one barely grazed me,
because I'm Korean,
and Pikachu is Japanese.
You don't know anything about Pokemon.
Han, you may not be Japanese,
but in the future, you're definitely
gonna be poked by a Mon.
And it was you.
No, it was not.
- Yeah, it was.
- Wasn't.
- Was.
- Was... wasn't.
English is my second language.
Admit it, you're jealous
we're spending time
with another restaurant.
I am not jealous.
- Are so.
- Am not.
- Are so... not.
Oh, my God!
Caroline, what the hell are you doing?
I'm smelling a $100 bill.
It's from my other restaurant.
It buys me nice things.
Jealous?
I took you in when you had no one.
Hi, can you help me?
I'm looking for Max.
Why, hello. Is it too late to be gay?
Nashit?
Oh, my God, he even looks good here
in morgue light.
We are so doing it.
Caroline, you left your
phone on the table
at the restaurant.
I confess, I used it as an excuse
to come and see Max.
This isn't mine. It's
Joe's girlfriend's.
I don't have an iPhone 6.
I have an iPhone sick.
D-O-I-N-G it!
Max, why is Nashit here?
Because God owes me.
You can't seriously be into him.
He looks like someone in a boy band.
Yeah, and he's going one direction...
Down there.
But if you sleep with him,
then Nashit is gonna hit the fan.
How do you know you even like him?
You know what I like?
That we're doing it.
Hey, everybody!
I just got hit by a cab,
and, boy, am I in the
mood for crab legs.
The thing about you, baby...
you bounce back from a good pounding
every single night.
Wait a minute.
That's my booth.
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
What?
What the hell kind of accent is that?
I'm from Ireland.
What?
Max, you are not doing it.
- Are.
- Not.
- Please, I went to Wharton.
Look, we should go to
your place when we do it
so that Caroline won't be
there while we're doing it.
Lovely, but I just came
to America two days ago.
I have no place to go.
In fact, I've been sleeping
on that dirty chair
Joe spoke of.
What?
Is he singing?
Oh, my God.
He's gorgeous and homeless?
That's your dream guy.
We are so doing it!
Ugh, this is impossible.
I feel like I'm putting an
Oscar dress on Precious.
I'm making up the couch for Nashit.
That is so nice of you.
He's gonna need a place
to crash after we have sex.
No, that's off the table.
I can't believe you
invited him to stay here.
And I can't believe you refused
to sleep at Starbucks tonight
to give us some privacy.
I mean, you like Nora Jones.
[whistling]
Max likey.
- Max, listen.
- No, you listen.
I can't afford candy,
so he has got to be it.
Thanks for the shower.
Oh, no, his muscles point to his penis.
[knock at door]
Max, stop with the banging.
I'm not letting you out
while you're still in heat.
(Max) It's not me.
I'm making a list of ways to kill you!
I feel like I'm being a bother,
and I think I'm sleeping on a bong.
[knock at door]
(Joe) Open up.
I know what's going on in there.
(Caroline) Oh, my God.
That's Joe.
She must've found out about
you and Max hooking up.
(Nashit) Oh, no.
Max, Joe is here.
You need to do that thing you do
to scare people out of the hallway.
What do we think, guard dog
or little old lady with poor eyesight
and loaded gun?
[Max imitating dog barking]
Fine, I'm going.
This is why I never leave Manhattan.
Hey, you need to get
in the girls' apartment?
I have a key.
Find it here in my big bag.
I know it's in here somewhere.
Well, I got the lip balm.
I got... Oh, look, I got the Holy Bible.
I got...
Oh, look. Oh, the DirecTV remote.
Oh, my God, I'm losing estrogen.
Max, you and Nashit
go hide in your room,
but no sex.
You heard her, no sex,
so everything but,
and I mean everything,
and I mean but.
Oh, here it is. It's right...
It was right under the
cold cuts the whole time.
(Joe) Caroline.
Hey. Hi, Joe.
Oh!
Yeah.
Ha!
Yeah, the shorter hair makes sense now.
(Sophie) Yeah.
Good for you, Caroline.
I hope you like long, boring stories.
Okay, where's Allie? I know she's here.
I put a spy app on her phone,
and I'm not proud of it,
but I'm a jealous woman.
Oh, her phone. I have it.
She left it at The High when
I threw her ass out today
per your instructions.
I don't know how I thought this thing
was gonna work out to begin with.
We met at Coachella.
We were both on Molly,
this intensely hot
Filipino girl.
- Shh, shh.
- I'm hearing sexual sounds.
And hints of secret shame
coming from the bedroom.
- Allie is here.
- No, no one's here.
That's just our white noise machine.
I'm shocked. You're not even her type.
Your lips are like two flair-pen marks.
[Nashit laughs]
That's hot.
Please don't fire Nashit!
The Dr. Seuss hats were my idea.
We were playing Hop on Pop.
I was Pop.
I didn't even know
there was a boy in there.
I only saw you.
Okay, since there are
no hookups at The High,
if you don't stop sleeping
with him immediately,
my new manager...
[clicks tongue]
Caroline here is gonna have to kick
his beautiful butt to the curb.
But I was mid-doing-it!
Honey, there's a real
funky smell in here.
I got to get out of here.
PS, this is where you live?
Take another $100.
Earl, hi.
What kind of mood is Max in?
Pretty good.
On the Max scale, she's
below slightly drunk
but above punching a customer out.
Oh, good.
I was worried she'd be mad at me
'cause I had to get rid of her boy toy.
Caroline, I'd put my
hearing aids back in
if I wanted to hear a story.
Guess what I have for you in my purse.
The tampon I asked for last week?
No, and again, so sorry about that.
Really dropped that ball.
Gummy worms.
Yes, I took away your man candy,
but I got you these, the
hot ones that you like
from the good candy store
with the sneeze guards.
[gasps]
Fancy.
And don't worry about Nashit.
I got him another job.
Hot worm!
Clean glasses coming through.
Nice rack.
Now I know why guys
like saying that to me.
There he is!
There's the new employee.
(Caroline) Han, I can't believe
you would hire someone
just 'cause Max asked you to.
This has nothing to do with Max or you.
The boy here said something to me
that you two couldn't understand.
What's that, sir?
That I was a hard worker?
That's it! Yes!
Manna from heaven.
I actually have an employee who works.
Jealous?
Now, this job, I can do.
You know, growing up, I had
five brothers and sisters,
and since I was the least attractive,
I had to clean all the dishes.
Meet you in the dish room, Nashit.
Max, what are you doing?
There may not be hookups at The High,
but there are hookups
here at our lowest low,
and we are doing it.
Caroline likey.
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.