Mike: Why me?
Because you understand.
Understand what?
Revenge.
Kevin: I'm not gonna let
some low-life shyster
bully me off my land.
No offense,
Kim.
That call center's not movin'
one goddamn inch!
There's no reason
to take this any further.
It gets nasty.
It gets personal.
It gets dangerous.
You broke
into his house?
What?
What is it?
[Wind gusting, leaves rustling]
[Engine humming]
[Vehicle passing]
[Vehicle approaching]
[Tires screeching]
[Rick Springfield's
"Affair of the Heart" playing]
¶ Heart in my mouth,
pulse in my head ¶
¶ Mercury rising into the red ¶
¶ The smell of your skin can
light up all the fires in me ¶
[Brakes squeal]
¶ Hungry to touch ¶
Woman:
Hey, baby.
¶ I'm eager to please ¶
You ready?
Where were you?
¶ Out of control
and I hand you the keys ¶
What?
Where were you?
I'm sorry, hon.
I got held up
down at the Clover.
Guess I kind of
lost track of time.
You were drinking?
Kimmy.
It was one beer.
Doesn't smell like
one beer.
Welp,
that's what it was.
So let's go.
¶ It's an affair of the heart ¶
Get in.
Kim,
I'm not doin' this.
Come on.
It's cold out.
Let's -- Let's go
get some food,
go home,
split a box of McNuggets,
see what's on TV.
I'm just gonna walk.
[Sighs]
Really?
You're gonna walk three miles
with a cello.
Don't be stupid.
Get in.
¶¶
I'll -- I'll let you choose
the radio station.
Come on.
¶ When we make love,
it's a passionate thing ¶
[Sighs]
¶ You shudder and shake,
sink you teeth in my skin ¶
¶ I almost believe you were made
to be played by my hands ¶
Kim, get in the car
right now.
¶ And you got the power ¶
I said
it was one beer.
You're gonna be
like this?
¶ How you play my emotions
with consummate skill ¶
You don't believe me?
¶ I don't have to look any
further than into your eyes ¶
Kim, get in,
or I'm driving home.
Right now,
in the car.
¶ So don't try to tell me
you think it's just physical ¶
I mean it.
I'm going.
¶ It goes way deeper than that ¶
¶ You better know
it's an affair of the heart ¶
Fine.
Don't listen to me.
You never listen!
¶ It's an affair of the heart ¶
[Vehicle departing,
music fading]
[Wind gusting, leaves rustling]
¶¶
["Home on the Range" playing]
Don: Freedom.
Freedom to ride.
Freedom to explore.
Freedom to bank...
the way you want to.
Hi. I'm Don Wachtell,
President of Mesa Verde.
For the past 10 years,
our family has taken pride
in helping your family
grow your savings
out here in the Southwest,
with freedom from hidden fees
and freedom
to choose the account
that's right for you.
Ain't that right,
Kevin?
That's right,
Dad.
¶¶
Yup!
Let our family help find
your freedom...at Mesa Verde.
¶¶
[Horse whinnies]
[Button clicks]
Jimmy:
So, can you do it?
The Media Lab
has a-a vision mixer.
I think we can get the effect
that you're goin' for.
And with makeup
and costumes,
we can make it look like
the same time period.
Jimmy:
[Chuckles] That's great.
I love it. [Laughs]
It's gonna sing.
I'm sensing that Schleprock here
is gonna puke on my parade.
You want it when?
Uh, as soon as possible.
Tomorrow would be optimal.
Let me break it down
for you, chief.
You got 10 spots.
I count 12,
13 locations.
Then there's post,
graphics,
this video-effects thing
you're talking.
That's, uh,
a week, maybe more.
Probably more.
We have midterms.
And plus we have to
lug all our stuff around.
And actors,
craft service...
You scout these locations?
Do I got a place to plug in?
Oh, and bathrooms.
People need bathrooms.
They literally need them
all the time.
Whoa, whoa. Just --
There's got to be a way,
right?
'Cause we're smart,
so we can figure out a way,
right?
Cut the number
of spots.
No. It's --
Shock and awe
is what I'm going for here.
Anything less, no.
Wh-What if you use voiceovers
instead of actors?
Or if we did it
all in one location?
So, no actors,
no scope, no impact.
No. Just...
I just feel like if we just
get out there and this --
we hustle,
we can do it.
We can.
Dude.
Can't be done.
[Sighs]
We --
Dude.
We can't.
I mean,
I don't know.
What if we did
the Superman thing?
Uh, a -- a what?
You know,
like Superman.
Like, um --
Well, like a weatherman.
Blue screen,
I think.
[Laughs]
You mean a green screen?
Whatever.
Blue, green.
Just --
Can we do that?
[Scoffs]
You got
a green screen?
[Sighs]
[Spray can hissing]
[Man singing scales,
woman trilling lips]
Man: Rubber baby
buggy bumper.
Looking good, gentlemen.
Rubber baby buggy...
Red leather,
yellow leather.
Very nice.
Man: Rubber baby
buggy bumper.
Rubber baby
Woman:
Ah, ee, ah, oh, ooh.
[Trills lips]
Mah. Mah.
Mom makes meat.
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma.
Red leather,
yellow leather.
Red leather, red --
Yellow.
Yellow leather.
[Man trills lips]
[Sighs]
We're ready,
ready.
Oh. [Clears throat]
Everyone, a lot to do,
no time to do it.
Who knows their lines?
Yes,
I believe I have it.
Ah, I love
a man of confidence.
I played Prospero
on the Plaza
a month after
prostate surgery.
One has to
have confidence.
That's wonderful.
Uh -- God bless.
Now bring that confidence
right over here
to this marker on the floor.
That's your spot.
Do not move from it,
okay?
Um, but also
don't be rigid, okay?
Try to be natural.
And speak to me,
you know, conversational,
everyday, like a friend,
but, uh -- [Clears throat]
[Sighs]
There's fear here.
There's emotion.
You're searching
for a hero.
You know,
will no one save you?
[Chuckles]
But don't hit it
too hard.
Just throw it away,
but with feeling, okay?
Good.
How we doin'?
Shoot this mother.
Alright.
Oh, [Clears throat] there's
cue cards if you need 'em.
But don't look at them.
Look at me, okay?
But, you know,
they're there.
So, roll sound.
Rolling.
Camera.
Man: Speeding.
And...action.
[Music stars]
This is great.
Stand right there.
You look great.
Eyes open.
Yeah, good, good.
Can I drop your jaw?
Sideways a little.
Perfect.
That's it.
Press "record."
I can't --
And five,
four, three, two...
Magic.
...magic.
Delicious.
You can't have the pizza
while we do the thing.
Because we're trying to shoot
the commercial. That's why.
I'm gonna keep it right here.
Doing something
with that thing?
Look up this way.
Right?
And then stay right like that.
Alright, show it to me.
Boom.
You're a cool guy, okay,
but not too cool.
I need you
to be relatable.
Give me that Fonz.
Alright, good.
Put it down.
Nobody's buying it.
Okay, the cane, I think,
is a little too much.
Can I have it?
And five, four,
three, two, magic.
What?
...need it.
Let go.
Just -- Really, okay?
¶¶
You look very,
very officious, okay?
Alright,
can you smile warmly?
No?
I'm trying to direct.
That's good.
Get out of the way.
Okay.
And...acting.
Cool, alright?
Do that. Ready? Yeah.
Yeah,
like this.
Too much, uh -- Put your hand
right -- Yeah, yeah.
¶¶
Stand on the X.
This is great.
Smile.
[Crunches food]
Turn sideways.
Take your Coke
out of her hand.
And now look sad,
glum.
Mnh.
And then when I say "action,"
you look here.
No. Faster.
Make it a whip --
Whip your head.
Up here, and then --
go! -- action.
Look back. Okay.
Anyone else?
So that
they don't reflect, okay?
That looks normal.
Look right in.
Look at me.
Point.
No. Like this.
¶¶
More, more.
Good.
Make it look real.
¶¶
And...cut!
Beautiful.
[Music ends]
[Vehicle approaching]
[Engine shuts off]
[Crickets chirping]
[Vehicle passing]
[Keys jingle]
[Car alarm chirps]
I'm Saul Goodman.
Did you or...
[Speaking indistinctly]
[Vehicles passing]
[Indistinct conversations]
Hold on. Hold on.
You came. I'm sorry.
You missed most of it.
I'm almost through my part.
Now, you comin' in?
'Cause, hey, we still got
a slice or two of pizza left.
Uh, no.
I-I-I-I ate the office.
I'm good.
You sure?
'Cause it's,
um, cold pizza
fondled by
community theater actors.
You gonna pass
on that.
[Chuckles]
Yeah,
I think I will pass.
I just --
I just wanted to talk.
Talk?
Yeah, sure.
Of course.
Uh, five.
[Clears throat]
Good news --
I tracked down Olivia Bitsui.
She is
92 years young.
She's part of
the Navajo Nation.
She lives
out by Window Rock.
I'm gonna call her
first thing in the morning,
hopefully have
a face-to-face.
Jimmy --
Think I'm gonna bring
a floral arrangement
or maybe a cake assortment
from Brother's Bakery.
Good idea.
Jimmy,
d-do you think...
Will Acker settle
for $75,000?
$75,000?
Yeah.
Will he go for it?
Are you saying
that Kevin is willing
to go
up to $75,000 on this?
I -- [Stammers]
Look, we'll negotiate
as far up as we can,
and then
I'll make up the difference.
Wait.
Hold on.
Y-You'll make up
the difference
as in "out of your own pocket"
make up the difference?
I -- Yes.
I just need to end this now
and move on.
But why?
No, hey,
we have him.
Rich is suspicious.
He said some things.
He's second-guessing
how you got to be Acker's lawyer
and questioning
my intentions,
enough to want me
off the case.
We move forward
with this,
Rich is gonna figure out
what's happening.
Here's the truth.
Rich knows nothing.
Well, not yet, no.
Not ever.
He has nothing.
There's no way
to prove anything.
[Sighs]
You may be right.
But it's just
not worth it.
But...what about
the play here?
The play
is beautiful.
[Sighs]
God, this is like watching
a walk-off home run
just drift foul.
Ugh.
[Inhales sharply]
It's your play.
If you want to walk,
we'll walk.
[Sighs]
So, I got to --
I got to break it to the kids.
[Chuckles]
[Sighs]
Well,
there's a lot to clean up
before Mrs. Ngyuen can open
in the morning, so...
I'll help.
No.
You've been
all day at work.
Jimmy, you're out here
doing all this because of me.
I'm helping.
[Stammers]
Alright,
just don't touch the camera.
He claims
it's an extension of his body.
Noted.
[Crickets chirping]
[Bell dings]
¶¶
[Vehicles approaching]
[Tires screeching]
¶¶
[Engine shuts off]
[Vehicle doors closing]
[Sighs]
¶¶
You're Michael?
The gringo
Lalo had a bug up his ass about.
If Hector or the cousins
ever find out about --
They're not
gonna find out.
¶¶
Get on with it.
Lalo's using
his C.I. connection.
He's having Domingo call the DEA
to rat out your dealers.
Times they're slinging,
locations.
Your guys
are gonna get swept up.
¶¶
Promote
low-level dealers...
or find new ones.
Let them get arrested.
Protect our people.
You got it.
What else?
He talks about
a lot of things.
Um...
hitting your supply trucks,
going after your restaurants,
getting your customers sick,
cutting off power,
busting open pipes.
He's gonna chip away
at your business
until the bosses down south
don't think
you're worth the trouble.
¶¶
From now on,
you report to this man.
¶¶
He needs you?
You do not hesitate.
Act.
¶¶
[Vehicle doors opening]
[Engine starts]
[Tires screeching]
¶¶
[Sighs]
Guessing there's something
you want to get off your chest.
You know
who you're workin' for, right?
The shit
that this guy does?
They shot me,
left me bleeding out
in the desert,
all part
of some plan.
I don't know
what to tell you.
I warned you.
What?
I warned you when you started
going after Hector Salamanca
there'd be others
to worry about.
You made a choice.
You got in
with both eyes open.
My father didn't.
He's got a gun
to my father's head.
I don't do
what he says...
Look...
first things first.
We take care of Lalo.
Then we'll talk.
[Car door closes]
[Engine starts]
Paige, you've got
Kim, Rich, and Marcie.
Paige: Guys, I hope
you're calling with good news.
You sitting down?
Oh, God.
Really?
Yep.
Acker's decided to settle.
Tell Kevin
he's got his call center.
Fantastic.
Kevin will be
over the moon.
When is it official?
There's a meeting
on the books
with Mr. Goodman
for Wednesday at 3:00.
Paige:
Music to my ears.
Kevin's gonna wanna be there
to close this out and celebrate.
I can't wait.
Congrats, Paige.
Paige:
Congrats to you guys.
Kim, this was
another tough one,
but you did it again.
A team effort.
We'll e-mail you
the details.
Great.
Talk soon.
[Receiver clatters]
Okay.
[Chuckles]
Well, now that that's behind us
and I have you here,
I want to talk to Jason
in Charlotte,
walk us through these
Fannie and Freddie changes.
Dorothy, can you set up
that North Carolina call?
Actually, before we do that,
c-- Sorry.
Marcie,
would you give us a minute?
Oh.
Sure, absolutely.
Dorothy, hold off
on that call, please.
Thanks.
[Door opens]
I, uh...
[Door closes]
[Sighs]
I wanted
to talk about yesterday.
Rich, you've been
nothing but generous to me.
And you don't deserve
to be yelled at.
It was unprofessional.
I believe me staying on the case
was the right thing,
but that was
the wrong way to react.
[Chuckles]
That's it.
Just that I'm sorry.
Hmm.
Kim...
you have a bone to pick
with me, pick away.
In fact,
you want to lose your shit,
that's alright, too.
I'm not perfect.
I've broken
plenty of times.
But never
in front of the troops.
I don't
have to spell out
what it does
for morale, confidence.
Never again.
Hi.
Yeah, no, let's punt the call
to Charlotte to another time.
Also, cancel my 12:30,
but keep the reservation.
Yeah,
that's right.
Thanks.
You and me?
We're going to lunch,
and everyone
is gonna see us.
Good?
Good.
[Door opens]
Alright, then.
After you.
[Telephone rings]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Vehicles passing]
[Birds chirping]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Cart squeaking]
Hi.
Excuse me.
Are these really
only a quarter each?
That's right.
Why so cheap?
Is there some kind of damage
I'm not seeing?
No.
We get lots of donations,
books we already have,
and there's just not enough room
on the shelves,
so we sell what we can
to pay for newer releases.
Wow.
Well,
you're kidding me.
"Treasure Island."
[Chuckles]
Yeah.
And "The Little Prince."
Mm.
My granddaughter's
gonna love these.
Alright, well,
I will start with...
eight.
Alright, eight.
That's $2.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Do you need a bag?
No.
I'm fine. Thank you.
May I ask --
is there
a Lillian Simmons working here?
Yes. I'm Lily.
Lily. Great.
My name's Dave Clark.
I'm a
private investigator.
Oh.
Is this about
Travel Wire?
That's right.
I already told the police
everything I saw,
which wasn't much.
You saw
a man with a mustache,
dark hair,
kind of tall.
I'm not
even sure anymore.
It was through
two sets of glass,
and he was
leaning over a desk.
Uh-huh.
Are you free to sit
and talk somewhere,
see if you remember
any other details?
As I said,
I told the police
everything I could remember.
Oh, I know.
And the police
are doing their best
with that information.
But I've been hired
by the family.
And I am trying
to help them find...
[Chuckles]
They're looking
for closure, Lily.
Anything to
bring them peace.
I send money back to my parents
back in Taiwan.
I-I do it every month.
Fred was always there.
We didn't really talk much,
but he was efficient.
So, you see that man inside
on the day in question.
That's right.
The door sign
was flipped "closed,"
which it never was.
And then the man pointed
at the sign and waved me off.
I don't know.
I thought they were having
Internet problems or something.
I came back
20 minutes later.
Oh, it was horrible.
Thick black smoke
and flames.
And the man
with the mustache --
you didn't seem him
when you returned.
No.
I got there just as
the fire engines were arriving.
Well, let's talk about
when you first got there.
You drove,
I assume.
Yes.
Where'd you park?
Right out front,
just to the right
of the entrance.
Where there any other cars
parked there?
Um, a few.
The normal amount.
Mm-hmm.
Any unusual
or unique cars?
Unusual?
Older cars,
classic cars,
something you might not see
every day.
Actually,
I think there was.
You remember what kind?
Oh, I don't
really know cars.
It had four wheels.
[Both laugh]
Okay.
That look familiar?
Is this the car?
Um...
that's not
for me to say.
Um...
yes, now that
I look at it, yes,
that was
the type of car it was.
Uh-huh.
A customized
1970 Monte Carlo?
Okay.
[Chuckles]
And that is
a huge help, Lily.
Thank you very much.
Oh, good.
Anything for
that poor family.
Uh,
there is something else.
Yes?
Uh,
if you were able
to call the detectives
who interviewed you
and pass this along
firsthand,
tell them that you remember
that detail?
That was so long ago.
I don't think I can remember
who I spoke to.
Well,
I have that right here.
Detective Tim Roberts.
That's his number.
Probably catch him at his desk
right now.
Oh, okay.
A gray 1970
Chevrolet Monte Carlo.
Gray?
Mm-hmm.
And if you don't mind,
don't mention my name.
Police get a little funny
about private investigators
horning in
on their business.
They can have
all the credit.
I only want justice.
Oh, absolutely.
I understand.
[Dialing]
Thank you,
Lillian.
Count your lucky stars
we got Judge Papadoumian.
She likes my flair.
Baby, you went the extra mile
for us today.
Don't think
I didn't notice.
Hey, you want
a quick rub-n-tug?
Just to say "thanks"?
Uh...
We won't mess up your suit
or nothin'.
We'll clean you up nice
with a warm towel.
A warm towel.
I appreciate the offer,
but I'm gonna --
I'm gonna politely decline,
if that's okay.
Rain check.
Well, we gotta get
back to it anyway.
Almost lunchtime.
Oh.
Oh, um...
hey, do you two think
that maybe --
maybe you should
take a break?
You don't see restaurants
closin' doors at noon, do ya?
Lunch is peak traffic.
Just be careful,
alright?
And try not
to get picked up again, okay?
Okay. [Chuckles]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Sighs]
Ladies, hey!
Ladies.
[Chuckles]
Uh...
Hey, um, how much for,
uh, an hour of your time?
["Sweet Cream" playing]
[Indistinct conversations]
Excuse me.
Judge Greene.
I keep hearing
the news.
A hole in one
at Sandia?
I don't want to say
it was all luck --
Then don't say
another word.
U.S. Open,
here we come.
Cliff.
Been waiting long?
Not at all.
You're right on time.
Uh, thank you,
Francisco.
Saw you shaking hands
with Judge Greene.
I don't know if you heard
about his retiring.
No. Retiring?
Yep.
"Retiring" with
his 22-year-old law clerk.
Really?
Wow.
Guess she's been filing
a different type of "brief"
for the judge,
now, hasn't she?
Very good.
Let's hear more about
that "hole in one."
[Both laugh]
Gentlemen, can I round up
some drinks for the table?
Absolutely.
More time with the menu, or you
ready to pull the trigger?
Let's do it.
[Music
and conversations continue]
¶¶
Woman: And I'll have a martini,
very dry...
I hear S&C
are following the playbook.
Erin and the gang
already had a jump
on redrafting
the complaint,
but then another box of receipts
were suddenly discovered.
What are you hearing
from Kiley?
Uh...
can I help you?
Howie.
You know.
¶¶
I, uh --
No, I-I don't know.
Oh, don't try to play us
like that, Howie.
Mnh-mnh.
Uh, this is --
I don't know them.
Ladies,
I don't know you.
This is
some sort of mistake.
Yeah, we made a mistake,
alright.
Joe Dog ain't happy.
Mnh-mnh.
You owe us.
Uh, owe you?
Yeah. Owe.
Mm-hmm.
You can't take a ride
on the Carnival Cruise
and only pay for
a tugboat.
Mnh-mnh.
You know
what I'm sayin'?
I can leave
if you need --
Uh, no, no.
[Clears throat]
Look, I don't know any Joe Dog
or "tugboat,"
so we can end this
right now.
We ain't leavin' without
our cash money, honey.
Mnh-mnh.
I don't know you
and owe no money to you.
That's it.
[Gasps]
Don't touch her!
Ahh!
I didn't touch...
Jimmy: "No, Cliff,
these are not my hookers.
Ahh. They're somebody else's."
"Howard, are you sure
they're not your hookers?
They seem to --"
"No, no, Cliff, m-my hookers
were taller than these."
[Chuckles]
Oh, God, I'm good.
[Sighs]
[Air brakes squeal, hiss]
[Vehicles passing]
[Dialing]
[Sighs]
[Ringing]
Hello? Uh, Olivia Bitsui?
Yes.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
My name is Saul Goodman.
I'm an attorney based in
Albuquerque, New Mexico.
Yes. Yes, I'm a lawyer.
Well, I wanted to ask you, um --
have you ever heard of a bank
called Mesa Verde?
[Indistinct conversations]
[Police radio chatter]
[Telephone ringing]
Mike: You.
What's that?
I'm sorry?
That.
How long's
it been down there?
Uh...
I-I don't know.
It's an
interoffice envelope.
Isn't there a date?
Uh, yes.
Uh, today.
Today.
And where's it
supposed to be today?
Uh,
Detective Roberts.
And don't you think
that Detective Roberts
should get it sometime today?
Uh, yes, absolutely.
Sorry, sir.
Hmm.
If the smell is coming from
under your porch,
it is most likely a possum.
That's right, a possum.
If it's a human body,
yes, I'll investigate.
But you need to call
animal control first.
Yes, I'm sure.
[Indistinct conversations]
You can also shine a flashlight
under the porch
and see
what's under there yourself.
Well...
if the porch isn't big enough
for you to get under,
then there's probably not
a dead body, okay?
Yes, sir.
You have a good day.
[Conversations continue]
[Telephone ringing]
Woman:
Thank you for calling.
Ed!
You need
to put eyes on this.
Hit-and-run,
same day
as our Travel Wire murder.
Check out
the make of the car.
1970 Chevrolet Monte Carlo.
Same model
our librarian just called in.
What are the odds?
Who sent this?
Officer McFloss?
I can't even read that.
[Drawer closes]
The guy rammed this car
right through a parking gate?
Wow.
So, we got a Monte Carlo
at a lot here
half-hour before
the murder.
Leaves the scene
of the hit-and-run,
headed east
towards Travel Wire.
20 blocks.
This is soundin' like
our guy.
[Conversations continue]
James usually run late?
He'll be here.
[Telephone ringing]
All I care about's
getting this behind us.
Done. Finito.
We won't have
finalized contracts today,
but we'll definitely
land on an agreement.
[Indistinct conversations]
Hello, folks.
[Door closes]
Nice to see
lots and lots of happy faces.
And you, too, Rich.
Kiddin'.
Jimmy.
Always a pleasure.
Saul.
Saul Goodman
during business hours,
"s'all" the time.
This is Paige Novick,
Mesa Verde's in-house counsel.
Very nice to meet you.
Paige.
I know
you're the one
who brought Kim Wexler
onto the team,
so I consider you
the brains of the operation.
I actually think
you're right about that.
And this is Kevin Wachtell,
CEO of Mesa Verde.
Oh.
You know what?
I could tell
from the impressive belt buckle.
Really looking forward
to settling this.
Me too.
Let's do this.
[Inhales sharply,
clears throat]
Hey, Viola.
How's it hangin'?
I, uh...
Good?
Jimmy: Cool.
Kim: Just to
jump into it --
Jump away.
[Clears throat]
[Chuckles]
As discussed,
considering we're only
contractually obligated
to pay $5,000
on top of fair market value
for Mr. Acker's home,
we believe
$45,000 is more than generous.
I hear that, but, um,
you and I
have a different definition
of the word "generous."
Because that's not
how I would describe it.
And here we go.
We're not prepared to offer
more than what's on the table.
No, no, I-I knew
there would be dickering,
so let's -- let's just hear
the number you're looking for
so we can all move forward
with our lives.
We'd like nothing more.
What amount
are you asking?
$4 million.
Rich: [Laughs]
Very funny.
Mr. Acker would like
to be paid $4 million
for his pain
and suffering.
It's what's fair.
What in the world
are you talking about?
Jimmy: It's a four
with six zeroes,
and it's preceded
by a dollar sign.
We had an agreement.
We had a discussion.
We had
a verbal agreement
on a number that both sides
would be happy with.
And I discussed the offer
with my client,
and he really, really
doesn't want to leave his house,
his home.
$4 million is the only number
he'll be happy with.
[Sighs]
I apologize.
We need
to end this meeting now
so Rich and I
can have a conversation
with Mr...Goodman.
Just...
incredible nerve.
[Door opens]
Ridiculous.
What's your endgame here?
Because you know you're never
gonna get that money.
Wait. Wait.
Don't leave.
You're not wasting
any more of their time.
[Clears throat]
Jimmy: No, I --
Kevin,
meeting's over.
Not while
the gang's all here.
I would love to bring up
a completely unrelated matter.
Kevin,
we can handle this.
No.
This is really good.
You're gonna want
to see this.
Kevin, you wanna stick around.
Your dad's in this.
What?
Kevin, I insist.
This is
a waste of your time.
There's only one way
to find out.
Kevin, I'm advising you
to please just keep walking.
[Telephone ringing]
No.
I wanna see this.
[Telephone rings]
Viola,
you mind getting the shades?
Viola, shades, please.
[Shades clacking]
[Door closes]
[Button clicks]
[Sighs]
Here we go.
[Beep]
Yee-haw!
[Slowed voice]
I'm Don Wachtell
[Normal voice]
President of Mesa Verde.
My bank took my home
over a technicality,
and I never missed
a single payment.
It's not right.
It's un-American.
Yup!
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
Have you or a family member
been wrongfully evicted
from your home by Mesa Verde?
Then you may be entitled
to a large cash settlement.
[Cash register dings]
Call 505-503-4455 today!
[Coins clinking]
Are you kidding me?
Paige:
None of that is true.
Rich: You can't air this.
It's libel.
It's defamation!
It's libel,
and we will sue you.
That's my father
you're making a fool of.
Yee-haw!
Kim: Jimmy, turn it off.
You know you can't do this.
Shh.
This is a good one.
[Slowed voice]
I'm Don Wachtell.
I went into my bank
to withdraw cash for groceries,
and I came out with a rash.
I-I can't stop itchin'.
It's everywhere.
Don: Yup!
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
Did you or a family member
visit a Mesa Verde branch
and come into contact
with black mold?
Then you may be entitled
to a large cash settlement.
[Cash register dings]
There's no way in hell
you can legally run these.
Call 505-503-4455 today!
Mm. Maybe.
But, you know,
we'll fight it out
after they run in New Mexico,
Arizona, Utah, Tex--
Yee-haw!
No, no, no, we will stop it
before it ever gets that far.
Some might call that
prior restraint.
You know what?
You can stop us.
Some news outlet
will pick it up.
They'll run for free.
I went into my bank
to open my safety deposit box,
and Mr. [Buzz] was standing
there with his pants down!
Bare genitals.
Yup!
My dad never,
ever did anything like that.
None of this is true.
This is all fantasy.
It doesn't matter.
This trash airs,
our reputation is in the toilet.
It'll never,
ever get that far.
Shh.
Jimmy:
And, hey, yee-haw!
[Slowed voice]
I'm Don Wachtell.
The bank manager
couldn't explain
where all the extra fees
were going,
so I followed the money trail.
The evidence
was as clear as day.
My bank was funding terrorism.
Yup!
Kevin: Stop.
Stop it!
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
Worried your
Mesa Verde savings...
I've seen enough of
this horseshit. Jesus.
...are being used
to help America's --
There's lots more.
You know what?
I can leave you this one because
I've got plenty of copies.
Paige: What do you hope to gain
with all this?
We agree
to Acker's ridiculous demands
and you don't run
this garbage?
It's illegal to do that.
No lawyer can play
one case off another.
It is unethical,
and it is blackmail.
She's right.
One has absolutely nothing to do
with the other,
which leads me
to my next topic.
This is Olivia Bitsui.
She's a photographer.
In fact,
she took this self-portrait.
It's really lovely.
Here's another picture she took
54 years ago.
Kevin,
say nothing.
Kevin:
No, Kim, I got this --
Kevin,
I'm strongly advising you --
I know this picture.
Kevin!
My dad bought it
fair and square.
I have a copy of it
hanging in my office at home.
I think we all just heard
Mr. Wachtell admit
that he owns a copy
of Olivia Bitsui's photo,
a photo that looks
remarkably like
the official
Mesa Verde logo.
That's right.
We own it!
You own
a copy of the photo.
You don't own the rights to it.
That's copyright infringement.
You'll never be able
to prove that.
Well,
you know what?
[Exhales sharply]
Wow.
Looks like
a mirror image there.
So I think I can convince
a judge and probably a jury
that Mesa Verde
misappropriated
Ms. Bitsui's
intellectual property.
It's not your fault.
Sins of the father.
But, um, we filed
an injunction,
so you're gonna have to
take down all your horsey logos
or throw
a big tarp over 'em
till we can
get this thing settled.
Shouldn't take
more than --
I don't know --
a couple years?
We'll be seein'
a lot of each other.
Till next time.
[Whistling]
[Indistinct conversations]
Yeah, the problem
we're facing is that
none of the so-called victims
said, "Mesa Verde did this,"
or, "Mesa Verde did that."
No. Everybody said "my bank."
They never used the words
"Mesa Verde."
Exactly.
But it's in front of our images,
our logo.
Yes, Paige,
it's all heavily inferred,
but it's done in a way to keep
us wrangling in the courts.
We'll be there forever,
going 'round and 'round.
So, how do we keep them
off the air?
We're -- [Sighs]
We're gonna have to
get ahead of him.
How?
We notify the stations
that -- that --
that they're susceptible
to a libel suit if they air.
Rich: It might an extended game
of whack-a-mole.
Rich, any way you slice this,
it's a long-haul battle.
We have to take things
one at a time.
Meanwhile, we have to counter
the copyright injunction.
Paige: I mean,
do we need to discuss libel?
We can start with that.
That's straightforward.
Do we need
to discuss terrorism?
[Overlapping arguing]
Kim: Kevin.
Rich: Kevin!
Kevin, Kevin,
I know you're upset,
but please
don't do anything rash.
Let your lawyers
take care of it.
We'll fix this.
Kim, can I just go
to the men's room?
Of course. Yeah.
Okay, now, with the copyright
infringement, I think we...
[Telephone ringing]
[Door closes]
505-503-4455...
[Elevator dings]
...today.
Where are you?
Man: ...pretty
well ironed out...
Stay there.
[Horn honking]
[Metal screeching]
[Sighs]
What'll it take?
Oh, you're gonna have to be
more specific.
I let Acker stay
in his shitty little house
and I move
my call center
and all the rest of it
goes away?
Is that the game?
Ahp.
As your counselor,
Ms. Wexler informed you
I'm not allowed
to do that.
Gimme a break.
You're
a third-rate huckster
who'd sell your own mother's
organs to get what you want.
What will it take?
Mind you, again,
I'm not actually allowed
to do any of this,
not intentionally.
Cut to the chase,
jackass.
Well, Kevin, would you --
would you close your eyes
and imagine a world
with me?
Just if you...
It's a world where Mr. Acker
gets to keep his house,
plus the $45,000
you were gonna pay him
for his pain
and suffering.
And in this world,
you throw in
a public apology.
And imagine a world
where a Native American
photographer -- Olive Bitsui --
is compensated $200,000
for the use of her photo,
in addition to receiving
future credit
for the inspiration and use
of the logo from Mesa Verde.
Also --
you know what? --
throw in a public apology for
Ms. Bitsui while you're at it.
And then --
then I can imagine a world
where the injunction
disappears.
And those commercials --
oh, they'll never see
the light of day.
And, poof,
away they go into a vault,
never to be seen
by mortal eyes again.
What do you think of that world,
huh, Kevin?!
You can
open your eyes now.
[Chuckles]
Can you imagine a world
where we shake hands
on that, man to man?
[Helicopter blades whirring]
Nacho: Yeah,
he just dropped me off.
Usual route,
going south.
Uh-huh.
[Cellphone closes]
[Birds chirping]
[Car door opens]
[Car door closes]
[Radio turns on,
static crackles]
Baker 2-4-1 PD.
Woman: Baker 2-4-1.
Go ahead.
Ran a 26, got a hit
on a New Mexico plate --
1-Victor-1,
5-Robert-Zebra.
Gray Monte Carlo
occupied by one male.
Last seen headed south
on Brighton towards Lawrence.
Units stand by
for an attempt to locate
on a gray Monte Carlo
occupied by one.
Last seen
in the area of --
[Radio turns off]
[Camilo Azuquita's
"Borombón" playing]
¶ Borombón, bon ¶
¶ Que sabrosón ¶
¶ ¿Y qué es lo que dice? ¶
¶ Azúcar na más ¶
¶¶
[Siren chirps]
¶ Borombón, borombón, bon ¶
¶ Que sabrosón ¶
Officer:
Turn off the vehicle
and drop the keys
out the window.
¶ No te apures al bailarlo ¶
¶ Que despacito es mejor ¶
[Sirens wailing]
¶ En un solo ladrillito ¶
Turn the vehicle off
and drop the keys out now.
¶ Bailaremos este son ¶
¶ Que sabrosón ¶
¶ Borombón, borombón, bon ¶
[Tires screech]
¶ Dice mi son ¶
¶ Borombón, borombón, bon ¶
¶ Que sabrosón ¶
¶¶
[Gearshift clicks,
engine shuts off, music stops]
[Dog barking]
[Sighs]
[Keys clatter]
[Deep Purple's "Smoke on
the Water" playing on guitar]
[Music stops]
Hey.
How'd it go?
[Crickets chirping]
[Keys clatter]
That was pretty perfect,
right?
[Sighs]
Kim, uh...
[Inhales sharply]
Kim.
Look, apologies,
alright?
I'm -- I'm sorry
for sandbagging you
with the ol' switcheroo.
I-I should have
warned you.
But you know what?
You being angry at me --
that worked.
You were concerned
that Rich was suspicious.
Did he say anything?
No.
Great. See?
That anger,
real anger --
it worked like a protective
immunity shield, you know?
I mean, hey,
emotion like that --
you can't fake it.
No.
You can't.
Yeah, right?
So,
what'd Kevin say?
Uh...
he said
he was tired of lawyers.
Wait. Wait. Do the voice.
You got to do the voice.
Kevin is sick
of lawyers,
wants to be done
with all of it.
We explained that
your agreement is non-binding,
but he doesn't care.
He's sticking
with the handshake.
Boom!
There ya go.
That's a plan cooked
and served to juicy perfection.
We -- We should celebrate.
Really.
We'll go
to a steakhouse,
get a couple bottles
of red wine,
some Tiramisu,
the whole nine yards.
[Sighs]
Okay, Kim, look,
I said I was sorry.
And, again, it worked.
No way that Rich
or Paige could believe
that we were in cahoots
'cause -- guess what --
we weren't.
[Clears throat]
Acker gets
to keep his home,
plus a nice
chunk of change.
Olivia Bitsui gets reparations
for being cheated.
And Kevin still gets
his call center.
Everybody wins.
You win, Jimmy.
What?
You win.
Uh, yeah.
But, I mean,
well, we win.
Us.
No. I didn't.
What didn't you get
that you wanted?
I don't trust you.
Why?
You played me.
You made me the sucker...
again.
Again? What --
Wait. How can you be the sucker?
It was your plan.
Oh, fuck you, Jimmy.
God.
I --
Uh, you know what?
I can't
do this anymore.
Kim,
I was just --
No, you -- you turned
you and me versus the bank
into you versus me.
And it is not
just this.
It's the same thing
over and over again.
No, I kept things from you
to protect you.
Look, if I got caught and --
God forbid --
you're questioned
under oath,
you have
plausible deniability.
Jesus, Jimmy.
You can excuse
stabbing me in the back
by making it about
protecting me?
Is that -- Is that really
supposed to justify everything?
Okay, Kim, I'm sorry.
[Scoffs]
I'm sorry, alright?
It -- It will never
happen again.
That's a lie.
Well, I swear.
I swear it won't.
Look me in the eye
and tell me
it'll never happen again.
[Breathing sharply]
You can't.
I don't believe you.
You don't
believe yourself.
It is a lie.
You lie.
I lie.
This has to end.
I-I-I cannot
keep living like this.
No, no.
No, no, Kim,
we can fix this.
Jimmy, no, shut up.
Jimmy, Jimmy,
you know this has to change.
If you don't see it,
I don't know what to say
because we are at
a breaking point.
Oh, God!
Either we end this now --
No!
Either we end this now
and [Voice breaking]
enjoy the time we had
and go our separate ways,
or we're...
[Exhales sharply]
Or what?
Or we're --
we're -- I mean...
[Inhales deeply]
Or maybe...
Maybe we get married.