Previously on "The Originals"...
You're Klaus' father?
You can bring me back to life.
Welcome to my hell.
You're all right.
Have you dreamt of our father?
I saw Mikael.
I've been dreaming of him, too.
Your mother was clearly a very gifted witch.
Any way I do the math,
it ends with me and my guys dead,
So whatever it is you got coming with the wolves,
just know that I will fight until I am dead!
Nice job.
You saved me the trouble of killing all these vampires myself.
That baby is part witch.
She has to be born first before she can die.
No!
This the way it had to be.
Writing a love letter to one of your many suitors?
So who's the lucky recipient then--
Jackson or Elijah?
Don't tell me it's me.
I thought I was out of the running ages ago.
And the award for biggest ego goes to...
Oh...
How is our littlest wolf?
Do you want to...
Come on.
You feel that?
Right.
I'll leave you to your secret letter then.
"Dear Zoey...
"or Caitlin or Angela.
"To my little girl,
"your dad just asked if this was a love letter.
I guess it kind of is."
"I never got to know my mother.
"I have no idea what she must have felt when she carried me."
Let go of me, you bitch!
"So I thought I'd write to you
"so that you could know how happy I am at this very moment,
"Hh your father and I can't wait to meet you."
"And I want to make you a promise,
"3 things that you will have that I never did--
"A safe home,
"someone to tell you that they love you every single day,
and someone to fight for you no matter what."
"In other words, a family.
"So there you go, baby girl.
"The rest we're gonna have to figure out together.
You should know this brings me no joy.
I promise I'll make it quick.
Let's begin, shall we?
No, no!
THE ORIGINALS
Season 01 - Episode 22
"From a Cradle to a Grave"
Angels & Demons - Italiansubs
www.facebook.com/AD.ItalianSubtitles
Sync and corrections by
Wolfsbayne and Morrigan
Cami?
Oh, god. What happened?
Klaus.
They fought, and he got bit.
Marcel.
It's ok. I gave as good as I got,
but we need klaus' blood to heal.
You fought Klaus.
Did he bleed?
I got him pretty good, yeah.
Where?
Venez sanguis. Venez sanguis.
- Venez sanguis. Venez-- - Uh, Davina.
What the hell?
Josh, what are you doing here?
I told you to rest.
I'm fine.
You're gonna start hallucinating soon.
I mean, unless I'm hallucinating you standing
in the middle of the street and chanting for no reason.
Wait. Am I?
I'm gonna save you.
I'm gonna save all of you.
Venez sanguis. Venez sanguis.
Ok. I am hallucinating.
I will bring hell to your doorstep!
One last push. The baby's almost here.
I will bathe in rivers of your blood!
- No, no! - I can see the baby!
Ok. Now push.
Gently, gently.
You will die screaming!
There.
You have a beautiful baby daughter.
We must start the sacrifice
as soon as the moon sets with the morning sky.
Please. Please can I hold her?
No!
Hayley!
Oh, no...
No.
She's gone.
You've been bitten.
There's only enough here for one.
No. This has to be enough!
I... I can't choose.
Please don't make me choose.
Save your friend.
I can take care of the rest of us.
Marcel.
- I can't.
- Judging by the look of that bite,
You don't have time to argue.
Marcel.
Josh is one of my guys,
and enough of my guys have died today,
So come on.
One point for you
And one point for Niklaus.
Where do you think you're going?
To find Klaus, get his blood,
and save as many of my guys as I can.
Wait.
For that, you'll need a weapon,
and it just so happens I have an arsenal.
How?
I was bested.
You were bested?
You... Were bested?!
My invincible brother?
They took the baby, but there's still time.
We can save her.
The tombs are empty, the grounds are deserted.
She's not here.
This is the only place they can be.
- We'll keep searching. - They are not here, Niklaus.
We're wasting time.
Their harvest was here,
the reaping was here.
They are about to perform a ritual
which will feed their ancestors for centuries,
ancestors who are buried here!
This statue.
We've passed by this 3 times.
We were going in the same direction.
They have fabricated some kind of illusion.
That's one word for it.
So this is what Kieran was hiding.
More like stockpiling.
From what I can gather, it's mostly weapons.
Dark objects created by witches.
And co-opted by the humans.
Kieran's been keeping this a secret for years.
You really sure you want to show me all this?
You said knowing my uncle's secrets could get me killed.
What if those same secrets could save the lives of my friends?
Look at this.
I learned about it in the lycée.
It's called the devil's star.
They say one throw can make a thousand cuts.
A thousand cuts sounds about right.
I need to make Klaus bleed.
It's ingenious.
I can see them, I can feel them,
and yet they are not real.
There has to be a way.
Even if we could just push through.
What we need to do is focus.
My only focus right now is that child
and her safety, do you understand me?
This, all of this,
this is the world that you created, Niklaus.
Brother. All of your scheming,
the enemies that you have made every single day of your miserable life.
What results did you expect?
That your child would be born into a happy life,
that the mother would be alive
to know her daughter,
that we could live and thrive as some sort of family?
That was your fantasy, brother, not mine!
No, brother.
This was our hope.
This was our family's hope,
and now she is gone.
Do you understand? I...
let this person in.
I let her in.
I don't let people in.
You knew this,
and you've taken her from me.
I needed her, and you've broken me.
You can tell your niece
how much you cared for her mother
when we save her.
Push!
No!
The moon has almost faded from the morning sky.
I need to prepare.
She'll go through with it.
The ancestors promised her her life.
What about their promise to us?
4 harvest girls sacrificed, 4 girls returned,
but her friends hijack it,
and ours have to stay dead?
Cassie was our friend.
I hope she doesn't go through with it.
Then you and I can do what the ancestors want,
and they'll give us Cassie...
and drag Genevieve back to where she came from.
It says I need to channel power from a nexus vorti.
Ah, yes.
My wife Esther always did love to dress things up a bit.
It's fancy witch speak.
Nexus vorti-- a rare occurrence,
something so infrequent
it's almost a miracle
like an astrological event or...
A miracle baby.
Voila!
So are you certain that you have the power to bring me back?
I do now.
De la cendre ?L'os, de la chair ?La vie.
We've passed through here twice already.
We're running out of time.
Then we move faster.
Or smarter.
Hayley.
How are you here?
I woke up in the church.
I felt this hunger.
I knew what I needed.
I can feel her.
She's here.
I can feel my baby.
You died with the baby's blood still in your system.
She's in transition.
Which means she has to drink the blood of the child
if she's to survive.
To be reborn a hybrid.
I don't care about me.
I'm gonna go find our daughter.
No!
You fools.
to come against us in our place of power,
in our strongest hour.
You do not face 3.
You face us all.
Who the hell are you?
No!
I was too late.
There should have been more time.
Looks like the wolves came back and finished what they started.
You took my daughter so I would heal you and your friends.
Here.
This bite...
All this...
I know it didn't come from nowhere.
This is the last note in a song
that I started a century ago...
when I brought your dad to town...
And for that, I am sorry.
No.
You saved my child's life, Marcel.
For that,
you deserve this.
We will take down
whoever brought this upon us.
I swear it.
May I?
Hey there.
Stop!
No.
Why is this happening?
You brought me back to kill my son.
I brought you back to punish him,
and you will when I'm ready and not a minute before.
What...have...you...done?
I added a little something extra in the spell that brought you back.
I spent 8 months of my life up here being used as a secret weapon.
Now you can see how it feels.
Kneel.
Why?
The ancestors left me no choice.
You were willing to sacrifice
an innocent baby for more power.
Oh, not just power.
It was the ancestors' decree.
It was her decree.
It was whose decree?
I'm surprised you have to ask
after all, you were the one who convinced
your siblings to consecrate her in New Orleans soil.
Esther.
So not even death can stop my mother from seeking the annihilation
of her own flesh and blood.
This isn't the end.
As long as that child lives, the witches of New Orleans
will never stop coming for it.
Esther will never stop coming for it.
It has been decreed.
Your baby will be consecrated among her ancestors.
She will not live.
They're coming for me.
I can feel it.
I've failed them.
Please. Understand, I just wanted to live.
Tell Klaus...
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
We should have felt our mother's hand in this.
We should have known she would not be bound
by anything as obvious as death,
and now she has control of the witches.
- They will never stop. - No.
Nor would I expect the Guerrera wolves to back down.
Hayley and the child are wolf royalty,
and as such, they are a threat
to Francesca's claim to leadership.
They will never be safe.
What was it you said to me earlier,
that I've made enemies every day of my miserable life?
Well, the worst of them are within these borders, brother.
I have brought into the world a weapon they can use against me.
Then we will arm ourselves.
Brother, we've fought every adversary in this town,
and we have won,
and we'll fight them again,
no matter who they are.
We'll make this home a fortress.
I will not have her live her life as a prisoner.
Then we leave here together, all of us.
Wherever we go,
however far we run,
those who seek power and revenge will hunt us,
they will hunt her.
She has inherited all our enemies with none of our defenses.
So whether we stay or we leave,
we condemn her.
There is a third option.
I grew up in a war zone.
My parents thought they could protect me,
but in the end, they were slaughtered,
and I spent my childhood alone and unloved.
I made a promise to my baby and to myself...
That she would not grow up like I did,
that she would grow up safe and loved,
and yet here she is on her first day in this world
with a grandmother that is bent on sacrificing her
and a mother that has to drink the blood
of her own baby to survive transitioning into a hybrid,
and I'm the one that loves her the most.
I think the only thing to do is
send her away while we stay behind
and clean up the mess that we've made.
No. This is insane.
You heard Genevieve.
So long as she lives, that baby will be hunted.
Not if on one knows she lives.
What is it that you intend to do, brother?
Whatever it takes
to save our family.
Today begins a new day in the quarter.
My family, long-time residents of this great community,
pledges to help every citizen recover
from the terrible outbreak of gang violence
that erupted on the streets of our city last night.
We will rebuild.
We will remember those who perished
as we seek to disinfect this town of its worst elements.
We will work together
to ensure the heart of the Crescent city
thrives again.
Last man standing, huh?
I'm interested in making a deal.
Don't look like you got much to offer.
I'm hearing word that the Guerreras want
the quarter to be a no vampire zone.
I can make that happen
in exchange for you leaving us alone
across the river, or...
I can unleash hell on your new wolf pack.
And how can you do that?
Easy. I made my peace with Klaus.
He cured me.
So now it's you versus us.
Klaus...
is a warmonger.
You think he's gonna choose to side
with a pack of scrawny vamps
or an army of the new wolf breed that he created?
I'm thinking he's gonna side with us,
especially after he finds out
that your pack killed his kid.
What?
Open the box
and let me know what you think
Klaus will believe about who's responsible
for what you find inside of it.
Cremation may be the best way to go
before Klaus smells it on you.
Klaus.
Your baby?
She died
a few hours after the Guerrera attack.
This is...
This is all my fault.
I can assure you it is not.
No. If I hadn't hesitated,
I could have uncovered Francesca's plot
in time to stop it.
And how would you have stopped the coven of witches
in league with her?
No.
If anyone is to blame, I am.
I am so...so sorry.
Camille...
I appreciate you being here,
but we cannot be friends.
What?
You had me pegged from the start,
a man damaged by his demons,
and those demons are not dormant.
They are hell-bent on killing me
and everything I find beautiful...
And you...
You are beautiful.
- Please, please just go. - Klaus.
Go.
Did Marcel play his part?
He managed to locate a stillborn baby
in a hospital in upstate Louisiana.
I trust he agreed to the terms.
He has agreed to allow me to compel him
to forget what he knows of my child.
In exchange, he wants vials of my blood.
The witches will have to believe this.
Soon that fourth harvest girl will resurrect.
The coven will rebuild.
If they sense that your child lives,
they will hunt her.
The witches will buy what we sell.
We just have to sell it properly.
Then all that remains is to say good-bye.
They will be watching us,
all of them.
The 3 of us leaving together will draw too much attention.
I will go alone.
Take your mourning public while I'm gone.
I don't imagine that will be too difficult.
Grief, after all, is grief.
In what world will she be safe without us?
Who can protect her better than we?
There is one person.
Hello, sister.
She looks like her mother.
Maybe there is a god after all.
Well, she has a hint of the devil in her eyes.
That's all me.
You'll need a witch you can trust
to cast a cloaking spell.
I'll get one.
No one can ever find her.
I know what to do, Nik.
Perhaps we'll get a white fence.
I think that would be lovely.
This city would have seen you dead,
but I will have it your home,
and every soul who wishes you harm
will be struck down.
Just as sure as my blood runs in your veins,
you will return to me.
In spite of our differences, Rebekah,
there is no one I would trust more with my daughter's life.
Be happy...sister.
She will be happy, Nik, I promise.
What's her name?
Hope.
Her name is Hope.
May you rest in peace.
What's the fun in that?
Come along.
We have much to do.
Yes, mother.
Sybc and Corrections by
Wolfsbane and Morrigan
Angels & Demons - italiansubs
www.facebook.com/AD.ItalianSubtitles
http://italiansubtitles.blogspot.it