♪ We face the music together ♪
♪ And throw our hats
in the ring ♪
♪ Facing all kinds of weather ♪
♪ And not afraid of anything ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When the sun comes up,
we'll be on our way ♪
♪ And we don't care
where we land ♪
♪ And the waves are high,
but we won't turn round ♪
♪ 'Cause your hand
is in my hand ♪
♪ And, oh-oh ♪
♪ You make me feel invincible ♪
♪ 'Cause it's you and me ♪
♪ Through the wind and hail ♪
♪ Setting sail into the world ♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
[Lucy] I'm actually dead
serious. You cannot talk...
[Moush] Okay, oh, my God, okay,
you're like Katie and Tyler.
- Her and Tyler are meant to be.
- [Lucy] I know, know,
know this.
- Katie. You and Tyler.
- What?
- Oh, my God, Moush, stop.
- Oh, my God!
- I don't like him, okay?
- No, a Leo and a Gemini
- have to be together, right?
- No!
- Yes, they do.
- Amber. Amber, come on.
- Bye!
- [Lucy] I kissed him
one time for two minutes.
I took this quiz for Katie where
it's, like, a soul mates one,
and it ended up in T,
T for Tyler.
- For Tyler. For Tyler.
- The universe is speaking.
- Okay, no, no, no.
- Mother Nature is speaking.
- She wants you
to have his baby.
- No. No.
- It's meant to be.
- Oh! Too far, too far.
[Moush] Like,
it's gonna be so much fun.
Like, I think I'm gonna wear
this new tie-dye sweatshirt.
It's blue, so it's perfect; it's
gonna, like, match everybody.
And, like, I got it for,
like, seven dollars.
Oh, we have to make a pact now,
though, to sleep
next to each other,
because otherwise...
No shit I'm sleeping
next to you.
I can't believe... Oh, my God.
Look at Tyler's Instagram.
He just posted a picture of you.
I knew it. He likes you so much.
The T in the soul mates quiz
is definitely Tyler.
- I told you. I told you.
- Shut up.
Oh, my God, I just realized
that if you marry Tyler
and I marry Isaac,
they're best friends,
which is gonna make us family.
[gasps] And we're gonna share
our first dance together.
Ugh, but Isaac isn't
a good dancer at all.
Like, it's gonna be
really embarrassing.
[♪ Chong the Nomad:
"Two Colors"]
- Katie!
- What?
I was talking about
what a bad dancer Isaac is.
[chuckles] Yeah.
Okay, if I'm gonna marry Isaac,
I'm gonna have to totally
teach him how to dance.
- And if he is dancing...
- That girl, um,
who is dancing to "Motivation"
- on the red team
is really good.
- Uh, yeah. I don't...
I-I don't think I've actually
ever spoken to her,
- but she hangs out with,
like, Dez and...
- What's her name?
Uh, Alexa.
Yeah, she's got to be... Ugh.
Hey, my mom says
I have to get off the phone
- and do my homework.
- Okay.
- All right, bye.
Love you forever.
- All right, love you.
[♪ Chong the Nomad feat.
Stass THEE Boss: "Undervelvet"]
[dog barking in distance]
Hey, hi. Just wanted
to see if you were up.
- Yeah.
- [Amber] Mom!
Yeah, I'll be right there!
Do you want some water
before you go to bed?
Uh, sure.
[Lori] I'm sorry
I'm so late again.
Such a mess.
I can't believe it's 10:00.
- Um, how was school?
- [Katie] It's fine.
How's little Miss Moush?
- Great.
- What's this?
Uh, chili, from the back
of the pantry.
- Did you heat it up?
- Yeah.
Very impressive.
Did you give some to Amber?
- Of course.
- Wow.
Uh, what is this, on your face?
Oh, it's just for the
color wars thing. I'm blue.
- Is it a sticker?
- Uh, yeah.
- Take it off
before you go to bed.
- It's fine.
It's not good.
It suffocates your skin.
Okay. Good night.
All right, good night.
- Night. Mm-hmm.
- For real.
- Turn off the lights.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ Got me feeling half crazy...
- [Amber] Mom!
- [Lori] Yes,
I'll be right there.
♪ Mad shady ♪
♪ Take it to the next level,
will we make it? ♪
♪ You know I dig you like
a shovel, we so gravy ♪
♪ If we put the pedal
to the metal ♪
♪ Are we racing? ♪
♪ But if we settle into orbit,
we too spacey ♪
♪ Too spacey, spacey ♪
♪ ♪
♪ My love, my love ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ My love, my love ♪♪
[Vacher] Don't want to have
to repeat myself.
Jeffery and Jameela,
Nicholas and Charlotte,
Katie and Tyler.
- Hey.
All right, bet.
Uh, five minutes.
We got five minutes.
All right, you guys.
Romeo and Juliet, and I want
you to learn your lines.
- I want you to come in
prepared.
- [Jameela] Ms. V,
uh, why don't we do
gender-neutral casting?
- Jameela.
- I feel like we should do
all girl, no boy partners.
[Vacher] It's important to
work with the opposite gender
sometimes; this is
one of those times.
- All right, let's go.
- [rising chatter]
[Lucy] ...was right next
to that gross old bagel shop?
Where they would do
whipped cream cheese?
So my brother also goes there,
and he's actually really good.
- [Tyler] I go there, too.
- Oh, really?
- That's kind of weird.
- [Tyler] Uh, Katie.
I won't be able
to rehearse today,
'cause after school I have
parkour till 4:30.
She could totally do
this weekend.
Um, but, like, aren't we just
rehearsing at school?
- Yeah, but...
- Yeah, but you want the scene
to be good, right?
[Katie] Yeah.
Uh, yeah, sure. Uh, let's do,
like, this weekend.
- Anytime, I'm free.
- Awesome, I'll DM you.
[Vacher] Derek, I see you!
- [chuckles] No, no.
- It's too scandalous?
I'm too scandalous.
[Vacher] A.P., you are
in these two rows.
These two rows only.
[overlapping chatter]
[Tyler] Hey, what are you doing
on your phone?
Uh, nothing.
[chatter continues]
Useless. Does anybody else
have another idea
how to get up into the circle?
- [boy] Lasers!
- Good.
- Elizabeth! Elizabeth!
- [screams]
Good sir,
have you seen my magical,
super-strength wine elixir?
[man] Meanwhile,
up in the castle,
this lizard shall grow
and be my companion
- unless you step on it.
- [screams]
- [woman] A lizard!
- Where is it? There!
- [man shouting]
- [audience] Oh!
[quiet chatter]
[man] My dear daughter!
The news I have
is terrible indeed.
The poppy has been purloined.
[Rainer] Gonna need everybody
back up on the grass, please.
- Everybody's on the grass.
- [Lucy] It's, like, ASMR
for your skin.
It's a massive line,
we got Alyssa here.
- Hey, yo, Alyssa.
- Okay, but I'm not
wearing any eyeliner.
Absolutely not.
So, what did y'all think
of the show?
- How we feeling?
- Great.
- It was a slap. I was...
- [overlapping chatter]
Okay, and then we got
the lock-in at school tomorrow.
- We got everyone
sleeping in the gym.
- I'm so excited.
- This my other girl Lucy,
by the way.
- Hi, babe.
Anyways, and this is Katie.
- Sho-go.
- Now, what the hell was that?
- [laughs]
It's-it's a Dachi stance.
- [Lucy] It's from an anime.
- You don't know karate?
- [Lucy] It's from one
of her baby shows.
- [Dez] I don't even know
what the hell...
- It's a baby show.
- It's not a baby show.
It's anime.
- I'm sorry. I love you.
- It's just a dumb show
called Kaleido Star.
- [Alexa] What's it called?
- [Dez] That shit is weird.
- [Katie] Anime?
No. I mean,
what was the name of the show
- that you mentioned?
- Oh. Um... Uh, Kaleido Star.
- [Becca] What is this?
- Anime?
- It's, like, animation.
- [Alexa] It's
Japanese cartoons.
They have the really big eyes.
[Katie and Alexa laugh]
Have you seen... Wait,
have you seen Black Butler?
- No. No, what's that?
- Okay, that-that one's
my favorite. It's about this boy
who signs a Faustian contract
with a demon
to get revenge
on the people
who have murdered his family
- and then tortured him.
- That's so dark.
- That sounds cool.
- I think you would like it.
And, um... Wait,
what was your name? [chuckles]
- I didn't get your name.
- Uh, Katie.
Katie. Okay. I'm Alexa.
So, no,
I've heard of Kaleido Star,
but I haven't seen it.
I watched Gakuen Alice
when I was a lot younger.
- Yes. Yes.
- Okay, cool.
- Yeah.
- Like, nobody knows that one.
- This is crazy. [laughs]
- Hey, I don't know
anyone else
who's watched it, either.
Yeah, and, like,
all my friends think I'm, like,
super stupid for watching anime.
- Oh, really?
- But they haven't even seen,
like, any anime, so they can't
really judge me, you know?
- But, um...
- [Rainer] All right, everybody.
Let's get down
for a group picture, please!
Group picture!
- [overlapping chatter]
- [Alexa] That's really neat,
by the way.
- [♪ Sylvan Esso:
"Rooftop Dancing"]
- ♪ Moonlight's bright ♪
♪ And the kids don't care ♪
♪ Meet me at the streetlight,
gonna take you there ♪
♪ Take you rooftop dancin' ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[Katie] Amber, why would I
take those? Stop touching
- my stuff! Get out!
- Fine!
♪ I'll take you
rooftop dancin' ♪♪
- [mouths]
- [Tyler] Have you, um...
- Have you done
any Shakespeare before?
Uh, not really.
- Have you, um, looked at the...
- [Vacher] You guys,
use your dictionary.
- I'll just pull up
the SparkNotes.
- [phone buzzes]
- [Tyler] Okay.
- [Vacher] See if you
can figure it out.
- [boy] This is so stupid.
- Should we, uh... I don't know.
Should we try to memorize it?
Uh...
Yeah, if that's
what you need to do.
[Vacher] Hold on. I'm coming.
[Tyler] Coolio.
Uh, did you get my DM?
- [Katie] Hmm?
- About us hanging out
over the weekend.
Uh, 'cause of rehearsing the...
If you... If you can't,
- that's okay. Um...
- [Katie] Um...
[Tyler] I understand.
Um... No, uh, yeah.
Yeah, I would really...
- Really?
- I would really,
really love to.
- Awesome. Okay.
- Yeah.
Um, unless you want
to rehearse it in the lock-in,
- since, you know,
we're both blue.
- [chuckling] No way.
- That sounds awful.
- [laughs]
Yeah, you're right.
Um, okay, let's...
[Katie] She told us that she
was gonna be gone for a while,
but I didn't expect it
to be overnight,
so we came here.
And she'd been in this, like,
terrible car accident.
- What?
- It was...
It was traumatizing, really.
And she was there for, like,
another twoish weeks.
Um, but that was, like,
a really long story. I'm sorry.
[Alexa] No, really,
is your mom okay now?
- [phone buzzing]
- Oh, yeah, no,
she's totally fine.
Just basically made her,
like, quit her job
and reevaluate
her whole life, but...
Uh, she's in med school now,
and she's almost...
These things are so stupid.
Here, you can take it.
What's the combination?
It's, uh, 15-42-3.
[Alexa] You can take it.
It's just spam.
[chuckles]
Oh.
- What's this?
- No.
- [laughs]
- No, it's nothing.
- Is it true
you're 93% dateable?
- No. No.
My friend made me do this,
and it was not willing,
and it's...
"You love holding hands,
talking about feelings,
- and you're ready
to fall in love."
- No. No.
- [laughs]
- No. No. No, no.
These things are so ridiculous.
Okay? I did one the other day
about how my Patronus
is a beagle.
- Which is ridiculous bec... No.
- Aw.
No, beagles are so lame.
- No, they're not.
- Do you ever think
- about beagles?
- They're so sweet.
- No. Well, maybe.
- [chuckles]
- I think my Patronus
is a dolphin.
- Ooh.
- Dolphin. I like that.
- Dolphins are cool.
Yeah, they are cool. They have,
like, superhuman emotions.
Did you know
that they're the only animal
other than humans
to have sex for pleasure?
- [laughs] What?
How do you know that?
- Yeah.
- Why do you know that? [laughs]
- I don't know. [laughs]
So have you ever dated anyone
since you're 93% dateable?
[laughs]
Uh, no. No. Have you?
Oh, no. I'm probably
zero percent dateable.
- [phone buzzes]
- Oh, that's my mom.
We live about five minutes away,
and she still insists
- on driving me everywhere.
- Yeah, mine, too.
We're literally,
like, four blocks away.
I'm on 126th and 107th Ave.
- I don't know if you're...
- Oh, my God.
- I'm on 124th and Liberty.
- I don't...
- That's, like, I...
- No. That's, like,
really close.
- Really?
- We're only, like,
a couple blocks
- down from each other. Yeah.
- Oh, that's really cool.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That's her. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
[indistinct chatter]
- Slow down!
- Sorry!
- [Lori] Driving me crazy.
- [Amber] Definitely Miranda.
- She's pretty dusty.
- [Lori] Okay, here she is.
Amber, just tell me
where I'm going.
Hi. Hi. I'm so sorry.
Class ran a little late.
- Left or right? Kathryn!
- [Amber] Uh...
Why do you have a phone
if you're not gonna
- answer it when I call you?
- Uh... it's a left.
Left. Thank you. Kathryn,
you could at least text me back.
That's the whole point of why
you have the thing
in the first place.
Uh, sorry. I was just talking
to Ms. Vacher about my scene.
[Lori] Amber, can you get,
uh, Jenna's mom
on the phone and tell her
we're gonna be 20 minutes late?
Uh, Cynthia.
Kathryn, put your seat belt on.
Is it a... is it a "C"
or an "S" or a... Cynthia?
No, no, no. "C." C-Y-N.
[Katie] My battery was
running a little low,
too, so I just didn't
want to text you. Sorry.
[Lori] Today is the day
that you had to be in the car,
and I need to hear from you.
- Don't forget.
- [Amber] Huh?
[Lori] No, no, no.
Just text her. Cynthia.
[Amber] Okay. Oh, I see.
Okay, there we go.
Okay, now what should I do?
[Lori] All right,
tell her, we're g...
we're gonna be 20 minutes late.
I mean, seriously, Kathryn, the
reason why I got you the phone
is so that I could be
in touch with you,
not so you could write
to Moush and Lucy ten times.
[Lori]
This is what we have.
- Massive rip in the top.
- Nobody is gonna notice.
Move.
[Lori] Look, this is the
sleeping bag that we've got.
- Katie, do not go into my room.
- Mom, I can't take that one.
Here. Look. It's not even
- that big of a rip.
- [Katie] I can't. I can't.
It's just this little thing
with the fuzz coming out.
- I can sew it for you.
- It's gross, and there's
- a huge rip, and it just...
- Well, I don't why
I'm finding out about it now
a half hour before
you're supposed to be
at the school that you need
- a brand-new sleeping bag.
- 'Cause you're never home,
and when you are home,
all you're doing is studying,
- studying, studying.
- Excuse me?! All right,
Kathryn.
- I don't have time for this.
- You don't care
about me
or what's important to me.
Amber, can I have
your sleeping bag, please?
She cannot take my sleeping bag!
You're gonna have
to clean all this up.
- Can't leave
this big mess for me.
- ...and go to Dad's,
I could've done this beforehand.
- Okay?
- Can't have my sleeping bag!
If you want to go
to your father's...
- What? Who paid for it, Amber?
- I wanted to before,
- but you wouldn't let me!
- Then, fine.
It takes an hour
to get to your father's.
You could go or you can miss it.
Ugh!
I thought you were just going
with Moush and Lucy.
- I don't know why
you need something fancy.
- Here.
Here. Look.
This one is newer.
No. That is a ginormous
Peppa Pig sleeping bag.
Okay, so we'll turn it
inside out.
All right, look,
there's nothing in here.
- It's purple.
- Ooh.
Still see the pink Peppa Pig
zipper. I'm not a nine-year-old.
Well, then, we'll just cover it
up, or take the thing...
I don't understand why
everything has to be so...
There's no freaking way
I'm taking that thing
- to the lock-in.
- Kathryn!
[loud, overlapping chatter]
- Katie!
- Hey!
Dude, I thought
you were freaking dead!
I was about to call the cops.
- You guys aren't playing?
- [Moush] Oh, no.
- Dodgeball is the worst.
- No.
Mr. Daniel said we're gonna play
capture the flag soon
- all over the entire school.
- Are you kidding me?
[Lucy] I'm seriously gonna
ask to switch colors
'cause, legit,
no one on green is athletic.
Like, none
of the guys do sports.
- Really?
- [Lucy] Yeah. They got all
- the athletic guys.
- Oh, but did you see Jake?
He had a major grow-up
over the summer.
[Lucy] Okay, kind of,
but just Jake. That is...
- No, there's also Charlie.
- Is anyone else hungry?
[Lucy] I... You got all the...
Collect all three
of the other team's flags.
Big rule: the second floor
is off-limits.
- Yes!
Can everyone say that with me?
[all] The second floor
is off-limits.
Right? So we shouldn't see
anybody running on the stairs.
I don't want to see
any pushing, any kicking.
Does everyone understand that?
- Robert, does everyone
understand that?
- [girl] Yes.
Great. Okay. So I will be
with the red team.
- I want all of you
to walk, not run.
- Oh.
- Get your flag.
- Come on!
- Go. Go, go, go!
- [Daniels] Yellows are with me!
[overlapping chatter]
[boy] Mr. Daniels!
The team comes in,
just it's called...
Uh, yeah, just make sure
part of it's open, okay?
Uh, stop talking about it.
Nobody look at it.
Everyone, over here.
Okay, come on.
- Shh.
- Guys, just listen up. The way
everyone will know
where we've hidden it is,
is if we just have people
standing outside the library.
- Yeah.
- We've got to keep
switching defenders, okay?
- So, maybe you two
could start? Right?
- Perfect.
And then, I'm gonna lead a party
to the cafeteria
for yellow.
Who's with me?
Okay. Go. Go, go.
There are no other places
to hide in the gym.
And, like, shouldn't we try
to get red anyway?
No. The cafeteria is
such much closer to our base.
- We just... We're fine, right?
- Um, no.
- Like, why are we gonna
get red out?
- I feel like
it would be better
if we got red out.
It would be better. Like...
- Oh, Moush!
- Can you just let the...
What are you do...?
- [boy] Watch out!
- [giggling]
I'm faster! No, no, no.
No. No, it's like a tactic
I'm throwing you.
- [laughing]
- A tactic. I'm throwing you off
- by chasing you.
- Okay, okay.
Do you want to help me find
the yellow flag?
- Okay. Yeah.
- All right?
It could be... it could be
a shared blue-red win.
Yeah, we could, like,
cut it right down the middle.
- Brilliant.
- And we have perfect,
amazing...
- Cool. Let's go. Great. Great.
- Let's go.
[overlapping chatter]
[both laughing]
Well, there aren't any
yellow defenders in here.
- We have to go
where the defenders are.
- All right.
- Defenders!
- Defenders! Where are you?
- [hums] Defenders!
- Defenders!
Defenders.
[whispers] Alexa?
Alexa?
You're not supposed
to be on the stair...
Oh, my...
[whispers] Alexa?
Alexa?
Alexa, come on.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
[both laugh]
There's no one here.
We can sit down.
- Behind the MPR.
- Okay. Go.
- This way.
- No, this is faster.
It's faster.
[woman] Hello?
Who is that?
[door squeaks open]
[door closes]
- [laughs]
- Shh.
Wait.
[woman] Hello? Who's up here?
- Okay.
- What?
- [panting]
- [door opens]
[Katie] Duck down.
Yeah.
[both panting]
- [shoe squeaks]
- [gasps]
Oh, my God.
- Hey. Shh.
- [footsteps approaching]
[door squeaks open]
- Shh. Shh.
- Okay.
[door squeaks]
[door closes]
[footsteps retreating]
[both panting]
- [groans]
- I think she's gone.
I think she's gone.
How long do you think we're
gonna have to wait in here?
[panting]
For eternity.
I got a detention for this once.
It was...
[laughs]
[both laughing softly]
Okay, come on.
[both giggle softly]
[both laugh]
We can't hold hands.
Why not?
[laughs] We just can't.
Don't be crazy.
I don't care.
Well, you're-you're crazy, too.
[laughs]
- [laughs]
- What?
[indistinct chatter]
Girls, you're late! Come on.
[chatter continues]
[Moush] Hey,
where were you guys?
- Nowhere.
- What?
- Huh?
- What is going on?
What happened?
- Nothing. Just stop talking.
- Why were you with that girl?
- Katie! She won't tell me.
- What's happening?
- Nothing's happening.
- Okay, why are you guys talking
when you're on different teams?
Okay.
I don't know why you're making
such a big... Moush!
- Hey.
So what were you guys doing?
What do you mean?
Okay, why were you guys late
getting back?
Nothing. I, um...
I don't know her.
We don't know each other, right?
I just saw you.
- No. I...
- So you weren't together?
- No, we...
- I don't... Yeah, I don't...
I don't know what she was doing.
I was just going
to the bathroom.
- What were you doing?
- Nothing.
Oh, my God.
Okay, what is going on?
Katie, what aren't you
telling me?
Katie Stonebaker
and, uh, uh, what's your name?
Uh, Alexa.
With me. Now. Come on.
[Daniels] Okay, guys, 10:00.
I want you all done
with your ice cream. No more...
Stop. Right here.
This is good.
Why were you
on the second floor?
Nothing, huh?
Okay, I'm gonna have to ask you
to empty your pockets.
We weren't doing anything.
You were told not to be
on the second floor
and nobody was to be
on the second floor.
You need to tell me why
you were on the second floor
where you were specifically told
not to go, and I need you
to tell me now, or I'm gonna
call your parents.
- I'm not playing.
- I was sick.
I had a...
I... I really wasn't
feeling well,
and I was embarrassed.
She was helping me. That...
It's the only reason
why she's with me.
Come on, girls.
Really. Gonna have
to do better than that.
[Alexa] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Neither one of you are gonna
play any more games tonight.
I want you to go get your bags,
go to opposite sides of the gym
by yourselves, not with
your friends, alone, you got it?
- [Alexa] Yes.
- Okay, go.
[indistinct chatter]
[Daniels] Guys, we'll have
a TV set up, okay?
Mr. Lopez and Ms. Jones
have a film for us.
If you like, you can watch it.
[phone buzzes]
Ms. Vacher,
I'm really not feeling well.
Can I please go home?
- You want to see the nurse?
- No.
Well, Katie, I can't
let you walk out of here.
- It's the middle of the night.
- No, my mom's gonna pick me up
in, like, ten minutes, so...
You texted your mom?
But you're gonna miss
the morning.
You're gonna miss all the fun.
It's fine, I don't...
I don't want to have
to be sick here, I-I...
I just can't be here anymore.
Fine, get Mr. Mihill
to wait outside with you.
That's my mom.
Okay, good night.
Are you okay?
[Katie] Yeah. Yeah.
- Something happen
with one of your friends?
- No.
No, they're okay.
- Like Moush?
- No. No.
- Well, what happened?
- It was just...
I was just feeling
a little sick, but, I mean,
I feel a little better now,
so I'm okay.
Did somebody say something
to you?
No.
[sighs]
[turn signal clicking]
You're feeling sick?
Yeah. Just... I mean, I-I
wasn't feeling well, but I am.
I do feel a lot better now,
so...
If it's all okay,
then how come I'm driving home?
No, it's-it's all okay now.
It's fine.
Just don't worry about it.
Well, I do worry about it,
'cause you're my daughter.
I want to know.
- Well, do you need something?
- No. No.
Well, did you feel
like you're gonna throw up?
Mom, just stop asking me
so many questions, okay?
- I told you I was okay.
I'm okay.
- If you need something
- for your stomach or for...
- No. No, no, no, I'll be okay.
Don't-don't worry about it.
[sighing] Okay.
[engine turns off]
Wait, Katie.
Katie, stop. Just...
Please, just stay for a second.
- Just...
- [door closes]
- Thank you.
- [sighs]
[exhales]
You can talk to me.
You can always say
whatever you want to say to me.
I'm right here.
All right?
You can alw...
You can say whatever you want
- to say to me.
- [sniffles]
Even when I'm not home.
Just call me.
[crying]
Oh.
[whispers] Katie.
- I'm sorry.
- [crying]
Oh... sweetie.
I know I haven't been home.
And you've been doing so much
to help me.
- I'm sorry.
- [crying]
I'm so sorry.
[crying]
- [kisses]
- [crying]
[woman] Now,
you put the eyeliner...
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Don't be suspicious,
don't... ♪
[sniffs]
[man] Spin it a little bit
so that the flour's
distributed equally and you're
just gonna have one...
[rhythmic music playing]
[♪ Sylvan Esso: "What If"]
♪ What if end was begin? ♪
♪ Then would men
be like mothers? ♪
♪ And the falling of others
would be like ♪
♪ The first leaves of flowers ♪
♪ What if darkness was light? ♪
- ...to Katie. Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
Katie, she's literally
been sleeping the entire...
She's dead. Oh, my... Just...
- Do you see that?
Look at the drool.
- Look at that.
- Look at the drool.
- ♪ We'd stalk our prey ♪
♪ They can't see in the day ♪
♪ It's too white ♪
♪ Oh, life ♪
♪ Dying out ♪
♪ And the oceans ♪
♪ Turn to clouds ♪
♪ Soggy birds ♪
♪ Raining down ♪
- [creaking]
- ♪ From the sky ♪
♪ Having drowned ♪
♪ Oh, it's not ♪
♪ What you think ♪
♪ It's a memory bank ♪
♪ And it's living ♪
[dog barking]
♪ In our mouths ♪
♪ So open wide ♪♪
[dog barking in distance]
[Belinda exhales]
Hi!
Hi. Uh... Sorry. I...
Wait, you're Lori's daughter,
right?
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm just here
to talk to Alexa.
But it's, like, not a big deal.
Okay.
Does your mom know you're here?
Do you want to call her?
No, uh, she knows.
- It's okay. But I can...
I can just...
- Mm.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on in. It's okay.
Just, uh... Come in.
She's just not back
from the lock-in yet.
Can you come down, honey? I want
you to meet Alexa's friend!
[coughing]
- [grunts]
- Craig?
- Hi.
- Morning.
- Morning. [chuckles]
What's your name?
I'm Katie.
Hi, Katie. I'm Alexa's dad.
- Nice to meet you.
- Coffee?
No. No coffee.
[chuckles softly]
Coffee's for adults.
He's kidding.
What'd you guys get into
and talk about at the lock-in?
Uh, nothing, really. Just, like,
some games, I guess, and stuff.
- Yeah.
- Sounds like fun. You know,
Alexa should be back soon.
If you want to just wait up,
her room is
at the top of the stairs
- on the left, okay?
- Okay.
- Uh... thanks.
- [chuckles]
- [Craig] You know,
Adam called me last night...
- [blender whirring]
[Belinda] Just let me know
if you need something to drink
- or-or breakfast! Whatever!
- Okay.
Thanks.
[Belinda speaking indistinctly
in distance]
[blender whirring in distance]
- [door opens]
- [Alexa] Mom!
- [Belinda
speaking indistinctly]
- [door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
- Hey.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
I... I just...
I have to talk to you.
[Alexa] Okay.
[exhales] Sorry,
could you just, um,
close the door?
Thank you.
[door closes]
Okay.
- Listen, I'm really sorry.
- No, no, no, no.
- I'm the one apologizing. You
don't have to apologize, okay?
- I got us in trouble for...
I am... I'm really messed up
for what I did,
and I should not have said
what-what I said.
And I-I'm really sorry for that.
And I...
I-I don't want to give you,
like,
the wrong idea,
because I-I know I'm not gay.
Like, I'm 100% positive
that I'm not.
And-and I really don't want
to lead you on or whatever.
But, like, you're a Leo, right?
A-And I'm a Libra.
And there's, like,
zero compatibility there.
Those are, like,
the worst combination.
So it just really wouldn't work.
And I took this quiz,
and it, percentage-wise,
turns out I'm asexual.
- So I-I...
- Katie, you...
No, no. I really just don't want
to give you the wrong idea.
And that is...
what I wanted you to talk...
- I-I wanted to talk
to you about.
- Well, I don't...
- So maybe I should just,
like, go.
- I don't understand.
Why did you kiss me?
Well, I-I wasn't thinking
in that moment,
- and-and I wanted to, but I...
- Well, you wanted to?
Yeah, I wanted to,
but I just wasn't...
I-I wasn't really thinking
about...
Then that's okay.
If you wanted to.
Well, did you want to?
Yeah.
[Katie] Really?
Yes. [chuckles]
Okay.
Okay. [chuckles]
[chuckles softly]
Sorry that I'm just, like,
- standing here in your room,
creepily.
- [chuckles]
It's fine. I'm pretty sure
that my parents
are probably making us breakfast
right now.
So...
We usually have pancakes
every Saturday.
[chuckles] Um, okay. Yeah, if...
- if you don't mind.
- No. [chuckles]
- Will your parents mind?
- Nope. [chuckles]
Okay, yeah. I just, like,
probably have to, like,
call my mom or text her
really fast.
But, no,
if-if you don't mind, I...
♪ Looking out, made no sound,
you're a first ♪
♪ Can I follow you? Now I know ♪
♪ I can't be the only one ♪
♪ Make a mess of it all,
take the rest ♪
♪ Out the drawer, shut the door,
for who knew ♪
♪ You're the best by tomorrow ♪
♪ You and me then ♪
♪ Look forward to the weekend ♪
♪ Look forward
to the weekend ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Look forward to the weekend ♪
♪ Hey, shorty,
wherever you are going ♪
♪ Eye contact,
make me want to lose it ♪
♪ Too early
for myself to call it ♪
♪ Too early, too early ♪♪