TED: I can't believe your mom's
not coming to the wedding?
Okay, seriously,
I-I need to stop crying
Does anyone know how
to turn this off?
Is there, like, a button
or something?
Want me to feel
around for it?
It's probably
somewhere on your back.
Stop it.
What? I'm trying to cheer you up.
I don't think that's possible
at this point.
Challenge accepted!
No, Barney,
I just need to get myself
to stop crying, that's all.
Boogity-boo!
Lily, what the hell?!
It's not the hiccups.
I was just going on a hunch.
(hiccups)
And now I have the hiccups.
Original Air Date on November 11, 2013
Look, guys, just, seriously,
don't worry about me, okay?
Just let me deal
with this on my own.
I'm afraid that's
not possible, Robin.
Once I've accepted a challenge,
it cannot be unaccepted.
I will not rest
until the job is done.
Oh, is that so?
Then where are our diapers
and Samosas?
Aha!
NARRATOR: Diapers and Samosas.
Oh, that's about something
that happened six months
earlier in the fall of 2012.
BOTH:
Major craving for a mojito.
Oh, God, we're back
to your stupid little
private joke again?
Are you guys really still doing
this seven years later?
It's so annoying. Just stop it.
Private joke again?
Are you guys really still
doing this seven years later?
It's so annoying.
Just stop it.
You don't salute a private!
I'll be right back.
All right.
Lily, are you playing
footsie with me?
What?
Oh, no, no. I was just feeling
around for your shin.
My shin? Why would you...?
Ow! Why'd you do that?
To remind you what pain is.
You keep it up with all the
cutesy-tootsy stuff with Robin,
gonna be a whole lot more
where that came from.
Lily, you have nothing
to worry about.
I better not.
You and Robin are platonic.
Please.
Ted and Robin are not platonic.
Just like me and Robin
are not platonic.
Just like no two single people
in the world are ever platonic.
Symposium: two people
are only platonic if
in the next 20 minutes
there is no chance
of them hooking up.
Truth is, I only know of one
genuinely platonic relationship.
You and me.
Don't make me laugh, Lily.
You want to hit this
so hard.
Seriously, she's playing
footsies with me as I... Ow!
No, I'm talking
about Marshall and Robin.
NARRATOR: Marshall and Robin wouldn't
hook up even if this happened:
Marshall, Robin!
If you guys don't full-on
make out in the next 20 minutes,
they're gonna blow me up
and everyone in this bar!
My God, no!
Anyone but Robin.
I really don't want
to do this!
Guys, we have no time!
Just do it!
I'm sorry, baby,
I just, I can't do it.
Aw...
(explosion)
And the only survivor
was me
because I was upstairs
banging Ted's mom.
What? Get that blond girl's
phone number?
Challenge accepted.
(phone rings)
Unknown caller, stop calling me.
Are you gonna answer it?
Yeah, 'cause it's 1994
and I'm gonna pick up a phone
without knowing who's on
the other end.
I should get going.
Ted...
Lily, by every definition
of the word platonic,
including Barney's fake one,
I can say
with total certainty...
that Brussels sprouts
are the comeback vegetable
of the 21st century.
Well, see you guys later.
Bye.
Challenge completed.
I'm sorry. I-I missed
the first half of this.
Um, why is picking up
a drunk chick sitting alone
and rubbing a tan line
on her finger where a wedding
ring used to be, a challenge?
Because I said
challenge accepted.
See? That's your problem,
Barney.
You only accept challenges
you came up with.
Just once,
I'd like to see you accept
someone else's challenge.
Challenge acc...
Wait-- what's the challenge?
Interesting. An opportunity rife
with possibilities.
We need to find something
with just the right amount
of poetic...
Get a girl's number
while talking like a dolphin!
That works.
(chittering like a dolphin)
Open your eyes, ref!
That's not a pregnant lady!
It's a basketball
under his shirt!
Blow the freakin'
whistle!
Anyways, Barney's right;
I would absolutely
let the bar blow up.
But you'd die, and
Lily would die, too.
Yeah, but then we could
haunt the bar for eternity
like we always planned.
Anyways, Robin's your girl.
Why do we keep
coming back to this?
It's fun. Tickets are cheap.
Gets us out of the house.
No, me and Robin.
Because Robin told me that
she's still in love with you.
Are you serious?
Robin told you that she's
still in love with me?
No, I just made that up.
But it was worth it
because I can tell
by that look on your face
that you still have feelings for Robin.
Okay, ball is sitting
on the basket!
That's not only illegal,
it's unsafe!
Come on, Gens, D up!
It's this monastery
in Connecticut out in the woods,
and the nuns there,
they make this gourmet cheese.
It's just amazing.
(chittering)
Wow, was that
three glasses of wine?
Where does the time go
(chitters)
(chuckles) Look, I know
that you need
to get back
to your studies.
Maybe we could get together
some other time?
(clicking, chittering)
No! Not possible!
It was the performance
of a lifetime.
Man, if I'd have hung around
for a few more minutes,
I probably could have
gotten her to touch my blowhole.
Give me that.
(distant phone rings)
Hello?
Hi, did you just give
your phone number to a guy
who was squeaking
like a dolphin?
(chuckles)
Yeah.
Honey, listen to me.
I need you to take
a year, a full year
and just be
celibate, okay?
No boys.
One year.
I think you know
I'm right about this.
You're right.
Yeah.
That was heartbreaking
And pants-breaking
Boing-oing-oing!
All right, next challenge.
Oh, this is an all-night thing?
Okay, um, pick up a girl...
wearing a garbage bag.
(scoffs)
I'd be "Glad" to.
Just hope she's not too "Hefty""
And those are all of the brands
of trash bags I can think of.
I'm not done.
You also can't use
the letter "E."
Challng... accptd-d.
You're single,
she's single,
It's time to do this.
You're only saying this
because you bet Lily
that Robin and I would
end up together,
and you want
that five bucks.
I need that five bucks, Ted.
But more importantly,
I need you to be happy.
Marshall, we're platonic.
But you're not platonic!
You are 20 short minutes away
from happily ever after.
I mean, if you left
right now.
Hey.
I have loved you from
the moment we met.
I know we're meant
to be together.
I don't want to waste
another second without you.
Let's give it
another shot.
Okay!
No!
(buzzer sounds)
Pay up, baby.
Pay up.
TED:
Oh, yes!
♪ Sweet, sweet five bucks,
you soon will be mine ♪
♪ Even though Lily
and I share bank accounts ♪
♪ You're already mine
to begin with. ♪ Sorry.
And you and Robin get a lifetime
of happiness, so there's that.
But you better hurry up
before some other guy
snatches her up.
Really? And who's
my competition?
Okay, don't use the letter "E."
Don't use the letter "E."
Hey.
Damn it.
Hi. I... am...
Barney. Damn it!
There's an E
in my name!
Hi. My word for...
this guy is Barno.
Barno. You look...
not ugly.
(chuckles)
Your... dial thing...
is what?
Do you want
to just go back to my place?
Yes. Damn it!
I want to buy you a drink.
But first, what do I call you?
Elaine Edelstein.
How about I just call you...
tomorrow?
Your digits, m'lady?
Seriously, guys,
you're gonna have
to try harder than that.
Challenge accepted.
Excuse me, hi.
I'm Ryan Gosling's
personal assistant.
He saw you
as you were walking in,
and he sent me over
to tell you to wait here.
Be cool. This is real, okay?
But listen, Ryan is super shy.
Aw...
I know.
Which means that if he comes in
here and he sees you talking
to some other guy, he's gonna
turn right around and leave.
Nod if you understand.
Redhead at the bar.
Challenge accepted.
Hey, there.
Get away from me!
It's like you're trying
to lose, Eddie!
Hey, Eddie,
last time I saw
this many turnovers
was at a bakery. - Oh!
So are you doing this or what?
No.
And for the record,
if I were gonna do it,
I wouldn't just be, like,
"Hey, we should get back together".
Amateur hour.
Here's how you do it.
Excuse me. Okay, sorry.
(text alert sounds)
Sorry.
Huh.
Stop, thief!
MARSHALL: The blue French horn,
it's so romantic!
Oh, my God, do you know
who you are?!
You're Nicholas Sparks!
Hey, everybody, we got
a, uh, celebrity
in the crowd over here.
We got, uh, Nicholas Sparks!
You didn't let me finish.
Ted, listen...
(buzzer sounds)
I can do without reliving that.
Are you completely blind?
What?
Open your eyes, ref!
The ball hasn't touched
the ground in seven minutes!
Hey, ref, check
your voicemail!
I think you've missed
a few calls!
(scoffs)
Are you completely blind?!
Wait-- me or...?
You, Ted!
Robin has changed her mind.
No, Robin doesn't change
her mind.
Except that she does.
Remember how she used to claim
to hate white guy funk bands?
And yet, at the farewell
performance of my band,
"The Funk, the Whole Funk
and Nothing but the Funk,"
there's Robin
rhythmically nodding her head
and shouting out a request
for "Give Up the Funk."
I think she was nodding her head
in response to my question,
"Do you want
to leave soon?"
And she was
legitimately suggesting
that you give up the funk.
Can we just drop this?
I have moved on.
Well, except that you haven't.
You didn't just come up with
this blue French horn thing.
You've thought about this.
EDDIE:
Mr. Sparks?
I loved The Notebook.
Eddie, you're down by 80.
Will you watch the ge?
Do not come any closer!
I swear to God I will kill you.
It's cool.
I'm not gonna come any closer.
You're looking at the door,
you're waiting for someone.
Someone important,
someone who will fill
an empty space in your life.
A movie star?
Ah-huh.
But which one?
Clooney,
DiCaprio, Zabka...?
No...
I'm gonna go with Ryan...
Reyn...
Phil-Phillip...
Seacr... Gosling...
Ryan Gosling!
Yes, I'm waiting
for Ryan Gosling, okay?
Now, leave me alone.
You passed my test, girl.
Ryan?
ROBIN: No.
Just... no.
I told her I'm a method actor.
And I had to get plastic surgery
for an upcoming role
where I play a man
much more handsome than myself.
Congratulations, you win.
Win? No, I don't want to win.
I want to keep playing.
More challenges.
Fine, you want
another challenge?
More challenges,
more challenges.
Fine, here's your challenge.
Go down to the pharmacy
and buy some diapers.
And, uh, get me a Samosa
from the Indian place.
Sounds like an errand.
While picking up a girl.
Challenge accepted!
Come on!
Whatever happened to the guy
who wasn't afraid to charge
headlong into the unknown?
What unknown?
Sure, eight years ago
when I stole
that blue French horn, yeah.
That was the unknown.
But now? I mean, how many times
have we been here?
I know exactly
what's gonna happen.
You know who else knew exactly
what was gonna happen, Ted?
The Washington Generals
on January 5, 1971.
They knew they were gonna lose,
but they went in there anyway,
and then gave it
their best shot.
And they won that game, Ted!
For one reason
and for one reason only.
A scoring error and the fact
that Curly Neal had the flu?
Perseverance.
It was the only win
in Generals history,
but that's all you need.
Just one win.
(cell phone ringing)
I'm gonna go
grab us some beers.
(clicks tongue)
Hi, I don't know who this is
or what you're trying to sell,
but you are disturbing me
during the Globetrotters.
Hello, Ted,
it's Hammond Druthers.
Target acquired.
I'm recruiting volunteers
for the starving puppy orphanage
where I work.
For free.
So, if you wouldn't mind just
writing your number down
on this signup sheet...?
Listen, I appreciate
that you feel
like you need my number.
Um.
Maybe it's because
you're really sad
about something
and this is your way
of feeling better
about yourself.
But...
since I have a boyfriend,
and I'm pretty sure
I heard you call me a target
earlier over there,
Wha...?
I'm gonna go ahead
and not give you my number.
I'm gonna give you
something even better.
Wow, right to the chase.
Meet you in aisle six.
I'm gonna give you this.
Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
You're a good guy.
You will get through this.
Uh, okay.
Weirdo alert.
(chuckles)
(scoffs)
Have you met...?
(groans)
Excuse me.
What do you mean "sad"?
HAMMOND DRUTHERS:
Ted?
I'm calling you
from Chicago, Illinois
where I'm a key player
in a very successful
architectural firm.
Oh, yeah, I read about that.
All right,
about what you read...
You built
that big concave glass tower.
And it melted a few buildings
across the street.
Yes, fine, but come on.
What architect has made
a major design flaw
that raised the temperature
of the city aquarium
to 190 degrees
and killed thousands
of very rare fish?
That's the past, Ted.
I'm looking forward.
I want you on my team.
And I won't take no
for an answer.
No.
I don't think you heard me, Ted.
Come on, Ted!
Please?
They're gonna give me
a parking spot if you say yes.
Do I get a parking spot?
Well, we can go tandem.
No.
Every other week then?
You know, Chicago's
more of a walking town.
No.
All right!
You can have the parking spot.
So, that's a yes?
Mm, no.
Look, Ted.
I can make your life
very difficult.
How?
How?!
I will call you a lot.
I will Tweet at you like crazy.
I will live
on your Facebook wall!
We're not Facebook friends.
Yeah, what's going on with that?
It's been pending, like,
for eight months now.
Look, Ted, you're a...
a very hot commodity.
Everybody loves the GNB Tower.
And how it hasn't blinded
any pilots
on final approach into O'Hare.
(laughs)
And I-I may have told
the partners here
that you and I are
very, very good friends.
So, please, just say
that you'll think about it.
Fine.
I'll think about it.
Druthers shoots, he scores!
Sad? Lady, I got 14 girls'
numbers in the last hour.
And this was an off night.
(chuckles)
What can I possibly
be sad about?
I think you were in love
and you messed it up.
And every moment of your life
since then
has been spent trying to stay
busy enough to ignore that fact.
NARRATOR: And that's how Barney met
your mother.
Well, the Generals lost.
What a nail biter--
the whole fourth quarter
my heart was in my throat.
What was the final?
216 to 12.
Nobody talk to me right
now, I can't even...
The strangest thing
happened at the game.
I got a phone call
from an unknown number.
And when I answered I...
You're eating olives.
Yup.
Do you want these?
I hate olives.
I... thought you hate olives.
(laughs)
I guess I changed my mind.
(phone ringing)
Ah!
Hello, partner!
Boy, that just sounds right,
doesn't it?
Yeah, actually, Mr. Druthers.
My answer is no.
What? No, Ted, come on!
I'm sorry, I still have things
to do here in New York.
I am going to build
a tower of glass
and melt you with it!
No, you won't.
No, I won't, but know this.
After today
this offer
is gone forever.
When I hang up this phone,
you and I are done.
The door is closed!
Okay.
The door's always open, Ted.
If you change your mind,
just call me back, okay?
Bye.
I think he's coming around.
We tried dating a while back
and it was a disaster.
But I-I always regret giving up.
It just ended so quickly.
(quiet laugh)
What about you?
You and your boyfriend
gonna go the distance?
I don't know.
I think maybe I still
haven't met the right guy.
Hmm.
I wonder if I know someone
to set you up with.
Drawing a blank.
Are you gonna
go get this girl?
Or what?
I don't know.
I'm kind of
at my peak right now.
I don't know if I can
just walk away from the game.
Do you want to keep playing
or do you want to win?
I want to win.
What am I doing?
In less than 20 minutes,
Robin and I could be...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
It's gonna take a lot more
than 20 minutes.
This is gonna take everything
you have got.
This is gonna take all of your
time, all of your attention.
All of your resources.
This is the big one.
Diaper man.
You got to do it right.
Can't be messing around,
picking up girls in drug stores.
♪ It's only time
You got work to do.
♪ It's only time ♪
♪ It's only time
♪ What could stop...
We're not platonic.
Platon-ish, maybe.
If that's even a word.
But not platonic.
♪ It's only time...
I mean, there's
something between us.
And there always will be.
♪ If rain won't...
If this was eight years ago,
I'd be jumping
into a cab right now
to go steal
that blue French horn.
Well, why don't you?
I don't know.
Just doesn't seem to work
that way anymore.
I used to be in such a hurry
all the time, you know?
Everything was so urgent.
Now, I just, I don't know,
I figure...
it's gonna happen, it'll happen
when it happens.
I'm not going anywhere,
she's not going anywhere.
What's the rush, right?
♪ And swim your sea ♪
♪ And swim
♪ Your sea
♪ Marry me
I have no idea
who that girl was.
But she set me straight.
After that, I had one challenge
and one challenge only.
Get Robin Scherbatsky
to fall in love with me.
Challenge completed.
♪ Why would I stop loving you
a hundred years from now? ♪