God, I love seeing you laugh.
Oh, well, it's been a long time
Since I've been in the mood to. Thank you.
Persistence paid off
for Susan's new friend.
You're gonna leave me out here
in the middle of nowhere?
And Bree began to regret
what she had done.
Orson Hodge dreamed
of the perfect honeymoon.
Indeed, he'd begun planning it
the moment Bree Van De Kamp
agreed to marry him.
They'd start by flying
first class
to an exclusive 5-star hotel
where they'd spend
their days by the pool
and their nights making love.
And when they returned home,
their perfect honeymoon
would continue... Forever.
Mrs. Hodge?
Yes, Mr. Hodge?
Do you have any idea
how happy we're going to be?
I don't need to be any happier
than I am already
at this very second.
Oh, my goodness, there's only 15
minutes before our plane.
If you want that latte,
you should go now.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
... short of heart-wrenching.
The population of homeless
teenagers continues to climb.
This is Andrew.
Andrew, what is it like
to live on the streets?
It's not so bad.
I mean, you know,
sometimes people give you food.
You can find a lot
in dumpsters.
Uh, I-I mean,
just last night,
I found almost a whole bucket of chicken
that had hardly been touched.
Andrew told me
his heart-wrenching story--
an alcoholic mother,
a ther murdered by the woman's boyfriend
and a childhood shattered
the day his mother abandoned him
on the side of the road.
I'll tell you one thing.
Some people just should never
be allowed to have children.
Darling, I got an extra one
just in case you...
Bree, what's the matter?
A reporter just did a story on homeless teens,
and my son was one of them.
Oh, my god.
Well, we'll call child welfare
the minute we get to the resort.
Orson, you can't imagine
that we're still going!
Well, darling,
the tickets are nonrefundable.
My son is eating out of dumpsters!
Well, yes, but think
how much better you'll be able to deal
with this crisis after a nice, relaxing--
Orson!
My child is in trouble.
Don't make me choose between the two of you,
because believe me, you will lose.
Now please, get your ass in gear.
It was at this moment
that Orson realized
their honeymoon was over...
in more ways than one.
It was a holiday weekend
on Wisteria Lane,
and everyone was packing
their bags,
hoping to get away
from it all.
-  No, no, all right, good-bye, good-bye!
- No, no! This is so... unfair.
no, no! what's unfair is
that we're slowly running out of money,
and you've barely even looked for a job.
you're gonna have a good time, all right?
I love you. Good-bye!
Lynette was getting away
from growing tension in her marriage.
You can call it blackmail, Carlos,
but the court calls it "spousal support,"
so unless I get a check by monday,
your shower buddies from jail will
be throwing you a "welcome back" party.
Gabrielle was getting away
from an increasingly bitter divorce.
Hi.
I'm ready.
So that's my number, in case there's
any change in mike's condition.
I'm going to the mountains with a friend.
And, uh, just in case you were wondering,
it's strictly platonic.
He wasn't wondering.
Susan was getting away
from mounting guilt.
So you can't tell me anything
about my son's whereabouts?
And then there was Bree,
who had just learned
there are some problems...
- Fine!
- You can't run away from.
Some reporter.
All she could tell me was
what neighborhood they found him in.
They don't have any contact information,
no phone number, no address.
Well, dear, if he had an address,
he wouldn't be homeless.
This really blows. I am this close
to becoming homecoming queen,
and now I'm gonna be that creepy girl
whose brother's a pathetic street junkie.
You know, you could ** a little compassion.
Your brother is out there on the
streets, struggling to survive.
And whose fault is that?
Oh, she's right. This is all my fault.
You can't blame yourself.
No parent can stop a child
who's determined to run away.
He didn't run away.
I kicked him out.
You what?
I left him on the roadside with
some money and his clothes.
I didn't tell you because I was afraid
of what you'd think of me.
You did what you had to do.
I just wish you'd said something sooner.
Don't you know there's nothing
you can't tell me?
I don't want there to be
any secrets between us.
There won't be, not anymore.
You know, Andrew is not the only
one having a rough year.
I'm the one whose boyfriend got
shot right in front of her.
We'll talk in the car.
Don't you love this?
Oh, god bless Tom for taking
the kids camping this weekend.
This is exactly what we needed,
especially after everything
I've been through lately.
I'm all about relaxing and rejuvenating--
Gaby? yeah?
Could you be all about shutting up?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
Please don't tell me you brought
your cell phone.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just--I'm waiting for Carlos'
lawyer to call.
This whole spousal support
thing's gotten ugly.
Hello?
Oh, hi, Tom!
No! No, no, no. No!
Yeah! Yeah, she's right here.
Hang on.
Did you say something?
Hey.
Honey, I know it is your weekend away,
but it's my damn back.
I threw it out again. So?
So I can--I can barely sit up.
The kids are running wild.
I... I need you to come up here.
Well, why don't you
take a muscle relaxant?
Honey, I've already taken two.
They're not making a dent.
Well, why don't you give them to the kids?
Ugh, Lynette!
Please don't--  please
don't do this to me.
Parker, for the last time,
put down the damn ax!
Oh, all right. Yeah, yeah.
I will be there as soon as I can.
God, I hate my life.
I know.
I wouldn't trade with you for anything.
Oh, wow, look at the view.
Oh!
Don't you just love when the
leaves change color?
Well, that's why I suggested this,
so--so we could hang out for the weekend
and... and enjoy the, um...
*****
Yep, the scenery's great.
So, um...
maybe I should unpack.
Where should I do that?
Well, there are-- there are two bedrooms.
One--one is mine...
and there's a guest room.
Oh!
A guest room. That--well, that's handy.
Yeah.
Uh, unless, of course, you--you'd like
to sleep in my room.
In which case, I would take the guest room.
Oh! I... uh, no, no!
I-I should take the guest room
because I am the guest.
Yeah, well, it's, uh, it's up the
stairs at the end of the hall.
Okay.
Susan, I, um...
I think I have your suitcase.
Yeah, and I think I have yours.
So, did you, um,
did you happen to see the, um--
Yeah.
- And did you notice...
- Hard to miss.
- Well, I'm just going to, um...
- ...hide pathetically in your room?
Me, too.
Hey, Lynette.
What are you doing here?
Kayla called,
and she told me about Tom's back.
And my car got impounded again,
so I thought that I'd hitch
a ride with you.
Hitch?
You mean, like, we're gonna be
driving in the car together?
Well, you could strap me to the front bumper,
but, uh, yeah, I'd be more comfortable inside.
Uh, it's like an 8-hour drive.
So?
Um, how far is the impound lot?
Because, you know, I could just
drive you over there and--
What's your problem, Lynette?
I don't have a problem. I just
don't think we both need to go up there.
I can grab Kayla and bring her back.
Oh, I see your plan--
You just wanna go charging up
there on your white horse
and save everyone, and then I get to be
the rotten mother who didn't give a rat's ass
and stayed home eating bonbons.
No.
- Due to Lynette's sudden departure...
- Thank you.
Gabrielle was forced
to spend the last night of her spa vacation alone,
but she didn't mind.
In fact, she looked forward
to a quiet dinner alone with her thoughts.
unfortunately for Gabrielle,
her thoughts quickly turned
to her impending divorce
and the empty house
she'd soon return to,
and she began to resent
the happy couples she was seeing...
everywhere.
What is this, freakin' Noah's Ark?!
I guess it really is a small world.
Who's there? I can't see you.
Can you see me now?
How much, baby?
Excuse me, Ma'am?
I mean... Miss,
I'm looking for someone.
Uh, his name is Andrew.
Have you seen him?
Hard to say, boo.
I see a lot of lost boys his age.
Good-looking one, though.
Someone special?
Yes, very, and I'm worried sick about im.
You might try the soup kitchen
at st. malachi's on third.
- Oh, thank you, miss...
- Gates. Pearly Gates--
'Cause you can't get to heaven
without going through me.
How very saucy.
Great pIano. Do you play?
Oh, no, I'm a-- I'm a bit rusty.
Jane loved to sing, so I'd play for her,
but since the accident...
Right.
So...
Brandy,
a roaring fire--
what could be more romantic?
Well, I can think of-- of something.
Wow, my heart is pounding.
Uh, is that a bad thing?
Consider the alternative.
Your heart is beating
even faster than mine.
I guess I'm excited.
It has been a while.
Me, too.
So was that, uh, okay?
It was bloody fantastic.
Of course, it's a bit different
than what I'm used to.
Different?
Well, I-I was with the same
woman for a long time.
Oh, yeah.
But, I mean, you kissed other
girls before that, right?
Sure, but most of them were 12.
As was I.
I met one at a school dance,
and after we started dating,
well, I--well, I never looked at anyone else.
Are you saying that Jane is
the only woman you ever...
Oh, God, I so didn't want to tell you that.
Why not? I think that's adorable.
Well, I don't want to be adorable.
I want to be dashing and worldly and...
Oh, Ian. It's okay.
Some people have a lot of lovers,
and some just a few.
It doesn't matter.
Well, see--seeing as it doesn't matter,
where--where do you fall on that spectrum?
You know, how--how many men have you been with?
- Ian.
- Oh, I'm sorry. That--that was rude.
I withdraw the question.
It's not that it's rude.
It's just immaterial.
I mean, it's just a number.
It doesn't mean anything.
- Seeing as it doesn't mean anything--
- Ian!
Well, you know my number. It's only fair.
Is it-- is it more than three?
Nine.
Please tell me you were answering in german.
Nine lovers is not a lot!
Nine lovers does not make me a slut!
Why are you getting upset?
Because it was really 11, and I knocked
off two, and you're still judging me.
I'm not judging you. It's just...
did you work in the recording industry?
Okay, just so you know,
11 is not a lot for a woman my age.
How old are you?
What is this, the Gallup poll?!
- Where--where are you going?
- To bed, alone.
You know, it's something that I've always wanted
to try, but I've just never gotten around to.
So they liked the landscaping
I did here so much
that they hired my company
to do whole sinclair hotel chain.
Your company? You have a company now?
Oh, my gosh, when I met you,
all you had was a bike.
Well, not only that,
the, uh, Gardening Channel's approached
me about hosting my own show.
I mean, we're still
in the talking stages, but...
What?
Nothing. I just...
I can't get over how mature
and confident you are.
You've really changed.
Thanks. I was hoping you'd notice.
So I guess, uh, there's no chance
of getting you over to the house
to pick the dead leaves off my ficus.
Yeah, you know, I'm--I'm kind of past that.
Besides, I don't think
Mr. Solis would approve.
Actually, we're getting a divorce.
Um, I'm--I'm really sorry to hear that.
Really? Then why are you smiling?
I don't know. Why are you?
Gabrielle...
It's really great to see you.
Gabrielle.
I think that's the first time
you've ever called me that.
Well, um...
I hope you enjoy the rest of your stay.
I intend to.
Your cuppy thing is full.
Do you mind if I put this
in your glove compartment?
Yeah, I do mind. I mind deeply.
Jeez-a-marooni.
I'll just get rid of 'em.
Oh, that's...  delightful.
That's delightful.
Maybe it'll just soak up
the cream soda you spilled.
Why do you  always pick on me?
It's like your new favorite game is
"finding fault with Nora."
No, my favorite game
is counting all the things
I'm dying to say to you,
but I don't.
Like...
"Pipe down, you annoying nut job."
I'd never say that.
You think I'm crazy.
No!
You're colorful--
colorful in a way that might
respond to medication.
Well, you know...
there's levels of crazy, Lynette.
I mean, there are people like me
who just have a big personality.
Then there are the kind of people
who do things like this.
- Aah! Oh, my God! Knock it off!
- What is the matter with you?!
What is wrong with you?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Oh, lighten up.
Come on, it was a joke.
No, well, it wasn't funny.
If you wanna kill yourself, fine,
- but don't take me with you.
- Ooh, you'd like that, wouldn't ya?
You'd really like that,
if I killed myself.
That is not what I'm saying.
But if you did,
I'd find a way to carry on.
Pull over.
- Oh, lighten up. It's a joke.
- Pull the car over.
- Nah.
- Pull it over!
- Pull over, or I will jump out of this car.
- All right, all right, all right, all right.
I'm pulling over! Jeez!
What the hell are you doing?!
Hitching my way...
to the campsite!
Nora!
You can't be serious!
Shut up! Just get out of my face!
I'm not talking to you!
All right, now look, you've gone
from crazy to stupid.
This guy could be dangerous.
Well, then, it's your lucky day,
huh, Lynette?
Shut up!
See?
This is what you do.
You just manipulate.
You wormed your way into my family.
You conned your way into coming
on this trip with me,
and now you wanna force me into saving you.
Well, forget it! You wanna go, go.
No, I've tried that.
It wasn't enough power.
Yeah, I'm way ahead of you.
All right, here it goes.
Ah, it worked! I'm a genius.
Oh, hi. Um, I'm looking for Edie.
She's out.
- Ugh, God, where is everyone tonight?
- Anything I can do?
No, not unless you can fix a fuse box.
My science fair project blew the power out.
Oh, what's your project?
Oh, uh, it's complicated.
You think I'm too dumb to
understand your little science project?
It's not little.
I finished third in the state twice.
Now can you fix the fuse box or not?
Most houses built after 1990 are
wired through a circuit breaker.
You didn't blow a fuse. You tripped a breaker.
Not to challenge a 2-time state science fair
almost-champion or anything.
Let me grab a flashlight.
Maybe you could also grab a shirt...
and some pants.
Pants would be nice.
Susan, can I come in?
I'm with a client. Take a number.
Susan, please.
Everything I said
came out of my--
my own insecurity and fear
that I--that I might...
well, I might disappoint you.
I was gonna stay mad
at you another hour,
but your damn accent gets me every time.
Blimey, you--you don't say?
Don't push it.
Oh, no, I-I don't mean to break the flow,
but I-I just, um...
Look, I know that I'm only
your second lover ever,
and that--I-I know that means a lot,
and I just don't want it
to mean.. too much.
I'm not following you.
What do you want it to mean?
I mean, the last time you did this,
it turned into a lifetime commitment,
and I--I'm just-- I'm not ready for that.
You think I am?
Well, I assure you, I'm as capable
of having meaningless sex as you are.
I have never had meaningless sex.
So you were--you were passionately in love
and deeply committed to all 11
of your conquests?
Don't judge me, Mr. Virgin... plus one!
Okay, okay, we--we seem to have gotten
off on the wrong foot again.
Susan...
Cheerio? Bob's your uncle?
Get out.
- Can't we at least talk?
- Why?
You know, every time we do,
we just get angry.
Well, we're still getting
to know each other,
and that's good. You--you've learned
I'm a tad insecure,
And I've learn--well, you're just
a wee bit touchy.
Okay, Ian, you know what?
This is-- this is not happening.
I am just **ing ep**,
and you can just drive me home
in the morning.
Uh, excuse me. I'm looking for my son.
Have you seen him?
Excuse me, young man.
Have you seen this boy?
Andrew! Oh, my God, thank god!
What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
How did you get that bruise?
- It's none of your business.
- Andrew, please!
Shouldn't you be at home,
taking care of your new husband?
How did you find out that--
I read it in the paper-- you know,
the one I sleep under.
Andrew, you have every right
to be angry with me,
but if you knew how sorry I am--
if you came here sucking after forgiveness,
you came to the wrong place.
Andrew, please,
can't we just talk about this?
I'm your mother, for God's sakes!
You're my son.
No, you dumped your son
at a gas station seven months ago.
I'm somebody else now.
Andrew.
Andrew!
Andrew, please!
What happened to your ride?
The guy grabbed my boob,
so I hit him over the head
with his bong, and I got out.
Look, I'm sorry I freaked out there before.
It's just, when you made that crack about suicide,
it just... kind of hit home.
Oh, my god, Nora.
Did you actually...
Well, I'm... I'm very sorry. I had no idea.
But your life is better now, right?
You have a beautiful daughter,
and you have that fun job at the...
pancake house.
Oh, yeah, my life's better.
Yeah.
But it's not your life.
Your life's perfect.
Excuse me? Did you smoke that bong
before you beat the guy with it?
It's just, you have it all.
You have the kids. You have the career.
You have a husband.
You're Supermom.
And you think that's easy?
Okay, I have a good life.
Yes, yes, I am very lucky,
but I work 12 hours a day,
and then I come home
to what seems like 33 children
and husban who resents to get a job.
And believe me, there is not a Supermom
out there who wouldn't trade in her cape
for a chance to read a book
and get a massage
by a man who has the decency
to leave when it's over.
Okay, sorry I brought it up.
I'm sorry I said that about Tom.
He's doing his best to find a job.
Well, you know, maybe he'd try a little harder
if he didn't hate advertising so much.
He doesn't hate advertising.
Last week, when he came
to pick up Kayla,
and he'd just come
from some crappy interview,
he said that he'd hated the ad game for,
like, freakin' ever
and would like to bag the whole thing.
He said that to you?
He's never told me that.
He's probably afraid to.
Why would he be afraid?
Probably because you're the kind
of woman who,
when someone says they wanna kill themselves,
you say, "go ahead."
- You sure you don't want to come in?
- No, I'm good.
Uh, you really should see what I'm doing,
you know, for next time.
Okay, here's the tripped switch.
So first, you move it to "off"...
to reset, then you press it... to "on."
- That's it?
- Yeah.
You didn't have to come all the
way over here to do that.
You could've just explained it to me.
Yeah, I guess I could've.
Well... hello there.
Edie! Hi.
Oh, sorry.
Uh, he was just-- he was helping
me get the lights back on.
I-I overloaded my circuits.
I can see that.
Yeah, so she's doing
some big science project,
and she needed me
to explain how electricity works.
I think that's called "irony."
Julie, where's your mom?
She's on a trip.
Do you need something?
Yeah, back when I could stand her,
I loaned her my cd player. I need it.
Oh, she took it to the hospital for mike.
Oh, God.
This Florence Nightingale
act is really chapping my ass.
Hey, science guy,
I have an experiment for you.
Go home,
mix ounces of gin,
a splash of vermouth,
and see if it improves
my mood when I drink it.
Julie, sweetie...
you're a good girl.
Do yourself a favor
and stay away from my nephew.
Oh! Trust me, I have no interest
in swaggering, muscle-bound juvenile delinquents.
Honey...
that's what every good girl says
just before she becomes a bad girl.
Trust me, I know.
Except now when we're done,
I don't have to proofread
your essay on "Ethan Frome."
And I don't have to jump out
of a window. That's a nice change.
- Yeah.
Hey, how about I order
up a bottle of Dom?
Ooh, I like Rich John!
Hello? Oh! Uh, hi.
Nothing, uh, you know, just, uh,
room service and a movie.
What?
Really? You're--you're kidding.
Uh, no! I'm--I'm thrilled.
It's, uh, room 424.
Me, too. Bye.
- You gotta get out of here.
- What?
My fiancée's on her way up. Oh!
- Your fiancée?
- She was supposed to come tomorrow.
Guess she decided to surprise me.
Get dressed!
Uh, you-- you're engaged?
To who?!
Her name's Tammy.
Where's your other shoe?!
How could you do this to me?
I would never have let you seduce me
if I knew you were getting married.
Well, you didn't have any problem sleeping
with me when you were married!
You knew about Carlos!
My cheating was upfront and honest.
Look, Gaby, we don't have time
for this. Get moving.
No, I'm not going anywhere. In fact,
I wanna meet the blushing bride.
Listen to me, okay?
Her name is Tammy Sinclair,
as in Sinclair Hotels,
as in her father owns
this whole damn chain.
So if she catches you in here,
I am totally screwed.
Poodle!
Look at you, surprising me.
- Oh, I missed you.
- I missed you, too.
Ugh, this room blows.
Daddy was supposed to hook us up
with a suite.
You know, you're right.
Why don't we go down
to the front desk and demand one?
- Come on.
- Oh, no. They're all booked.
They call this a closet?
Where am I supposed to put all my stuff?
You know, I could really use a drink.
Why don't we go down to the bar?
I'm wiped. I just wanna stay in.
Didn't you unpack yet?
No, um, actually,
the--the zipper is stuck,
um, but they have a guy
at the hotel that can fix it.
You know I should-- I should probably
go ahead and take it down to the lobby.
Now?
I'm horny.
So am I...
but I will be a lot hornier...
once I get rid of this suitcase.
Poodle?
Where did this diamond watch come from?
Oh, shoot, um...
That's what you get
for surprising me.
I didn't get a chance to wrap it.
You like it?
I love it!
- I'm never taking it off!
- Son of a bitch!
Come here, you!
John?
John, where are you, damn it?
Don't laugh.
I saved a bundle on airfare.
Susan, I'm so--
Your azaleas are breathtaking.
Thank you. Ahem.
You should be very proud of them.
Yeah, it's nice to know
that I can raise some things correctly.
Darlin', be patient.
Andrew will come around.
No, I don't think he will.
I failed him.
I think you're being
too hard on yourself.
And you're not being hard enough.
Stop saying that
what I did was understandable.
I'm a mother who abandoned her child.
That's... unnatural.
Bree, it's hot. You're tired.
Why don't you come inside?
Because there is a bottle of Chardonnay
in the refrigerator, and right now
this little chore is the only thing
that's keeping me from going inside
and drinking the whole damn thing.
Well...
the azaleas really are lovely.
Yes, they are, aren't they?
Hi.
Look, I'm sorry.
Here's your watch.
I guess I'll just buy Tammy a new one.
Don't you mean her daddy will buy her
a new one and just launder the money through you?
I don't blame you for being angry.
All right, I should've
told you the truth from the start.
But when I saw you there
in the moonlight,
it took me right back
to when we were together.
Me, too.
Do you wanna sit down?
You know, you're pretty hard
to stay mad at.
Good,
'cause I really didn't want
this to end badly.
Who says it has to end?
What are you talking about?
Well, I'm single now,
and I thought we could maybe...
Gaby... I'm getting married.
Sure, and I was married
when we got together.
Right, but that
is not how I'm gonna be married.
Well, that's what I thought,
but trust me, marriage is hard.
I know that, but...
I love Tammy,
and I don't wanna screw it up.
'Cause enough of those screwups and...
you just end up alone.
Yeah, that can happen.
Good-bye, Gabrielle.
Um, hey, mister, uh,
could you spare a buck or 2?
I'm--I'm really hungry.
Hey, thanks!
I'll give you $50 more,
if you let me buy you lunch.
Fries and a large root beer.
What am I gonna have
to do to earn this?
I told you, I just wanna talk to you.
- You another reporter?
- No.
You a youth pastor?
You trying to save my soul?
Oh, you make it sound like a challenge.
No, I just wanna understand you, Andrew.
Wait, how did you know my name?
You're him, aren't you?
You're, uh...
The new husband.
Orson.
You know, I wouldn't talk to her.
What makes her think I'll listen to you?
Your mother doesn't know I'm here.
All right, Dad.
What do you wanna talk about,
Dad?
I wanna know how you survive out here.
What do you do for money?
I ask. People give it to me.
That's it?
What--what do you wanna know?
Have--have I done stuff for money
that I'm not proud of?
Yeah, sure, but you figured that out
as soon I asked you what the $50 was for.
But, uh...
Don't--don't tell my mom.
Or--or you know what?
Do. Who cares?
Well, I think part of you wants me to tell her
because you know how much it would hurt her.
I mean, that's why you're out here,
isn't it? To punish her.
When will you have punished her enough,
Andrew?
When you turn to drugs to numb the pain,
or you catch a disease
you'll never be rid of?
Don't pretend to care
about me, all right?
I do care about you,
because Bree cares about you,
because we're more alike
than you think.
I know about rage.
I know how it eats you up.
But rage goes away,
and when it does,
you're just left
with the mess you've made.
Thanks for lunch.
You change your mind,
you know where to find us.
How's your back?
If I don't breathe, great.
God, it has been so long
since my back has acted up.
Then wham, out of the blue,
I'm crying by a tree stump.
Well, you're under a lot of stress.
You got a new kid in the family.
You're job hunting.
Ugh. Are we gonna fight about
that again? 'Cause if so,
I'm gonna need those last four
muscle relaxants.
No, I don't wanna fight.
In fact, I was thinking...
if you can't find something
you like in advertising,
maybe you should cast a wider net.
Meaning what?
You're a bright guy. Isn't there anything
else you might wanna do?
I'd like to play bass for Aerosmith.
Okay, let's call that the backup plan.
But, seriously, don't you have
some road not taken,
some dream you never got around to?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Maybe?
I don't know. You get married.
You have kids and...
you lose track of that stuff.
Well, think about it, okay?
Cause whatever you wanna do,
I'm in your corner.
Man, did I luck out marrying you.
Tell me something I don't know.
Hi, Mike.
It's Edie.
I'm sorry that I haven't
come by to visit.
Pretty rough luck, huh?
Anyway, I'm, um...
here to pick up my cd player.
So...
Well, I hope you feel better soon.
Damn!
And that's with the coma.
We all carry something with us.
Of course, it's nice
if we travel with someone
who can help lighten the load.
But usually it's easier
to just drop what we've been carrying
so we can get home
that much sooner...
assuming, of course,
there will be someone there
to greet us when we arrive.
Why do we clutch
at this baggage
even when we're desperate
to move on?
Because we all know
there's a chance
we might let go too soon.
sync:ytet-cflily  ydy.com
edit:ixquic