Previously on The Originals...
Whoever I am now,
- I want you to marry me.
- Yes.
Hayley's missing.
Your family needs you now.
Elijah Mikaelson is dead.
Who is Hayley?
Someone Elijah Mikaelson used to love.
Freya, I couldn’t find him in France.
He’s gone.
I figured with everything going on,
you could use a friend.
I gotta get back to work, Aunt Freya.
Or you could tell me about
that cute boy you had hidden
in your room last week.
That stuff you were
studying in those books.
My mom’s missing.
I can’t just sit around and do nothing.
Until Hayley Marshall is found,
I am changing the rules.
Break the rules, no more
head garden, just your head.
I put the pressure on
to see how the factions react.
The wolves were prepared
to die for their Alpha,
the witches worked with us,
but the vampires...
Did nothing but resist.
- What is that?
- A message.
From enemies I thought
I buried long, long ago.
Rise and shine, Nightwalker Nation.
If it was your aim to get my attention,
then I must say you’ve been
wildly successful.
I am now singularly focused
on your impending suffering.
And to whomever sent this coin
and took my daughter’s mother...
...it’s time to show your face.
Man, don’t look to me for help.
Y’all lost your chance to
trade loyalty for protection.
No.
This would mark your very last
opportunity to confess.
Look, I don’t know anything.
Well, that’s a pity for you, then.
It’s me you're looking for.
Perhaps we should talk.
You know, for someone who organized
this little summit,
you’re woefully short on details.
So I’m going to ask you one last time.
Where are you keeping Hayley?
You knew we’d have this little chat.
No doubt you binged on vervain
till your throat was red and raw.
And now, sadly, drip, drip, drip--
All over the floor it goes.
"Sein Mangel an Vision...
wird sein Untergang sein."
"His lack of vision
will be his downfall."
That’s what he always said about you.
He?
You and I have a friend in common.
Oh, I sincerely doubt that.
It’s true.
August Müller.
I don’t blame you for forgetting.
It was a long time ago.
Rostock, Germany. Spring...
1933.
The purpose of art is
to portray life as it is.
When that world is joyous,
art must reflect that beauty, but
when our existence is beset
with unrest, humiliation,
hyperinflation,
the indignity of reparations,
art must necessarily
be equally drab and ugly.
Or perhaps, August,
the ugliness is a result
of the artist lacking
any discernible talent.
The mission of art,
is to engage our most
primal selves...
to inflame our passion,
to provoke our insight.
And it should inspire us
to drink and brawl
and "give our sensual race the rein."
Derivative.
And so...
extraordinarily tedious.
I wouldn’t argue with this fool
when he’s not listening
to a single word you say.
He’s simply waiting for you
to draw a breath
so that he might pontificate anew.
I believe you’re thinking
of my brother Elijah.
He’s the pompous, controlling one.
Interesting. I’d always heard
that Elijah was the
enigmatic and charming one.
The truly distinguished element
of the family.
13 years, you don’t look
a day over a thousand.
How do you do it, Niklaus?
God, I’ve missed you.
I fear word of your presence
in Germany has spread.
Rumors of Mikael are
rampant across Europe.
Come.
Sit tight, August.
I’ll get back to
your hackery momentarily.
Little friend of yours?
Hardly.
Do you remember him now?
As an elephant considers
a gnat, merely a trifle.
That trifle
is my Bodhidharma,
my Guru Nanak, my Jesus!
August is the touchstone
to everything that I believe,
and the reason
that I and my friends
have taken your sweet Hayley.
We have a room, you know.
Maybe we should go there.
Yeah, but then we couldn’t make out
in this filthy alley.
You were right.
About?
The feeling after sundown
without the ring,
it’s just...
a most transcendent joy.
I’ll take credit for most of that joy,
thank you very much.
Behind you, on the corner.
Don’t look. He was in the bar earlier.
You think it’s your family again?
I think...
...we ought to introduce ourselves.
Ladies first.
Well, somebody’s been busy.
Busy watching you.
Okay,
let’s see what you can do.
Okay.
Pretty cool, huh?
What do you think?
I think I wish
I had core muscles like yours.
And that’s nothing compared to what
I’ll be able to do once
I trigger my werewolf side.
Yeah.
Um...
Has your mom ever talked you through
- turning?
- A little.
And I-I have friends. I mean,
the whole killing a human part
sounds kind of rough, but...
What about the whole breaking
every bone in your body part?
You know, when your mom
talked to me about it,
when she, um, really described it,
it sounded worse than almost
anything I could imagine.
And, honestly, it’s...
it’s not what she wanted for you.
"Wants."
Not what she wants for me.
That’s what I meant.
Your daughter is dangerous.
A menace, a threat.
My daughter is a child.
A child born of werewolf blood,
who can create hybrids at will.
Her defect must be corrected.
Her defect is my defect!
Say that again, I'll
pluck out your eyeballs
and eat them like olives
off my fingertips.
I’ll call it what it is.
A dirtying of my species.
Which diminishes the pure
and superior nature
of vampires.
Make your point.
Your daughter will purify herself,
submitting to the same spell that
your mother, Esther,
once used to bind you.
Once her werewolf side is sublimated,
Hope will no longer be capable
of creating her abominations.
And what if I don’t agree?
It’s a simple choice.
Your daughter’s werewolf nature
or her mother’s worldly life.
Clock is ticking.
50 werewolves killed in Stäbelow.
A further 80 in Wittenberg,
this village just outside of Bentwisch.
Entirely wiped out.
A dozen massacres, all within 20
miles of where we sit, Niklaus.
Well, this is too systematic for Mikael.
Besides, I’ve been
keeping a low profile.
Oh, is that what you call this?
Yes, Elijah, besotted
fornication is the norm here.
The only one who stands out is you.
Rebekah.
What if that lunatic we call a father
found Rebekah and forced
her to surrender your...
Rebekah is ensconced in Chicago
with this Stefan character.
She writes me often
because I’m her favorite.
Yes, I’m afraid to disappoint
you, Niklaus,
but Rebekah writes to absolutely anybody
who will indulge her
about this nauseating affair.
She does seem happy.
Well, her happiness
is of my highest order.
You should know that.
Hold on a minute.
What is it?
If you don’t mind.
Do we have a problem?
Yes, I believe we do.
The man was a forgettable artist,
a virulent fascist and a murderous slob
who slaughtered werewolves by the pack.
And what did you do to him?
What makes you think I
had any piece in this?
Oh, I don't know, a couple
hundred years of history.
That hideous Greta woman with
her reverence for a dilettante
who made no mark upon the world.
I will not entertain her hateful ask
and bind my child.
All right, look,
shouldn’t Hope get a say in this?
This fate which she demands,
the curse which I bore for a millennia,
I can't put my daughter through that.
It’s a pain worse than death.
No, I will see that woman
roast upon a pyre
before I give in to the demands
of these cultists.
Look, all right, I got your back.
I do, okay?
But if they kill Hayley,
and Hope isn’t given a chance
to save her,
she will not forgive you.
And if I impose this shame
upon my daughter
and then they kill her mother anyway?
I won’t forgive myself.
You should really lock your door.
You know that, right?
Pretty sure I did, Roman.
Okay.
Well, then next time use
a lock I can’t pick.
So what’s the deal with you
and your out
She’s my aunt.
And why do you care?
Hey, I’m just curious.Hmm.
Hmm?
Why are you so interested in me?
- In truth?
- No, lie to me.
Okay.
A Mikaelson.
Daughter of an Original,
which is supposed to be impossible.
Dad’s a vampire, Mom’s a werewolf,
lineage of witches.
I’m interested in you because...
you’re the most interesting.
Other than you, of course.
You don’t know anything about me.
Hmm, which is, I’m sure,
exactly how you like it.Maybe.
How about this?
You tell me something about you,
and I won’t go to Alaric
with breaking and entering.
I once pissed some people off
and ended up desiccated in a cave.
Desiccated?
Yeah.
What was that like?
It was... bad.
But then the pain took over and...
I just lost track of everything.
Everything but time.
How long were you in there?
Long enough to replay the first
pain-free 16 years of my life
several times over
before moving on to my 17th.
An ancient bad boy vampire
with a damaged soul.
- How positively...
- Literary?
Cliché.
Oh.
Ouch.
Look at you.
The vampire supplicant
delivering poison in a bag.
It’s a hangover cocktail
I keep behind the bar.
Electrolytes, five "B" vitamins,
a little glutathione.
Klaus told you to show me pity?
No.
My choice.
Guess I’m hoping
showing you a little kindness
convinces you to let Hayley go.
She’s a good soul, Greta.
And none of what happened was her fault.
Not directly.
But we had years of peace, Josh.
All of which ended because
her loathsome daughter
sullied the evolutionary pool.
Poppy was a good soul, too, wasn’t she?
Josh.
Have you gone insane?
She’s no good to us dead,
and the drip will only help
clear the vervain from her system.
And honestly, Marcel, she...
she’s kind of got a point.
Choose your next words very carefully.
Come on, dude.
Look, I don’t know exactly what
your new deal is with Klaus,
but think about it.
Binding Hope means a safe
Hayley, no more hybrids, and...
And the Mikaelsons go back
to where they came from, right?
Oh, believe me, I have gamed
this out already.
Okay, so, not that I’m in any
position to give advice here,
but maybe, just maybe, you side
with the community on this one.
A question.
How do you feel about your skull, Josh?
I’m pretty attached to it.
Then stop engaging with the enemy
and keep your damn opinions to yourself.
You want to talk to me about
the guy with the camera?
He’s come for me before...
to watch me.
Stalk me.
Sometimes to bring me back.
Bring you back to where?
It doesn’t matter.
Then why are you packing?
Look, all those times that I’ve said
that there are things in my past
that I prefer to forget...
...the man with the camera,
he’s part of those things.
So, problem solved. He’s dead.
They’ll send a replacement.
Who is "they"?
Who is "they," Antoinette?
Yes.
I proudly participated
in the thinning of the werewolves.
Decapitated some 90 with my own hands.
"Thinning"?
That’s a convenient euphemism.
I’m simply ridding us
of the mongrels who diminish us.
Mongrels?
Inferior scourges.
Hardly the apex predators
born of Viking stock
like you and I, friend.
No, you and I are quite
different, friend.
A fact which I feel I’ll
have to educate you on.
I believe what my brother
is trying to say is that you
are a runt.
You are a runt amidst
a species of leviathans.
I recommend you not give me
any further reason
to stake that feeble,
incurvated sternum of yours.
This is the first and last
warning I will give you.
Time to go, Antoinette.
Yes, Father.
You shouldn’t underestimate
the movement.
We will not fail.
You know, history is littered
with eugenicists
who overstate their sway.
The Khmer Rouge, the Hutu,
the Turks in Armenia.
All of whom
left death and suffering in their wake
and all of whom buckled under
the weight of their own hatred.
Still...
...if you’re feeling confident,
tell me the names
of your coconspirators.
Sorry.
Tank’s not quite empty yet.
You know, August was
very weak and very small.
And yet he spawned a crusade
that lasted a hundred years.
I don’t see a crusade.
I see a lone woman grasping to
justify her last gasps of hate.
And I see a man who knows that’s a lie.
But what you can’t figure out
is how many of us there are.
And just how deeply we have
infected your world.
I have wanted
to tell you more about our past,
but I was afraid of how you’d react.
I was thinking we could head east.
Someone once told me Shanghai
is a safe place to hide out.
Yeah, feel free to send me a postcard.
You gave me a ring, Elijah.
You asked me to marry you.
You spent the last seven years
lying to me.
That’s not fair.
How could you not tell me that
you and I knew each other?
Because we barely met
once or twice in passing.
And the part where my brother
and your father have an entire
history together, you neglected
to tell me that, too.
Because I know how this ends.
I keep my secrets and
you’ll walk out that door,
but that’s still better than...
telling you the truth and
having you hate me forever.
Enjoy Shanghai.
Marcel, I have a question.
Would it be wrong of me to assume
there are traitors in my midst?
So...
- What?
- Now we’ve moved from "blameless Klaus"
to "paranoid Klaus."
Well, if that zealot claims
to have friends,
I’ll choose to believe her.
It’s been two days since
you pledged your allegiance,
and your first response
to Greta'’s demands
was to question me.
It was to find a way out.
It’s gonna take hours to get her clean.
And in the meantime,
Hayley sits some damn place.
I’m just looking for a way
to get them to give her back.
I’ll tell you
how they’ll give her back:
breathless, in a wooden box.
These people respond to strength,
not capitulation.
Do you both understand that reality?
Can I count on you not to blink
in the face of their hatred?
Always.
You see that? You see,
that is the problem
with our relationship.
I think I’ve signed up
to be his partner,
he thinks that I’ve pledged
allegiance to the king.
Yeah, well, uh...
Not to risk my skull again, but...
you probably should've told him
you called Freya with Greta'’s demands.
There’s nothing to say
until Freya calls back and tells me
if Hope intends to bind herself.
It’ll be painful.
- I don’t care.
- You could die.
Same answer.
We’re talking about snuffing out
a fundamental part of who you are...
Which, as according to you,
my mom never wanted me
to trigger anyway.
But which she wanted
to be your decision.
And I’m making it.
Not like this, Hope.
Listen... I know
what it’s like to have
something taken from you
against your will. Okay?
For me, it was time.
Years and years, cursed to sleep
by Aunt Dahlia,
while the world spun around me.
And I am telling you: when you realize
everything you’ve missed,
it devastates.
You know, if it were just to
save my mom, I’d want to do it.
Or it could be the fact that...
I’m partially responsible
for her being taken.
Or that I’m not even sure
I even want this freakish side
of myself.
But it’s all those things.
So, please, Aunt Freya,
get whatever supplies that you need,
because you and I are doing this.
The whole "note goes poof in my pocket"?
It’s really kind
of an invasion, you know.
Kind of hypocritical,
coming from the guy
who keeps breaking into my room.
Fair.
Um, so...
I need a favor.
There’s this thing that
I have to do, and...
there’s a chance it might not end well.
A "thing..."
...that "might not end well"?
Does this thing have anything to do
with what you and your aunt are...
♪ She always takes it black
♪ But you’ll love her... ♪
Okay. Didn’t really expect that.
♪ Goes dark
♪ You’ll love her even after that. ♪
Um...
I might die today.
Okay.
It’s how I get my mom back,
so I just...
needed to cross a few things
off my bucket list first.
Wait, was that just your first...?
Can we not talk about it?
You should've stuck your
hand down his throat
and ripped out his entrails.
Instead, you let him off the hook.
To prevent you from exposing yourself.
Might I spend the balance of time cowed
and ashamed of what I am?
Not cowed and ashamed,
discreet and safe.
The moment you reveal yourself,
you unleash an angry horde.
None of whom can kill me.
Father can.
And given the chance, he will.
So why empower him
with an army to hunt you down?
Let’s find out how powerful
this army really is.
This was August and his people.
They did this.
They tore these poor wretches
from their beds.
And they killed them
in their place of worship.
It’s not your battle, Niklaus.
Isn’t it?
Not this time, no.
You’re not the savior of the wolves,
and you cannot change
what happened here.
Klaus, please.
Those of us that matter
accept you for what you are.
Your acceptance rings a tad hollow
considering you stood witness
as Mother bound the part of me
these people want to kill.
No, I did everything
that I could to protect you.
Protect me?
You were ashamed of me.
You stood and you watched
as Mikael beat me
till I passed out cold.
I never watched you suffer!
I was beside you,
tortured and beaten without mercy.
Now, you tell me
what you want from me.
I need you to do something!
To take action
when people call my kind "mongrels."
Not just to talk.
Otherwise, you’re no better than those
who turned their backs
and allowed this to happen.
I have a good mind
to stick a dagger in you,
put you in a coffin and stack
you atop our dear sister.
Niklaus, you never cease to amaze me.
So, Rebekah's letters?
"Dearest Elijah,
springtime in Chicago
is ever so inspiring."
Oh, Niklaus.
Another talent revealed.
So how did you manage to deny
Rebekah'’s happiness this time?
Did you eviscerate this Stefan
fellow like you did Alexander?
Or did you simply toss him
from a balcony
like the unfortunate Emil?
I didn’t have a chance.
But eternity is long,
and I have an excellent memory.
Why do any of us bother?
Well, from here on out, don’t.
'Cause I'm sick and tired
of being betrayed by those
who claim to love me.
So go back to where you came from.
And next time you have word that Mikael
is on my trail, do us all a favor:
let him come.
There’s got to be
an easier way to do this.
Your blood is the key.
I just need enough
to soak the moonstone.
Anima marcam.
Iskoristi vuka.
That word.
"Marcam."
What does it mean?
"To mark"?
"The drenched stone
is heated and used
to brand the afflicted."
Brand me
"The palms of both hands,
the soles of both feet.
"And...
the site of the third-eye chakra."
And, Hope, listen to me,
you can’t pass out
or ever stop breathing, okay?
And if I do?
Just don’t.
If you ever want me to stop... No.
Just do it.
- Hope, I...
- Do it.
Anima marcam.
Iskoristi vuka.
Anima marcam. Iskoristi vuka.
Anima marcam.
Iskoristi vuka.
I will not let my past
become your future.
Do you understand?
Marcel told you.
He didn’t have to.
A thousand years of family
has taught me to expect betrayal
from those I hold most dear.
Bind her?
Really?
How many times
have you heard me rail against
the shame our parents gave me?
How many times have you heard me cry,
devastated over having lived
my life without my mother?
You have to go, Klaus.
You can’t stay here with Hope.
Hope, listen to me.
This ends...
now.
I thought you’d be gone.
It’s pretty hard to plan a future
when my past and present
are awash in death and deceit.
The very first time that I saw you...
I knew exactly who you were.
And yes, we have a history.
Your family and mine.
It was bloody.
It was also the first time
that I fell in love with you.
Excuse me.
I’m looking for my brother.
He hasn’t been in again.
I’m not my father's daughter.
I don’t share his hatred.
- But he...
- can’t be reasoned with.
And there are consequences
to defying him.
I’m familiar with that kind of father.
Eventually, even the children of
such a monster are not safe,
and believe me, it’s
only a matter of time
before he turns that rage on you.
Forgive me.
Listen to me.
I’ve been to the railway
station and to the port;
I have compelled the
ticket-takers to help
any who want passage
out of this country.
You say my name and they will help you.
I recommend heading east.
Shanghai’s a safe place to hide out.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Uh, your name.
If--If I'm going to use
your name as my ticket out...
Of course. Elijah.
Antoinette.
Until we meet again.
If we meet again.
Like I told you
when we met in New York...
...I abandoned my father’s
antiquated notions
and found faith in the purity
of my eternal soul.
I live by that code
because it brings me peace.
I want to share
this life with you.
Marry you.
Bathe in the joy
of those first moments
after sunset with you.
I love you, Elijah.
And I will be upstairs packing,
because yes, it is time to move on.
But I hope that it’ll be together.
Klaus Mikaelson has been
quite the busy boy today.
First you’re up and back
to Mystic Falls,
now you’re abducting
werewolves from the bayou.
If Greta'’s greatest fear
is "abominations,"
then I intend to give her that horror
in a never-ending nightmare.
I have a quart of Hope’s blood
and I will use every last drop of it
to create more hybrids.
You went behind my back.
You put my daughter’s life at risk
and you betrayed me.
I did what was right.
What was right for whom?
For your daughter. For my city.
This isn’t about what was right.
Your city rejected you.
So did my sister. Now all you want
is for them to take you back.
You just need to be loved, Marcel,
that’s your weakness.
That’s how I knew what you’d done
without you having to say a word.
And that’s why I know,
no matter what you promise
when you claim to be an ally,
you...
...you will always falter.
Drink up.
And when you go back out into the world,
be sure to tell everybody
Greta Sienna
is responsible for your fate.
I’ve made a mistake.
I don’t want to die.
So... come clean about Hayley.
The second I talk, they’ll kill me.
Look, you’re clean of vervain.
Okay? So if you confess
without being compelled
and Hayley's still alive...
Oh, she is.
Very much so.
Then Klaus isn’t without compassion.
Where is she, Greta?
You tell me.
You tell me where she is,
and I will vouch for you
with Klaus and Marcel.
Please tell them.
What?
- Tell them.
- Tell them what?
Tell them I am so very much stronger
than they could ever imagine!
Hey, you didn’t die.
That’s pretty cool.
What happened?
What happened is that...
I’m on my own, as far as getting
my mom back is concerned.
And what’s this?
A binding spell.
All I need to do to get her back
is to lose a part of who I am.
And I mean, I’ve got three.
How bad could it be to lose one of them?
Do you want to find out?
Well... none of the witches here
are strong enough to do this.
Yeah.
Man... if only somebody knew
a way to sneak out of here, huh?
Will he survive?
- Josh?
- Yeah.
He’s lucky to still
have his face, but...
I think so.
Does he have any idea
where Greta'’s gotten off to?
Do you remember that part
where I said he’s lucky
to have his face?
What I said earlier...
I was angry.
Yeah, well...
you weren’t wrong.
I’m off my game.
Your sister really did
a number on my head.
Absent Elijah, my temper
gets the better of me.
It did today.
And it did a century ago, with August.
♪ Everywhere I turn
I am far from blameless, Marcel.
♪ Everything is changing
Although he got nothing less
than what he deserved.
In fact, I think I took it easy on him.
I don’t want any trouble, Klaus!
As if I give a damn what you want.
After I kill you,
I’m gonna hunt down everyone you know
and everyone you love.
Aah!
♪ Everyone
But the rest never saw it coming.
When you’ve had enough...
pick up this coin.
Some of them were guilty of hate.
But most were innocent.
And they all became victims of that...
part of me I’d been forced to suppress.
August...
my beloved...
♪ This could be the downfall
Please.
Mercy for myself.
So, you see,
in the end,
I was the match that lit the fuse.
Mercy...
for my daughter.
My mistake
was that I humiliated them,
and in doing so, I empowered them
with the most potent form of hate...
that which has fueled my rage
for a millennia.
Shame.
I gifted them shame.
Please, mercy for my son!
♪ This could be the downfall.
Hey. It’s me.
Just letting you know
everything is... cool here.
I’m getting in the car and...
Hope Mikaelson is coming with me.
I love you, Mom.
Anybody see you sneak out?
No.
Ready to go?
Yeah.
Let’s do this.