For those of you
who were too fucking busy,
this is what happened
last week on Shameless:
Hey, you filthy fucking Portuguese.
Stan's losing his marbles.
What happened?
I know you fucked my sister!
You're right, he shouldn't
be left alone up there.
Call his daughter. I'm gonna come down
there and I'm gonna kick your ass!
He wants to stay
in his apartment.
Where the hell've you been?
Brazil.
We should get together, have
lunch, just to catch up.
I'm seeing someone. So am I.
Bring him. A double date.
Estefania doesn't really
speak English.
You're married?
Ah, si!
You married a drug lord's
daughter, to hang onto your ear?
I missed you.
Hey!
Okay.
Whoa.
- Was it weird seeing Jimmy?
- Who's Jimmy?
Jimmy is Steve.
V, they're gone.
Ethel and Jonah.
All their stuff is gone.
His clothes,
her suitcase, gone.
Fuck you, Lip!
I'll make West Point on my own.
I don't need you.
She's a married mother,
publicly flaunting
the geriatric
she's sleeping with.
Come on, I need an accomplice.
When I tell Hal we're going out
for a girls' night,
then I won't be lying.
I'm sorry, who are you?
I'm your grandmother,
sweetheart.
Grammy showed up.
Grammy's back.
Jesus...
They let you out?
Surprised to see you, Peg.
Thought you were
doing 20 to life.
I will fuck you up!
Oh my God, there's a woman...
Shit. Shit!
...with a gun.
She's at a party,
she's shooting people!
Go ahead and pull it!
Do it! Do it!
...and I'm gonna kick your ass.
Put some pants on, man.
I got pants on.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ ♪
♪ Think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ Know that it's not
for naught ♪
♪ You were beaming once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Round up the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that they're not
for naught ♪
♪ You were willing once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so... ♪
♪ Sure of? ♪
Mm.
Babe, stop.
Come on, you know I hate that.
I'm going to stick my thumb in
your butt if you don't stop.
Mm.
Now we're talking.
Morning, sunshine.
Who let you in?
Carl.
We don't let people
in the house before I wake up!
Which guy doesn't like
a finger up the butt?
What are you doing here?
I came to invite you out
in David's boat today.
I thought you weren't
allowed on the boat.
Isn't it the wife's?
Yeah, but they're in Indiana.
Dropping one of the brats
off at college.
Steve's back in town.
Not sure what to do about it.
Bring him.
Boat's got a Jacuzzi.
Nah. Kids start school Tuesday.
I got a lot to do to get ready.
So, come for an hour!
Everybody says that,
but it never happens.
I'll kick you out
after an hour, then.
Shouldn't you be getting your
kids ready for school, too?
Hal's on it.
He loves doing that crap.
So you'll come?
I'll think about it.
I gotta take a shower now,
wash your slobber off me.
You know, men pay lots
of money for that slobber.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for the visual.
Mm. Go make yourself useful.
I need coffee.
You look like shit, Frank.
You just getting in?
Just got up.
It's 7:00 a.m.
Hurry up in there. I gotta
help my mother out of bed
and take her to the bathroom.
Really putting a damper
on your drink, puke,
sleep schedule, huh?
I can't take it anymore.
Your problem. Not ours.
What about this little guy?
Hey, fella!
Ah, I don't know, V.
Oh, come on, he's so cute.
How could anyone
have abandoned him?
And his tongue is almost
as good as yours.
A dog is not going to
fill the hole in my heart.
When you going to
get over this, Kev?
Doesn't it bother you
that Ethel's gone?
It bothers me we're not gonna
get the money anymore.
How could she just
leave us like that?
Because she's
an ungrateful bitch.
All right, stop.
I'm serious.
If she doesn't give
a shit about us,
why should we
give a shit about her?
She was family.
Well, we have to move on.
I liked having someone
depending on me.
Well, then pick out
a stupid dog!
Dogs are too much
responsibility.
A kid isn't?
A cat, then.
It's gonna piss everywhere.
Well... we're not leaving
here without something.
Fine.
We'll get that.
This baby's pushing
on my bladder.
Morning.
Ah, Jesus.
Not again.
Knowing you were peeing
made me horny.
You're a sex addict.
Knowing I have a cold sore
makes you horny.
♪ I've been kissed
by a rose... ♪
Look at me.
Look at me, I'm about to come.
Oh, babe.
Oh. Oh, baby.
Oh, baby!
♪ My power ♪
♪ My pleasure, my pain... ♪
♪ To me you're like
a growing addiction ♪
♪ That I can't deny ♪
♪ Won't you tell me,
is that healthy, baby? ♪
Why do you always do that?
What?
Cry?
It's a release.
It's weird.
I can't help it.
I just feel so close to you.
It's like I'm giving you
all my hurt and joy
to hold and protect.
So gay.
Be nice to have a little
Jean Nate in the water.
I'll get some tomorrow.
And stop breathing all over me.
I want to go to
Indian Bingo today.
Feeling lucky.
Can't.
Got a big day planned.
Where?
At the Alibi?
We can go after you take
me to Indian Bingo.
Was thinking...
we should look for a new place
for you to live today.
Why the hell
would I want to do that?
Be a lot more comfortable.
Walk-in tub.
One of those
chair-stair things.
A ramp on the front porch.
You'd be a lot more
independent.
Don't need it;
I have you.
Well, I can't always be here.
Got a full-time job,
six kids to raise.
Are we talking
about the same person?
Scrub harder.
You're scrubbing like a pussy.
Disturbing image.
Morning, Lip.
How's it going, Grams?
You fuck girls
with that pecker?
As often as they let me.
Hard to believe he got Karen
pregnant with that thing.
It's so small, isn't it?
Don't kiss up to me
because you feel
like a worthless piece of shit.
Missed a spot, Frank.
Ass fuck.
Jack off.
You guys still not talking?
Dude?!
Carl?!
What the fuck?
Holy crap, why have I
never done that before?
You have too much
time on your hands.
Summer school next year.
How's your head?
Little dizzy.
You're fine.
Go have some breakfast.
How much we looking at
in the winter-squirrel fund?
Just over nine grand.
That's all we made
to get us through
the entire winter?
Frank screwed us
when he gave Liam away.
And there was that new
compressor for the fridge.
And that stuff for Liam's
ear infection, mwah!
Everyone needs
to get winter jobs.
Debs, get down here.
Breakfast.
I'll be right there.
I'll use the downstairs toilet.
School supplies and clothing,
nothing else.
No candy, drugs, beer,
or concert tickets.
And I want receipts.
What if the drugs
are really good?
You're still here?
I got caught up
reading a magazine.
Hey, that's mine.
Debs, I need you to find
the backpacks
and any old school books.
Carl, put the day care supplies
- back in the basement.
- Okay.
Roger that.
Lip, you and Ian clean out the pool.
I think there's a few
surprises in there for you.
Carl, tell Lip to
do it himself.
Lip, Ian says you
can do it yourself.
Carl, tell Ian he's being
a douchebag
for still not talking to me.
Ian, Lip says you're being a...
Okay, whatever it is
that you guys are
still doing, I want it over
before school starts.
So figure it out.
Mommy, what's my assignment?
Uh, go home to your family.
Actually, I need to
go get the boat ready.
Belmont Harbor.
Slip 22. 2:00.
I said I'll think about it.
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna see what
Fiona's cooking for breakfast.
Rooster in the henhouse.
Hide the money!
Morning, Gram. Morning, Gram.
Morning, Grams.
Bye, Gram.
Bye, Grammy!
Your grandmother thinks
you're being selfish
by not spending
more time with her.
Why don't you two hang out?
Have girl time.
I'm gonna go.
Frank,
give me two three-minute eggs,
dry toast,
and a cup of Maxwell House
before we go to Indian Bingo.
Have fun, you guys.
Only one cup.
Huh?
That's your second cup.
So?
So the baby book says caffeine's
not good for the fetus.
Well, it's good for me.
Hey, you want our baby
to come out healthy?
You okay?
Yeah.
Sure?
Yes, stop asking me.
I'm fine.
They're here.
Door's open.
Who's here?
My friends from tattoo
school, I told you.
Come in, come in.
They're gonna give us some info
about natural childbirth.
Hey, you guys!
Look at this man,
hey, motherfucker!
Yeah, looking good,
looking good.
Just fucking sits there.
Should we take her
out of the cage?
Probably needs to acclimate.
Let's call her
Ethel Number Two.
What did we do wrong, V?
We didn't do
anything wrong, Kev.
I just feel like we should be out
there looking for her or something.
Social services says they're on it.
Oh, please.
Social services; you
think they have any time
to go look for her?
You heard that woman.
85% of foster kids run away.
Well, there's nothing we can do.
Maybe she didn't
like living here.
You just said 85% of
foster kids run away.
What makes you think we're
in the top 15% of households?
How can you be so cold
about this?
'Cause she hurt my Kev.
And no one hurts my Kev.
Come here.
Mmmmm.
Mmmm, my baby's
getting his mojo back.
It was never gone,
just on hold.
Oh, shit.
What?
One of her weird underwear
things, so what?
I-I'm not in the mood anymore.
What? Well, where are you going?
The Alibi Room. We can do Lady
and the Tramp, if you want.
You know, I'm sorry if it's
gonna take me longer
to get over losing
our child than you, V.
Please don't go out in
public with that shirt.
Hey!
I didn't text you back
for a reason.
I wanna explain.
Don't. I got everything
I need, Jimmy.
I'm still Fiona, by the way.
Fiona, Fiona.
When I found out that you were
married, I was hurt.
But then when you had
a whole other life,
man, I realized I
dodged a bullet.
I was trying to explain
at the restaurant.
Not necessary.
We're totally cool.
Everything's great,
Jimmy-Steve.
I'll be seeing you around.
These powdered
donuts are fantastic!
I got them at Costco.
Case was only five dollars.
We were there to get
a Vizio flat screen.
200 bucks later, no Vizio,
just a cart full of groceries.
Which we needed more than a TV.
It's hard to watch the game
on a baked ham, hon.
You guys can use our membership
card anytime you want.
Great. Lots of stuff we need
around the house, huh, babe?
I guess.
You know what you and I should
do, Karen?
Can you pass the
Pop-Tarts, honey?
We should go in on a couple
of cases of diapers together.
Huh? Since our babies will
probably be born
around the same time.
You're pregnant?
Why do you think
I'm eating so much?
You could save a bundle
on your hospital bills
if you just have the baby
at home. You have a tub?
Yeah, upstairs.
Besides, if you
deliver at the hospital,
you run the risk
of them slicing you
like a turkey.
- What?
- Yeah, it's true.
Victor here-- come here, baby--
he was nine pounds.
His little elbow was stuck
behind my pelvis.
Doctors had to give me an episiotomy.
What's that?
It's where they cut you open
from vagina to anus.
You don't feel a thing.
It's good drugs.
I've got the video.
Honey, she doesn't wanna
see that. Nobody wants to see.
I'm telling you, just have
the baby in the tub upstairs.
It'll squirt right out.
My lady business hasn't been
the same since the episiotomy.
I swear I could fit
a walrus up there.
It's not that bad.
Then why did you wrap your
penis in toilet paper
before putting
the condom on the other night?
You saw that?
I've been pulling pieces
of tissue out of me all week.
Hey, Karen, you okay?
Guess who the big winner was
in Indian Bingo.
That a girl, Peggy!
Did you cheat?
Of course.
"How" about you, Frank?
You win anything?
Come on, Mom, let me play.
Did you bring any cash?
No...
Then no Bingo for you.
Fuck you, Tommy.
Hey, Kev.
Hey, guys. What can I get you?
Couple of Old Styles
with whiskey backs
and a round for everyone on me.
Except for Jinny.
I haven't forgotten
you fucked my husband, you
miserable excuse for a vagina.
Hey, Kermit.
Frank.
Was wondering, your
sister still has MS, right?
Yeah, it kinda doesn't go away.
So your house is tricked out
with all that
handicapped crap then?
Handrails, shower bench,
Rascal scooter.
How would you feel about taking in my mother?
She could pay rent.
No. It's just that I'm
getting really busy.
I'm not taking care
of your mother, Frank.
When he was ten,
our family cat was in heat.
And he thought that meant
we should open the windows.
Fire in the hole.
Jasmine invited me out
to David's boat today.
I never been on a boat.
Said it has gold-plated
bathroom fixtures. You going?
I don't know if I have time.
It's the end of summer.
Before you know it,
you'll be back to mittens
and multiplication tables
again.
Maybe. I'm coming down.
It'll be a nice distraction
for Kev.
He's driving me crazy.
He's still upset?
It's not like Ethel was our real kid.
She was our job.
I'm getting them now!
Bring down the Jergens.
I need you to massage my feet.
Fiona?
Hmm?
We have to get rid
of your grandmother.
What?
Where are the toenail clippers?
I didn't wanna have
to say this,
but she's not happy here.
Put 'em back when you're done.
These are never gonna cut
through her crusty talons.
How could she not be happy?
She just moved in a week ago.
Ah, he's full of shit.
He just doesn't wanna deal with her.
That's not true.
I love having her here.
I wish I could spend
all my waking hours with her.
Do we have any bolt cutters?
Good, because she's staying.
The kids like having her around.
It's not their house.
Do they pay rent?
She buys 'em things.
And she likes good food
that she pays for.
You should've been here
two nights ago.
We had porterhouse.
You're invited and I'm not?
And I need some
more chocolate Ensure.
Fiona, she's gone, with
or without your help.
What do you make
of these, Kermit?
Three of the most boring
states of our country.
My foster daughter ran away.
Been sending me these.
I'm trying to figure out a
clue where she might be going
or why she left.
"Having a nice time
in Kansas. Ethel."
What does it mean?
If I had to guess,
I'd say she's having
a nice time in Kansas.
Or she's being held at gunpoint.
Forced to write that.
Great, Tommy. Like I'm not
worried enough, already.
I'm just saying you should get
these postcards DNA tested.
See if there's any other
fingerprints on them.
That's not gonna prove anything.
You know how
many people have touched this postcard before it got here?
Then throw a blue light on it.
Check to see if there's any
blood or sweat on it.
Or semen. That'll
tell you a lot.
Could be right.
Many foster kids become prostitutes.
Jesus! Give me those!
There's no semen on them,
and my kid's not a prostitute.
Social services is on it.
Yeah, like they're on my
sister's welfare checks
that keep getting stolen
out of her mailbox?
I got to go to my game.
I'll see you guys later, okay?
Stan, Stan, what
the fuck are you doing?
Holy shit!
Look at the hog on Stan!
Got a baseball game.
What do you think?
I've heard rumors
about that thing.
Go back to your
apartment, please.
Oh, get your hands off
me, you knucklehead.
You're gonna make me
late for my game.
You don't have a baseball game.
Yes, I do-- it's
at Archer Field.
I saw it today on my calendar.
Oh, yeah, your calendar
from 1984? Come on,
let's go back upstairs.
Well, who's gonna
play first base?
You know, I just got a call.
They canceled the game.
Oh, geez!
I had a lot of
money on it, too.
Damn it!
Come on, Kevin.
It's time to call
Stan's daughter.
Put him in a home.
Shut the fuck up, Kermit.
Stan's not going anywhere.
And Ethel is not a prostitute.
I'm surprised you called.
I need you to do
something for me.
What?
Get rid of Jody.
Kill him?
No.
Just make him go away.
Everything he does
is bugging me.
Get a divorce.
Can't. He'll take half of the money
from my dad's life insurance.
Oh, you didn't get that yet?
No, they said another
couple of months.
The police are
still investigating.
Oh, yeah? But when I do
finally get it, though,
I'm gonna open a tanning salon.
Or buy a convertible.
Or get a boob job.
I should've done a prenup.
Well, it's not too late.
Aren't you supposed to get that
before you get married?
Yeah, if you want to do things
the traditional way.
Look, we can print
one up online.
I know a guy;
he's a notary.
He'll predate it for a
couple hundred bucks.
Really?
All you got to do is
get Jody to sign it.
That'll be
easy-- he's an idiot.
You said it, not me.
...and the detectives
working with him decided
the time had come to pick up
the suspected murderer...
You're in my way.
What's wrong with the TV?
Nothing. This show's
in black and white.
You're still in my way.
Looks old.
So do I.
- Now, move.
- Here, Carl.
I found these old
readers you can use.
Little old for third
grade, aren't you?
It's my second time.
Not too smart, huh?
Anything you're good at?
How about let's
teach you a skill?
Okay, we'll
have to do the best we can.
I'm not promising I'm having
any fun today, ladies.
Here it is.
Wow.
Thought she was only
having a few people over.
Why don't we party like this?
'Cause you keep forgetting
to buy us a boat.
Oh, that's right.
♪ ♪
Fiona! Hey!
Hi! Come on board!
Grab some champagne.
There's sushi.
Guess who's here?
Right there!
With his W-I-F-E.
Oh, shit.
Are we doing this?
I want to see the Jacuzzi.
Excuse me.
My grandmother's having
an allergy attack,
and I need to buy
her some Sudafed,
but I'm under 18 and her
driver's license was revoked.
Can you please buy it for her?
You making meth?
Free rock when
we're up and running.
♪ Man ♪ All right.
♪ People just don't know,
it's the mack, the mack ♪
♪ So I have that,
I've got it like that ♪
♪ Been there, done that ♪
♪ That's a fact... ♪
You wanted to speak with me?
Yes, Officer...
Rodrigues.
I think we may have a problem.
What kind of problem?
Well, uh,
I'm not one to be a rat,
but I think you might have
released an inmate in error.
And who might that be?
Peggy Gallagher.
You mean Body Bag?
That's her
prison nickname.
Yes, she was released on medical furlough.
That's just the thing.
She's not sick;
she's faking it.
Are you her doctor?
No.
But I saw her in a
kick-boxing class today.
A 78-year-old woman?
I'm trying to do my part
to preserve the integrity
of our penal system.
She's old;
she can barely walk.
What threat could she
possibly be to society?
♪ Let me get my money ♪
♪ Let me get my bread,
money on my mind ♪
♪ Or you end up dead,
heard what I said ♪
♪ Dollar bills, got a stack ♪
♪ You ain't talkin' money,
you ain't taking smack ♪
♪ All I see is green,
all I make is cheese ♪
♪ Put it in my pocket,
then we goin' overseas ♪
♪ Think I'm-a spend it
on a girl bitch? Please! ♪
♪ Stay on my grind,
and I gotta get my cheese ♪
♪ A nigga gotta ♪
♪ Get that money ♪
♪ A nigga gotta get that... ♪
Ooh...!
Ooh, that shit is awesome.
Oh, you should've been
hanging out with me sooner.
It was snowing all summer
in Chicago!
So this is where
the party's at.
What's up, you dirty fucker?
How's it hanging? Long and hairy.
Hard to carry.
I miss you, man.
You sure that's not
just the drugs talking?
It might be.
You remember Kev and the gang.
Si, si. Ola.
Ola!
Ooh, I love this song!
Estephania, let's go dance.
Have you ever done
Jell-O shots?
Ooh, you are so sexy!
What are you waiting for, bro?
Drop trou, jump in.
All right. What?
Ooh!
What do you expect? I've been in
Brazil for the past six months.
Where are you going?
I thought you said
we were totally cool.
I like your bathing suit.
Thank you.
For the first day of school,
what if I wear this red top,
with these blue shorts?
Must be nice to not
get hand-me-downs.
Or is the pink top better?
Not stuck with Lip's old crap.
It has flowers on it.
Flowers are for
babies, aren't they?
You're lucky Fiona's clothes
don't fit you yet.
Get to have
all new stuff.
Ian, I'm gonna need
a little more help than this.
Oh, good, you're here.
I'm trying to make
a good impression
for my last year
of elementary school.
Red top, blue shorts.
That's what I thought.
Thanks.
Karen and I are
getting back together.
She ditched Jody.
Now I can step up,
be a father to our kid.
Why? What's wrong with Jody?
He's a tool.
He is?
Mm-hmm.
How will I know if
I'm dating a tool?
You'll figure it out.
Or I'll beat the shit
out of him for you.
Okay. Cool.
Pathetic.
Ladies and gentlemen,
he speaks!
You could have
anything you want.
This is the life you choose?
I'm not gonna split
on my kid like Frank.
Fucking waste.
You know what?
You're the one that's
pretending to date Mandy
so you can fuck her brother.
You know, even the Pentagon
says it's okay to be gay,
but you're too chicken-shit
to let anyone know.
At least I'm not getting trapped
by some pregnant skank.
Fuck you!
You'll probably quit
high school, huh?
Start working at Best Buy.
Watch your fuckin' mouth!
Wonder how long it takes
before you start huffing glue.
Hey! Hey!
Put all that Sudafed
down in the basement, Carl.
I know what's going on here.
Saw it with my own boys.
One of the lions
has to leave the den.
Strongest one's got
to push the other one out,
or eat him.
Only one way to resolve this,
somebody's got to bleed.
Fight it out.
See who's alpha wolf.
I'll kick your fuckin' ass.
You won't last two minutes.
No knives, no guns, no bricks.
Just fists.
Tomorrow?
Labor Day.
I work till 5:00.
At 6:00, then, under the El.
Okay.
Dark chocolate Ensure,
just like you wanted.
Too late.
Got to go to bed.
Take me upstairs.
And I'm gonna need you to
powder under my tits.
I'm chafing like
a son of a bitch.
Honey, I'm so sorry.
We should try to get
on Take the Money and Run
after you have the baby.
We could totally win.
Oh, gosh, I forgot.
I need you to sign
a few things.
Can it wait till
after the show's over?
It'll just take a second.
What are they?
Joint credit card application.
Checking accounts.
Safety-deposit box.
Just some boring bank stuff.
Oh, man, poor guy's crying
like a baby.
Just sign here.
And here.
I feel like, you know,
that cliche saying, you know,
whatever doesn't kill you
makes you stronger.
I feel very strong.
♪
♪ We know that in these
trying economic times...
Prenuptial agreement?
We're already married.
You can do it afterwards
in some states.
Okay.
I love you no matter what.
♪ I love it, I love it, love it,
love it... ♪
♪ I love it, I love it,
I love it, love it... ♪
Ow. What the fuck?!
Quit trying to rape
my friends, Scotty.
How you feeling?
Oh, my God, great party, Jazzy.
Good. I'm glad
you're having fun.
Hey, did V tell you we're
gonna hit the highway,
try to find Ethel?
We're what?
Shit, did I not say that
out loud to you yet?
No.
The idea came to me
when I did my third
line of coke.
We are not riding
down Route 66 looking for Ethel.
Why do you have
to be so heartless?
Guys, we're supposed
to be having fun.
Yeah? Well, tell him to stop
calling his wife heartless.
My fake wife.
Guys, guys, guys, come on,
relax-- it's just
the drugs talking.
Yeah, and this is
the drugs leaving!
Oh, you know what?
You're not leaving. I'm leaving.
I said it first.
Yeah, well, I said it last.
I will throw your ass
over the boat! Keep it up!
I'm gonna check
on Estefania,
make sure she's still breathing.
I can, uh, give you a
ride home if you want.
I'm all set.
I took Kev's keys
a couple of hours ago.
I'm gonna get some more champagne.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
♪ Got me floating, got me numb ♪
♪ Hypnotized when
I'm on the floor... ♪
♪ Even though we move,
forever changing ♪
we might have been... ♪
How many of these people do you
think Jasmine actually knows?
Were you ever gonna tell me?
Yes, many times.
When? On the
flight to Miami?
Or is telling your girlfriend
about your other life
more of an international-waters
conversation?
Why does my name have
to make a difference?
You're also married.
You just say the word,
and I'll leave her.
The fact that you would do that
means that I could
never be with you.
She doesn't hold
her liquor very well.
You should take her home.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
♪ Forever changing,
even though we move... ♪
Uh, we'll finish this later?
Good night, Jimmy.
♪ Even though we move... ♪
Fuck!
Fuck.
Thought she was out for good.
You have a chance to talk?
I don't know what I'm doing.
Honey...
I'm sorry.
Why couldn't he
just stay in Costa Rica
or Brazil or...
wherever the hell he was?
Hey, look at me.
Men are assholes.
And you deserve to have someone
treat you like a queen.
I misread that, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
It's late. I...
I should get going.
It's just that
I love you, Fiona, and...
I-I... Forget it.
Forget just everything
I said. I'm...
I'm really drunk and high.
I'm gonna go.
That's a good idea.
I'm an idiot.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Thanks for the party.
Yeah.
Fuck.
♪ ♪
♪ I've been kissed ♪
♪ By a rose on the gray ♪
♪ There is so much
a man can tell you ♪
♪ So much he can say ♪
♪ You remain my power ♪
Oh, yeah.
♪ My pleasure, my pain... ♪
What's wrong?
Is everything all right?
I can't breathe!
Is it the baby?
No! It's you!
Get out!
What?
Shit! Out where?
Did I do something
to upset you?
Yes! Everything!
Get out!
Baby, are you sure?
I love you. I...
Karen! When do you
want me to come back in?
Never!
Well, shouldn't we
talk about this?
Karen?
What was that?
No idea.
I-I'll investigate.
What was it?
Nothing out there.
Fiona, Fiona!
Where's your grandmother?
Buying more supplies.
I'm gonna kill her.
She could live upstairs with
Stan, look after each other.
They've always had a
thing for one another.
And I wouldn't
charge you that much.
For what?
My matchmaking services.
It's a win-win for everyone.
Frank, I have no idea what
the fuck you're talking about,
but if you don't shut up,
I'm gonna stab you
with this ice scooper.
Oh, what did I do this time?
Where's your mother?
Said she didn't need me
this morning,
had some personal
business to do.
I change her diaper-- what's
more personal than that?
Shot of Jager, Kev.
Oh, don't hit the bar, Fi.
If you're buying...
Make-Make it two.
I never thought I'd say this,
but you were right.
We have to get rid of her.
Hey, Lip.
Jody.
How's it going, man?
What, uh...
what are you doing?
Karen kicked me out.
So you're, uh...
sleeping under the El?
Talked to my friend Lisa,
and she said
this is what happens to women
when they're pregnant.
It's hormones.
You sure about that?
As soon as Karen's hormones calm
down, I'll be back in the house.
No, you won't, weirdo!
I'll see you.
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ We're going all the way ♪
♪ All the way,
take it all the way ♪
♪ Going all the way ♪
♪ All the way,
push it all the way... ♪
We could put a hit out on her.
She's your mother.
Oh, like you haven't
thought about doing
that to me before.
Can't we just call the police, the
FBI, tell them about the meth lab?
They'd haul us away.
Not me-- I had
nothing to do with it.
Happened in our house--
you're an accomplice.
And there are minors involved.
Yo, Kev,
something's leaking. Come on.
Aw, shit, not again!
What the fuck?!
Fuckin' Stan.
What if she happens to commit
another crime away from the house?
You mean like...
we set her up?
I don't know, I hadn't
fleshed it out.
Yeah, I guess
that's what I mean.
Finally thinking
like a Gallagher.
She's putting our
lives in danger.
We could have the cops...
pick her up, tell them
it's a Chapter 405.
A mental disorder?
They'd take her away.
Involuntary psychiatric hold.
Just like that?
No questions asked.
That'll work.
Stan!
You leave the tub running again?
Goddamn it.
Ow! Fuck!
Cock, cock, cock, cock, cock.
Goddamn it.
Stan?
No, no...
No, no, no, Stan? Stan?
What the hell are you doing?
Jesus Christ!
You stupid old shit,
you scared the hell out of me!
What? What?
I thought you were dead.
No, no, I'm just taking a bath.
Well, why was it overflowing?
Well, the water got cold, so
I was adding some hot water.
I guess I fell asleep.
Stan, you can't keep doing that,
or you won't be able to
live on your own anymore.
Please, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Oh, yeah? Well, you
left the stove on, too.
Yeah, I know that.
I did it on purpose.
Now, get the hell out of here.
Get out.
You're lucky I don't
drown you.
Ah, get out.
Geez...
Okay, so we'll clean up the meth
lab, air the place out,
and then call the cops.
They'll bring her to
a geriatric psych ward,
Hold her 72 hours,
do an evaluation.
What if they find her normal?
Aw, get the f...
Okay, you're right.
When she doesn't pass,
they'll hold her
for another 14 days
and test her again.
Why didn't we think
of this sooner?
I warned you about
this yesterday.
But do you listen to
me? No, you don't.
Shit, Carl.
We could've avoided every...
What's going on?
What happened?
I'm fine.
Don't listen to them.
Are you the guardians
of Margaret Gallagher?
She is.
She's my grandmother.
What happened?
Well, your grandmother
blacked out.
She was at an Ace
Hardware, fell,
Was taken to the emergency room.
What was it?
E.R. doc says cancer.
Stage four pancreatic.
Doesn't have long to live.
Thank you, Lord.
Grammy.
Hey, it smells in here.
You blow up our lab?
A little bit.
Oh, come here.
We'll get it right next time.
She's got to be in
a lot of pain.
Shouldn't be leaving the house.
These morons don't know
what they're talking about.
Sign this form, please.
If she were my grandmother,
I'd call hospice.
They can manage her pain,
make her more comfortable.
Hey, knucklehead,
set up the card table.
I want to teach Carl a
little five card stud.
♪ I'm all out of love ♪
♪ I'm so lost without you ♪
♪ I know you were right ♪
♪ Believing for so long ♪
♪ I'm all out of love ♪
♪ What am I without you? ♪
Shit, I can still see him.
♪ I can't be too late
to say that I was so wrong ♪
Shut the fuck up!
Now, where were we?
You know, it's okay.
It's okay.
But I owe you for the prenup.
It's a little hard to keep going
with Michael Bolton
out there serenading us.
I'm gonna get a
restraining order.
That's okay.
I got to go beat the shit
out of Ian anyway.
I'll call you later.
If you don't like Air
Supply, I know other songs.
You're late.
Where the fuck have you been?
Getting blown
by some pregnant skank,
as you called her.
'Cause that's what she is.
Ow!
Fuck.
I'm sick of living
in your shadow.
Who the fuck's asking you to?
It's hard not to when all my
clothes are hand-me-downs.
Yeah, well it's not my
fault I was born first
or more handsome or...
...smarter.
Asshole.
Dickhead.
Want to get a beer?
Yeah.
Let's go.
School, come on, monkeys.
Carl, come on.
Get out of there.
Our house still
smells like meth.
Yeah? Whose
fault is that?
Whoa, good way to start school.
Wow, you look nice, Debs.
Thanks.
Hey, little fella, did you get
out of your crib yourself?
My gosh.
Lip, come on, wake up.
The Gallagher tickle spot.
Come on, first day
of school, senior.
Oh, not going.
You sick?
Nope.
Dropped out.
What are you talking about?
Quit.
You only have a year left.
Got to get a job.
Take care of Karen and my kid.
Kev?
Kev, wake up.
What is it?
Ethel's missing.
I know, for two weeks.
Not that Ethel,
Ethel Number Two.
Ethel!
How'd she get out
in the first place?
Ethel!
Baby?
Was cleaning out her cage.
Ethel!
And?
Forgot the back door was open.
V...
It was hot inside.
Yeah, well, you let
our new bunny escape.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Hey. Come here, I'm
sorry, don't cry.
It's all my fault.
No, it isn't.
I was... I was cold to her
when she first got here.
Yeah, but you warmed
up real quick.
'Cause I loved her.
She knew that.
Then why did she leave us?
I wish I knew.
We're talking about
the real Ethel, right?
I think we should
have our own kid.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Well, hell.
Could we start right now?
Mm-hmm!
Ethel!
Oh, shit, there she is.
Hey, hold on.
Don't you hop away from us,
you dumb fucking whore.
Hi, I'm calling
about my brother.
Uh, yeah, I can hold.
Hey.
Hi, I'm on hold.
Sorry about the other night.
I was pretty drunk.
Uh, yeah, I'm still here.
Uh, Phillip Gallagher,
12th grade,
Uh, won't be in school today.
He's sick.
I think it's just
a summer cold.
He'll be there tomorrow.
Okay, okay, bye.
I'm pretty embarrassed
about the other night.
It's okay, don't-don't
even worry about it.
Hey, I have some
blow left over.
Could get into some
trouble today.
Uh, you should go home.
Actually, I don't have a home.
What?
Yeah, Hal found out about David.
He kicked me out
a couple of weeks ago.
Jesus.
Yeah, it's okay.
It was bound to happen
sooner or later, right?
I guess so.
Now I get to start over.
Do what I want,
be a single woman.
What about your kids?
Are they doing okay?
Hal's better with them.
I've just been staying
on David's boat, although
he didn't know about it until
the cops showed up last night.
You've been breaking in
to his boat?
He never uses it;
it's just sitting there.
I gave him the best
blow jobs of his life.
You saw him.
I was so out of his league.
I got to get in the shower.
Start looking for a job.
Hey, do you think I could
stay here for a couple of days?
What?
Yeah, I'll kick
in some rent money.
No.
No?
But I do everything for you.
What are you talking about?
I brought Steve to the party,
I gave you a job this winter.
I-I gave you clothes
and jewelry.
She still alive?
I haven't been up there.
Fuck me.
I got Estefania drunk
so that you could
have sex with Steve.
I didn't want
to have sex with Steve.
Right.
I don't need you
meddling in my life.
Meddling?
When you need something
from me it's fine,
but when I need something,
suddenly little Miss
Fiona just runs away?
Okay, you need to go.
Fine! I don't give a shit!
You just kick me out,
like David and Hal.
You're all just a
bunch of assholes!
Jasmine?
Fuck...
Get out of my yard.
Why didn't you meet
me at the airport?
I was on my way.
What happened?
Doesn't matter now.
I love you.
Don't.
♪ ♪
♪ We met in a snowstorm,
I guess ♪
♪ And our fingers
were stinging to the bone ♪
♪ I sold what was mine ♪
No one's gonna
notice some new dude
suddenly showing up overnight?
No one gives a shit.
This is Irving's room.
Kicked it a few days ago.
It'll be weeks before
anyone figures it out.
Okay, I'll get his legs.
On three-- one,
two, three.
Let's do it again, ready?
One, two, three.
Fuck it, just leave him here.
Wait, we forgot his buddy.
Okay...
Aw, I'll look in on
him every day.
♪ Hold on to me... ♪
See you tomorrow, Stan.
♪ Hold on, hold on ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Hold on, won't you
hold on to me? ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Ain't it weird? ♪
♪ I disappeared ♪