Miss?
I have to apologize.
Well, not to me, but I'm
sure the Amish are pissed
that you're gaying up their look.
I don't have enough money for the tip.
Weird. You survive the diner chili,
and it's the waitress that kills you!
But I can tip another way.
I'm a psychic.
So, uh, you already know
where they're gonna find your body.
Oh, please. I die in a bridge collapse
you have nothing to do with.
I can tell you your future.
Ha! You're wrong. I don't have one.
See the guy in the booth over there?
Jared "Leto Himself Go"?
He just offered to read
my future as my tip!
Ha! You don't have one.
Miss, let me read your palm.
Sir, coming over here right
now is not a good idea.
We don't like to be
stiffed by strangers.
In six months, maybe,
but we're not there yet.
I'm a legit psychic.
I predicted long hair was coming back
in time to have long hair when it did.
Okay. You can read my palm.
I could use some good news.
I could also use some
hand moisturizer... sorry.
I see two Ms?
You bitch! Have you been
holding out on M&M's?
Ooh! Is it the male model
I'm managing
who's also making it with Max?
Actually... I see a small failure.
I take it back. You are good!
(Peter Bjorn and John)
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
[cash register bell dings]
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
Here's your chocolate lemon crumble.
Sounds like it shouldn't
work together, but it does.
It's the Tony Bennett and
Lady Gaga of desserts.
Max, can I have just a wee bite?
A crumble of the crumble?
Caroline won't let me eat anything
because of my big photo shoot.
[sighs] Hurry!
No chewing, no enjoying. Just swallow.
Spit that out!
No!
I said spit that out!
You're a model now! Shame on you!
Bitch, he's starving.
He's not eating, is he?
I don't want the Stay
Puft Marshmallow man
showing up at my
girlfriend's photo shoot.
I haven't eaten anything since Tuesday!
This morning, he tried
to swallow his toothpaste,
but I was right there to stop him.
Good, honey.
That kind of heartlessness
is why I've decided
to make you the manager
of our hot new location
of the High.
Oh, my God! This is so exciting!
Someone's finally realizing
my full potential,
and it's not me!
Will I be able to make
Max head pastry chef?
And where is this new location?
Well, right now, everything's under wraps
the way my face was six months ago.
But as manager, you can
hire your own staff,
and I'll even let you poach Max.
I'll also tell you
the new spot is amazing.
It's international. It's a hub.
I'm talking major flagship.
Honey, I get that you're happy,
but enough with the eye contact.
No one can look me in the eye.
I'm the Medusa in Chanel.
Max doesn't let me look her in the eyes
during sex either.
I told you, eye contact's extra.
Max, did you hear that?
Major flagship!
Uh, did someone just
call me a major flag?
I think you did, and if I don't get to
go to the new place with you two,
I'm telling HR.
That's Hector Rodriguez, my therapist.
Would you be interested
in coming to the new High
as part of our team?
If you say "part of our team" again,
I'll rethink the whole thing.
I'll take it.
But I have to be upfront with Max.
I don't like it in the back.
Which, by the way, is what
I say to all my dates.
Samesies!
Well, this is great news.
How about we celebrate
with a piece of pie?
No!
Earl, we have great news.
Guess what it is.
No, don't. Okay, guess.
No, don't. Yes, guess, guess!
Can we hurry this along?
My cousin is on Maury Povich today,
and I wanna find out if he's the father.
'Cause then I can stop
paying child support.
Sorry. She's a little amped.
She hasn't had good news to share
since we found out the washing machine
in our basement takes buttons.
Sure, you do.
And I'm playing center
for the New York Knicks!
Have you seen the Knicks lately?
He can only help.
Well, according to my time card,
I've been here for six hours already,
so I'm gonna head back
and catch some Zs.
The Mattress is all yours, Max.
Hey, everybody.
We weren't expecting company.
I came by
to discuss wedding details with Oleg
while we had intercourse.
What is this, the Bunny Ranch?
Baby, I think these are yours.
Yeah.
Yeah. Why, thank you, honey.
Can we just make it a general rule
that there's no
fornication in the diner?
Or in Han's apartment, ever.
Okay, Max and I have some
really exciting news.
Yeah, yeah.
We know all about the buttons.
Oleg!
I think you crushed my
seating arrangement!
I'd like to think so.
So, back to us.
How 'bout back to work?
Max and I...
Need to do some work!
There. End of news.
Where are you running off to so fast?
Is someone having a
sale on smaller heads?
I'm too small, I'm too big... pick one!
Here's our big news.
You are looking at the manager
and the head pastry chef of
the brand-new High location.
Actually, he's looking at our kneecaps.
Okay, so we're going with too small.
If you two quit the diner,
how will I ever replace you?
Unless I hire... literally anyone else!
No, Han, we still have
to work here at night.
We have more debt
than Jada Pinkett-Smith
has excuses for Will not being home.
But at the new High,
we're gonna be the big bosses
calling all the shots.
Yes, yes... by day.
But by night, you'll be
the coleslaw's bitch.
Don't listen to him.
Clearly, Han just resents our success.
I know! Why can't women ever
just be happy for each other?
Wow, that is really hot.
Yeah.
The milder salsa's right here.
Listen... oh!
Do girls eat now?
Wow! Lena Dunham changed everything!
Listen, which one of you
is sleeping with the model?
I know one of you said you were,
but I don't listen when you talk.
[muffled] She is.
This is a massive ad campaign,
and I don't know how else to say this,
but I need his penis to look bigger.
Oh! Yeah...
It gets nervous when
you shine a light on it.
Sometimes I hear her coaxing
it out of its crawl space
with treats.
Well, do something.
I haven't touched one since college,
and even then it was just
to look under it for my keys.
Max, take him off set. Be professional.
How professional can I be?
She's asking me to fluff his nutter.
Yo, Nash! Break time.
So... Marie.
Did Joe tell you about
my big new job promotion?
Of course she did. We're lesbians.
Talking is most of what we do.
It's why we rule daytime.
(Irish accent) Eh... pardon me.
You, maybe. That coat... never.
I'm lookin' for someone.
You also look like an extra
from Angela's Ashes.
But this is a private shoot,
as in we're shooting someone's privates.
I'm looking for me son.
Okay, people! The
groundhog's outta the hole!
Six more inches of winter.
That's him! That's me boy!
Ma?
Huh?
Ma, how did you know I was in New York?
Aw, no, you saw me in
the Today Show window,
didn't ya?
You checked into "America" on Facebook,
you bleedin' idiot.
I flew all the way and been
lookin' for you day and night
in this dirty, God
forsaken city for a week.
I'm takin' you home.
Ma'am, Nash can make his own decisions.
He's a grown man.
Yep. Thanks to my handiwork.
He's no grown man. He's just now 18.
He's got his prom next month!
I can't believe it!
I had sex with a teenager!
Who am I, Woody Allen?
Roman Polanski?
Pretty much any of your
big-time '70s movie directors?
You had sex with me innocent child?
Uh, not so innocent.
He made me blush a few times,
and I have two positions named after me.
Well, that's that.
You've seen the last of
big booby dirty girl here.
I'd object, but when you're
right, you're right.
But Ma, I like New York.
People want to take
pictures of me willy here.
This is all me fault.
I should have never let you
watch that Magic Mike.
That's great.
I don't have a model now.
I'm Seal.
Wait until I tell Joe about this.
How can you not know how old he is?
Uh... what can I say?
We're a typical couple!
He lied about his age, and I
pretended he was interesting.
Okay, Max, when Joe gets here,
I'm just gonna tell her
that me managing an underage twink
has nothing to do with me
managing her restaurant
which sells overpriced twink... ies.
Yeah. I'm sure she'll
be professional about it all.
Professional?
Yesterday, she slapped a woman in here
for wearing cheap heels.
I know. My face is still red.
Here she is.
Good morning, Joe!
Hey, ladies.
Well, obviously, you're both fired.
Obviously.
Can I keep the hat?
You are not gonna want this back.
My head sweats like a
watermelon at a picnic.
Please don't fire us
over the Nash situation.
It was out of our hands.
Actually, it was in her hands,
and it was only 18.
You two embarrassed my girlfriend.
And embarrassment in
the lesbian community
is worse than not owning a dog.
It's worse than dating Anne Heche.
Oh, my God. We committed a Heche crime.
How can we make it better?
Just get that kid back to
the photo shoot tomorrow,
and we're back in business.
And Max, next time,
stay out of his barely legal business.
Done. Don't know how, but done.
You won't be sorry.
Just get him back,
'cause I gotta tell ya...
Marie's crying face?
Not for me.
Well, coleslaw...
just when I thought I was out,
you pulled me back in again.
Max, don't tell the coleslaw that.
Don't give it that power.
My plan to get Nash back will work.
We still have a bright, bright future.
Yes! By day.
Han!
Do you want to spend another night
in this coleslaw bucket?
No. And had I not been able to
roll myself out to the street,
I might have suffocated!
Nash and his mom will be
here any minute, Max.
Do you really need to
expose 60% of your boobs?
It's not up to me.
These girls have a life of their own.
The right one just started
a Fleetwood Mac cover band.
You know how I know?
'Cause when I take my bra
off, it goes its own way.
Do you really think you
can get Nash's mother
to change her mind when they come in
to pick up the rest of his stuff?
Yes, I do.
Because she and I have a lot in common.
I may not be Irish, but I'm dirt poor,
and I'm living with someone
who drinks way too much.
(Oleg) Max, look.
All those purple post-its
are Sophie's friends and family.
My family's nowhere to be seen!
It's like I'm looking at
the last U.S. census!
Hey, girls. Come over here.
We need your help with the seating chart.
Yeah. You know, planning
a wedding is more work
than waxing Oleg's back
during a full moon.
Sophie, I have my own issue right now.
Okay. Then Max can
help me with the chart
while you go worry about
your obviously thinning hair.
Uh, full disclosure...
the last time someone asked me
to help them with something,
I free-based half their beard off.
[chime]
I just got a text from Nash.
He's here? I'll go get him a kid's menu.
They're not coming.
His mom found the racy
pictures I sent him.
"Flying out of JFK tomorrow.
Taking the morning Aer Lingus"?
A little morning "Aer Lingus"?
Isn't that what got Max in
trouble in the first place?
Okay, well, we just have
to go to the airport
and stop them.
I'll buy us plane tickets
and then return them,
like I do with shoes or Tom
Cruise does with wives.
Jackets and shoes off!
And make sure you check
all your pockets.
Don't make me shut this airport
down for a piece of gum.
This line is longer than
the movie Gone Girl.
What does TSA stand for?
"Time Stands A-still""
That's cute. Never
heard that one before.
Most people just go with
"This Sucks Ass."
Max, please don't yell out again.
People get very jumpy in airports.
Oh, what? It's not like I
screamed, "I have a bomb""
Miss, will you step over here, please?
Oh, I was kidding. I don't have a bomb.
But I have been known to... be DA bomb.
Max!
Please, please, if we step away,
we'll lose our place in line.
I know it sounds like we're
here to blow up a plane,
but we're really just here
to stop an underage kid
she had sex with from
leaving the country.
So I should just come over there now.
Yep. You just been hand-picked
to join the "I don't
trust you" dance party.
May I see your tickets?
Nice day. I like your hair.
Thanks. We're allowed to be creative
from the neck up.
Ooh! You traveling to Paris.
First-class.
In those jeans?
You got first-class tickets to Paris?
Are you insane?
My fingers did it.
It was rich girl cellular memory.
And if we're not going anywhere,
why can't we not go to Paris?
And why can't we not go to the Louvre?
And why can't we not
stay in the penthouse
Is it too late for me to
say I don't know her?
Ma'am, are you carrying any explosives?
I had leftover Chipotle for breakfast.
Does that count?
It does to whoever's
sitting next to you.
(woman, French accent)
Air France flight 113
will now begin boarding at gate 24.
Max! That's our flight.
(bad French accent)
Air France, flight 113.
Ooh! I bet on the plane,
they'll have caviar and Bellinis.
You know what won't be on the plane?
Us!
We're not going!
Have you been smoking the half joint
I have hidden in my bra?
You have a joint?
Bank account? Ha!
You went through security with pot?
I went through third grade with pot.
There he is. There's Nash.
I'm sure his mom is asking
if he can visit the cockpit
and meet the pilot.
Wow. He's young.
So young, Bruce Jenner has been a woman
for most of his life.
Nash! Please.
You can't go. Our entire lives depend on
you finishing that photo shoot.
Nash Terrence O'Brien,
you're not going anywhere.
Or I'll take you over
my knee right here.
Well, he likes that.
Well, you...
You are just loose as
a goose, aren't ya?
Again... when you're
right, you're right.
Max, let me talk to Mrs. O'Brien.
Go up to the gate.
Ask what movie they're
showing on their flight.
Okay, but if they're showing anything,
and I mean anything
from Mr. Adam Sandler...
I'm getting on the plane too.
Please. I'm begging you.
You don't know me. I'm a proud woman.
The only other time I ever begged
was to get off of P. Diddy's yacht.
I mean, a party shouldn't
be three days long.
Miss, you can save your silly breath.
I'm taking him home.
Would passenger Maeve O'Brien
please report to the gate desk?
Oh, Nash, maybe they're bumping us up
from the last coach row to the
second to the last coach row!
I knew I'd be rewarded for
not having any abortions
in spite of me circumstances.
Grab Nash... let's get out of here
while I got her distracted.
Max, you did that? How?
I no longer have the
half a joint in my bra.
You bribed an airline
employee with a joint?
Pain? Oh, you really gotta
stretch out for that.
Max, this is kidnapping.
Oh, he's not that young.
When I was his age,
I had already robbed
three Blockbuster videos.
What's Blockbuster video?
Oh, my God, I screwed a baby.
Okay. I'm gonna text Joe
and tell her we have Nash
in our custody. No, I'd better call.
That text won't play well at our trial.
I'm sorry I didn't tell
ya I was so young.
But honestly, I didn't think it mattered
since you're so immature.
I know you are, but what am I?
Okay, so Joe was really impressed
with the kidnapping, and
she gave us our jobs back.
But Nash, you've been replaced.
They found another model
who wouldn't give them
any parent trouble...
a well-hung orphan.
A well-hung orphan.
Well, the Lord gives and the Lord takes.
So what now?
Well, you go back to Ireland
and brag to your friends
about having sex with
someone who once had sex
with Axl Rose's best friend's son.
Good-bye, Max.
Later, Nash Potater.
You know, I think I'm gonna miss him.
Especially since kids eat
free at Quiznos before 6:00.
Ugh! Let's get out of here.
The only good thing about airports
is leaving them for someplace better.
Max, next time we're here,
I'm gonna take you to Paris.
Well, first take me to the bathroom.
I've had to pee since our
tram hit that pothole.
Well, at least we're gonna be
working somewhere with class.
I wonder where it is.
Joe said it's a real hub,
flagship, international.
Yeah. It's gonna be
international terminal 8!
What?
Here?
We're working here?
I've got to find out
who I brutally murdered
in a previous life and
make it up to him or her.
This sucks! The one place
no one will ever give us a ride to work!
(female announcer) Final boarding
for Air France, flight 113.
Of course it is.
Look at the bright side.
These days, most planes
don't even make it to where
they're supposed to go.
(announcer) Paging first-class
passengers Caroline Channing
and Max Black.
Those rich bitches are so lucky!
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.