Why are you wearing
a Band-Aid?
Halley bit me.
(laughs)
You got beaten up by a girl.
Hey, that's sexist.
You're right.
(laughs)
You got beaten up by a baby.
Hi.
Hey.
What you got there?
Oh, I grabbed a sandwich
at the food truck
out front.
Wait, n-now, hold on.
Tonight is Friday,
and I believe you know
what that means.
That my fun, young life took
a drastic turn somewhere?
No.
But yeah.
No, that means it's
Chinese food night.
Yeah, and you have Chinese food.
So eat it.
But I can smell your pastrami.
And we can all hear
your complaining,
so no one's happy.
It does smell good.
Oh, it is.
I had one the other day.
(stammers)
What is happening?
Everybody's supposed to be
eating Chinese food.
Well, actually,
I believe the Chinese
may have invented
the sandwich.
Their dish "rou jia mo"
literally means
"meat between bread."
So, it looks like all
of us, including Penny,
are eating Chinese food.
Except for you, Sheldon.
You're eating crow.
I'm sorry, I think
you're forgetting
that the sandwich
was invented
by John Montagu,
the Earl of Sandwich.
Oh. The truck's called
"Pearl of Sandwich."
Now I get it.
All right, that smells too good.
I got to get one of those.
And I think you're forgetting
that there are written documents
of meat between bread
being eaten in China
during the Tang dynasty.
You know what,
I'll go with you.
And then maybe we just go home.
I think you're defining
bread very loosely.
If we go down that road,
where does it end?
Well, I would say
when we go to bed,
but you talk
in your sleep.
I don't want to get into this
with you right now.
We'll talk about this
when I'm asleep.
I don't want to talk
about it when you're asleep.
How come we can't
talk about it now?
Well, because I'm eating now.
Fine. How's your moo shu?
You know what?
It's great.
Wait, look at that.
Hmm. Well, maybe the Chinese
did invent the sandwich.
I guess you were right.
Too bad no one's
around to hear it.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
I can smell that food truck
from up here.
Just close the window
if you don't like the smell.
Of course I like the smell.
It's salt and fat.
My brain may be evolved,
but my tongue still wants
to pick up a club and drag
that truck back to my cave.
So, there's something
you like,
but it's also
driving you crazy.
Been there, doing it now.
No, it-it's a distraction.
How can I focus on my work
when all I can think about is
how much I want that sandwich?
So, go get one.
I can't just give in
to every urge I have
when I have it.
That's why I have
a rigid schedule.
It's bad enough I had to
give in to my urge
to create a rigid schedule.
You know, why don't I just
go down to the food truck
and ask them to move?
Why are you
taking cash?
No reason.
Oh, this is the life.
What could be better than this?
If you weren't wearing
one of my swimsuits.
I'll give it back.
(chuckles)
You know the rule--
once it touches hiney,
it's no longer miney.
You're such a prude.
Do you know all the things
this water's touching right now?
Well, I'm relaxed enough.
Hey, Howard, look.
What's that?
Huh.
Looks like someone's drone.
Oh, no.
Do you think it was spying on us
in the hot tub?
'Cause I'm only 40% of the way
to my beach bod.
One of the propellers
is broken.
It must have crashed.
Oh. Do you think
you could fix it?
Maybe. Should we try and
track down the owner first?
Yeah, that's probably
a good idea.
Anyone lose a drone?
Looks like it's ours.
Yay, we got a drone!
Shh.
(whispers): Oh.
Yay, we got a drone.
(sighs)
The pastrami truck moved.
That is the danger
of a restaurant on wheels.
No, apparently someone
complained
to the tenants association,
and they're not allowed to park
on our street anymore.
Who would complain about
something that everyone loves?
Oh...
Did you complain
to the tenants association
about the food truck?
Yes.
And they actually
took you seriously?
Oh, the tenants association
takes every complaint seriously.
Oh, great, because I'm about
to send them an e-mail
complaining about you.
(phone chimes)
Excuse me.
Wow.
Someone should have
spell-checked.
What is going on here?
You're the tenants
association?
(laughs): You should see
the look on your face.
You might want to
tell your wife
that there's no "Y"
in "pastrami."
Okay, that ought
to do it.
I've replaced the propeller
and reattached the
gimbal controller unit.
Dude, you're like
Grey's Anatomy for robots.
Also, why isn't that a show?
I just need to see
if I can re-sync
the controls to
this old remote.
We should name it.
The drone, or your
stupid robot show?
The drone.
The show's already got
a name--
General Bot-spital.
I got it working!
(chuckles)
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Oh, oh!
Let's play William Tell.
I'll put this bowl
on my head.
See if you can knock it off
without hitting me.
You read my mind.
What are you doing?
Either breaking a bowl
or breaking Raj's head.
Be careful, they don't
make that bowl anymore.
(chuckles)
It's a nice one.
Yeah. We found it in the yard
and fixed it up.
Aren't you worried there's
some kid out there
missing his drone?
Oh, please, Bernadette,
this is not
a children's toy, okay?
This thing's got
an HD camera on it.
Okay, then aren't you worried
there's some rich
Peeping Tom out there
missing his drone?
We asked around,
and no one claimed it.
Ha. I think we've
done all we can do.
Did you check the video card?
Maybe you can see where
it started off from.
What a great idea, honey.
So, let me get
this straight.
You are the president
of the tenants association?
President, only member,
and harshest critic.
I once gave myself
an official reprimand
for conducting a meeting
in the shower.
The steam warped my gavel.
Okay, so when I got a fine
for leaving my clothes
in the dryer for too long,
that was from you?
$14.99.
The exact price of a new gavel.
And the noise complaint
we got
for singing you
"Happy Birthday"?
As a friend, I was touched.
As a representative
of the building,
I thought that you should
pick a key and stick with it.
Hi.
Do you know he is the entire
tenants association?
No, but I'm not
surprised.
He's also the pope of a planet
he invented in hyperspace.
Why didn't you tell me?
'Cause I wanted to make sure
that you loved the man,
not the office.
You can't just declare
yourself president.
I didn't.
I called a meeting,
I was the only one to attend.
I nominated myself, and after
a pretty moving speech,
I voted myself in.
Well, if you can
vote yourself in,
then we can vote you out.
Yeah.
Fine. Make a motion
at the next meeting.
When is that?
It's the first Saturday
of every month.
Unless there's
an emergency meeting.
Then we call
You really don't have to.
This is the first Saturday
of the month.
Okay, fine.
Then we vote you out.
Uh, uh, hold on.
Hold on. First,
we have to read the minutes
from last month's meeting.
Amy, would you do the honors?
Why not?
"Saturday, March 3rd.
"7:05, meeting called to order.
"7:06, president gets
shampoo in eye.
7:07, meeting adjourned."
Okay, can we
vote you out now?
Ah, very well. New business.
I move for a vote
of no confidence
in the president.
Yeah.
Two to one, you lose.
Not so fast. I believe
we have one tenant here
who has not made
her voice heard.
Oh...
We're waiting, fiancée.
Yeah, we're waiting,
best friend.
neighbor who needed a battery
and totally got one from me,
no strings attached.
I don't want to be
in the middle of this.
No matter which way I vote,
I'm either
a bad friend,
a bad fiancée,
or an ungrateful recipient
of a battery.
Next time I have a meeting
in the shower,
you're welcome to attend.
Sheldon. Sheldon for president.
I pick Sheldon!
Ugh, I can't believe my best
friend sided with Sheldon.
Can't believe my best friend
is Sheldon.
Ah, I should've taken
that gavel
and shoved it right down
this throat.
Ugh.
I would've gone the other way,
but it would've gotten
to his throat.
What?
Don't be mad at me.
I mean, I can't vote
against him.
Even when he's being crazy?
Well, what other times
are there?!
So you just let him get
away with anything?
Well, not anything.
But honestly,
pastrami sandwich
is not the hill
I want to die on.
It's not about
the sandwich.
It's about
the principle.
Yeah, principle.
And a little bit sandwich.
Yeah.
Look, there are a bunch of other
tenants in this building.
All you need is for one of them
to vote your way,
and then Sheldon's out
and I didn't betray him.
Hey, you know, that's
actually a good plan.
That you came up with
all by yourself.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
told Sheldon
I was going to the market,
so... I'm taking
some of your stuff.
I was never here.
Sometimes you don't see it
'cause she's next to Sheldon,
but she's pretty weird.
Okay. All hooked up.
Here we go.
I hope there's nothing
disturbing on there.
Like you two in a hot tub?
Hold on.
Now I'm getting a picture.
That's not very
much to go on.
Oh, that's plenty to go on.
We can't give up.
We got to find her.
You just want to find
her 'cause she's cute.
Not just because she's cute.
She also owns
a pretty expensive drone,
which means she has money
and doesn't mind wasting it.
And I... I like that in a woman.
Do you see anything that could
help us locate her?
Hmm, let me have a look.
She's got eagle eyes,
always spotting continuity
errors in movies.
(chuckles)
It's not annoying at all.
Oh. There.
Right there.
Check out the pin
on her jacket.
Isn't that from
the comic book store?
Hmm, is it?
Hey, Howard, zoom in.
Oh.
Fine. Zooming in.
(whooshes)
Yeah, I know
you're being a jerk,
but it's actually helpful.
Hi.
Hi. We're your neighbors
from downstairs.
We've met.
Remember?
I invited you to my housewarming
when I moved in.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
You know, it's been
a crazy couple months.
That was two years ago.
Welcome to the building.
Mm-hmm.
So, I-I'm running for president
of the tenants association.
I could really use your vote.
You said you were gonna stop by.
I bought a lot of food.
Anyway, meeting's tomorrow.
We really hope
you can make it.
I'll be there.
Oh, really?
Yeah. You should buy
a lot of food.
So, I'm running for president
of the tenants association
and I could really use
your vote.
Uh, who's president now?
Uh, Sheldon Cooper.
You know, about yay tall
and about yay annoying.
So you want me to vote
against Sheldon Cooper?
Yeah. You just need
to show up at a meeting...
Oh, no, no. No can do.
He's got a restraining order
against me.
Really? Why?
Uh, I locked him
on the roof once.
(whispers):
Three times.
So, Mrs. Petrescu,
we were hoping you would vote
for Leonard
instead of voting for Sheldon.
Vote Sheldon.
No, no. Vote Leonard.
No vote Leonard.
No. Vote Leonard.
Thank you.
She's wearing a pin
from your store.
Do you know who she is?
Oh, sure, yeah.
That's Cynthia.
Wha... s-so,
she's a customer?
Yeah, yeah, but I-I haven't
seen her in a while.
And before you say anything,
there is a lot of reasons
women stop coming here.
It's not just me.
But this time...
It was me. Yeah.
I was trying out
a flirty new smile.
Now, I don't use the word
"ghoulish" a lot, but...
I-I just can't think
of another word.
Wait, do you know
how to find her?
Yeah. I think I have her
address on my mailing list.
Oh. Hey. Please, let me bring
the drone back to her.
You think you've got a shot?
What if she's married?
She's not.
It's meant to be.
A little tip.
Uh, stick with the smiles
you know.
Hi. What are you doing?
Leonard and Penny are trying
to turn the tenants against me,
so they are about to see
just what kind of power
the president of
the tenants association wields.
"You must be at least this tall
to use washing machine"?
I'm gonna hang it up
higher than Leonard.
And then his clothes
will smell.
And nobody's voting for a man
with smelly clothes.
No, not when there's
a perfectly unscented
incumbent on the ballot.
Sheldon, I have
an advanced degree
in the study of
the human brain,
so if my fiancé
is a raving lunatic,
it's kind of a ding
on my reputation.
If leaders
just stepped aside
every time they didn't have
the consent of the governed,
what would we have?
Democracy.
Not on my watch.
Okay. Don't be weird.
Don't be weird.
(deep voice):
Hello.
Hey. You found my drone.
(normal voice):
Yeah, yeah. Yes.
It took a while
to track you down,
but to see the look on
your face, it was worth it.
Aw, that's sweet.
Rajesh.
Cynthia.
Ah, pleasure to meet you.
Likewise.
I-I feel like I should give you
a reward or something.
Oh, oh, no, you don't
have to do that.
No, I insist.
How about your
phone number?
Give me your phone.
Thanks. So, I'll-I'll
call you, Cynthia.
Great, Rajesh.
(both chuckle)
And thanks again.
Uh, sure.
(phone rings)
Just checking.
(knocking, door opens)
Hey, Sheldon.
We found something
pretty interesting.
Huh. Well, that is surprising.
I, for one, have no idea
what they're talking about.
Turns out, when Amy took over
Penny's apartment,
she was put on the lease,
not you.
PENNY: Yeah, and when I
moved across the hall,
you got taken off the
lease and I got added.
Well, what are you saying?
That Sheldon's not
technically a tenant at all
and therefore,
has no standing to be president
of the tenants association
no matter who votes for him?
I don't know
how you found that out,
but I am guessing
all on your own.
So, looks like
we need to figure out
who the new president
should be.
I nominate myself.
I second it.
Huh.
Well, as a woman in love,
I want to stand by my man.
Too bad that's been rendered
bureaucratically impossible.
Well, this is hard for me
because I do love
a legal technicality
and this is a good one.
Although, not quite as good as
the provision in California law,
which states a person
who occupies a dwelling
for 30 consecutive days becomes
a tenant at will and as such...
I vote for Leonard!
You...
What?
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
With minimal power comes
minimal responsibility,
and you couldn't handle it.
Don't you misquote Spider-Man
to me.
It's not your fault.
I mean, what man
wouldn't be seduced
by the power to decide how late
the laundry room stays open?
Wait, you're the reason
I had to come back
and get my jeans
the next morning?
I can't believe you expect
me to give that up.
Sheldon,
it's the American way,
the peaceful transfer
of power.
I don't know.
Think about Ant-Man.
I'm always thinking
about Ant-Man.
Michael Douglas had the suit
and then he passed it on
to Paul Rudd.
Maybe you're right.
Really?
The Ant-Man thing?
That's what won you over?
Yes. He got the details right.
That's how you use
a superhero.
Mm.
I suppose it is time I
passed this on to Leonard.
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks.
I-I know that's hard for you.
Well, it was.
But you know what?
Instead of being in charge,
I can now be
the vocal opposition,
criticizing and badgering
the president at every turn.
I think you'll be
really good at that.
Me, too.
I think I've made
a huge mistake.
Me, too.
Can't believe you
got her number.
I know, right?
How amazing would it be
if this worked out
and the story
of how I met my wife
started with you and me
in the hot tub together.
Well, do us both a favor
and start the story later.
Whatever.
I have a good feeling
about this girl.
Like, we really hit it off.
Stop flying it around.
You're gonna break it.
Why do you care?
Because we have to give it back
to the beautiful mystery girl.
Aw.
I mean, did you see
how hot she was?
I want to get all up on that
and start making babies!
I know exactly what underwear
I'm gonna wear
on our first date.
None!