Previously
OnWhy Women Kill...
I've been accepted
into the Garden Club.
You shouldn't be here.
I was invited. I-I'm
the new member.
No, we-we voted.
Oh, dear.
I am so terribly
sorry for the mix-up.
Rita deliberately
humiliated me today.
Is that Rita?
- Do you know her?
- What Rita did...
It's not 'cause she hates you.
- It's 'cause she hates me.
Good morning,
it's Dr. Rice.
Are you aware you're pregnant?
I'm his girl.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
You murdered 26 people?!
You've got to stop this
madness. Promise me.
I think this is what Alma was
- talking to me about.
- Listen to her.
Why are you so anxious to spend
time with an old lady like me?
You're a dame who doesn't
know how beautiful she is.
Oh, Papa, you must
be getting your strength back.
I think he's
pointing at something.
He couldn't possibly.
Is there
something on the board?
Oh! Ah!
You can trust
me with your secrets.
You and Scooter.
No one will hear a
word about it from me.
Threaten me again, and
this will be your family.
From the
moment Alma Fillcot
decided to join the
Elysian Park Garden Club,
she began to change.
But her husband was
completely oblivious
to her stylish transformation.
He had no idea she'd
begun to polish her nails.
He had not noticed how elegantly
she was wearing her hair.
And he paid no attention to
her new shade of lipstick.
It was unfortunate.
If Bertram had noticed
these changes in Alma
he might have been prepared
for what happened next.
Shall I take you
straight to the clinic?
Yes, yes. I have an
early appointment.
Hmm. Very well.
Since we have a moment,
there is something that
I would like to discuss.
Well, what's that?
- Your little hobby.
- Ah.
- Hmm.
- That's funny.
'Cause I've been doing some
thinking about that myself.
You know, I regret
some of the words
that I've hurled at you
in the last few weeks.
Sick, psychopathic, demented.
You were only trying to
alleviate the suffering
of some people who
were already dying.
I see now that you're a hero.
I'm
con... I'm confused.
I couldn't comprehend it before
because I didn't know
any of those people.
But now I understand,
because I'm aware of someone
who is desperately in
need of the kind of help
that only you can supply.
Wh... What are you saying?
There's someone
that you want me to...
Oh, yes.
And you'd be doing
God's work, my love.
My hero.
Who exactly are
we talking about?
You know Rita Castillo?
She came to our house
with the Garden Club?
Yes. Yes, I treat her cat.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is she ill?
Oh, no.
No, but, um
she has a husband.
His name is Carlo and
he's in so much pain.
Yes, Alma
Fillcot had truly changed.
But by the time her
husband could see it
it was too late.
At the exact same moment
Alma Fillcot was asking her
husband to kill Carlo Castillo,
his wife was doing some
diabolical plotting of her own.
Phone for you, Mrs. Castillo.
- Hello?
- Hey, gorgeous.
- It's me.
- It's about time you called.
How'd your date go
with you know who?
- Swell, if I do say so myself.
- Good.
Because I need you to
screw her... tonight.
Tonight?
Carlo is starting
to communicate.
He even tried to warn
Catherine about you.
I need that compromising
photo as soon as possible.
She's a church-going spinster.
She's not going put
out on the second date.
Well, then get her drunk.
Tell her you love her.
I don't care how
you do it, just...
Just, just make it happen.
Goodbye.
You ended that
call awfully fast.
Who was it?
Your secret lover?
For a woman who
dresses like a nun,
you certainly have
a filthy mind.
Hello?
Oh.
It's for you.
- Hello?
- Hey, Catherine. It's me.
You got any plans tonight?
I thought maybe we
could grab some dinner.
It would be lovely to see
you, but I'm busy tonight.
What about tomorrow night?
You can't say no to that.
It's, uh... my birthday?
Well...
I-I don't want you to be
alone on your birthday.
So, shall we say 6:00?
It's a date.
Are you serious?
You really want me to
kill Carlo Castillo?
I-I want you to help him.
Isn't that the term you prefer?
Yes, and every time I've
used it, you've corrected me.
So, what's changed?
Well, I saw him for myself.
He can't move or
feed himself or bathe.
When did you see him?
Last night, at Rita's.
Sounds like you two
have grown close.
Oh, yes.
She's become a good chum.
Did she get you into
the Garden Club?
Rita tried.
The other ladies
voted for Ada Coy.
Ah, Alma.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's fine.
I only wanted to get in
so that I could make some
new friends, and now I have.
Rita's really gone out of
her way to be kind to me,
even while dealing with
a crippled husband.
Did she come to you about this?
Why would she?
It's not as if I go around
advertising your services.
So... you'll help him?
Alma.
While I was away on my trip,
I had a bit of an epiphany.
An epiphany?
I realized I'd only been ending
the suffering of others
to ease my own pain.
My actions were more
selfish than merciful.
So I vowed to never do it again.
And you won't.
After you help Carlo,
you'll put away your
trusty syringes forever.
I'm sorry, Alma.
The answer is no.
I should go.
Bertram!
We're not done discussing this.
Alma, my mind is made up.
There's nothing you
can do to change it.
Hey, Dee.
Hey. Thanks for meeting me.
Come here.
I-Is something wrong?
Is everything all right?
You sounded so
strange on the phone.
Yeah.
I've gotten myself
into a situation.
Okay, well, we-we can
go somewhere and we can
- talk about it, right?
- Oh, I can't.
And I'm really sorry
to spring this on you.
I, I like you so much.
More than you know, but
we can't see each other anymore.
Why not?
I can't say.
Did I do something?
Oh, God, no.
This has nothing to do
with you. I promise.
Well, whatever it is,
we-we can talk about it.
Like we always do.
You're such a good guy, Vern.
And I think you deserve all
the happiness in the world.
Wait, Dee.
Dee!
Oh, hello there.
Hey, Grace.
What a surprise.
What is going on?
Oh, I
just thought my garden could
use a little spiffing up.
Oh, yeah, well, I understand.
New projects help us take
our minds off our troubles.
Oh. Well, that's not the only
new project I'm working on.
Hmm?
Believe you me. Tea?
I still don't know why
Rita treated you so badly.
I asked all the
ladies in the club
if they knew something I didn't.
Any theories?
No.
But she's always been
a very unhappy person.
- Mm.
- Not surprised,
- given who she's married to.
- What does that mean?
Apparently,
Carlo was something of an ogre.
Before he had the stroke,
he used to beat Rita.
- That is just awful.
- Mm-hmm.
Please... go on.
Look at that.
It's been ages since
you baked a cherry pie.
Yes, well,
I wanted to do something special
to apologize for this morning.
Oh, when you asked
me to help Carlo?
Yes.
You see, I-I wasn't
completely honest with you.
I held back some
important details.
That was wrong of me. I'm sorry.
What details are
you referring to?
Well
the truth is, I don't
care about Carlo at all.
In fact, I think he deserves
every bit of pain that he's in.
Well, if that's
the way you feel,
why would you want me
to hasten his death?
Because I care about Rita.
Oh, Bertie.
Carlo is an awful man.
He used to beat her. Savagely.
Rita wept when she
spoke of his cruelty.
That's horrible.
Thank God he can't
hurt her anymore.
Yes, but now she has
to take care of him.
And can you imagine?
Being forced to
nurse your tormentor?
She's so unhappy.
Drinking and neglecting
her own health.
I fear that she might
die before Carlo does.
That poor woman.
But you could help her.
Oh, Bertram.
You want to. I know you do.
You can't ignore that
kind of suffering.
All I'm asking for
is one final act of mercy.
Please.
Save my friend.
All right.
I'll do it.
Oh...
Bless you, Bertie.
You know what would
be nice on this pie?
- Some ice cream.
- Mm.
- Sounds delicious.
- Doesn't it?
Mmm.
Are you glad to be back?
You know I am.
Ah, hey, look.
It's our old pal Mr. Murphy.
Oh.
I forgot there was a
fire escape here.
This is the perfect place
for my photographer to hide.
I hope he's patient.
It's going to take a lot
of booze during dinner
to get Catherine back
here for dessert.
You may want to knock
a few back yourself.
You'll have to be drunk
to jump those old bones.
She's not so bad.
Excuse me?
Oh, I thought she was an
old pickle-puss at first,
but once she lets
her guard down,
she's actually got
a really nice smile.
And she's only... what?
Five years older than you?
You know
this seduction doesn't have
to end in consummation.
Aw, I thought that
was the whole point.
No. The photo is the point.
Once Catherine is
naked and on her back,
you'll have hit the high note.
No need to sing
the entire opera.
You're jealous.
Of her?
Don't be preposterous.
You know, I have missed
this old murphy bed.
What do you say
we rechristen it?
Why? So I have nothing left
in the tank for Catherine?
How devious do you think I am?
You've been to the gym
this morning, haven't you?
Oh, what gave it
away, the muscles?
No, the smell.
You need a shower.
Oh.
Well, give me five.
And-and keep the motor running.
You the manager here?
I'm looking for a
guy who lived in 3B.
I thought maybe he left
a forwarding address
where he can be reached.
You talking about Scooter?
He moved back in this morning.
He did?
Oh. Ah.
Well, thanks.
Oh, it's you.
Is Scooter here?
I thought you were
done with him.
Something's happened.
And it's very important
I speak to him.
Please.
Oh, my God. You're pregnant.
You can tell?
Oh, it's all over your face.
That and some
fairly cheap makeup.
Nice.
Oh, before I forget, I have a
message for you from my mom.
You get all that?
Or do I need to repeat it?
You know what?
I'll come back later
when Scoot can talk.
Are you, uh, sure
you want to tell him?
How can I not?
It's his baby.
Well, what are you hoping for?
That he'll tell
you he loves you?
Because he doesn't.
And what if he decides to do
the right thing and marry you?
You'd have two infants to
take care of instead of one.
Scooter is not ready
to be a father.
Or a husband.
Hell, he can barely
cut it as a boyfriend.
I do not want to marry Scooter.
But I don't got a
lot of choices here.
You'll think of something.
You're too smart to
let one stupid mistake
ruin the rest of your life.
Congrats.
He's all yours.
Thank you.
You know, if you
need some money...
Who was that at the door?
Just a door-to-door salesman.
What were they selling?
Nothing we need.
Mmm.
- Delicious.
- Hmm.
You made my cocoa just
the way I like it.
Thank you, my darling.
You're very welcome, Bertie.
Say, how are you
at housebreaking?
What's that?
You know, picking
locks and all that?
I think it's best
if you visit Carlo
late at night when
everyone's asleep.
But have you ever broken
into a locked house before?
Well, I mean, usually,
when I drop in on someone
to help them, they
just open the door.
Unless they're
too ill to get up,
and then I find a way in.
You're so clever.
Now, it is a very,
very big house.
And so, I have made you a map.
Oh. Many is the time I could
have used one of these.
Yes. So, Carlo's room is here.
Up the stairs, take a right.
Last one on the
left, not the right.
- That's Rita's bedroom.
- Right.
Now, the front door
is very, very solid,
but if you come around the back,
there are French doors
that lead into the foyer.
- Is that easier?
- Oh, much.
Hmm. Now, will you have
to break the glass?
No. No. I can't leave any
signs of forced entry.
I'd just be asking
for an autopsy.
And if the police
did do an autopsy,
would they find the
drug that you use?
They'd have to be
looking for it.
And they wouldn't be unless
they suspected foul play.
- Hmm.
- And it's never happened.
My
record is spotless.
26 deaths, each ruled
to be by natural causes.
- That's quite an accomplishment.
- Oh, thank you, darling.
You know, it seems odd
getting compliments
for something I hid
from you for many years.
I think it's good that
I know these things.
Makes our marriage stronger.
Yes, it does.
- Yes.
Mmm. Mmm.
You want me to
photograph your lover
screwing your stepdaughter?
If you try hard enough, you
can make anything sound sordid.
Boy, you are a piece of work.
This is completely justified.
That crone has had it
in for me since day one.
I have to fight back.
By using your own
gigolo as bait?
It's not like he hasn't
cheated on me before.
At least he won't get
this one pregnant.
Pregnant?
Remember that large
girl he was seeing?
She showed up at his place
today to give him the bad news.
The... the waitress?
She's having a baby?
I convinced her not
to tell Scooter.
She's not so dumb that she can't
see he'd make a lousy father.
So, if you're not going
to take the photo,
can you refer someone who will?
Did I say I wouldn't do it?
You haven't even
made me an offer yet.
Oh.
So, your disgust can be
overcome for the right price?
Some days money doesn't
mean a lot to me.
Lucky for you, this
isn't one of them.
That's it. Open up
and chew slowly.
Catherine.
Your friend from the dry
cleaner is downstairs.
Thanks.
Do you want one more fry
before I leave, Papa?
What's wrong?
Are you full?
Why are you mad?
Because I'm going
out for dinner?
That's silly.
I need to start
enjoying my life.
You know, I'm not 23 anymore.
I'll vouch for that.
I won't be too late.
I'll tuck you in when
I come home. Hmm?
She's going to have sex tonight.
With a man you don't approve of.
If you hadn't threatened
to disinherit her,
I wouldn't have anything
to blackmail her with.
But now I can scare her
all the way back to Texas.
And then it's just you and me.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
I hear this is
their best chianti.
But why
buy the whole bottle?
We won't be able
to drink it all.
Oh, we got to try.
It's my birthday.
That's right.
I almost forgot.
- Oh, you got me a gift?
- Just a small token, really.
Those are real diamonds.
Catherine.
This is too expensive.
No.
Didn't cost me a cent.
I bought them years
ago for another man.
Do you like them?
I love them.
I'm so glad.
This is shaping up to be
my best birthday ever.
Oh.
So I don't get expensive
gifts for Papa anymore
because I know they're going
to end up going to Rita.
Now, that's your stepmother?
I guess you never
liked her, huh?
Well, actually, we
used to be friends,
right when she and
Papa got engaged.
She was nice back then.
But right after the wedding,
that's when Rita
showed her true colors.
- She wasn't so nice anymore?
- Mm.
No. You see...
Rita can be sweet as pie
as long as she needs you,
but once she no
longer needs you...
You're out on your ass.
I should powder my nose.
Excuse me.
You want to hurry it up, Romeo?
It's almost midnight.
You must be the guy Rita
hired to take the photo.
And I hope I'm doing my job half
as well as you're doing yours.
Excuse me?
I've been watching you work.
If I didn't already
know the plan,
I'd swear you had a
yen for that broad.
He left it for
Catherine to find.
Yeah.
She told him she'd check on
him when she gets home tonight.
I'm just glad you
found it first.
What are we going to do?
Well, we need to keep
him away from all lawyers
and condiments.
This is no joke.
I'm worried.
Once we have the photo,
Catherine will go back home.
Trust me.
She does not want
to be disinherited.
So, what if we get rid of her?
Carlo heard you with
Scooter the night he fell.
If he tells someone
he wants a divorce...
And how's he going to do that?
He can't talk.
For now.
What if he gets his voice back?
Wh-What, what if
he gets to a phone
when one of us isn't looking?
We might not know until a lawyer
shows up with divorce papers.
Then what?
Well, then I'm screwed.
Not just you.
If you lose your home,
I lose mine, too.
Let's not panic.
Once Catherine is gone,
it'll just be the three of us
in this house, and we can
watch him like a hawk.
Sedate him
if we have to.
Or
We can kill him.
Isabel.
We've gotten away
with it before.
Are you ready?
Why are you dressed like that?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm going with you.
No, no. That wasn't
part of the plan.
It's far too risky.
What's risky is sending
you into Rita's house
without a lookout.
I won't go inside.
I'll stay in the car and
keep watch, just in case.
Well, I suppose
that'll be all right.
Now, don't forget your coat.
It's chilly out.
We can't have you
catching your death.
What?
It's just nice to know that
you still worry about me.
Makes me feel like
we're back to normal.
Of course we're back
to normal.
I think I saw your coat
on a chair in the kitchen.
- Go get it.
- Yes.
- Dee.
I've been meaning to call you.
How are you doing?
Everything okay?
Not really. You got a minute?
Look around.
I got all the time in the world.
What's up?
You remember last summer?
You told me about
your predicament.
Well...
It seems I'm now
in the same boat.
No.
Have you told your parents?
I'm thinking maybe they
won't need to know.
If I do what you did.
Remember, I had no choice.
My folks would have disowned me.
And the guy I was seeing
was married, so...
Tell me about the
place you went.
St. Anne's?
It was nice.
They took good care of me.
What was it like?
When you gave birth?
The doctors gave me
something for the pain,
so it's a bit hazy.
I remember one of the nuns
said not to look at the baby
when it came out.
That it would be too painful.
But I looked anyway.
It was a boy.
He looked just like me. I think.
They took him away so quick.
Do you know what
happened to him?
My little guy was adopted
by a family in Utah.
They got money, a big
house with a yard.
It makes me feel good
knowing he traded up.
Ever think about him?
What do you think?
But the good news is,
I graduate secretarial
school in May,
and my folks will be
there to cheer me on.
No. I made the right decision.
It's getting late.
I should go.
If you do decide to
go to St. Anne's,
can I give you some advice?
Sure.
Listen to the nuns.
Don't look at it.
I'm telling you, it's the
only way to protect yourself.
You don't think I've thought
about killing Carlo before?
I came this close to drowning
him in the tub last month.
Then why didn't you?
It's not worth the risk.
I say it is.
We shot Harry. Look
how that paid off.
Elysian Park is not Galveston.
And Carlo's not some violent
brute no one will miss.
I'm not saying we shoot him.
There are poisons we could buy.
Something undetectable.
Yeah, and if the
police get suspicious?
Then we run, like before.
- We change our names.
- No.
I don't want to change
my identity again.
I've spent the last ten
years perfecting this one.
Ooh, God. My head is spinning.
Oh. You're drunk.
We're not going to
solve this tonight.
We can talk
about it tomorrow.
Just promise me,
no matter what happens,
you won't leave me.
I promise. I won't.
Good.
I love you, Isabel.
I love you too, cousin.
There's still
a light on upstairs.
That's Rita's dressing room.
Let's hope she's
not a night owl.
Are you hungry?
I brought us some
snacks and cocoa.
The taking of a human life
is a grave and sacred task.
It's not a night
at the drive-in.
This isn't frivolous.
You know how you get when
your blood sugar drops.
Yes. I'm sorry.
I'm a bit nervous about Carlo.
I'm just not sure what
his reaction will be.
He'll probably be a bit scared.
He might be a little
bit startled at first.
But, you know, you
have such a warm smile.
I'm sure you'll put
him right at ease.
Thank you, Alma.
I'm glad you're here
to tell me that.
Me, too.
Chocolate chip cookie?
Oh, go on then,
just one.
Yes.
I had a lovely evening, Scooter.
Oh, does it have to be over?
We could swing by my
place for a nightcap.
Oh, I had too much
to drink already.
I'm not sure I can trust myself.
Don't you trust me?
Even less.
It's been wonderful,
but I do think
you need to take me home now.
Ah...
Ah, hang on a sec.
I... I-I think
- I left something at the table.
- Okay.
Change of plans.
She wants me to take her home.
Are you calling it off?
What am I supposed to do?
Drag her back to my place?
Rita expects a photo
in the morning.
How do you think she'll
react if we don't deliver?
Oh, geez.
Okay.
Follow me back to Rita's place.
I'll try to get
something started there.
It's off. Rita's light is off.
Here we go. Wish me luck.
Here. When you get
into Carlo's room,
just give me a signal
- through the window.
- Why?
So I know that you made
it upstairs safely.
Just shine your
flashlight out the window.
- Oh.
- All right? Yeah, okay.
Bye. Good luck.
And if anything happens
downstairs, let me know.
How will I do that?
Honk the horn.
We're having quite an
adventure, aren't we?
Yes. We're like
Bonnie and Clyde.
- But with cookies.
- Yes.
You're awake.
I'm sorry to startle you.
I'm not sure if
you'll remember me.
I'm Dr. Fillcot.
Your vet.
What?
I know you're
in a great deal of pain.
And I'm here to relieve
you of your suffering.
Perhaps we'll start
with a sedative.
Boy. How about that wind?
I think a storm is coming.
My hair is frightful.
Make yourself at home.
I'll only be a moment.
Did you hear something?
You said, "Make
yourself at home."
Scooter, really.
I'm old enough to
be your mother.
You're never too
old to have fun.
Why do you want to
have fun with me?
Let's face it.
I'm not a great beauty.
I'm lonely, okay?
You seem like
you're lonely, too.
Yes.
I am lonely.
And rich.
If having money means
you can't trust anyone,
that you can't accept
love when offered
then what good is it?
There's no need
to be frightened.
It'll all be over so soon.
I want your last
moments to be serene.
- And beautiful.
Oh. Did the lightning
startle you?
I'm so sorry.
So, you
really like me?
Of course I do.
You're the nicest person
I've met in this town.
I'm not that nice.
Come on.
You're a doll.
You treat me like I'm somebody,
and the sweet way you
take care of your dad.
Oh, I hate my papa.
Even more since I met you.
You make me remember
everything he took from me.
When I still had
something to offer.
I know what it feels like to
think you've missed the boat.
That it's too late
to get what you want.
Maybe it is.
Or maybe it isn't.
Bertram.
Alma, what are you doing?
There are two people downstairs.
I don't know who they are.
Why didn't you honk the horn?
I did. You must just
not have heard it.
Oh. Is it done?
Yes, his suffering has ended.
Which is more than
can be said for mine.
That old man grabbed me.
Will you stop complaining.
We need to get out
of here. Come on.
There were two people talking
in the living room earlier.
A man and a woman.
Well, they're not talking now.
Are they there?
Shh.
Maybe the wind
will distract them.
They don't need any more
distracting. Come on.
Rise and shine, Papa.
The clouds are gone.
It's a glorious day, Papa.
Papa?
Papa!
We have to talk.
Yeah. Yeah, I'd like to talk.
I'm ashamed of
how I left things.
Now, just forget about it.
No, I have to explain.
The truth is, I...
I'm in so much trouble.
And lately it's felt like
you're my best
friend in the world.
So, I'm back.
Because I trust you to
give me good advice.
See, the...
The thing I couldn't
tell you was...
You're pregnant.
How?
I am a detective.
Oh, Vern.
What am I gonna do?
Here's a thought.
Marry me.
What?
Look, if you're just trying
to be a good guy here...
No. That's not what this is.
But you'd be raising
another man's baby.
With the woman I love.
Oh, Vern.
Are you absolutely sure?
Oh, yeah.
I've given it a lot of thought.
In fact...
I bought this for
you last night.
I hope it's okay.
Sorry for being so blunt.
I probably should have had
a fancy speech prepared.
But...
But if you'll have me...
I guess that's a yes, huh?
Oh. That's more than a yes.
That's a "you betcha."
Hello.
Yes, hello.
My name is Mary Booth.
I live in your neighborhood.
I drove by your home
and saw the ambulance.
I was concerned.
Did something happen
to Mr. Castillo?
Yes.
My father died last night.
Oh, no.
Well, um...
This is just awful of me to ask,
but do you know how he died?
What do you mean?
Well, I was in a café last week,
and I overheard his wife Rita
saying the most awful
things about him
and the money that she
expected to inherit.
Uh, "Any day now" was
the phrase that she used.
When you said that he'd died,
the hairs on the back of
my neck just stood up.
I...
Maybe it's wrong of me,
but I felt that I had
to say something.
No.
It's a good thing you called.