Previously on "The Originals"...
Klaus: This town was my
home once. I want it back.
- You mean, you don't recognize me?
- It's been a long time, Finn.
- I'm Kaleb.
- Davina.
- Esther.
- I have come to heal our family.
What could possibly
be more important
than the return of our mother?
Our father.
I saw him.
He was enslaved with some
spell cast by Davina.
Aah!
Release me.
[Kaleb chanting]
Let's finish this.
Aagh!
Elijah: Perhaps your next body
will last a little longer
than this one, brother.
Ugh...
Ohh...
What do you want?
I only want us
to be a family, Elijah.
[Hayley panting]
[Hayley whimpers]
Uh! No.
No!
Agh!
[Panting]
Lenore: Have you forgotten
where you are, son?
Save your strength.
My chains don't break so easily.
Having sweet dreams?
Get out of my head.
I'm not in your head, dear.
You were screaming.
Go ahead.
Get your bearings.
We have much to discuss.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/
who were you dreaming
about ripping apart
when you woke earlier?
Was it your new little
plaything Hayley,
or was it someone else?
Stop fighting, Elijah.
I brought you here to listen,
and you're not going anywhere
until I've said my piece.
So speak.
I want you to rejoin
our family but as a witch.
I want you to leave behind
the grotesque savage
vampirism has made of you.
Take the body of a mortal, and
we can all be happy again,
start over.
You do know you're entirely
demented, don't you?
Am I?
I'm not the one who
pulls the wings
off every beautiful
butterfly that he finds,
like the woman who flits
across the edge
of your nightmares.
You let me go now.
How quickly you slip back
into your more savage self.
The moral son I raised
is now but a mask
worn to hide ancient demons.
You know nothing.
See, that's where you're wrong.
I know more about the secrets
you carry than you do.
Shall I list them?
I can begin with the first
little butterfly you destroyed,
the sweet young widow
from our village
who caught your eye
when you were still human.
Ah, you remember her.
Of course.
How could you forget
the first girl
to ever steal your heart,
she of mystical blood,
the doppelganger Tatia?
I did nothing
but love that woman
till the day you took her life.
I know that's what you believe,
which is precisely
why you are here.
I need to show you the
monster you really are.
When I do, you will
beg for salvation,
and happily, I shall provide it.
[Music playing]
Lenore, voice-over:
It was Samhain, when we danced
and killed the best
of our livestock
to appease the gods
for a new season.
All women envied her.
All men wanted her,
but she only had eyes for one.
Tatia: Do not tell me you came
to save loki the pig
from his fate.
No. I'm afraid loki the pig
is fated to be food...
Just as you are fated
to love another.
And you fated to watch from the
shadows, the noble martyr?
Fate does not dictate
my heart, Elijah.
I was fated to throw
myself on a pyre
after my husband died in
battle, but I did not.
I chose to live, and I chose
to give my heart once more
to someone strong, protective,
fierce, and yet
noble and gentle.
I choose you, Elijah...
And you choose to
have our first kiss
where your mother
slaughters the pigs.
Not very romant...
Perhaps we should set
loki the pig free.
Seems one's fate can
change after all.
But that was just the beginning,
a brief moment of happiness.
That is how it always begins.
A butterfly lands
upon your finger
unaware that it will lead
to her tragic end.
Her tragic end came when you
drained her body of blood...
All for a spell
to smother the wolf
within Niklaus,
as memory serves.
Actually, Elijah,
your memory doesn't serve you at all.
You just don't realize it yet,
but by the time
we are done here...
You will.
We should get her to a hospital.
Oh, hello, darling.
Back to huff and puff
and blow the house down?
You know, it's funny how often
a person's sharp tongue
can end up cutting
their own throat.
Klaus, he's just a kid.
Give him a break.
Kaleb: Yeah. She's right.
You might want to try a bit of
lavender under your pillow.
Does wonders for stuck-up
pillocks with anger issues.
Hey, shut it.
I promised not to kill Davina.
I said nothing
of this insolent sod.
Klaus, come on.
A minute ago, you had
the opportunity
to kill your father with
this thing, and you didn't.
You're not gonna kill
this kid with it either.
Fine.
Thank you.
Go get the car.
Let's take her to the hospital.
You've got a way with words.
Well, I've traveled.
You seem to have
crossed continents
in order to weasel your way
into Davina's good graces,
thereby meddling
in my family business.
Strange, isn't it,
unless, of course,
it's your family business.
Ever since my dinner
with my mother and Finn,
I've been wondering when you
might make an appearance, Kol.
[Chuckles]
Well, the jig is up.
Hello, brother.
It's not that I begrudge you
hitching a ride back to
the land of the living.
It's just that you're making
all the wrong friends,
brother, and I have half a mind
to show you how wrong you are.
But you're not gonna
do that, are you,
because your little,
blonde friend
told you to leave me alone.
I'm curious.
Does she take one of those
little plastic baggies out
when she takes you for a walk?
Cami, I've changed my mind.
I am gonna kill him, after all.
Cami...
Elijah, where are you?
Mikael is loose with the stake,
and Cami is a hostage,
and I'm weaponless and in need
of reinforcement urgently.
Wake her up.
Tell her to get Mikael
back here now.
Let me think about that.
No, but you should
probably get going, Nik.
Mikael is probably jonesing for
a restorative snack about now.
Be a shame for you to find...
Cami, is it?...
Nothing more than
a bloodless husk.
We're not done, you and I.
It'd be really useful if
you woke up about now.
I've kicked a few
familial hornets nests.
We really need to scarper.
[Cell phone rings]
[Ring]
[Beep]
Did you have to do that?
I despise voice mail.
Do you have the white oak stake?
Hit a bit of a snag, truthfully.
Is that what you would
like for me to pass along?
Tell her that I've got
everything under control.
I'm keeping an eye on Davina.
She's working on a spell
to unlink her mates
from Klaus' sire lines
so that she can kill him
without them dying, too.
I'm sure the stake will
come back into play
when she's ready.
How close is she
to completing the spell?
Well, she's joined
mother's linking
and sire bond spells in reverse.
Quite clever, really.
Huh. What's she using
as a binder?
I'm not sure.
Still trying to work
that one out.
Work harder.
Mother needs Klaus
alive and connected.
So may I suggest that if
you can't find that stake,
you either kill the girl's
spell or you kill that girl.
Klaus will find you.
Oh, he will, but
I will be ready.
How? I've seen the kind
of pain that blade causes.
I have fought through more pain
than anyone living or dead,
but once I feed,
I shall be restored.
Not on you.
You, my dear, are leverage.
Once I threaten to dismember you
in front of him, Klaus
will hesitate,
and in that moment of
weakness, I shall end him.
This is crazy, the two of you
going round and round
trying to kill each other.
You're obsessing over
the death of someone
whose fatal flaw is he was
fathered by another guy.
Hush!
You are the enabler of the weak.
No wonder he seeks your company.
What?
I hear music, and where
there's music, there's food.
[Music playing]
Aah...
Well, well, well, well.
What have we here?
Hillbilly Halloween.
How perfect.
[Creak]
Used kandahar root as a binder.
Where'd you find that?
[Speaking]
Oh...
What happened?
Davina, you're awake.
I was starting
to freak out. You ok?
My head.
Klaus?
Angry bloke with
the deadly aim? Yeah.
He smashed the place up,
and then he left.
Where'd he go?
To hunt down your
pet serial killer friend.
Listen. Not to be
Mr. judgmental here,
but I'm starting to question
the company that you keep.
The white oak stake?
It's gone, I'm afraid.
The serial killer one took it.
Mikael? Mikael.
Mikael.
Why isn't this working?
Sit... sit down, all right?
You were out for
quite a long time.
Maybe that's got
something to do with it.
Here. Have some water.
No.
You don't understand.
If Mikael is free,
he can kill Klaus,
and then my friends die, too.
Well, if I understand all
this, Mikael has been trying
to kill Klaus for eons.
How are you gonna stop him?
I'm not.
I need to finish my spell now.
[Hayley clears throat]
So those werewolf kids
you helped get
out of the quarter made it
to the safe house up north.
Great. My good deed
for the decade.
No. I'm good.
Maybe the vampires
and us free wolves
can work together, after all.
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend.
Anyway, thanks for helping.
Mm. Don't thank me.
Thank Elijah.
I would've, but I can't
get a hold of him.
I went to the compound
thinking he'd be there.
Really? I thought you
always had tabs on him.
We haven't really been on
the best terms lately.
He wouldn't just
disappear, though.
Last I knew, he was gonna
keep the wolves distracted.
Your boy Oliver
was gonna help him.
I couldn't track down
Oliver either.
If they're both missing...
Where are you going?
To find them.
Not on your own, you're not.
Lenore: You're hungry,
aren't you?
It's been hours since you fed.
What an awful thing, to feed
upon the blood of others.
For this I blame myself
and your father.
We tried to make
you children strong,
but instead we cursed you all.
[Birds calling]
Brother?
What am I?
How many...?
Six.
You slaughtered 6
villagers, brother.
You tore them apart as if
they were nothing at all.
[Stammers]
Brother...
What have I become?
You seem like the wolves
in the village.
Cursed to turn
when the moon is full.
Listen to me.
Father is beside
himself with rage.
It seems this...
Affliction can only be passed
by some kind of conception.
And do our siblings
share this affliction?
Do you...
Share this affliction?
No...
I don't.
He is not my father, is he?
You listen to me.
This changes nothing
for any of us.
We are here for you as we
shall be always, mm-hmm?
Tatia. Tatia!
I fail to see your point here.
I compelled Tatia to forget
what she saw, and she did.
You'd only been a vampire
for a few days.
You hadn't yet learned
compulsion.
No...
I remember that clearly.
Do you?
You still thought there were
lines you wouldn't cross,
people you wouldn't hurt,
things you wouldn't do.
But you were wrong.
That is what I'm here
to show you.
[Rapid footsteps]
Elijah: Tatia!
Tatia! Tatia!
Wait! Wait.
Stay away from me.
I won't hurt you.
What have you become?
I am who I've always been.
I'm the one who loves you.
Lenore: You knew how
special she was.
I always thought you
would protect her,
that she would be your wife,
that one day I might
call her daughter.
Instead...
I didn't hurt her.
You've taught yourself
to hide from who
and what you are for
thousands of years.
No.
I did not hurt Tatia.
I could not.
But you did.
Your mother asked for my blood.
She said nothing of
the dark magic
that would turn you
into a monster.
Look at me.
I am not a monst...
Tatia.
Oh, my beautiful
boy, no more hiding.
It is time now for you
to remember it all.
Tatia: No! No!
I said I wouldn't hunt you.
And I don't want t...
Elijah.
Run.
You didn't want to hurt her.
You loved her.
No! Ugh!
Lenore: But you couldn't
fight what you had become,
what I had turned you into...
[Tatia gasping]
A predator...
And she became your prey.
This was you.
You murdered her
for her blood...
And then used it to cripple
Klaus for centuries.
I won't listen to another word.
You don't have to listen, son.
All you have to do is remember.
Did you honestly think
to hold me
with a blade forged for pain?
Unlike the weak, unlike you,
I gain strength from pain.
Soon you will know
the taste of white oak
as it pierces your heart.
Very clever, Mikael.
Compelling the locals to say
to my face what you dare not.
Enjoy the theatrics.
They only delay the inevitable.
[Yells]
Well, perhaps we should
hold off on this.
No. I hai everything I need.
Combine a knotting spell
with a sire bond spell.
I just have to combine
them the right way.
Then do them in reverse.
That's pretty advanced
for a wee girl like you.
I can give you a list of people
who have underestimated me.
Not one of them has
done it a second time.
Well, perhaps I should help you.
I'm pretty good at
stuff like this.
I don't think so.
It's not just saying
spells backwards.
It's changing the verb
tense into...
Nemo unus animabus
carnem et sanguinem de ista duo.
Like I said, I'm pretty.
It's never paid to
underestimate me either.
Ok. Let's do this.
Cami: I used to
try to convince Klaus
that there was good in everyone,
that you really did
care about him...
Deep inside once.
He told me I was naive,
that I could never fathom
how deep your hatred ran.
I didn't always hate him.
When Niklaus was born,
I was overjoyed.
I thought, this one...
This one has the eyes
of a warrior.
He will be worthy.
But my hope was short-lived.
And when I found out that
he wasn't really my son,
my relief was glorious!
But that passed
with the knowledge that
he was begat of a beast.
His mother's infidelity
was not his fault.
Everything that followed
was because of Niklaus'
obsession with the wolves.
He ventured out to watch them
turn under the full moon,
and he took my youngest
son, Heinrich.
He was but a child.
And he was torn apart.
An accident.
An accident?!
He murdered my wife!
His own mother who
sought to cleanse him
of his beast-like nature.
He betrayed me.
He turned my entire
family against me.
And yet you defend him.
I have desperately
tried to convince him
not to kill you, that
the bloodshed
in your family does not have
to be an endless cycle.
And after centuries on this
earth, do you really not see
that all of your
violence is pointless?
[Laughing]
Let me hazard a guess.
You are one of these
alienists, right?
We're called therapists
these days.
And to be honest, you could
do with some couch time.
Actually, my dear,
since my wound
does not appear to be healing,
what I could do with
right now is some food.
You... you said you wouldn't.
Yes, I did, didn't I?
And all of the blood of
a fawn barely makes
for good fodder.
In times of need, even
the devil eats flies.
[Screaming]
Oh.
[Yells, groans]
[Cell phone rings]
[Ring]
I'm a tad busy.
What is it, Hayley?
Something has
happened to Elijah.
He was supposed to be
our decoy last night,
and now he's vanished.
There's blood everywhere...
Werewolf and vampire.
There is a trail.
I need you to help us track it.
Well, as much as I might
like to help you find
my brother, I have more
pressing matters at the moment.
What's more important
than your own brother...
My life.
Davina had Mikael on
a magical leash.
And it broke.
Now Mikael has Tunde's
blade, the white oak stake,
and Cami.
I'm going to get her back.
And then I'm going to end this.
Either Mikael or I will be
ash by night's end.
And if you do find my brother,
please tell him I
could do with a hand.
[Neck snaps]
Both: Sanquinatum venetus
barkael meh.
Sanquinatum venetus
Sanquinatum venetus barkael meh.
Stop! Stop.
This isn't working.
Well, maybe you're
just doing it wrong.
No. We have to get this right.
Josh, Marcel, their
lives depend on it.
Look, just stop chanting.
I'll chant and channel
your power.
Release me!
[Kaleb chanting]
I've been wondering when you
might make an appearance, Kol.
You're one of them.
You liar!
[Gasps]
That hurt.
Ok, ok, ok, ok.
You ruined a spell.
And now my friends are
gonna die because of you.
My mother said, kill
the spell or kill her.
And I happen to like you.
Oh, please.
Listen, you don't disobey
mother dearest
without some consequences.
Yes, she brought
me back to life.
But she's mad as a hatter.
And that man you've made
your pet, my father,
well, he's more of
a lunatic than she is.
What, so you just unleash him?
You're the one who brought
him back to life first.
I had him under control.
Yeah, right up until
the point you didn't,
which is when he threatened me.
He wanted freedom,
so I freed him.
You want to know my secrets?
Then here you go. Go on.
Have at it.
Yes, I'm a Mikaelson.
But I've got just as much
reason to loathe
the lot of them as you do.
You deactivated
my bracelet. How?
It's a dark object.
I know a little something
about creating
and destroying them.
Show me.
All right.
You're distorting my memories.
It was you who killed Tatia.
Oh. I used her blood
to bind the spell
that suppressed Niklaus'
werewolf aspect.
But by the time you
brought her to me,
she was already dead.
You can't rewrite history.
No. I cannot.
And I did not...
Not until I had your consent.
Lenore: When you became
yourself again,
you brought her to me
but too late.
I told you that you
were a good son,
to let me take care of it,
that I could help make
it all go away.
And then I said to you,
"you will not suffer
"from this memory or be
tormented from the guilt
"of your misdeed.
"What goes behind that
door shall stay there
and be forgotten."
I told you to clean yourself up,
that if you were clean,
no one would know
what you are or what you'd done.
And you did exactly that...
And more.
You created a place in your
mind to put your victims.
You began to believe
that as long as your
suit was immaculate
and your hands clean,
you could look in the mirror
and tell yourself it's all ok.
No one need know what's
behind that red door.
[Screams]
But a thousand years
is a long time, Elijah.
And a place meant to hold
one unforgivable sin
is now full to bursting with
your most monstrous deeds.
Stop!
How long before it's your
beloved Hayley's corpse
behind that door?
Stop.
You must be afraid that
loving you will destroy her,
as it destroyed Celeste, Tatia.
Take my offer...
The both of you.
In new bodies, you'll
be alive again.
You could give her a child
to replace the one she lost.
You will not break me.
Oh, you are already
broken, my dear boy,
but not beyond repair.
I am here to fix you.
I am here to fix you all.
Bleeding power from
a dark object is tricky,
so it does help to know
what kind of object it is.
The white oak stake.
You want to drain
the white oak stake, do you?
It's a dark object.
If I can't stop Mikael,
I have to stop
that stake from working.
See, usually I like
a girl with ambition,
but this is just beyond mad.
Just show me the spell,
Kaleb... Kol...
Or whatever your name is.
The problem's not
the spell, love.
The problem's the
white oak stake.
It's too powerful.
We can't just drain it.
The best you can hope
for is to disable it,
but just for a bit.
So do you have
a better solution?
Because I don't have
time to argue.
So show me the spell
and hand me the keys.
Oh, what are you gonna do?
You just gonna drive around
till you bump into them?
You may have messed
with my bracelet,
but I made sure months ago
that I would always be
able to find Mikael.
All right. Fine.
Your funeral.
I'm still not going to allow you
to drive me bloody car, though.
You're gonna pay for
hurting her.
Oh, that's sweet.
The cur whines for its bitch.
I'll make sure to drain
the rest of her
right in front of your
eyes just before you burn.
Davina, wait. We need
to do this together.
I'm strong enough on my own.
No, you're not.
Listen, I know you
don't trust me...
And that's fair enough...
But these are your mates
that we're trying to save here.
The only way that we can do
this is if we work together.
You need to trust me, all right?
Take my hands.
Take my power.
Channel me.
[Mikael grunting]
Klaus: I'm not as weak
as you remember, am I?
[Screaming]
[Chanting]
Cami: No!
Aah!
[Klaus screaming]
[Chanting continues]
Why aren't you burning?!
If you were dead,
you would burn.
Burn!
Kaleb, I can't hold it.
Just trust me.
[Both continue chanting]
Is this your doing,
little witch?
Then you will undo it.
Return the power to the stake.
[Cami breathing heavily]
[Screaming]
Klaus?
Mikael: What do you
think you're doing?
Stay the hell away from us.
Or, I swear to God,
I'll kill you myself.
You have a warrior's heart.
Perhaps I'll keep it
as a souvenir.
Now enough!
This night has been
a long parade of fools.
I'll enjoy killing every
last one of you.
I wouldn't bet on it.
It's over, Mikael.
You're outnumbered.
Are you going to beg
for your miserable life?
[Chuckles]
You think having people
makes you strong?
It proves how weak you are.
Come find me when you
don't have fools, women,
and children fighting
your battles.
Are you ok?
Ah, a bit lightheaded.
It might have something
to do with being knocked
arse over teacup by
dear old dad.
You are lucky to be
alive, young lady.
You want to tell me what
the hell you were thinking?
Can we not do this right now?
Am I gonna embarrass you
in front of your friend?
Who the hell is this guy anyway?
Haven't we got to stop meeting
like this, pal?
Davina: He's my friend.
And he's helping me.
Help you do what,
wage war on Klaus
and help me get killed
in the process?
I just saved Klaus'
life trying to protect you.
Yeah, from a psycho
vampire hunter
that you brought back to life.
Kaleb: All right. Enough!
Well, I think it's enough.
Well, it should be enough.
I mean, we're all friends here,
aren't we?
Just stay here till I get back.
I'll handle Klaus.
We should get out
of here. Trust me.
My brother's not
the forgiving kind.
Even if you did help
out back there,
his hatred of betrayal
far outweighs
his sense of gratitude.
I'm not afraid of him.
You out to get yourself killed?
I'm out to get even with Klaus.
And you're gonna help me.
But, first, you're right.
Let's get out of here.
You pulled the stake
out in the Nick of time.
A moment longer, and I
would have been done for.
It's the least I could do
for telling you not
to kill that bastard
the first chance you had.
Well, he hurt you.
For that alone,
I would kill him.
You know, in a thousand years,
I think it's the first
time I've seen him run.
You're still weak.
Hayley: And he knew
he was outmatched.
We checked the perimeter,
and he's definitely gone.
I appreciate your assistance.
Well, hey. You die, I die.
Just call me selfish.
Yeah. You die, a lot
of people die.
But, Klaus, we have
another problem.
[Music playing]
No more.
I'm afraid we've just begun.
You will hang here remembering.
Every atrocity you've
hidden behind that door
will emerge to haunt you.
And as you grow weaker,
you will be ripped
of your strength,
your will, your hope.
And as you rot here alone, you
will reconsider my offer...
A new life, a way to be
freed of your demons,
a chance at peace.
Hayley: Oh. That's about enough
of that, don't you think?
I would have ripped
her heart out,
but she would have just
body-jumped me.
How do I get these off?
The doll. There.
Break it.
She's using it to bind me.
You need to feed.
I can't.
You're weak.
I crave you.
My hunger, it could
overwhelm me.
Look...
I'm not afraid.
What did you do to him?
I let him dream.
That's considerate of you.
I cannot lead him
out of darkness
by simply exposing him
to the horrors of his past.
I have to let him bask
in his own version
of a better world to come.
And by the time he wakes,
he will know the only way
to find peace, is my way.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/