How long were you waiting?
Not long.
GARAGE ROCK MUSIC PLAYS
MUSIC STOPS
Thank you.
No-one else stopped.
Most people are dickheads. Yeah.
THINKS: I wondered why Alyssa
had wanted to pick someone up.
Maybe she was putting off
going back.
Are you OK?
What?
Well, it's the middle of nowhere,
you're on your own...
So you're either in danger
or you're mental.
Alyssa.
What?
THINKS: Or maybe she just didn't
want to be alone with me.
Did you just get married?
She did.
Where do you need to go?
Anywhere.
OK.
I'm Alyssa, this is James.
Hi.
I'm Bonnie.
Hi, Bonnie.
THINKS: Alyssa found quiet people
difficult.
I don't think we automatically
made sense to her.
Where are you from?
Bonnie! Hm?
THINKS: Maybe something
happened to her.
CAR CLUNKS AND SCRAPES
What was that?
Oh, no. What the fuck
is wrong with your car, James?
It's literally the bane of our life.
THINKS: It was nice she said
"our life".
Shut up. Do you have a spare?
That is the spare.
I'm going for a piss.
Sorry about this.
I'm thirsty.
OK.
Have you got any water in your car?
Oh, yeah.
I thought it was here.
Maybe it's...maybe it's in the back.
Maybe I've finished it.
Good news. What?
There's a house or something up
the road, I saw smoke. How close?
Really close.
Do you want to sit in the car? Why?
So your dress doesn't get ruined.
I think we've gone beyond
that point, James.
Well, this isn't creepy at all.
LO-FI ROCK MUSIC PLAYS
# You know I've sailed
the stormy seas
# Just for you to notice me
# I'd fight a million wars
# Just to lay down at your door
# Now I've... #
FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
DOOR CREAKS OPEN
Ooh.
HE SIGHS
Oh. Congratulations.
What, were you the bridesmaid?
HE LAUGHS
How can I help you?
Let me use your phone.
And, please,
could I use your toilet?
Yes.
THINKS: Everything was refusing
to go to plan.
But then, we had no plan.
That was the problem.
OK.
They can't do anything
until the morning. Shit.
Sorry.
Do you have a number for a taxi?
Well, there's only Steve,
and he's just had a baby, so...
Right.
Do you have any rooms? What?
Yes, we've got all of them.
We'll take two.
No, we can't afford that.
I'll pay. You picked me up.
You saved me.
THINKS: Saved her from what?
OK.
Thanks.
You and James want to be
in the same room, don't you?
Yeah, that's fine.
THINKS: It's better that way.
It's cheaper.
It's...room ten.
Seven.
This was the last room they had. OK.
Do you reckon those are real?
I don't know.
They're quite sharp.
All right, Captain Safety.
Chill out.
We should check on Bonnie.
We should leave her alone.
Why?
She's not right.
Just because someone's quiet
doesn't mean they're not right.
Are you talking about yourself?
She paid for the room.
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
What you've done to me
SHE SIGHS
# What you've done to me
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
What you've done to me
# I never will forget
what you've done to me
# I took your tender lovin'
That's what... #
I'm your little salmon.
KNOCK ON DOOR
Would you like to have
a drink with us?
Hello?
Ahh, hello!
What can I get you?
THINKS: I can't believe
this is my wedding night.
I don't think this is proper wine.
Is that a burn?
Yep.
Suits you.
Thank you.
So where were you headed
when you picked me up?
I was taking her home.
Why are you still
in your wedding dress?
Cos I ran away from the wedding.
Why?
Because I did.
Who were you getting married to?
My boyfriend.
Did he cry?
Do you want to mind
your own business?
I was going to get married...
..but then my boyfriend died.
THINKS: Aw, fuck.
How did he die?
Are you feeling like
a bit of a spare part?
What? Well, three's a crowd,
four's a riot.
Well, I can sit down if you want.
Why would she want that?
Oh, I'm just being friendly.
Calm down.
How do you know I didn't marry her?
What? Maybe I was the vicar.
Just stop bothering her,
she's not desperate.
Thank you.
DOOR CLOSES
Probably get stabbed
in our beds now.
THINKS: I probably deserve it.
You look so beautiful!
Thanks.
I thought you were more likely
to end up dead than married.
Right.
You can relax now.
He's safety, he's solid.
THINKS: Says the woman abandoned by
every man she's ever been with.
Look at him.
I am.
How do you feel?
Exactly the same.
You're a lucky girl!
THINKS: I do.
I feel exactly the same.
Shit.
# In the chapel of dreams
# Chapel of dreams
# Oh, was until I found... #
Alyssa.
You OK?
I'm tired.
I don't normally drink.
OK.
You're quite small up close.
Am I?
Shall we get another one?
Actually, I should check
if she's OK.
Night.
Sleep well.
DIAL TONE
# Across the evening sky... #
Who were you speaking to?
No-one.
# All the birds are leaving... #
I need to take this dress off.
OK.
# But how can we know
# It's time for them to go?
# Before the winter fire
# I will still be dreaming... #
You were right about Bonnie.
What?
She's a bit strange.
Er, yeah.
Are you OK?
Yes, James.
This is exactly how I pictured
my honeymoon kicking off.
You're thirsty.
Have they abandoned you?
I'm waiting.
For what?
For them to fall asleep.
Fair play.
Could I buy you another drink?
I'm all right, really.
I promise.
SHE SIGHS
I'll take you back. Tomorrow.
If that's what you want.
Maybe.
THINKS: I didn't know
what that meant.
What happened to you?
After the beach?
No-one told me anything.
Not properly, anyway.
It was quite bad.
Yeah, obviously.
I couldn't walk for a bit.
He was really supportive.
Until he died.
Yamas! What?
I'm a bit Greek.
Mmm...
So, what do you think of the place?
The bars of soap are very small.
Noted.
I'm single, by the way. I'm not.
Are you happy? Yes.
That's good.
I get lonely.
My wife ran off with...
You off, are you? Yeah.
Night.
I'm really sorry. I am.
I tried to see you, I did, but
no-one would let me. And then...
THINKS: I was going to tell
Alyssa about the time
her mum came to see me,
but then she said something
that made me
forget everything else.
I think I want to kiss you.
What?
Is that bad?
No.
I don't think I can have sex.
I didn't say sex, I said a kiss.
I, er...
I don't think it works any more.
I haven't tried,
but I got shot near there, so...
Sorry.
HE SOBS
# We come in through the morning
# Until the long time ago
# And we search in through
the morning
# Cos you have lost your soul
# Don't go, don't go
# Don't go, I don't want you to go
# But I know you must go today
# We're erasing lines
on our unholy faces
# We eat our souls and don't
bother to replace them... #
We do a turn down service.
What?
Can I come in?
SHUTS DOOR
Um...
That's better, isn't it?
Yeah.
These are nice.
Can you leave, please?
You don't have to touch it.
You can just watch.
You can turn round, if you want.
Get out.
Wait!
Get out!
COCKS GUN
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Please don't hurt me!
Please!
I've got kids.
Please put the gun down.
Please put the gun down!
Put it down.
GUNSHOT
SHE GASPS
What was that?
I don't know.
It's OK.
What's wrong?
Look, can you just give me a minute?
I'm sorry, this is, like, a lot.
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
I'll, er...
I'll be in there. OK.
Do you mind sleeping in there?
No.
That's fine.
Thanks.
It's going to be OK, Alyssa.
# Hello, little girl
# Goodbye, little girl
# I'm not your kind of guy,
little girl
# I'll only make you cry,
# Trouble
# Trouble, trouble,
trouble, trouble, trouble
# Is my middle name
# Each kiss, little girl
# Is sweet, little girl... #
THINKS: Maybe James was right...
..and it is going to be OK.
# Trouble
# Trouble, trouble, trouble... #
Maybe it will all work it.
Or maybe, as usual,
everything's completely fucked.
# By changing your name to mine,
little girl
# Trouble
# Trouble, trouble,
trouble, trouble, trouble
# Is my middle name
# Oh, trouble
Trouble, trouble
# Trouble, trouble, trouble
# Is my middle name. #