Come on, Joey!
I toId you everything I knew
Iast night.
It's not that big a deaI.
So they're doing it.
I cannot beIieve you wouId say that!
Sorry. Monica and ChandIer
are making Iove.
No, I mean, come on.
This is a huge deaI!
I need more detaiIs.
Who initiated the first kiss?
I don't know.
Is he romantic with her?
Are they in Iove?
I don't know.
You don't know anything.
I know one thing.
They did it right there.
The One with ChandIer's Work Laugh
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
CouId I have a scone?
Want to hear some good news?
Someone I know is getting married.
Weddings are happy occasions.
Oh, it's my ex-wife, EmiIy!
Sorry, man.
-Here's your scone.
-Thanks.
Stupid British snack food!
Did they teach you that
in anger management?
You know what might
heIp you deaI with it?
You two are in the past.
You can't be mad about the past.
Are you stiII mad about, you know,
the Louisiana Purchase?
Nobody's mad about that.
ExactIy!
Because it's in the past.
Anybody going to eat that?
Look at us aII dressed up for the party.
What are we ceIebrating?
We had a Iot of Iiquor
Ieft over from Christmas.
Our friends aren't here. We can be
a reaI coupIe. We don't have to hide.
I know. I can do this.
And I can do this.
We can't do that.
Hey, Bing!
Who's the pretty Iady,
and what is she doing with you?
I asked myseIf
that very question, sir.
My boss, Doug.
-This is Monica.
-Hi.
-This is my wife, Kara.
-Nice to meet you.
Did you hear about the new Iaw firm
working for us?
Dewey, Cheatem & Howe.
Let's go drink our body weight.
What was that?
That noise you made?
Oh, my work Iaugh.
Your work Iaugh?
If you're going to survive this party,
come up with one too.
AII right. Check me out.
He says, " $30, Father.
Same as in town. "
Everybody at work Ioved you Iast night.
And they Iike me more
just because I was with you.
You repaired the damage
from when they met Joey.
Doug wants to pIay tennis.
He never taIks to me outside of work.
Except for that time
at that strip cIub.
Strip church.
-I'II go find a racket.
-I thought you had one.
I used to, but then Joey thought
it'd be fun to go hit rocks. . .
. . .at bigger rocks.
Do you have a tennis racket?
I Ient it to Joey and
I've never gotten it back.
Good Iuck with that.
What's up?
Why are you here?
I thought you had inventory.
I do, but I decided I'd take
a Iong Iunch. . .
. . .and spend some time
with my friend, Monica.
You know, I feeI Iike
we don't taIk anymore.
How are you?
What is new with you?
Not much. Work's good.
We don't have to taIk about work.
TaIk about anything.
You know what?
Let's taIk about reIationships.
What's going on?
Nothing.
You go.
There was this guy at the bank
that I thought was cute.
But I don't anymore.
That's juicy.
You know what? I actuaIIy do
have a Iot of work to do.
You're sure there's just
not anything eIse?
I'm sure. Is there something
you want to taIk to me about?
No!
If there was, I wouIdn't teII you.
Then what happened?
You'II get your turn.
-Hey, Pheebs. What's going on?
-Nothing.
This is not over.
No, no, no!
I was up aII night writing
this nasty Ietter to EmiIy.
It was perfect,
and now it's aII covered in. . . .
ActuaIIy, thanks!
AII right!
Ready to go to the movies?
ActuaIIy, I think I'II skip it.
ReaIIy?
I'II read my book.
I just want to be aIone right now.
Sure you don't want to?
Tom Hanks, Meg Ryan.
They get maiI and stuff.
That's okay, Joe.
Let's go, Pheebs.
Game!
I got to teII you, that partner
of yours is a reaI tiger.
Are you aII right?
We'II just get
a IittIe sip of water.
Am I on fire today or what?
Those birds are browned,
basted and ready to be carved.
Okay, easy, Martina.
I think we shouId Iet them
win the next game.
I'm sorry, I don't understand
what you just said.
Let them win one.
Are you crazy? We own those two.
Look at them!
He can't even breathe,
and she's popping piIIs.
You're not giving them a chance.
They have rackets.
We'II make this the Iast game.
Yes, sir. Put me out of my misery.
Are you sure you never pIayed pro?
PIease Iet them win.
I'II take it down to 95% ,
but that's the best I can do.
-Missed it!
-I got it!
Nice shot.
I got it!
Long!
I can't beIieve you Iet them win.
WeII, at Ieast you hid
your feeIings weII about it.
I was frustrated.
It's my racket.
Frustrated with you!
If we hadn't Iost, they wouId never have
invited us to dinner tomorrow.
What bothers me. . .
. . .is how different
you act around them.
The throwing the tennis games,
the fake Iaugh. . .
. . .the " See you Iater, Bing! "
"Not if I see you first, Doug! "
I don't Iike " work ChandIer. "
The guy's a suck-up.
Because you said that. . .
. . .I'm not putting out tonight!
Something's wrong.
My brother doesn't stay out aII night.
Maybe we shouId check
the trash chute.
Ross couIdn't fit
down the trash chute.
That's right. He aImost couId.
Which is exactIy
how I got stuck there.
Oh, my God!
Where the heII have you been?
Just, you know, out.
Oh, out! God, I don't know
why we didn't think to check there.
What were you doing?
I went to a bar and then. . .
. . .I just waIked around for a whiIe.
You waIked around aII night
in the city by yourseIf?
He hooked up!
He hooked up.
I don't have to answer your questions.
I'm a big boy.
I can do what I want.
He hooked up!
TeII us about her!
Ross, you Ieft your scarf--
Hey, you guys.
I know what you aII are thinking,
but ChandIer is in Yemen.
I'm a young woman. I have needs.
I can't wait forever.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
So I'm asking you, pIease
just take a moment before you judge me.
Nobody's judging you.
Mr. Right-pIace-at-the-right-time. . .
. . .caII me.
I know what you guys are going to say.
You two wouId have
very hairy chiIdren.
I didn't know you'd say that.
Ross! Janice?
AII right. HoId on, hoId on.
This is Ross.
He's our friend.
He obviousIy went crazy.
He obviousIy Iost his mind.
I didn't Iose my mind, okay?
Janice and I have a Iot in common.
We've both been divorced.
We both have kids.
Are you going to see her again?
-Don't put ideas in his head!
-I wiII see her.
Damn it, Phoebe!
I have to teII you something
that I've never admitted.
In high schooI, I made out with James
even though I knew you Iiked him.
That feeIs so good to get off my chest.
Okay, you go.
My turn? What are you taIking about?
I know about you and ChandIer.
I overheard you
on the phone the other day.
You said, " I'II teII RacheI I'm doing
Iaundry for a coupIe of hours. "
And he said, " Laundry?
Is that my new nickname?"
And you said:
"You know what
your nickname is, Mr. Big. "
You're writing yourseIf
a IittIe pIay there, Rach.
Let me know how it turns out.
I wouIdn't know because I got
so freaked out I hung up the phone.
WeII, if you had kept Iistening. . .
. . .you wouId have heard me
caII him Mister. . .
. . .Bigot.
Mr. Bigot.
He teIIs the most racist jokes.
AII right. So that's it.
There's nothing going on
between you and ChandIer?
Me and ChandIer?
Put your $20 down.
First one to find
the tasty treat wins, okay?
AII right, Iet's get the contestants
out of their isoIation booths.
And they're off!
Get your foot off my contestant!
Judge?
Judge ruIes no vioIation.
It's so weird to say this,
but I just had a great date with Janice.
-What?
-Are you serious?
I opened up to her about aII
the stuff that's been happening to me.
I mean, I taIked for hours.
It is amazing. . .
. . .to have someone give you
such focused attention.
You don't need Janice for that.
You've got us.
The duck gets the Nutter Butter!
That's not a Nutter Butter.
That's an oId won ton!
Judge ruIes. . .
. . .Nutter Butter.
Tough caII.
SeriousIy, I strongIy beIieve that
we shouId support President CIinton. . .
. . .and her husband, BiII.
How do you Iike your coffee?
-None for me.
-A IittIe sugar.
I'II have Monica stick her finger in it.
That wiII sweeten it up.
-That Iaugh doesn't give you a headache?
-You get used to it.
I don't think that I can.
This wiII be it for me
on the work things.
I Iaugh at my boss's jokes.
What's the big deaI?
I'd rather not be with
this work-weaseI guy. . .
. . .when I can be with my boyfriend,
who I actuaIIy respect.
I got to apoIogize for Kara's coffee.
I'd feeI sorry for it in a fight.
It's not strong enough
to defend itseIf.
Hear what I said?
What?
It's a joke.
What's the matter with you?
WeII, I just didn't think
it was funny, sir.
Excuse me?
-WeII, I just--
-Honey?
I just don't think
you understood the joke.
ReaIIy?
I mean, it was reaIIy funny.
I just don't think that you got it.
You see, Kara's coffee
is weak-tasting.
But what Doug did was impIy
that it was weak physicaIIy.
-You get it now, honey?
-I think I do!
-Thank you, Monica.
-I thought you couId use the heIp.
Coffee in a fight!
You mind if I read
my comic books in here?
Sure. Why?
ChandIer and Monica are over there.
It's kind of hard to concentrate.
She just caIIed and said
she was going to be working Iate.
She keeps Iying to me.
That's it! I'm going over there
and confronting them right now.
AII right, so you're teIIing me
that I have to teII racist jokes now?
I'm just not very good at this.
I'm a terribIe Iiar.
I hate having to Iie to RacheI.
-But we're not ready to teII yet.
-I know.
Ever since high schooI, RacheI was the
one person that I toId everything to.
I miss that so much now.
She's my best friend.
Oh, my God, RacheI!
What are you doing here?
WeII, I actuaIIy came over here
to borrow this Iamp. . .
. . .to Iook at my books.
You know, see them a IittIe better.
Okay, great.
WeII, what I was doing
in ChandIer's room is that. . .
. . .I was cIeaning it.
He pays me to cIean it.
What a great way to make
some extra pocket money.
When I said to you earIier
that I was at work. . .
. . .I'm at my new work.
Good enough. Right?
I'II go Iook at my books.
Go get back to my new job.
CongratuIations on your new job!
Man, she is reaIIy guIIibIe.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
-ActuaIIy, I shouId get going.
-You're sure?
I can stay out as Iate as you want.
I toId you I'm on
sabbaticaI from work--
Yes, yes. You did.
-Oh, man!
-What is wrong now?
This isn't what I ordered.
Man! Can't anything
go right in my Iife?
First, my marriage faIIs apart,
and then--
I know!
You Iose your apartment,
you Iose your job. . .
. . .your ex-wife gets married so fast!
And now the coffee!
We need to taIk.
-Sometimes I feeI--
-No, no, don't.
I'm going to taIk.
I beIieve. . .
. . .that the sun has set. . .
. . .on our day in the sun.
You're a very sweet person, Ross.
UnfortunateIy. . .
. . .I just don't think I can take
another second of you whining!
Let me make sure
I'm hearing this right.
You're ending this with me because. . .
. . .I'm too whiny?
So you're saying. . .
. . .I've become so whiny. . .
. . .that I. . .
. . .annoy you. . .
. . .Janice.
WeII, yeah!
Oh, my God!
WiII you be okay?
I am now.
I guess, that's two out of three. . .
. . .Joey!
Dude, we got to taIk.
I want to teII you something before
you heard it from someone eIse.
I hope this isn't too weird but. . .
. . .I had a thing with Janice.
You're not mad?
Why wouId I be mad?
Because there's certain ruIes
about this kind of stuff.
You don't fooI around with
your friends' ex-girIfriends. . .
. . .or possibIe girIfriends
or girIs they're reIated to.
I am mad.
But you know,
I'm going to forgive you.
Because that's what friends do.
They forgive their friends when
they do everything you just said.
Thank you.
But I want you to remember. . .
. . .that I forgave you.
I aIso want you to remember
that I Iet you Iive here rent-free.
AII right.
And I want you to remember
that I gave you. . .
. . .twenty-seven doIIars.
No strings attached!
If you can't remember that. . .
. . .we shouId write it down.
Let's write it down!