- Hey.
- Hey, guys, how's it going?
I'm gonna finish this.
We had dinner
with Stella's sister and her fiancé?
- They're getting married before us.
- How you've dreamt
about your perfect wedding day
when you were a little girl?
- Yeah.
- Totally.
My sister is stealing
my dream wedding.
Down to every last detail
on Shelter Island, at sunset...
... just down the beach
from our family's old summer house.
It's my dream wedding.
I'm gonna finish this.
- The lamb here is supposed to be great.
- I'm a vegan.
I wish I could tune out
that moral voice
inside me
that says eating animals is murder,
but I guess I'm just not
as strong as you are.
That's 'cause you need protein.
I'll have the lamb.
Okay, new goal:
I want our wedding
to kick her wedding's ass.
to take her wedding's head
and shove it in the toilet
and flush it, like,20 times.
Ted, in high school,
you were her wedding, weren't you?
You know,she's always trying
to one-up me. I mean, I love her, but,
there's a part of me that kinda wishes
this whole thing would just fall apart.
I hate him. I hate him!
I hate him.
God, this steak is so good!
Four days to go and he just runs off
with the vitamin consultant
from Whole Foods?
I gave up makeup for him.
I gave up showering for him.
I gave up shaving my armpits for him.
Hard to imagine
where it all went wrong.
Now it's so close to the wedding...
There's like bacon or something
in this dipping sauce. I love it.
I can't get any refunds.
I'm gonna be out
thousands of dollars.
Kids, when you're in a relationship,
you develop a kind
of telepathy with your partner.
What do you think?
We could help her out.
No, Stella,
we should help her out.
Let's pay for dinner.
Nora. Don't worry.
We got this.
That's right.
We'll take over your wedding,
pay you back
for everything you spent.
Ted and I will get married
this Sunday.
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Arrow
We're getting married this Sunday?
Are we sure we're ready for this?
Ted, I wasted years
trying to get Lucy's dad
to decide he was "ready" for this,
but he never got ready for this.
That's why we never got married.
Come on, let's just be spontaneous.
I used to dream that Tony
would be spontaneous like this.
Okay, I'm in.
And I'm also... spontaneous.
I wish I hadn't done that.
Kids, morals usually
come at the end of stories,
but this one is so important,
I'm gonna tell you now:
Don't ever, ever
invite an ex to your wedding.
If someone had given me that advice,
well, it'd've changed everything.
Come on, you've got to come,
it's my wedding.
I can't. I'm in Tokyo.
It's my first week on the job.
I can't just take off.
Plus, I'm finally
doing serious news.
Robin was doing serious news.
It was the number one
English news network in Japan.
Of course, the news was
a little different over there.
The Federal Reserve Board voted
to leave interest...
rates unchanged.
It's my wedding.
You have to be there.
Okay. I'll be there.
I gotta go.
Good evening.
And I'm Robin Scherbatsky.
Peace talks were stalled once again
in the Middle East.
Despite a promising start
in the latest negotiations,
talks foundered on security issues.
She's in.
All right,
your bachelor party, tonight.
I have got three of the most
physically and morally
flexible exotic dancers
you've ever seen...
- There's no time.
- I'll let you know how it goes.
We should really rent
the cars for tomorrow?
- What?
- No, "Don't get married, Ted"?
No, "You're making
a big mistake, Ted"?
Barney Stinson...
are you no longer committed
to the war on marriage?
No, I just know
a hopeless cause when I see it.
It's the same reason
I don't recycle.
Plus, Ted getting married
is in my best interest.
You see...
Lately I've been working on a problem
of the utmost importance.
I confess I was stumped.
Until one night I decided
to tackle it once and for all.
Then, at last,
I cracked the code.
- So you're back on Robin.
- Hopefully.
I mean, this weekend is the best chance
ever to hook up with her again.
You'll never pull it off.
There's too many distractions.
The first drunk bridesmaid you see,
you'll have your head under her dress
like an old-time photographer.
Lily, don't cheapen this.
I don't want to sound all
mushy-gushy and romantic,
but this weekend,
Robin is the only woman I'm banging.
And so, the day before our wedding,
Stella and I made the trip up
to Shelter Island.
With everyone else not far behind.
- Zitch dog.
- Z... Zog...
This isn't exactly
where I pictured Ted getting married.
"The Namaste Yoga
and Meditation Collective."
I don't know about you, but Nama-stay
here any longer than I have to.
Sweetie,
go check in with that dirty hippie
over there
and we'll get some drinks.
What scotches you got?
Here at the center,
we have a very strict no-alcohol policy.
Great, and all the meals
are included, right?
And they're all 100% vegan.
I need alcohol.
I'm not gonna get Robin
with this stuff.
Look at this.
Berry Blaster Brain Revitalizer.
My God, some of these drinks
could actually make a girl smarter.
What sort of hell
has Ted brought us to?
- There's no meat.
- There's no alcohol.
It gets worse:
I'm 90% sure that guy
you were talking with used to be
lead singer of the Spin Doctors.
Hey, guys,
Stella and I have a little problem.
The programs look great.
I mean, it's not our names on the front,
but otherwise, really nice.
I talked to Robin.
She's running a little bit late,
but she'll be here just under the wire.
- You invited Robin?
- Yeah, of course.
You never told me that.
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
Can I help?
You feel glad.
- You like Robin.
- Yeah, but
she's your ex-girlfriend.
- It's weird.
- It's not weird.
It's weird.
You don't get what it's like for a bride
to see her groom's ex at their wedding.
Your new husband used to nail me,
like, three times a day.
Having exes around,
I don't know, it brings up...
unresolved things.
How do you know that spark won't come
back with your ex sitting out there?
Come on, we're just friends. Plus,
Robin and I already had our backslide
last Thanksgiving,
not even that long ago.
Did you place a large bet
against yourself in this argument?
She already got her ticket.
It's important to me.
I would never invite Lucy's dad.
I wouldn't care if you did.
Tony's great. Let's invite him, too.
Tony is the last person
I want at our wedding, okay?
And Robin is a close second.
Robin's probably
about to get on the plane.
Plus, she left
a really important job for this.
Spurred by environmental concerns
and high gasoline prices,
sales of hybrid vehicles have risen
11% over the previous year.
What should I do?
I don't know.
I kinda get the no exes thing.
Why ask a failed romance to come
and watch your successful one?
It's like inviting the Seattle Mariners
to a World Series game.
It's weird for everyone.
What? Robin has to come.
Right, she's, like, my best friend.
Female friend.
My best female friend.
I don't care, why fake it.
- Dude, Robin has to be here.
- She shouldn't come.
- What are you talk...
- Justice Aldrin, tie-breaking vote.
Wouldn't feel right without Robin.
But you don't mess with the bride.
- I'm gonna tell her not to come.
- It's the right decision, Ted.
This is gonna be, like, the worst
phone conversation of all time.
Co-best man, I'm on it.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
Just heading to the airport.
We'll see you soon.
Have a great flight.
Bad news.
I couldn't reach her.
Robin's already on her way.
Robin's on her way.
You know what, I'm glad.
Exes should be allowed
to come to weddings.
I'll just tell Stella
she's got to deal with it.
You need to be more delicate with Stella
about this whole Robin thing.
- What do you mean by delicate?
- Brides are under a lot of stress
before a wedding.
I mean, of course,
I held it together pretty well.
You don't remember?
The florist just told me
the roses are more light medium-pink
than medium-pink.
Light medium-pink!
Everything's ruined.
Our wedding site uses
a gravity furnace
instead of forced-air heating.
That's the one thing I cared about.
Why are we even getting married?
After a while, it's all noise.
Poor Stella's had to jam months
of crazy into just three days.
- So what do I do?
- You wait for the next crisis,
you solve it, you're a hero.
Then you bring up the Robin thing,
but this time she'll say yes.
But what if there's no next crisis?
She's a bride.
There will be a next crisis.
- There's an next crisis.
- Awesome! What is it?
My daughter, my own daughter
isn't coming to our wedding.
What?
Tony's supposed to drive her up
tomorrow, but now he's being all petty
about me getting married,
and he won't do it.
It's been five years.
Why can't we just move on already?
So first thing tomorrow,
I drive down, talk to him,
get him to let me drive Lucy up,
then, boom, crisis solved.
Stella's happy.
Robin comes to the wedding.
- You Barney?
- Yes.
I hear you're a real man whore,
so listen up.
Tomorrow night, I want to do things
so dirty and so depraved
that I forget that this was supposed
to be my wedding.
I'm kind of here with someone.
Bring her.
You're never gonna make it.
So, the morning of my wedding day
I made the trip back
to Tony's house
to get Lucy.
Doing a little karate?
Sorry, sorry, man.
You set off my internal defense alarm.
You got to watch these things.
- Stay alert, stay alive.
- Right.
So what brings you here?
I thought you'd be off
in some honeymoon suite
with my woman right now.
Not yet. Soon.
That's right, tonight's the night.
Oh, man,
you are going to be sticking it
to the mother of my child.
Actually, I've already stuck it
to her plenty of times.
Why do I always have
to correct people?
You and Stella.
You lucky dog. I could just...
I'm so happy for you, guys.
Listen, here's the thing...
- You can't take her.
- Tony, stop.
This is a big day for Lucy, too.
You're going to have
to put aside your own issues
and think about what's best for her,
here. Whether you like it or not,
she really should be at
her mother's wedding.
I'm taking Lucy with me.
You're right, man.
You're right.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just...
seeing you guys...
has made me realize
everything I had.
Let's stop hugging.
I'm sorry.
Lucy means the world to me.
I feel like I'm losing her to this new
family, a family I'm not even a part of.
- Come on, sure you are.
- I wasn't even invited to the wedding.
You are now.
Road trip.
Right?
"Road Trip 2. Back in the Car".
Today's the day. You hydrating?
Dear female, thank you
for your interest in Barney Stinson...
Your back is going to look like
a Jackson Pollock.
I regret to inform you
that at this time...
I was a vegan for two years.
I need meat.
There are currently
no positions available.
I'm a yoga instructor.
Every position is available.
Your room, 20 minutes.
No foreplay.
- I'm not going to make it, am I?
- Not a chance.
- Remember, let me talk to Stella first.
- Mommy!
Ted invited Daddy!
Hi, sweetie. I missed you.
Give me just a sec, okay?
You invited Tony?
To our wedding?
We talked about this.
No exes at our wedding.
- Why would you do this?
- Oh, boy.
What did Ted do this time?
What is Robin doing here?
I thought I made myself clear.
No exes at our wedding.
To be fair...
- your ex is here.
- You invited him!
- Come on, it's not weird.
- It is weird.
It's like things are not finished
between you two.
And Tony...
I can't deal with Tony now.
Can you please go out there
and tell him to leave?
You can make me the bad guy.
I'll go talk to Robin,
so she knows it's nothing personal.
And, kids, if I had just let
Stella talk to Robin,
this whole story might have
ended differently.
I understand.
I get it.
For the first time,
Ted and Stella Mosby.
And that's how I met your mother.
Is your dad finally done yakking?
Now, come on, who wants ice cream?
But I didn't.
Can you talk to Tony?
Robin flew all the way here from Tokyo.
I should talk to her.
Sure.
- Sorry about running off like that.
- It's okay.
You would not believe the trip I had.
I was on a plane for almost a full day.
It's worth it to see you get married.
How could I not be here...?
- You can't come to the wedding.
- Thank God!
What?
- It's weird.
- It's not weird.
It is weird. Do you know how it feels
to be somebody's ex at their wedding?
Suck it, bitch! I win!
We broke up over a year ago.
Yeah, but that's not that long ago.
Watching your marry another woman
isn't exactly something
I was looking forward to.
I don't know, I just thought
if I ever changed my mind about
marriage and kids, it was...
it was nice to know
that you were there.
So, I was your safety school.
How flattering.
- That's not it. It's just that...
- Why are you bringing any of this up?
- There's nothing between us anymore.
- Maybe there is.
I mean, of course there is.
That kind of stuff
doesn't disappear without a trace.
I'm not just another guest here.
Right. We used to date, but...
we both moved on.
And, look, we got what we wanted.
I'm getting married,
you got your dream job in Tokyo.
- And they all lived happily ever...
- I quit my job.
- You what?
- I'm moving back to New York.
I thought I wanted that job, but...
I want to come back to my real life.
And I think you should
go back to yours.
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't get married.
Look, you're rushing into this.
It's like you're trying to skip ahead
to the end of the book.
You're the most romantic guy I know.
You stole a blue French horn for me.
You tried to make it rain.
- I did make it rain.
- It was a coincidence.
But after all that, this is how your
great romantic quest comes to an end?
You're just disappearing
into someone else's wedding,
someone else's house, someone
else's life without a second thought.
That's not the amazing ending
that you deserve.
That's not Ted Mosby.
I love Stella.
She's the one.
If you really feel that way...
I guess it's a good thing you're not
coming to the wedding after all.
- Big fight?
- Yeah.
Here...
It's on the house.
Just keep 'em coming.
God, do not keep them coming.
I am having a horrible day.
I snuck some scotch in from the duty
free store. You want to join me?
Let's go to your room.
Far away from this room.
- And we can knock it back.
- They didn't get me a room.
I was actually hoping
I could stay with you.
No problem.
I just have to straighten up
a little bit.
I've got some clothes
on the floor, and...
And a naked girl tied
to your headboard.
Towels all over the bathroom.
It's a mess.
So, anyway...
Give me ten minutes
- to get the place in order...
- See ya, Barney.
Okay, let's do this.
Who the hell is that?
It's the girl from the front desk.
Kids, sometimes you think
you're living out one story,
but the truth turns out
to be something else entirely.
At the time I thought the story
was about whether Robin should be
at the wedding.
If only I'd understood
what the real story was.
Having exes around...
I don't know, it brings up
unresolved things.
How do you know that spark won't come
back with your ex sitting out there?
Like things are not finished
between you two.
I wasted years trying to get
Lucy's dad to decide
if he was ready for this.
Seeing you guys...
It's made me realize
everything I had.
I used to dream that Tony would be
spontaneous like this.
Seriously, kids,
never invite an ex
to your wedding.