At Birmingham East,
the Returning Officer
is declaring the result.
James George Hacker: 21,793.
Arthur William Gaunt: 19,321.
So Jim Hacker's back, and after
many years as a Shadow Minister
seems almost certain to get
a post in the new Government.
- I haven't had a call yet.
- Who from?
- Our new Prime Minister.
- What do you expect?
The car's only just got back
from the Palace.
Any moment now, then.
So who was on the phone?
Frank Wiesel.
He's coming right over.
Why doesn't he just move in?
Annie, he's my political adviser.
- I depend on him.
- Why don't you marry him?
Darling, you do over- react
to everything, so.
Here we are!
Jim Hacker... yes.
Oh, it's you.
Yes, was a good party.
Yes, I've got a bit of a headache...
I will ring you back.
I'm waiting fora rather
important call... bye bye.
Alderman Spottiswood.
I wish people wouldn't ring
to congratulate me.
I'm waiting forthe call.
It's as if you're about
to enterthe Ministry.
Yes, but which Ministry,
that's the point.
Itwas a joke!
Oh, I see.
- Are you very tense?
- No, I'm not.
A politician's wife
is not allowed to.
A happy carefree
politician's wife.
- What are you looking for?
- A cigarette.
Try the cigarette box.
- It's empty.
- Take a librium.
I can't find it, that's why
I'm looking fora cigarette.
Oh, Jim, I've had it. Would you
pop out and get some?
Sorry, I daren't leave the phone.
If the PM wants you to be
in the cabinet,
he'll phone back.
Oryou can phone back.
I ran the campaign against
the PM forthe leadership.
- If I'm out, well, who knows.
- I could take a message.
There it is.
Hello... yes, speaking...
Oh, it's you Michael...
I haven't had a call,
have you?
Bill's had a call?
What's he got? Europe?
- Bill's got Europe.
- Lucky Europe.
- Does Bill speak French?
- He can hardly speak English.
I'll call you back if I hear
anything. Right... Bye.
Fingers crossed.
Hello... Yes, speaking...
The Gas Board.
Good Lord man,
thatwas weeks ago.
I'm waiting
fora rather important call...
Look, there happened to be
a general election yesterday...
You voted forthe otherside,
did you?
How did you get to the polling
booth on the right day?
With two assistants,
three return visits forspare parts?
Look, Mr. Franklin...
Frankly Franklin,
I don't care if the heating system
collapses in ruins.
I've got to get off this phone,
goodbye.
They won't come now.
If I get ConsumerAffairs,
they'll come.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Darling, thatwas
the front doorbell.
It'll be Frank.
- Martin's got the Foreign Office.
- Has he?
Jack's got Health
and Fred's got Energy.
- Has anyone got Brains?
- Do you mean Education?
No, I knowwhat I mean.
- What's left? What have I got?
- Rhythm?
Frank, I have heard
absolutely nothing,
not that it's surprising.
My whole career
is going down the drain
because the PM is unable
to reach me on the telephone.
You get it, darling.
- Hello.
- Hello, this is the BBC.
Would Mr. Hacker like to be
interviewed on the PM program?
- PM?
Jim Hackerhere...
Are you available this afternoon?
Yes. Any time you like.
Could we interview you?
I'd been hoping you'd call.
What job do you think
you're likely to get?
I beg yourpardon?
What job do you think
you're likely to get?
That's foryou to tell me.
- What?
- Well, it's not up to me to say.
That's forthe PM to say.
You're the PM's office...
Oh, I see.
The BBC PM office!
How silly, what a silly mistake,
Yes... yes. Good bye.
I did try and tell you.
You answerthe bloody thing.
Hello...
Mrs. Hackerspeaking.
Oh, congratulations,
"Prime Minister". It's Annie here.
Give me that phone.
Hello... Yes... Prime Minister.
Yes, of course... Yes, I...
Righto.
I'll be on the next train.
Top tip forAdministrative Affairs
is Jim Hacker.
Kenneth, isn't he on the young
side fora Cabinet post?
Yes, well, he's in his late forties.
But it's certainly
a jump up forhim.
On the otherhand,
this department's been
a bit of a political graveyard
recently.
A furthergroup
of Cabinet appointments
has nowbeen announced
from Number Ten.
The Ministry of Administrative
Affairs goes toJim Hacker,
the formerShadow Minister
forAgricultura.
- Good afternoon, Minister.
- Good afternoon.
Bernard Wooley,
Principal Private Secretary.
Mr. Lloyd Pritchard,
Assistant Private Secretary.
- This is my political adviser...
- Oh yes, of course, Mr. Weasel.
Wiesel.
I was the Minister's
Principal Private Secretary
in the last goverment.
However if you...
- I'm sure you'll be just the thing.
- Thank you, Minister, howkind.
- Where are we all going to?
- You are going to youroffice.
What about Frank?
- Where's Frank?
- He's being taken care of.
- Would you wait here?
- This is the Waiting Room.
- Precisely, sir.
- I'm Jim Hacker's adviser.
He has a whole department
to advise him.
- He needs me.
- Of course.
But until he sends foryou,
please, wait.
A sherry Minister?
Jim.
Oh Gin.
No, no, Jim, Jim.
Call me Jim.
I would preferto call you
Minister, Minister.
Minister, Minister?
Oh quite, quite.
I see what you mean.
Do I have to call you Private
Secretary, Private Secretary?
- No. Do call me Bernard.
- Thank you, Bernard.
You're mostwelcome.
Yourhealth, Minister.
Well what now?
Allowme to present
Sir Humphrey Appleby,
Permanent UnderSecretary
of State and Head of the D. A. A.
- Hello, Sir Humphrey.
- Hello, and welcome.
- Thank you.
- I believe you know each other.
Yes, we did cross swords in
the Public Accounts Committee.
I wouldn't say that.
You came up
with all the questions.
Opposition's about asking
questions.
And Government's about
not answering them.
You answered mine.
I'm glad you thought so.
Good luck.
- Who else is in this Department?
- I am the Permanent UnderSecretary
known as
the Permanent Secretary.
Wolley is your Principal
Private Secretary.
And I too have a Principal
Directly responsible to me
are 10 Deputy Secretaries
87 UnderSecretaries,
and 219 Assistant Secretaries.
Responsible to the PPS
are Parliamentary
Private Secretaries.
The PM will be appointing two
Parliamentary UnderSecretaries,
and you will appoint yourown
Parliamentary Private Secretary.
Can they all type?
None of us can type.
Mrs. McKay types.
She is the Secretary.
Pity we could have opened
an agency.
- Very droll, sir.
- Yes, very very amusing.
- I suppose they all say that.
- Certainly not, Minister.
Not quite all.
Right, now then, to business.
Forgive me if I'm a bit blunt,
but that's the sort of chap I am...
Frankly, this depart...
This chair's a bit...
We can change it, Minister.
We can change the furniture,
decor, office routine...
- Yourwish is ourcommand.
- I'd like a new chair.
Hate swivel chairs.
Two kinds of chairs to go
with the two kinds of Minister.
One sort folds up instantly,
the othersort goes
round and round in circles.
Now, frankly this Department
has got to cut
a great swathe through all this
stuffy Whitehall bureaucracy.
We're going to throw open
the windows,
let in a bit of fresh air,
cut through all the red tape,
streamline this creaking
old bureaucratic machine.
- You mean a clean sweep?
- A clean sweep.
Fartoo many people
just sitting behind desks.
Not like us, of course.
Butwe've got to get rid
of all those people.
- Get rid of them?
- "Redeploy them".
Yes. Good Lord no, I don't mean
put them out of work.
Open Government,
that's what my partybelieves in,
thatwas the main plank
of ourmanifesto.
Taking the nation
into ourconfidence.
Nowhow does that strike you?
Do sit down.
Just as you said in the House
on May 2nd last year,
and again on November 23rd,
and in The Observer
and in The Daily Mail,
and as yourmanifesto
made clear.
You know about that?
Please, have a look
at these proposals.
These are the ways
to implement this policy
and proposals fora white paper
foryourapproval.
The white papermight be called
"Open Government".
- You mean it's all been...
- Taken care of, Minister.
- Who did all this?
- The old bureaucratic machine.
No, quite seriously.
We are seized
of the need forreform.
- And we have taken it on board.
- I'm rathersurprised.
I expected to have
to fight you with this.
People do have funny ideas
about the Civil Service.
We're just here
to implement yourpolicies.
"Proposals forshortening approval
procedures in planning appeals"?
Hansard Volume 497,
page 1102, Column B.
Quote "Mr. Hacker:
Is the Ministeraware
that planning procedures
make building a bungalow
in the 20th century
slowerthan building a cathedral
in the 12th century?
Opposition laughter
and Government cries of shame".
- They didn't actually cry shame.
- Quite so, Minister.
- Right, I think that's it then?
- There are two more things...
This is yourdiary
fornextweek, Minister.
My diary?
You didn't know I was coming.
Norwho'd win the election.
- There'd be a Minister, Minister.
- Don't start that again.
Even though we didn't know
itwould be you.
Her Majesty does like
the business of government
to continue even when
there are no politicians around.
- Bit difficult surely?
- Yes... and no.
It's a busy week.
Nine cabinet committees,
the Annual dinner
of the Law Institute.
You will have to make a speech.
Deputation from the British
ComputerAssociation.
Opening the National Union
of Public Employers meeting.
- Anotherspeech...
- Wait a minute...
- What about all the otherthings?
- What otherthings?
I'm on fourpolicy committees
forthe party.
You won'twant to be putting
partybefore country.
No, no, of course not.
I'll just fetch yourboxes,
Minister.
Boxes? Already.
The last Ministerhad some work
throughout the campaign,
but I fear... well,
it's not forme to criticise...
- What do you mean?
- It's a harsh thing to say.
Some of the boxes actually came
back with the work not done.
If you complete the first four
by Saturday,
yourdriverwill deliver
the othertwo.
Villa's at home to Liverpool.
And I've got a surgery
on Saturday.
If we minimise it, you need only
take the majorpolicy decisions.
No, no. No. No. I take
all the decisions round here.
Now then what time
shall I come in on Monday?
You'll catch the 7.45 train
from New Street,
and yourdriver
will meet you at Euston.
If I could just put in
these draft proposals.
And here, this is yourkey,
Minister.
Out of my way.
I've had enough of this.
- You can't go in there.
- Just try and stop me.
- Jim, what's going on?
- Frank, where've you been?
- Stuck in the waiting room.
- We are in private conference.
- Then I should be here, too.
- Calm down, Frank.
Humphrey, Frank has got
to have an office ofhis own.
- Certainly, if you insist.
- I do insist.
I do think we have some spare
office space in Walthamstow.
- Walthamstow?
- Yes, it's surprising.
The Government owns property
all over London.
- I don'twant to be there.
- It's in a very nice part.
Walthamstow's
a very nice place so I gather.
- I need an office here.
- Why's that?
Yes, I agree with Frank.
Bernard, we must find
an office here for Mr. Weasel.
Wiesel.
Copies of all the papers
that come to me go to Frank.
- All?
- All.
It shall be done.
All the appropriate papers.
How's yournew Minister,
Humphrey?
Learning the rules
very quicklyfora newboy.
- How's yournew Cabinet?
- No problem.
Similarto the last one.
Arnold, I hearthe American
Ambassador's been spending
a lot of time with the PM.
- Yes.
- Defence ortrade?
Both.
The aerospace systems contract?
Ssh. Don'twant the cabinet
to hearabout it yet.
This aerospace thingumy would be
rathera coup forthe PM,
wouldn't it?
Yes, now the new PM
will take the credit.
Sorry to intrude SirArnold,
Sir Humphrey,
if you could just OK
the Minister's speech,
I can get it
straight to the House.
Yes, of course. Like to join us?
Oh, thank you,
so long as I'm not too long.
Get yourself a cup of coffee.
So itwould be rather
an embarrassment to the PM,
wouldn't it? if a hypothetical
Ministerwere to rock
the Anglo American boat?
Grave embarrassment.
How grave?
Man overboard, I should think.
Enough to cut short a promising
new Ministerial career?
No question.
Pull up a chair, Bernard...
And tell us what you think
of ournew Minister.
Well absolutelyfine.
Yes, we'll have him
housetrained in no time.
He swallowed the whole diary,
and I gatherhe did his boxes
like a lamb lastweekend?
Yes. Yes he did.
We must head him off
this Open Government nonsense.
We were calling the White Paper
"Open Government".
Always dispose of the difficult bit
in the title.
Does less harm there
than in the text.
The less you intend
to do about something,
the more you have
to talk about it.
What's wrong
with open government?
Why shouldn't the public know
more about what's going on?
Are you serious?
Well, I mean it's
the Minister's policy, afterall.
It's a contradiction in terms.
You can be open
oryou can have government.
But surely the citizens of a
democracy have a right to know.
No. They have a right
to be ignorant.
Knowledge only means
complicity and guilt.
Ignorance has a certain dignity.
But if the Ministerwants...
You don't just give people
what they want,
if it's not good forthem.
Do you give brandy
to an alcoholic?
Thatway people don't know
what you are doing wrong.
I am the Minister's Private
Secretary, and ifhe wants...
You must not help him
to make a fool ofhimself.
Look at the Ministers we've had.
They would have been
a laughing stock
had it not been forthe most rigid
secrecy about theirdoings.
What do you propose to do?
- Can you keep a secret?
- Of course.
So can I.
Excuse me,
I have to make a phone call.
Well, I'd betterbe getting
this back to the Minister.
Martin. Has the weasel
had a copy of the invoice
forthe new American
addressing machines?
I thought you said
it was sensitive.
So it is.
Get it to him today.
Oh, and Martin, let him find it
nearthe bottom of the pile.
Jim, Jim.
- Yes.
- Look what I've found.
We've got them
by the short and curlies.
We've got Sir Humphrey
Bloody Appleby
and Mr. Toffee Nosed
Snooty Wolley
just where we want them.
See this?
This innocent-looking
piece of paper.
Political dynamite.
Calm down.
What are you talking about?
This is an invoice for 1.000
computervideo display terminals.
At 10.000 pounds each,
that is, ten milion pounds.
So?
Made by the Pittsburgh
Manufacturing Corporation Inc.,
- Imported from America?
- I know.
Butwe make computerperipherals
in this country.
- In my constituency.
- I know!
- What about unemployment?
This must be stopped.
- Sir Humphrey to see... oh sorry.
- Oh no. No, come in.
I want to see you both, come on.
Sir Humphrey, take a seat.
Thank you, Minister.
Now then, Frank here
has just discovered this contract
forthe import
of ten million pound's worth
of video display terminals,
from America.
May I see?
Oh yes. Forthe whole
Civil Service in Whitehall.
- But they're not British.
- That is true.
- We make them in this country.
- Not of the same quality.
Betterquality.
In my constituency.
- We were advised...
- This contract must be stopped.
It's beyond my power. This can
only be cancelled by the Treasury.
Why's that?
Would be a majorpolicy change
forthe Civil Service
to cancel contracts, especially
with overseas suppliers.
If you'd like to take it up
with the Cabinet.
How am I to face
my constituency party?
Why need they know?
Why need anybody know?
We can see that it nevergets out.
- Open Government.
- That's right.
- It must be published.
Why?
Well... er...
- Why, Frank?
- The manifesto.
And yourpredecessor
will look like a traitor.
- Two unanswerable reasons.
- You didn't bargain forthis!
You're not suggesting
that the Ministershould make
a positive reference
to this confidential transaction
in a speech?
Speech. That's it.
Jim, what about the speech
to the Union of office Employees?
I'll tell them about
this scandalous contract.
And we'll release it
to the press today.
- Who's running the country now?
- Well... yes.
- You object?
- It might be regrettable,
- if we upset the Americans.
- The Americans.
It's time they lose
theircommercial complacency.
We must think of the British
poor, not the American rich!
If that is yourexpress wish,
the Departmentwill back you,
up to the hilt.
That is my express wish.
I'd bettercirculate
the speech forclearance.
It does not involve
any otherdepartment.
Open Government demands
thatwe include ourcolleagues,
as well as ourfriends
in Fleet Street.
- Oh yes, that's fairenough.
- I'm not sure.
Thank you. And Humphrey...
See that goes
straight to the press.
We shall serve
yourbest interests.
Thank you.
Now then...
Let me see.
We've made a pledge to the
people about open government.
So let's have some.
I have discovered
that the previous government
signed a contract to import
office equipment
- foruse by the Civil Service...
- Bureaucracy!
Used by the Civil Service
bureaucracy.
So, we are being fobbed off
with second rate American junk
by smart Aleck salesmen
from Pittsburgh
while British factories
stand empty
and British workmen
queue up forthe dole.
- Unemployment benefit.
- The dole, Bernard.
"Much as I personally value
the friendship of ourgreat cousins
from across the sea".
- Minister, something's come up.
- Yes?
- A minute from the PM's Office.
- I'm prettybusy.
- You ought to read this.
- What does it say?
The PM is planning
a visit to Washington
fora valuable Anglo American
defence trade agreement.
Its importance
cannot be overestimated.
Fine. Has my speech gone
to the press?
I presume so, as you requested.
I'm sorry, but all hell's just
broken loose at NumberTen.
They're asking why yourspeech
didn't obtain clearance.
- What did you say?
- I mentioned open government.
But it seemed
to make things worse.
The PM wants to see you
in the House, right away.
What's going to happen?
The Prime Ministergiveth
and he taketh away.
Blessed be the name
of the Prime Minister.
Hello, Vic...
Sir Humphrey Appleby,
Vic Gould, ourChiefWhip.
You really are a pain in the arse.
The PM's going up the wall.
Hitting the roof.
You can't go around
making speeches like that.
It's Open Government.
- Shut up, Weasel.
- Wiesel!
But Open Governmentwas
the main plank in ourmanifesto.
- The PM believes in it too.
- Open, yes. But not gaping.
In politics you have to say things
with tact, you berk!
And when to say nothing at all.
- How long you been a Minister?
- Week and half.
You will appear
in the Guinness book of records.
I can see the headlines already.
"Cabinet split on U. S. Trade.
Hacker leads revolt
against Prime Minister.
That's what you want, is it?
Ah, SirArnold, what news?
That speech is causing
the PM some distress.
Has it been released
to the Press?
Well, the Ministergave
express instructions fornoon.
- Isn't that right?
- I'm appalled at you, Humphrey.
How could you let the Minister
put himself in this position?
We believe in open government.
We want to open the windows.
Isn't that right, Minister?
It's good party stuff,
but it puts the PM
in a very difficult situation.
What about Open Government?
This seems to be the closed season
foropen government.
Do you want to give thought
to a draft letterof resignation?
Just in case...
Can'twe hush it up?
- Hush it up?
- Yes, hush it up.
You mean... suppress it?
Yes, I suppose I do.
You mean thatwithin
the framework of the guidelines
about open goverment
that you have laid down,
you're suggesting we should
adopt a more flexible posture?
Am I? Oh yes. Yes.
About the press release...
A development could precipitate
a reappraisal of ourposition.
We forgot the interdepartmental
clearance procedure.
The supplementary stop order
came into effect.
So, yourspeech
hasn't gone to the Press.
It's only gone
to the PM's Private Office
and the Duty Officerhad
no instructions to pass it out
- without clearance.
- But how come?
The fault is entirely mine, Minister.
The holding up
of press releases dates back to
before open government,
and I unaccountably omitted
to rescind it.
- I hope you forgive this lapse.
- Well, yes, of course.
- That's quite all right.
- Thank you, Minister.
Afterall, we all make mistakes.
Yes, Minister.