Previously on Why Women Kill...
BETH ANN: I used to play the piano.
- Do you still play?
- My husband...
didn't care for my playing.
Our daughter died because of me.
I'm the one who's responsible.
It seems I only have six months to live.
[CRYING]: Six months!
I thought a clean break
was just better for...
I'm pregnant.
He got down on one knee
and asked me if I would marry him.
He told me that his marriage is ending.
He said he just needs six months.
Six months.
MAUREEN: Do you know
your husband's a homosexual?
He has that new disease that
all the gay men are spreading.
That's a lie.
He's the third man my
husband's seen who's had it.
The first two are dead.
You need care.
Karl, you think I'd leave
you at a time like this?
TOMMY: Cancel the trip?
That's not fair.
This was supposed to be
the best summer of my life.
And this could be the last
summer of Karl's life,
so please stop sulking.
NAOMI: What's happened to my boy?
Tommy's been in a car accident.
He needed some stitches.
What in the world?
NURSE: Is that a tattoo?
One of these days he'll regret that.
So will she.
- Oh. Wow.
- Right?
- You bought me a car?
- I said I would take care of you.
JADE: You can't return the car.
It's not yours.
Yeah, but he's coked out of his mind.
To accept a gift from
a man in that condition
is not a good look.
- Just give me the keys.
- Stop it.
Go upstairs, get your stuff!
I want you out of my house now!
That's not gonna happen.
How can I help?
Tell me everything you know about Jade.
Well, for starters,
that's not her real name.
[PHONE CHIMES]
_
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
♪ "L" is for the way you look ♪
♪ At me ♪
♪ "O" is for the only one ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ "V" is very, very ♪
♪ Extraordinary ♪
♪ "E" is even more ♪
♪ Than anyone that you adore can ♪
♪ Love is all ♪
♪ That I can give to you ♪
♪ Love is more ♪
♪ Than just a game for two ♪
♪ Two in love can make it ♪
♪ Take my heart and
please don't break it ♪
♪ Love was made ♪
♪ For me and you... ♪
EMILY: My name is Emily Stanton.
I was killed over two years ago,
but my mama still thinks
about me every day.
Even when she's just
putting on lipstick,
she'll suddenly remember
how much she loved me.
I look down on Mama from heaven.
I watch her because
I'm worried about her.
She's not happy,
but Daddy doesn't know...
because she keeps smiling.
Mama is very angry with him,
and I have a feeling
that she's gonna do something awful.
So, what have you got
planned for the day?
Oh, nothing much.
I'll be spending time with a new friend.
Oh? What's her name?
June.
I have a feeling you'd really like her.
And what are you two doing?
I offered to drive her to
a doctor's appointment,
but that's really just an excuse
for me to talk to her
about the man she's seeing.
Why?
I don't approve of the relationship,
so I've decided to break them up.
Beth Ann, that's not nice.
Maybe not,
but it's necessary.
ED: My name is Edmund Harte.
I was 57 when I died.
That's how my bitch
wife became my widow.
I check in from time to time
to see how my kid is doing,
'cause I'm worried about him.
His mother is desperate to control him,
but Tommy's a man now,
able to make his own choices.
And I know Naomi is going to fight him
every step of the way.
Good luck, kid.
My poor baby.
Simone?
No, it's me.
Mom. Oh, God.
It's okay, I know everything.
You don't have to protect her anymore.
And I am not angry,
not at you anyway.
NURSE: Mrs. Harte?
The hospital administrator has arrived.
Ah, thank you.
Mr. Kern, thank you so much
for agreeing to see me.
How can I help you, Ms. Harte?
Do you happen to know Simone Grove?
I do. She's one of our
hospital's biggest fundraisers.
Yes. Well, in between benefit galas,
it seems that Simone has
been molesting my son,
possibly for years.
If you allow her to
visit or even phone him,
I will sue this hospital and I will win.
Do you understand?
Yes. Um, I'm-I'm so sorry.
Rest assured,
this matter will be handled
with the utmost discretion.
No need to be discreet on my account.
I intend on telling
everyone in this town
what that woman has done to my family.
Nice tie.
VERNA: My name is Verna Roy.
I was 32 when I died in a fire.
At the time,
I was a foster mother
to this one right here.
I don't like to talk
bad about the living,
but this gal's pure poison.
I can see she's now living
in a fancy house with pretty things.
That means some man
has fallen for her act.
Eli, you're gonna be late!
VERNA: Stupid son of a bitch.
He don't know what she's capable of,
but I got a feeling
he's about to find out.
Wow.
Moving kind of slow today.
What did you give me last night,
a horse tranquilizer?
Well, I wouldn't have
to give you anything
if you'd stop doing coke after 10:00.
You talk like I have self-control.
I'm almost embarrassed for you.
Well, whatever. Here, look.
I've got a surprise.
ELI: Whoa. What's the occasion?
It's Scorsese day.
Oh, look, it's just a meeting.
I mean, the odds of
him directing my movie
are, like, a million to one.
He loved your script.
I think that's a big deal.
God, I just...
I hope I can burn this off by 10:00.
I feel so out of it.
Well, luckily for you,
I know how to prepare
a well-balanced meal.
Mmm. You take such good care of me.
Scorsese's gonna direct
your movie, I know it,
and it's gonna be a big hit
and we are going to be so rich.
From your lips...
I always knew something exciting
would happen to me one day.
I think this is it.
Again, all right, it's just a meeting.
I'm not worried.
This is the year where
all my dreams come true.
[CHUCKLES]
Hello, Jenny.
Oh, Mr. and Mrs. Grove.
Please tell me you have
the veal piccata tonight.
Just the thought of it
has kept me going all day.
I'm sorry, but I can't seat you.
Oh... oh, you're not overbooked again?
Well, I see our usual table is empty.
I don't know who you promised it to,
but they should have gotten here sooner.
KARL: Here we are, my darling.
Thank you.
- There we go.
- Anyway, I've been trying to talk
to Tommy in the hospital,
but I can't seem to get through to him.
It's bizarre.
Sorry, darling, is it my imagination,
or are people staring at us?
I'm wearing Givenchy.
They always stare when I wear Givenchy.
No, no, I think, actually,
they're just staring at me.
You're right.
It must be your jacket.
I told you plaid is over.
Mr. and Mrs. Grove.
Henry, how lovely to see you.
I'm terribly sorry, but I'm afraid
I have to ask you to leave.
Oh, for God's sake,
he can take the jacket off.
What's wrong?
Someone should have notified you.
Your membership to the
club has been revoked.
[SCOFFS] You can't be serious.
The committee met this afternoon.
The vote was unanimous.
W... We've belonged to
this club for 15 years.
Why on earth would you
want to kick us out?
It's because I'm ill, isn't it?
We have to protect our members.
It's a sexually transmitted disease.
You don't get it by sharing
a fucking tennis court.
All the same, your membership
contract has a morals clause.
[GASPS] Of all the people here,
you think we're the
ones who lack morals?
Mason Reed over there
is addicted to heroin,
and Susan Paul is sleeping
with her brother-in-law.
And you don't want to know
what happens in the club sauna.
That's not helpful.
For the last time,
Mr. and Mrs. Grove, please go.
Shall we?
Would you mind terribly...
Oh, thank you.
Goodbye, Henry.
[PATRONS GASP AND MURMUR]
Good for you, dear.
Oh, don't worry, Henry,
I'm gonna drink mine.
Thank you again for
recommending this obstetrician.
I talked to him on the phone,
he sounds wonderful.
Sheila?
- Hmm?
- [CHUCKLES]
What are you thinking about?
Uh, your upcoming wedding.
Aw. You excited for me?
- [CHUCKLES]
- I am.
Oh...
I'm curious,
have you had a chance to
discuss Rob's expectations?
- Expectations?
- Well, you want a career.
Some men don't allow
their wives to work.
Oh, well,
Rob knows I want to be a singer.
We've talked about it a lot.
Since you've become pregnant?
Well...
No.
Might be time for a chat.
Rob strikes me as the
kind of man who'd prefer
his wife to stay home.
You talk like you know him.
Oh, I know his type.
Rich, successful.
That kind of man wants
his wife in the kitchen,
feeding the kids and
pouring his martini.
Rob's not like that.
You absolutely sure?
Well, he better be okay with it,
or we're gonna have a problem.
That's what I was thinking.
Okay, according to this,
we're looking for Suite 203.
APRIL: Sheila.
Coming!
You okay?
Yeah, man, I'm sorry,
I'm just, I'm really nervous.
You know, I basically
grew up on Scorsese movies.
Hey, buddy, do me a favor.
I want you to manage your expectations
before we walk in here.
Shit. Why? Is he an asshole?
Let's just say it isn't
gonna be the meeting
you were hoping for.
What the fuck?
Hello, Eli.
[SCOFFS]
So I was never meeting Scorsese?
Sorry. You really need to hear her out.
Why?
Is this some sort of
bullshit intervention?
Something like that.
I'm gonna go get some coffee.
You want a cup?
No. Cool. Cool.
Well, this is humiliating.
Eli, that wasn't my intention.
But we need to talk. Privately.
About?
Irene Tabatchnick.
Who the hell's Irene Tabatchnick?
The woman who's been
sleeping in our bed.
You may want to sit down
for the rest of this.
If Dr. Bennett's wife told people,
that is a violation of
doctor-patient confidentiality.
We should have his license revoked.
How much energy do we really
want to devote to all this?
This is discrimination.
We have to fight back.
And draw more attention to
my sex life and my disease?
You don't think people
will be sympathetic?
On the contrary.
I think the situation's
going to get much worse
before it gets better.
Well, we won't dwell on it.
Why don't you take a
nice, long, hot bath?
You seem exhausted.
Mm.
Turns out being shunned by Republicans
takes rather a lot out of a person.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Naomi, I've been trying to reach you.
How's Tommy?
He's fine.
Well, I keep calling the hospital,
but I can never seem to get through.
What are in the bags?
Ah, presents.
For me?
No, from you.
Every gift you ever gave me,
I'm returning them.
I don't understand.
This lovely figurine you got me
while you were in Bavaria.
I don't want it anymore.
What the hell?!
Or this sweet silver music box.
I don't need that either.
Have you lost your mind?
I have,
because I know what you did to my son.
Oh.
That's all you have to say?
I-I understand your anger,
but if you'll just give
me a chance to explain...
I will, just as soon as I return
this darling crystal paperweight.
Stop it!
You can't come in here
and destroy my home.
Why not?
You destroyed my life.
If we can't talk about this rationally,
I will call the police.
Go ahead, I'm leaving.
You know, I would say that I'll
see you at the country club,
but, you know...
It was you.
Who got you voted out?
Yes.
The board didn't need much persuading
once they knew that Karl
was spreading a deadly disease.
We were unceremoniously ejected
in front of all of our friends.
I hope you're satisfied.
Satisfied?
You seduced my child.
Do you honestly think
that I would be satisfied
just getting you kicked
out of a country club?
I am just getting started, bitch.
And before I am done, I will burn you,
your business, and this poorly
decorated shithole
to the ground!
Satisfied?
[SCOFFS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
What the hell happened here?
Things just got worse.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Sorry to intrude.
I was wondering if I could
borrow a cup of sugar.
I'm baking a cake,
and I forgot to check my pantry.
You don't really need
a cup of sugar, do you?
No.
Come on in.
Can I ask what happened?
We were at a department store,
and the sales clerk recognized me.
It turns out that he'd
gone to my high school
two years after I did,
so he knew a lot of my old friends.
We only spoke for five minutes.
After we got back,
Ralph accused me
of trying to seduce the man.
That's why?
He thought you were flirting?
He gets jealous. He can't help it.
I don't understand how
you can live like this.
You can't possibly be happy.
I'm not.
So why don't you leave?
I could ask you the same question.
What?
Isn't your husband cheating on you?
He is.
I had a feeling you knew.
So why don't you leave him?
It's an entirely different situation.
He's humiliating you.
That's got to hurt.
It does.
Will you ever trust him again?
No.
And if you did leave Rob,
would he try and kill you?
Of course not.
Well, my husband would.
He likes to threaten me
with a loaded gun he keeps
in his bedside drawer.
So I stay.
What in God's name is your excuse?
I keep hoping for a miracle.
That one day everything will change.
You and I should be friends.
We have a lot in common.
Irene Tabatchnick is from Ohio.
By the time she was
16, she was thrown out
of three foster homes.
The first two times,
Irene had been caught stealing cash.
So what? She was young. She was a kid.
She was kicked out of her third home
because her foster mother accused her
of trying to seduce her husband.
Maybe the woman was in denial
about what her husband was up to.
Oh, we'll never know.
A week later, that house burned down.
Burned down?
Those foster parents died, Eli.
And Irene Tabatchnick just disappeared.
So, what, you think she...?
I mean, we can't prove anything,
but the cops in Ohio
are dying to talk to her.
Th-This is just so stupid.
This is... There's no way that Jade...
Her name is Irene.
Whatever.
She loves us.
If she loved you,
would she keep giving you cocaine?
You look terrible, by the way.
Thank you.
Come on, Eli.
She keeps you high so she
can take advantage of you.
So that you let her live in our house,
so that you buy her a new car.
You know, you didn't need to trick me
to have this conversation, Taylor.
You could've just called.
I did call. Every hour.
What are you talking about?
You never called me.
I most certainly did.
Look. Look.
No missed calls. No voice mails.
That sneaky bitch blocked my number.
On my phone?
She couldn't do that
without my pass code.
Well, she has your pass code.
How does she have that?
I gave it to her.
So you could take away my money.
- To keep you from buying drugs.
- Jesus.
You know what,
maybe she does take advantage of me,
but at least she builds me up.
She doesn't make me feel
like a fuck-up who's just
destined to crash and burn.
The only reason why I think
you're gonna crash and burn,
Eli, is because you've done it before.
You have no idea what it feels like
to come home from work
and then find you convulsing
on the kitchen floor.
And then to call the ambulance,
which took forever.
I'm not gonna do that again, Eli.
I'm... [SIGHS]
No one is asking you to.
I don't need your help.
I've got my career back. I'm fine.
The only one here with a problem is you.
You're an addict, Eli.
You need to go to
rehab, and you know it.
The only thing I know, Taylor, is that
this conversation is over.
- Eli, please stop...
- Stop!
Enough! Let me go.
[BETH ANN CHUCKLES]
- You like your new ball, don't you?
- Yes.
After dinner, we're going
to write a thank you note
to Aunt Lydia.
I don't know how to write.
I'll do the writing.
You can draw a big heart
right next to our names.
Look, dear, your father forgot
to bring in the trash can.
Play here for a second.
I'll be right back.
Come along, Emily.
Don't you want to show
your daddy your new ball?
Yes.
Hey there.
What are you two doing home?
I didn't expect you
back for another hour.
Aunt Lydia wasn't feeling well.
We had to cut our visit short.
Hey, princess, what do you got there?
A ball. Aunt Lydia gave it
to me for my birthday.
Well...
Her birthday was two months ago.
Be nice. It's the thought that counts.
Can I go play?
Of course you can.
Rob, did you lose a button?
I just found one on the floor.
Ah. Oh, I guess I did. Thanks.
- Mama.
- I'm sorry, honey.
Here you go.
I'm making mac and cheese for dinner,
so don't be too long, okay?
[TIRES SKID]
[LOUD THUMP]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[INDISTINCT ALARMED CHATTER]
Honey?
Someone call a doctor.
[SCREAMING]
Emily?
Emily, honey, wake up.
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes, honey.
[SOBBING]: Open your eyes.
Please wake up.
Please... Please...
What the hell?
[SCREAMING]
Who was driving this car?!
Sh-She, uh, she-she came out
of nowhere, mister, I swear.
I tried to stop...
You left the gate open?
- No. I'm sure I locked it.
- You're sure?
Then how did Emily get
out of the backyard?
The latch is six feet off the ground!
I don't know. Maybe I forgot.
You didn't lock the gate.
You didn't lock the gate,
and you let her out to play.
[CRYING]: I had to make dinner.
That's no excuse.
Our baby is dead.
I'm sorry.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
I thought it was locked.
[KISSES]
Amy.
I just got a call from Naomi.
Does Karl have AIDS?
How could you not tell me?
Well, we thought we had time.
I mean, as you can see,
I'm not exactly at death's door.
He has all the best
doctors, so don't worry.
Karl will absolutely be able
to walk you down the aisle.
At this point, I'm not even
sure there will be a wedding.
What?
Naomi's called all of our friends
and told them Karl is sick.
People have been
canceling right and left.
Oh, Lord.
And if nobody's coming, why bother?
Oh, I'm so sorry, my darling.
Is there anything we can do?
Well...
we might be able
to salvage this thing if...
you didn't come.
To the wedding?
I understand.
Uh, of course, I will stay home.
Thank you.
No. Karl has to be at the wedding.
Who's gonna walk you down the aisle?
You can do it.
I did not spend $6,000
on an Armani dress
just to give it a shared entrance.
Okay, let's not argue.
Thank you.
I don't mind.
No!
We are a family.
When bad things happen,
we're supposed to support each other.
The way I see it,
he is supporting me, by staying away.
I have to call my guests and
tell them it's safe to come.
Amy, think of what you're doing.
You're choosing a few cowardly bigots
over the man who raised you.
I'm the bride.
It's my day,
and I want it to be perfect.
I am sorry if Karl's deadly illness
is scraping some of the
glitter off of your event,
but let's face it,
this won't be your last wedding.
- Nice.
- More importantly,
if Karl can't attend, I won't either.
- Oh, Simone.
- Fine.
Stay home.
You'll save me some embarrassment.
Karl's not the only one
everybody's talking about.
[DOOR CLOSES]
My daughter is a monster.
Well, she's a bride.
It's basically the same thing.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Hey!
So... how'd the meeting go?
I want to hear everything.
Well, let's just say
that Scorsese's not gonna
be directing my movie.
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry.
But at least he loved the script, right?
- He did. Yeah.
- Good.
Yeah. Yeah, he especially liked the part
where Eva burns the drug
dealer's house down.
[CHUCKLES] He liked that?
Yeah.
Yeah, he liked it so much,
he asked me how I came up with it,
and, you know, of course I had
to tell him it was your idea.
[LAUGHS]
You didn't have to give me credit.
Yeah, well...
How did you come up with
that, by the way?
Uh, it just came to me.
Just out of the blue?
Yeah.
'Cause it-it's such
an unusual concept, you know,
arson as a form of revenge.
You have no idea how that came to you?
Why does it matter?
I-I'm-I'm just curious.
I don't know...
It just popped into my head.
Just, boop?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Boop. Yeah.
Sometimes, that happens.
Is that how you came
up with the name Jade?
It just popped into your head?
What? [CHUCKLES]
It suits you better than Irene,
I'll give you that.
Who have you been talking to?
Hey, watch the road.
Eli, do not fuck with me.
Or else what,
you're gonna burn down my house?
You talked to Duke?
Oh, my God. You did those things.
Did what? What did he say about me?
Oh, my God, you killed those people.
Oh, my God.
- Eli, Eli, the man is a liar!
- Hey, hey.
- All right, slow down, slow down.
- Eli, you can't believe
- a fucking word he says!
- Jesus, watch out!
[CRASH]
Karl, it's after 11:00.
When are you going to the gallery?
When people stop assuming
you can catch AIDS from a lithograph.
Oh, screw them all.
Shall we have lunch at the Huntington?
- Well, if you're paying.
- Good.
I can't spend another afternoon
staring at these walls.
Oh, I can't either.
What were we thinking
with all the damn purple?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER NEARBY]
- Is it just my imagination or...?
- No.
No. They're staring at us.
[SIGHS] What have we done now?
[GASPS]
_
Oh, my God.
Wha...
Did anyone see who did this?
Someone had to have seen something.
Don't just gawk. Answer me!
- Simone.
- [GASPS] Karl!
I'm-I'm a little dizzy.
I just need to go inside and lie down.
You need to see a doctor.
Can you make it to the car?
Can someone please help us?
Please help us to the car!
Is he the one with AIDS?
Who cares? He's a human being!
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
You know, I'm so grateful. [STAMMERS]
I want to hire you to
work on our property.
Darling,
he's worked for us for six years.
Oh, of course.
Um, thank you very much, uh...
- Julio.
- Right.
Julio. Here you go.
[BOTH PANTING]
- Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
- [GROANS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
I have to go.
What?
- Mmm. [CHUCKLES]
- God, I missed you.
I missed this.
Mmm, me, too.
[CHUCKLES]
So, I had an interesting day.
Yeah?
I talked to Mr. Porter,
that fella who runs the nightclub,
I told him about the baby.
Ah.
What did he have to say?
Well, he said congratulations.
He also said, once I have the baby,
he wants me right back up on that stage.
Isn't that terrific?
Yeah.
- Wow.
- [CHUCKLES]
I knew you would think so.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
But isn't it a little
early to talk about this?
Why don't we see how you
feel after the baby arrives?
I won't feel any different.
Well, taking care of
a baby is hard work.
You might be too tired to keep singing.
I'll never be too tired to sing.
We'll see.
- Rob...
- Hmm?
Hey.
It's my dream.
And dreams are great,
but you have to be realistic.
It's a tough business to break into.
I know.
My Beth Ann wanted to
be in show business, and...
she finally came to her senses and...
... gave it up. Thank God.
Well, maybe I'm more
talented than she is.
She wasn't half-bad.
She wanted to play piano.
Piano?
Yeah, she wanted to
be a concert pianist,
which is ridiculous.
But you do what you want.
As long as dinner's on
the table when I get home,
what do I care?
You know, it's kind of funny.
Uh, my friend Sheila also
wanted to be a concert pianist.
Yeah? Small world.
Well, I got to go.
- I'll call you tonight.
- Mmm.
DR. CHARLES: Mrs. Grove?
Yes?
Based on the initial exam,
we think your husband probably
has Pneumocystis pneumonia,
an infection common in men
with suppressed immune systems.
How serious is it?
Most patients recover with treatment.
"Most"? Do you mean some don't?
We're gonna run some tests,
then we'll know more.
Thank you.
Naomi.
Nurse, put that down
- and call security.
- SIMONE: Don't bother.
I just have one thing
to say and then I'll go.
If you think I'm gonna let you
go anywhere near my child...
I'm not here for Tommy.
I'm here to apologize.
An apology? Now?
Color me disinterested.
Then just tell me what I have to do...
to do to get you to leave Karl alone.
I haven't done anything to him.
You have spread your poison
and made him a pariah.
He has lost friends,
been banned from his daughter's wedding,
had his home vandalized.
God, he's sick.
He does not deserve
to spend his last days
hounded by scandal and shame.
Maybe he doesn't,
but if Karl's caught in the crossfire,
it's only because he's been
standing too close to you.
Naomi, I am begging.
Blame me, destroy me.
I promise I won't fight back.
But please leave Karl out of it.
Mom.
What have you done?
Eli.
Are you his wife?
Yeah.
Is he okay? Why...
why is he unconscious?
He needed to be sedated.
His ribs are fractured,
but he'll recover.
Oh, thank God.
Before we put him out,
he was asking for you.
We told him you were on your way.
I came as fast as I could.
He wrote you this note.
Said it was important.
_
Everything okay?
Yeah. I think it will be.
It's gonna be a while
before he wakes up.
Well, I'm gonna be here when he does.
Mrs. Stanton.
Hello, Claire.
I need to speak to Rob.
He's not here.
How long until he returns?
I'm not sure.
Are you going on a trip?
I'm going back home to Kansas.
- For a visit?
- No.
I'm leaving Rob.
He's been having an affair.
He doesn't know I know,
and I thought I should
tell him in person.
Oh, Mrs. Stanton, I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
Do you have any idea where he might be?
He's at her apartment.
So you've known about this.
I wish you had told me.
I thought we were friends.
I haven't been your friend,
not for one second.
And you should hate me
for everything I've done to you.
What are you talking about?
Rob's been cheating on you for years...
with all sorts of women.
And I was one of them.
I was protecting you.
By destroying their lives?
She took advantage of you.
No. I pursued her.
And what we had, it was real.
You only think that because
she twisted your mind.
Trust me,
you are better off without her.
No, maybe I'd be better off without you.
Tommy...
Dad always said that
you were vindictive,
and I should get away from you
as soon as I got the chance.
Your dad was a pathetic drunk.
But he had your number.
I'm leaving tonight.
And I'll be on the first plane
to Europe in the morning.
Well, you think I'm just
gonna pay for you to go
traipsing around Europe?
I'm 18. I have access to my trust fund.
I don't need anything from you.
I am still your mother.
No, from now on, you're just
some lady that I used to know.
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
You pulling out?
Not yet.
I'm waiting for someone.
You have to understand,
I have wanted to tell you
for years, but...
Oh, God, I am so ashamed.
I'm leaving him, Claire.
It doesn't matter anymore.
You won't feel that way
once I've told you the rest.
There's something else?
[SIGHS]
The last time I slept
with your husband...
... was the day your child died.
CLAIRE: We were in your
bedroom at your old house...
- [CAR DOOR SLAMS]
- ... when Rob heard a car door slam.
He got up to see you and your daughter
had come home early.
He yelled at me to get dressed.
You began dragging a trash can
to the backyard,
so we had time to run downstairs.
I was going to hide in a closet,
but Rob said it was too dangerous.
So he told me to get out
through the side of the house.
So while you were coming
in the front door...
Hey there.
... I ran around
the side of the house...
... and left through the gate.
And I left it open.
A few hours later,
someone from work called.
They told me what had happened,
and I instantly knew it was my fault.
Oh, Mrs. Stanton,
I can't even begin to
tell you how sorry I am.
I have one question.
What's that?
Did Rob know you had
not closed the gate?
I called him that night and I told him.
And he said he could forgive me...
if I never told anyone
else what had happened.
And I didn't.
I was so ashamed.
[SOBBING]
I know you can't forgive
me for what I've done,
but I will spend the rest of my life
trying to atone for what I did to you.
[SOBBING]
Get up.
You did... a horrible thing, Claire.
But I'll forgive you
if you promise to do one thing for me.
Oh...
Anything.
You will never tell another living soul
that we had this conversation.
What?
Rob can't know.
I've decided not to leave him.
I don't understand.
You don't have to.
All you need to do is
give me your solemn vow.
Do that...
and you have my forgiveness.
Okay.
I promise.
Thank you, Claire.
Hey, girl,
what are you doing here?
She missed you.
Jade.
I hope you don't mind.
I let myself in. Your lock's busted.
Why do I get the feeling
that you busted it?
Don't be mad. I wanted to see you.
Why, so you could break my other leg?
Oh, God, I'm so sorry about that.
Things got a little crazy last time,
but I'm trying to make it up to you.
[CHUCKLES]
See you cleaned a little bit.
It was kind of a pigsty.
Not that I'm being critical.
I know you've been busy with, um,
jail and stuff.
- And you're cooking?
- Yeah, pot roast.
The recipe you like.
Why aren't you cooking
for your rich friends
in their fancy mansion?
Did they kick you out?
Eli found out about my past,
so I packed up my stuff and I left.
What a shame.
[SIGHS]
Did you talk to him?
Now, why would you think that?
Because you're the only
one who knows my real name.
Hand to God, I did not tell Eli.
Did you tell someone else?
Taylor came to see me in jail.
Oh, shit!
Yeah, she offered to pay my bail
if I ratted you out, so...
Taylor is a lawyer!
She knows people,
and the cops are still looking for me.
I could end up in prison!
Yeah, and I may be walking
with a cane for a year,
so I guess we're even.
I got to get out of town. I need money.
- Don't look at me, I'm busted.
- Well, you must have something.
Like, what about your
grandfather's watch?
- What about it?
- Give it to me! I'll pawn it.
The hell you will!
Goddamn it, Duke! You owe it to me!
You really fucked me this time!
I don't owe you shit.
Now get the fuck out of my house!
You stay away from me.
Again with the crazy eyes, huh?
Look, baby,
just put the knife down, okay?
Just put the knife...
You're gonna pay for that.
You think?
["TAINTED LOVE" BY SOFT CELL PLAYING]
♪ Sometimes ♪
♪ I feel I've got to ♪
♪ Run away, I've got to ♪
♪ Get away from the pain ♪
♪ You drive into the heart of me ♪
♪ The love we share ♪
♪ Seems to go nowhere ♪
♪ And I've lost my light ♪
♪ For I toss and turn,
I can't sleep at night ♪
♪ Once I ran to you ♪
♪ I ran ♪
♪ Now I'll run from you ♪
♪ This tainted love you've given,
I give you all ♪
♪ A boy could give you ♪
♪ Take my tears and
that's not nearly all ♪
♪ Tainted love ♪
♪ Don't touch me, please ♪
♪ I cannot stand the way you tease ♪
♪ I love you though you hurt me so ♪
♪ Now I'm gonna pack my things ♪
- ♪ And go. ♪
- [GASPS]
CLERK: Afternoon.
What can I do for you?
I need to buy a gun.
♪ Tainted love ♪
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com