♪ Strawberries, cherries ♪
♪ And an angel's kiss in spring ♪
♪ My summer wine ♪
♪ Is really made from all these things ♪
♪ I walked in town
On silver spurs that jingled to ♪
♪ A song that I had only sang ♪
♪ To just a few ♪
♪ She saw my silver spurs ♪
♪ And said let's pass some time... ♪
[grunts]
♪ And I will give to you ♪
♪ Summer wine... ♪
Tighter.
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Summer wine... ♪
[grunts]
♪ Strawberries, cherries ♪
♪ And an angel's kiss in spring ♪
♪ My summer wine... ♪
[exhales]
♪ Is really made from all these things ♪
♪ Take off your silver spurs ♪
♪ And help me pass the time ♪
♪ And I will give to you ♪
♪ Summer wine ♪
♪ Oh, summer wine... ♪
[Eric] Hey.
- Hey.
- [Eric] What happened?
She hemorrhaged.
Still in surgery, and the baby's fine,
but I haven't seen her yet.
- I'm gonna get more tea. See you in a bit.
- Okay.
Is she okay?
Things are kinda tense at home.
[sighs]
My mum and I had a fight.
What about?
Everything.
And nothing.
She tried to ask me about Maeve,
and I told her
that everything she does is a mess.
I was horrible, and now I...
I just wish
I could tell her all about her.
Your mum
will be fine.
What if she's not?
She's Jean Milburn.
[emotional music playing]
She has to be.
Come here.
[emotional music continues]
- Michael?
- Hm?
You need to go.
Do I have to?
Should we tell Adam?
Michael,
we're getting a divorce.
[sighs] This is all so confusing.
Maybe you could come over
to the flat later, and I'll cook.
We can talk through everything then.
Okay.
[exhales]
[emotional music continues]
[phone chimes]
Is something up with you and Adam?
Otis, we're not talking about
my relationship problems now.
[chuckles] Please.
Just distract me.
[exhales]
I kissed someone else in Nigeria.
I told Adam. I think we might be over.
I wanted to tell you, too,
but I just... I was so ashamed,
and I didn't know how to.
- Do you want it to be over?
- I don't know.
I feel like a bad person.
I don't even know why I did it. It just...
It made me feel free.
You're not a bad person.
[approaching footsteps]
- Is my mum okay?
- [doctor] It's too early to say.
But we should have
more information for you soon.
Would you like to meet your sister?
We can see the baby.
[Ola exhales]
Uh, I'll wait here
just in case there's updates on your mum.
[monitors beeping]
Hi, guys.
- [inhales]
- [Otis] Wow.
- You can open the hatch if you want.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Can I touch her?
[Jakob] Yeah, you can touch her. Gently.
Hello. [chuckles]
- I'm Otis.
- Yeah.
- [door closes]
- Ola, you've...
[Jakob sighs]
[Anna] Morning.
[Maeve] Morning.
- [Anna] Brought you a cup of tea.
- [Maeve] Oh, thank you.
[Anna] You look happy.
Is that anything to do with Otis?
Look at you. You can't stop smiling.
[chuckles]
Do you know, I'm not planning on
having anybody else take this room.
It's free if you'd like it.
Elsie loves having you here.
I'd really like that.
- Do I have to keep that shit on the wall?
- [Anna laughs]
No. You can have
whatever you want on the walls.
Okay, good. [chuckles]
[phone chimes]
- Maeve!
- Good morning.
Good... Oh my... Good morning!
Oh my God!
What are we gonna do today?
- [Elsie giggles]
- Hmm? Whoo!
[door closes]
[Maureen] Adam?
Oh, I'm just popping to pick up
some things for Jean Milburn.
What's this?
I, uh, I'm competing with Madam tonight.
I didn't think you would wanna come.
Of course I wanna be there.
Is your friend Eric coming?
Uh, no. We... we had a fight.
Oh.
Sorry to hear that.
I really wish you'd told me about this.
People like to be asked to go to things.
Makes them feel like you care.
I will ask next time.
[door opens, closes]
- [knocking at door]
- [door opens]
- I'm off for my run.
- [Jackson] Okay.
- Hey, Mum.
- Hm?
Um, did you always know
that you were a lesbian?
Why?
Oh, I just never asked before.
It's fine if you don't wanna answer, I...
No, no, no, no. Um...
I actually didn't connect with that part
of myself until I met your mum.
Oh, so it's more about the person?
Well, I think I was in denial
for a long time.
I had a lot of shame.
I mean, I always knew those feelings
were there. I just didn't know know.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Sorry you felt shame, Mum.
Did you want to tell me something?
[laughs] I'm not telling you that I'm gay.
- Well...
- Thanks though.
[chuckles]
[chuckles] Actually,
can I join you for your run?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
- If you remember where your trainers are.
- [chuckles]
- Come on, then!
- All right.
[door closes]
[emotional music playing]
- [knocking at door]
- [door opens]
Oh, you're dressed!
Do you want a lift to school?
[sighs]
[Otis] Did you guys decide on a name?
No.
We couldn't agree.
[Jakob chuckles]
- Did you pick Ola's name?
- No.
Her mother did.
[sighs] It'd be bad luck if my mum died.
'Cause your wife died. You'd be cursed.
- I don't know why I said that.
- It's all right.
It's because you're scared.
[exhales] I'm scared too.
If something happens to my mum,
I don't wanna live with my dad.
Otis,
I know I'm not your father...
but I'm not going anywhere.
- You didn't finish the tree house.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
Won't be much time now...
- [door opens]
- ...with this little one.
Any news about my partner?
[doctor] They found
the cause of the bleed,
but they're still operating.
Gonna be all right.
[emotional music playing]
[vehicle approaching]
[car door closes]
- Hello, Aimee.
- Oh, hi, Mrs. Groff.
Oh, wait. Can I still call you that?
I heard you're getting a divorce.
Oh. Maureen is fine.
I'm here for an appointment
with Dr. Milburn, but no one's in.
Oh, she went into labor.
I'm just picking up some stuff for her.
Oh my God! Maureen, babes, this is huge!
[Goat bleats]
Oh yeah,
Mum couldn't look after Goat today.
[bleating]
- Can I use the bathroom?
- Yeah, sure.
I'm dying for a poo. I'm so anxious,
I think it's gonna be a sloppy one.
Oh.
♪ There's tears in your eyes ♪
♪ They seem so lonely ♪
[music stops]
You know, I think I saw an alien once.
It was when I was at nursing college,
and I was coming back from the pub.
Suddenly, there was this immensely bright,
green light in the sky.
It got closer and closer, and I could feel
the hairs on my arms and neck standing up.
Then it... it just vanished.
Were you drunk, Mum?
I have no idea what it was.
Maybe you should still go
to the Eighth thing later, love.
I mean, you never know.
I think it's time
I outgrew the alien thing.
But thanks.
Can you throw that stuff out for me?
I don't need it anymore.
♪ Warm it up ♪
♪ La-la la-la-la ♪
♪ My milkshake
Brings all the boys to the yard ♪
♪ And they're like
It's better than yours ♪
♪ Damn right, it's better than yours ♪
♪ I could teach you
But I have to charge ♪
♪ I know you want it ♪
♪ The thing that makes me ♪
♪ What the guys go crazy for ♪
♪ They lose their minds ♪
♪ The way I rhyme ♪
♪ I think it's time... ♪
- See you after school.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
- Buh-bye.
- [gasps, screams]
Ooh!
[squealing]
Miss?
- Yes.
- I, uh, I took your advice.
About how everyone's good at something.
Hm. [chuckles]
- Wait, is this tonight?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. I'll try my best to be there.
- Oh, hello.
- Hi.
You're back early.
Yeah, I got a call saying
I could come back in, so...
How are you?
[inhales] Uh, Eric kissed someone else.
You're probably happy to hear that.
I'm actually not.
Yeah, it feels shit.
I hate him, which is annoying
because I also love him.
I know that feeling, yeah.
What's this?
I'm competing in a thing where tiny dogs
jump through hoops and shit.
That's really stupid, man.
Charming.
[whimsical music playing]
[boy] Whoo!
What's going on?
She's gone! Her office is empty!
Holy fuck!
- Oh my God!
- [Vivienne] I don't believe it.
- [Rahim] Explains why they let me back.
- She's gone.
- No loitering! [laughs]
- [gasps]
- Your face. What's going on?
- Hope's gone.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
Is someone gonna take over?
Maybe you should apply, sir.
[chuckles]
No, I'm serious. Mm.
Yeah.
[whimsical music continues]
[music stops]
What do you want?
Um... Oh, a KitKat. Always a KitKat.
[coins jingle]
- [Eric] Thank you, Sugar Daddy.
- Mm-hmm.
[vending machine beeps]
[motor whirring]
- Oh my God!
- No!
[Otis sighs]
Why does this always happen?
- Every time. Every time.
- Innit?
Come on. Come on!
[Eric] Uh, I don't think that's helping.
[chuckles]
I can probably reach it.
I have long arms. I can reach it.
[announcement over PA]
- Uh, don't get stuck.
- I can do it.
- I don't need a KitKat.
Okay.
- [bang]
- Come on!
Just... I heard a man got trapped
under a vending machine, and he died.
[sobs] I can do it! [exhales]
[sobs] Fuck!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, mate.
- [Otis sobbing]
[sniffles] She can't... she can't die.
Oh no. Oh no, she won't.
She won't. She can't.
Will you be long?
I just wanna get a packet of Hula Hoops.
Excuse me?
Can you not see
that we are very upset here?
- [Otis] It's fine.
- [Eric] Go away. Right now.
- [chuckles]
- [Eric] Get out of here!
Now!
Nonsense!
Unbelievable.
[both laughing]
Jean is out of surgery.
♪ They wanna have fun... ♪
- [Jackson] Uh, why are you so happy?
- [laughing]
Because Hope resigned, and Eugene is here.
Uh-uh!
[laughing]
[clears throat]
I'm gonna go call Eugene.
So...
I acted a bit like an idiot yesterday.
Mm-hmm. [chuckles]
I think your cishet brain
maybe exploded a bit.
[chuckles]
You didn't have to run away.
- I freaked out.
- Mm-hmm.
[bell ringing]
I have a free period later
if you wanna talk about it.
- Yes.
- [chuckles]
I'll come find you, okay?
[whimsical music playing]
[music ends]
[mischievous music playing]
Knickers.
Three.
Oh!
[exhales]
[suspenseful music playing]
[toilet flushing]
I wouldn't go in there for a bit
if I were you.
- Oh. [chuckles]
- No, seriously.
Do you want to talk about
why you're feeling anxious?
Yeah.
I need to break up with my boyfriend.
He's so lovely to me,
but I've changed so much,
and I want to know who I am on my own.
Mm.
I don't think I know that either.
[breathes deeply]
It's so difficult to be alone.
There are so many man jobs
I don't know how to do.
Yeah! Steve is so good
at opening my crisps.
Hm.
Well, it probably will be hard,
but if you feel you want
to spend some time with yourself,
you should take that opportunity.
Your boyfriend will be all right.
[chuckles]
Can I ask you something?
You know Adam?
Well, obviously.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah.
[emotional music playing]
Do you think he's happy?
Oh, well, we don't really talk.
He doesn't really have many friends,
but he seems happier now he's with Eric.
Oh.
Right. [chuckles]
Toothbrush.
- Okay.
- [both laugh]
Oh.
- I think, then, I've got everything.
- Great. I'll meet you outside.
[Maureen] Okay.
[door opens]
- Oops.
- What?
- I left the keys inside.
- [gasps] Oh fuck!
What?
Goat.
There she is.
Oh!
- Hey.
- Hello, darling.
- Hey, Mum.
- [both chuckle]
- Do I have three eyes?
- No, no.
No, you just have two.
[sighs]
Feels like I've got three.
- [Otis] Yeah.
- Mmm.
Oh, I've got something to tell you.
Very important.
I've been meaning to tell you
for a very long time.
Yeah?
[inhales]
I
am the king.
[inhales]
The king of what?
The King of Everything.
[laughs]
Isn't that the best news
you've ever heard?
- Yeah, that's pretty great.
- Mm.
I knew you'd think so.
- [Jean sighs]
- [chuckles]
Oh my God.
- Why am I wearing this horrible dress?
- Mum. Mum, just... just rest.
- Just lie... just lie down.
- [gasps] Someone's taken my knickers.
- Has he taken my knickers?
- [Jakob] No.
- Um...
- Did he take them?
Darling, I think he took my knickers.
[whimsical music playing]
[music fades]
My mum thinks she's the king.
What?
She's high on anesthetic.
She told me she's the King of Everything.
[laughing]
[exhales]
- Oh, I'm really glad she's okay, man.
- Yeah.
[both chuckle]
You've been an amazing friend,
but you need to go talk to Adam now.
Oh God! [sighs]
I don't know what to say to him.
Just tell him how you feel.
...the energy required to completely remove
an electron from an atom of an element
to form an ion.
So, ionization energy. You're all to know
that formula for your exam on Monday.
If you look in your textbooks
on page 32, you will see...
[Erin] Over here!
You're supposed to be on the run.
[Erin] I know that.
That's why I'm hiding.
You should come in the bush with me.
Mum, you need to disappear.
I had to give you something.
- What's this?
- I want you to go do that America thing.
- Where did you get it?
- It doesn't matter. I sold some shit.
- [scoffs]
- I want you to go.
It's too late anyway.
Supposed to leave tomorrow.
I haven't paid, so...
Well, call 'em up and charm 'em.
Try not to sound so angry.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
Mum...
I'm moving in with Anna.
I feel really guilty,
like I've left you behind.
No.
You never left me behind.
I left you behind.
I was too young and stupid to have kids.
I've let you down over and over again.
That's why I need you to take this money
and go to America.
Or
buy yourself something pretty
for your new room.
Now, I don't wanna hear any more about it.
[emotional music playing]
- [cries]
- [Erin] Oh.
[sniffles]
- [Erin] I gotta go.
- [patting Maeve's back]
[sniffles]
[phone chimes]
So I thought about it a lot.
I just don't think I'm queer.
- I figured as much.
- [chuckles]
I thought you were all about
breaking out of boxes.
So what does it matter
if I'm queer or if I'm not?
Because I'm not a girl,
and I'm worried you still see me as one.
Yeah, maybe I do.
But I'm open, like, I'm...
willing to learn.
[Cal] Here's the thing.
I'm still figuring out
so much shit about myself.
I can't carry you too.
And I still wanna have fun when I can
because I feel so heavy all the time.
[chuckles]
So, what does this mean?
It means that we can still be friends.
[both chuckle]
I don't really have friends
that I've been with like that.
There's a first for everything.
I do really like you.
I really like you too.
I'm sorry that
this isn't gonna work out.
[announcement chimes]
Could sixth formers make their way
to the common room, please?
[emotional music playing]
[Jackson chuckles]
Could all sixth formers
please make their way to the common room?
Oh, Mark! Hello.
I was wondering whether you
and I could have a conversation
about the head teacher position.
What do you want to know?
I would like to put myself forward
for the job.
I have worked at Moordale for seven years.
- I have a good understanding...
- Sorry, uh...
- Emily. Yeah.
- Emily. Emily.
We're not taking applications currently,
but thanks.
[whimsical music playing]
Can you sign your story?
[girl] Glenoxi's my hero.
No. No, no.
I'm the grown-up.
[mischievous music playing]
[breathing anxiously]
Oh!
[gasps] It's open!
Go, Maureen! Go, Maureen!
[gasps]
Goat?
[Maureen] I think Goat might be a lesbian.
[Goat bleating]
[Mark] Following the coverage
of yesterday's events,
our investors have pulled
all of their funding from the school.
[students] What?
So we have no choice but to sell
Moordale Secondary to developers.
[students] What?
[Mark] Now, I have been sent
to tell you personally
because, as sixth formers, this decision
could have a dire effect on your futures.
You will need to find
educational alternatives
to complete your schooling
by the end of this term.
- [students groaning]
- [boy] This term?
Basically, you guys are fucked.
[students exclaiming]
Shit.
That backfired.
- What a waste of time.
- Hey.
Speaking up for what you believe in
is never a waste of time.
You did the right thing.
Thanks, miss.
I was not expecting that.
[Adam] Yeah.
Listen, I, uh...
was wondering if you'd read my poem.
I wanna give it to Eric,
but I think it's still shit.
Okay, I'll read it for you.
Um, they're selling the school.
What? When?
- Adam, I'm so sorry. I...
- Stop apologizing.
Can we walk home together?
Yeah.
[pensive music playing]
I'll give you a hand.
Thanks. This woman bumped into me,
and she didn't even say sorry.
Oh, it's you.
You have a bit of lipstick on your teeth.
[groans]
I've had a shit 24 hours.
Yeah, I heard.
Would you like some KitKat?
[whimsical music playing]
What the fuck?
[toilet flushing]
Hey.
- [clears throat]
- [water running]
Hey, are you following me?
Because you're starting to freak me out.
I... I wanted to say sorry.
[water stops]
- For what?
- For not speaking up.
That's okay.
You'll speak up when you're ready.
Also, uh,
I need your help.
- Delivery.
- Oh.
Maureen, thank you.
It means a lot.
She's out of surgery.
- Oh, thank goodness.
- Yeah.
I'll pop in when she's feeling stronger,
but if there's anything else I can do,
anything, just ask.
[sighs] Thank you.
See you.
[phone chimes]
Hi, kid.
How long you been sitting here?
I think I did this, Dad.
What do you mean?
I think I made
all this bad stuff happen to Jean.
I said some really terrible things to her.
I had some really horrible thoughts.
Jean is awake.
And she's fine.
- Okay.
- Okay?
And we all have
horrible thoughts sometimes.
Doesn't mean bad things will happen.
Something bad did happen.
[Jakob sighs]
- Dad?
- Yeah?
[kisses]
I'm pleased that you're happy with Jean
and that you're moving on.
But I'm also really worried
you'll like your new family more than me
because I remind you of the pain.
You remind me of joy.
[emotional music playing]
Only joy.
[chuckles]
Okay?
Okay.
[Adam] I'm thinking that maybe
we could pretend it didn't happen.
But it did happen.
I messed up.
Badly.
I... I can be okay with it.
It was a stupid kiss.
It didn't mean anything. I can get over...
I don't think it was just
a stupid kiss, Adam.
Did you...
did you sleep with this guy? Is that...
No. That's not what I mean.
We only kissed, but it wasn't stupid.
It was something.
You don't feel bad?
Yes, I feel bad.
I feel bad I hurt you.
But you wouldn't take it back?
No, I don't think I would.
- It felt easy with him.
- Mm.
[sniffles] And it feels hard with me.
I just feel like I'm... I'm ready to fly,
and you're just learning to walk.
And I've worked really hard
to find myself,
and I'm beginning to lose who I am.
We're gonna break up, aren't we?
- I think we have to.
- Yeah.
It's not your fault. [splutters]
We're just going in different directions.
- Adam, can we keep talking?
- Mm... Uh...
[inhales] Don't...
["I Get Along Without You Very Well"
by Chet Baker playing]
...have anything else to say.
♪ I get along without you very well ♪
♪ Of course I do ♪
♪ Except perhaps in spring ♪
♪ But I should never think of spring ♪
♪ For that would surely break my heart ♪
♪ In two ♪
Oh.
Sweet baby girl,
you've had a tough time of it.
[Jakob exhales]
Well, she's definitely not a Thor.
Oh, I don't know.
It might be growing on me.
[Jakob chuckles]
[Jakob] Look at that.
I think she definitely wants to meet you.
[Jakob] Yeah, come.
[exhales]
You can open the hatch.
[latch clicks]
[exhales]
[Ola] Hello.
[emotional music playing]
[exhales]
Maybe we should call her Joy.
Joy.
I like that.
Me too.
Did you know the school was gonna close?
[Hope scoffs] You all thought
you were being so smart yesterday.
But you've only destroyed yourselves.
I thought we made a pretty good case.
You know, I'm not much older than you,
but my generation knew
how to conduct themselves.
We knew what was important.
The issues we talked about
have always been there.
People just haven't felt
safe enough to raise them.
That's what's changing.
[Hope] Thank you.
So what you gonna do now?
I've been trying to get pregnant
for three years.
I'm currently trying to start
another round of IVF.
Well, I hope it works out.
It won't.
You have no idea what it's like
to wake up to the feeling of failure
every morning. [sobs]
I'm sorry. I'm clearly having...
[breathes deeply] ...some kind of breakdown.
How are you a failure?
Because my... my body won't... won't...
It doesn't do
the... the one thing it's supposed to do.
The one thing I want it to do.
[emotional music playing]
[Hope] But you can't have everything,
I suppose.
And dwelling on it makes me weak.
[Otis] I don't think you're weak.
I think
saying you feel disappointed by something
you want but maybe can't have
makes you honest.
And admitting your vulnerabilities
makes you courageous.
[Hope] Yeah.
[sobs] It's very hard.
[shuddered breath]
[sobs] But thank you.
- Darling?
- Hey.
- Could you help me back to the room?
- Yeah.
[Hope clears throat]
Congratulations, Dr. Milburn.
Thank you.
[audience clapping]
[dog owner] Come on!
[male announcer]
For those who have just arrived,
welcome to
the Midgeville County Dog Trials.
[chuckles]
Next up, ladies and gentlemen,
is the toy dog agility round.
First up will be Kelly Fuller
and Twinkle Twinkle, the Pomsky.
[audience clapping]
I overheard
some of your conversation with Hope.
It was really beautiful
how you navigated that.
I know we've had fights about it, darling,
and I never want you
to not pursue an interest in therapy.
I just really want you to know
the weight of the responsibility.
I think I do.
I can't really explain why
I love talking to people.
It's just...
Like a rush?
Yeah.
A rush of connection.
I didn't mean what I said
about all your relationships being a mess.
I actually think you're brave.
[breathes deeply]
I kind of thought
you were gonna die, you know?
I realized I still...
I still behave
like a child most of the time,
and I pretend to be so grown-up.
I still need you.
I can't not have a mum.
You're not a child.
You're a young man,
and sometimes
I find that difficult to accept.
And I'm sorry.
And thank you for being so brave.
You must be exhausted.
Why don't you go home and get some rest?
[sniffles]
- Love you.
- Mm, I love you too.
There's someone called Maeve,
and she's really important to me.
I know I don't really understand
anything about love,
but I think she's my person.
Oh, sweetheart. I don't know
if any of us understand much about love.
I just know we feel it when we feel it.
I can't wait to meet her.
[laughing]
[breathes deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh shit.
[chuckles]
- [knocking at door]
- [door opens]
You okay?
Yeah.
[inhales]
There was someone I liked a lot,
but it didn't work out, so...
That sounds shit.
[chuckles]
Shall we have ice cream, talk about it?
[Cal] I did it for a while
with Ace bandages. [chuckles]
Until I nearly broke a rib.
I didn't realize they tighten over time,
so they can restrict breathing severely.
[Cal chuckles]
- How are you doing, Layla?
- I'm... I'm good.
Wow! You're glowing.
- Truly! Yeah.
- [laughs]
All right, so that binder is designed
for safer chest compression.
You might be tempted to wear two binders
or wear a size smaller, but you shouldn't.
Okay.
Yeah?
How does it feel?
[laughs]
It feels so much better.
[Cal] Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I'm so proud of you.
[chuckles]
[dog barks]
♪ You look like ♪
♪ A perfect fit... ♪
And now competing for the first time,
it's Adam Groff and Madam the Cavapoo.
[audience clapping]
And through!
[Adam] Over.
And over!
Good. And through!
♪ But can you save me? ♪
[Adam] A boy I don't like told me
To write from the heart
♪ Save me... ♪
[Adam] I didn't know what that meant
Because I never knew I had one
♪ Save me... ♪
[Adam] I never knew I had a heart
Till you said you kissed a boy
I haven't met
Then I knew I had a heart
Because I thought it might stop
And when I thought
My heart might stop beating
I realized it had always been there
But it didn't know how to feel
Until I thought about losing you
I knew we wouldn't last forever
I was waiting for this day
But I hope we can fix things
And if we can't
I will always thank you
For showing me I have a heart
♪ Come on and save me ♪
♪ Why don't you save me? ♪
♪ If you could save me... ♪
[Adam] Yes, Madam! Over!
- Over! Good girl.
- [barks]
- Oh.
- Beautifully done!
That's my son. [chuckles]
[audience clapping]
♪ Except the freaks
Who could never love anyone ♪
[song ends]
Hey. Just tried you.
I was at the shops.
You going somewhere?
[sighs] Yeah.
Anna asked me to move in with her.
- I acted like a dick, didn't I?
- Yeah.
You did, but, you know...
I'm sorry.
So you're finally getting
out of this place, then?
Congratulations.
I still want you in my life if you do.
- As friends, maybe.
- Maybe.
Probably.
But let's give it some time, yeah?
[car horn honking]
Better go.
I would offer to help you with your case,
but, um, you're on your own, I'm afraid.
[chuckles] That's fair enough.
See ya.
On your way, sucker.
[emotional music playing]
Time to announce the three winners
of the toy dog agility runs.
This is the one.
In third place,
Kelly Fuller and Twinkle Twinkle.
- She was very good though.
- Yeah, she was.
In second place,
Francesca Hull and Bark Wahlberg.
[dog barking]
First place goes to...
Okay.
...Frank Larson and Howard the Jug.
[dog barking]
And a special mention tonight
goes to Adam Groff and Madam
for one of the best debut performances
we've seen in a long time.
Give 'em a round of applause.
[both whooping]
Hi. How'd you know I was here?
I didn't. It's the Eighth tonight.
This is where it's supposed to happen.
[laughs]
- Why are you laughing?
- I thought this was a bit random.
Oh, yeah.
Why are you here?
This is my mum's favorite place.
[emotional music playing]
I'm sorry. I... I didn't realize
how much you were missing your mum.
I think we've both been distracted.
I'm sorry I said that aliens weren't real.
I want to try and be more open-minded.
It's beautiful here.
She really loved this view.
I wish I could tell her about you.
I know she'd love you.
- Oh, here he is.
- Hm.
[Adam chuckles]
Is that Eric?
Uh, no, it was a... friend.
Um, Eric wasn't my friend, Mum.
He was my
boyfriend.
We broke up.
Please don't tell Dad
I didn't win a proper prize.
Okay.
Why?
He would just be disappointed.
["Moanin'" by Art Blakey
& the Jazz Messengers playing]
[phone chimes]
[music stops]
[Eric laughing]
[Otis] Hey.
Okay, what are you doing?
Well, you know, I wanted to finish it
before they bring the baby home.
- Aw.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
- Uncle Eric...
...is here. [laughs]
I don't know if I'm dressed for DIY.
How'd it go with, um, Adam?
We broke up.
- Oh, bro.
- Yeah, it was horrible.
[chuckles]
Do you wanna talk about it?
No.
- Let's finish this tree house.
- Yes!
How... What is this?
That's a hammer.
[all] Five, four,
three,
two, one!
[crowd groans]
Maybe it'll happen next time.
Do you wanna stay a bit longer?
No, it's okay.
[Ola gasps] Lily, look!
- [crowd exclaims]
- [laughs]
- [Aimee] Maeve?
- Yeah?
What the hell is this?
My mum gave it to me
for the trip to America.
They booked me on a flight tomorrow,
but I'm not going.
Uh, why?
Because things are good with Otis.
I don't wanna mess it up again, so...
Oh my God. Maeve Wiley, come here now.
- Sit down.
- [chuckles]
- I'm talking to you as your second mother.
- Mm-hmm.
If you decide to not go to America
and make
your disgustingly big brain even bigger,
I'm gonna have to end our friendship.
A bit harsh.
If I was gonna miss out on an opportunity
for a boy, what would you tell me?
Probably to screw your head back on.
Exactly.
[both chuckle]
Don't forget about me.
[Maeve] Impossible.
[breathes deeply]
[Aimee] Right.
We better get you packed, then. Again.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
- [Otis] So no more Moordale.
- [Eric] Mm.
[Otis] What are we gonna do?
Well, as long as we've got each other,
we'll be all right.
[Maeve] Otis?
[Otis chuckles]
[Eric] Come one, come on. Come on!
[Otis] Hey.
What are you doing here?
Mm, um...
[breathes deeply]
Okay, um... [clears throat]
I've changed my mind.
About what?
America.
I found the money, so I'm going.
Right.
When?
Now.
Wow.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
You know you don't need my help
for the clinic, right? It's your gift.
Yeah, and what about us?
[emotional music playing]
We'll see where we're at when I'm back.
[breathes deeply]
Proud of you.
- I mean it.
- [chuckles]
- America?
- Yeah.
So this is goodbye.
No.
It's see you soon.
[Otis chuckles]
[Otis sniffles]
Okay, cool. Wish me luck.
Yeah.
Bye, Eric.
Bye, Maeve.
["The Ballad of El Goodo"
by Big Star playing]
♪ Years ago, my heart was set to live ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ And I've been trying hard against ♪
♪ Unbelievable odds ♪
♪ It gets so hard in times like now
To hold on ♪
♪ But guns, they wait to be stuck by ♪
♪ At my side is God ♪
♪ And there ain't no one
Going to turn me 'round ♪
♪ Ain't no one going to turn me 'round ♪
♪ There's people around
Who tell you that they know ♪
♪ And places where they send you ♪
♪ And it's easy to go ♪
♪ They'll zip you up and dress you down
And stand you in a row ♪
♪ But you know you don't have to ♪
♪ You could just say no ♪
♪ And there ain't no one
Going to turn me 'round ♪
♪ Ain't no one going to turn me 'round ♪
[music ends]