- Are you excited about our honeymoon?
- Yeah, I am.
Get it out of your system
while we're alone.
- We came to say goodbye.
- Have a great honeymoon.
- Thanks.
- I'll go pack.
I already packed.
But I couldn't find your Speedo.
Speedo? I don't have a Speedo.
I'm gonna go pack
my regular, long bathing suit.
Good, you're still here!
Have a good honeymoon.
Oh, thank you!
And I wanted you guys to know
I am telling the father today.
What? What? What?
- We know it's Ross.
- How? How do you know?
It was his sweater. But, oh, my God!
I wanted Ross to know first.
But I'm relieved!
- I'm gonna be your baby's aunt!
- I know.
- Me too!
- I'm gonna be an uncle! Come here.
- You'll all be aunts and uncles.
- But I'm the only one related by blood.
Now that you all know, you can give
me advice on how to tell Ross.
What'll you say?
That I'm having it. And he can be
as involved as he wants.
That sounds good.
Yeah, but how do I start?
What's the first thing that I say?
- Okay, great. Thanks.
- Hey, good luck.
Yeah, bye.
What was that about?
No harm in telling you now.
Rachel and Ross are having a baby.
What? I didn't even know!
Why didn't you tell me?
Why am I talking like this?
I didn't think
you could keep it a secret.
I'm an excellent secret-keeper.
I've kept all our secrets.
- What secrets?
- No, no, Joey.
I'm not gonna tell you because
I am an excellent secret-keeper.
- You'll tell me later?
- You already know.
The One Where Rachel Tells Ross
It's so romantic to send people off
on their honeymoon.
You know, they're married.
Ross and Rachel are having a baby.
- Maybe you and I should do something.
- All in good time, my love.
I left my guitar in their apartment.
You can let me in, right?
They took my key to give to you.
- What? They took mine to give to you.
- Why would they take our keys?
- Maybe they don't trust us.
- They let me keep my key last time.
When you broke the ketchup bottle
and cleaned it with Monica's towels?
- I washed those.
- No, you didn't.
Yeah, that didn't sound like me.
- I really need my guitar.
- I have stuff in there too.
- What stuff?
- Monica's chicken parm. I'll fix it.
Mr. Treeger? I need to get into
Monica's apartment. It's an emergency!
Gas leak.
Oh, and bring garlic bread.
- Did Rachel find you?
- No, why?
- She was looking for you.
- I guess I'll catch up with her later.
- She really wanted to talk to you now.
- Yeah, it seemed pretty important.
- Oh, no.
- What?
I think I might know
what this is about.
Really?
Yeah. We promised we weren't
gonna tell anybody this...
...but a month ago,
Rachel and I slept together.
And?
- Wow, I thought you'd be more shocked.
- Oh, sorry. And?!
Well, we said we'd just
do it that one time...
...but now I think she may
wanna start things up again.
Yeah, I don't think that's what it is.
- Why? What else could it be?
- Oh, wow, I don't feel well.
I'm telling you,
that's what it is.
No wonder she was looking
at me funny at the wedding.
She didn't say anything to you?
Maybe it's something you ate.
- Please, just go and talk to Rachel.
- Yeah, I guess I should.
You know what I have to realize?
I'm not the type of guy
women can have just one night with.
They always seem to want
a little bit more.
I should remember that.
Next.
- They're kissing, let's go around.
- They're in love.
I'm in love too.
But in an orderly fashion.
- Next.
- Hi. Can you do that and walk?
Sorry, we didn't hear you.
We're on our honeymoon.
Let me see what I can do.
There are some first class seats.
They bumped them up to first class!
Let's act like we're on our honeymoon.
We are on our honeymoon.
- Grab my ass.
- Next.
Sorry, I almost didn't hear you.
I'm so in love with my new husband.
- We're on our honeymoon.
- Congratulations.
Mr. Bing, you'll be in 25J,
and Mrs. Bing, you're in 25K.
We're on our honeymoon, so can you
bump us up to first class?
I'm sorry, that couple
got the last two seats.
If we'd gone around them like I said,
she'd have given us those tickets!
25J and K, any chance
those aren't together?
They took my key.
You trust me with yours.
Of course, and I'll give it back...
...when they're done
at the key shining place.
What the hell is that?
- What are you doing?
- You said there was a gas leak.
- Why don't you use your key?
- I won't find it before it explodes.
If that happens at another building
I manage, people will ask questions.
We could have done that.
They're going into
the first class lounge.
- You know what's in there?
- No.
Me neither. We have to get in!
- Just act like you belong.
- Oh, my God! Oranges!
- Nice to see you again.
- May I see your tickets, please?
Yes, of course.
I can't see the seat number.
That's all right.
I have it memorized. It's 1A.
- This isn't first class, sorry.
- Apology accepted.
Sir, I'm afraid I'm going
to have to ask you to leave.
Fine.
Go, go, go!
I think there's something that
we really need to talk about.
I think we do.
Why don't we go inside?
- Look, I know why you're here.
- You do?
Yeah, and to save you from any
embarrassment, I should talk first.
Ross and Rachel.
Rachel and Ross.
It's been one heck of a seesaw,
hasn't it?
What?
I mean, look, that one night we had
was fun and certainly passionate.
But don't you think it's better
if we just stay friends?
Seriously, what?
Okay, okay. You know what?
If you want to,
we can do it one more time.
I'd be okay with that.
In fact, I have some time right now.
- You know what? Can I talk now?
- Oh, sure.
I'm pregnant.
Ross?
Okay, whenever you're ready.
And you're the father, by the way.
- Can I get you some water?
- I'm good, I'm good.
Ross, there is no pressure on you.
You can be as involved as you want.
Yeah, I... I'm just, I don't know.
I don't understand...
...how this happened.
- We used a condom.
- I know.
But you know, condoms only work,
like, 97% of the time.
What? What?
What?!
Well, they should put that on the box!
- They do.
- No, they don't!
Well, they should put it
in huge block letters!
- Let's just forget about the condoms.
- Well, I may as well have!
- I was really freaked out too when...
- Freaked out? I'm not freaked out.
I'm indignant as a consumer!
- You know what? Let's talk later.
- No, I wanna talk now.
In fact, I wanna talk to
the president of the condom company.
Okay, maybe I should come back...
Yeah, I'll press one!
- I looked everywhere. No gas leak.
- So now I can heat this up?
I'll get moving on that door.
Great. Could you not tell
Chandler and Monica about this?
They don't have any kids
of their own...
...and this door was
like a child to them.
I have to put in a new lock.
They'll find out anyway.
This looks like an all-day job.
I'll have to cancel my yoga class.
Could you tell Jasmine
I can't make it to yoga?
- Sure.
- Namaste.
- What happened to the door?
- So it's noticeable?
- Is Rachel here?
- Didn't you two already talk?
Yeah, but...
You guys know Rachel and I slept
together, but there's something else.
Rachel's pregnant.
- Holy mother of God!
- I can't believe it!
- With my child.
- That is brand-new information!
- You already know, don't you?
- A little bit.
- How you doing?
- Okay. I mean, I'll be okay.
I didn't handle it well.
- What'd you say?
- Nothing.
But the complaint department
at the condom company got an earful.
Then when I turned around,
she was gone.
But in my defense, I found out
that condoms are only 97% effective.
- What?
- I gotta go find her.
Hold on! Are you serious? So, like,
3% of the time they don't even work?
They should put that on the box!
- Evidently, they do.
- What?!
- I can't believe we're here.
- You've gotta be kidding.
What?
As a wedding gift, we're
giving you the Honeymoon Suite.
No! You have been screwing us all day!
- Who are you?
- We're you. Just 10 seconds later!
You got first class, the lounge.
We need free stuff!
You're not the only ones
on your honeymoon!
You can have the suite.
We don't care where we stay.
We're here to celebrate our love.
We just want to be together.
We need the stuff.
Hey, it's Joey. We smell gas
from your apartment.
- Are you serious? Joey smells gas.
- What else is new?
- We'd check it, but you took our keys.
- Do something. Get in!
- How? I could break down your door.
- Yeah, do that.
- You won't blame us for any damage?
- No.
- Are you doing it? I can't hear.
- Okay, I'll break it down.
He's doing it,
he's breaking down the door.
Okay, we're in.
- Rachel, are you comfortable?
- If I said I was, would you judge me?
The doctor'll be here in a minute
to do your sonogram.
Oh, man, I swear, if they sold
these at Pottery Barn...
We need to talk.
Right now? I kind of got an alfresco
situation going on over here.
I want to apologize
for the way I acted earlier.
- Can you stay up near my head?
- Yeah, sorry.
I went crazy. I was thinking about me,
and I should've thought of you...
- Head, Ross! Head!
- Right.
I want you to know that I'll be
there through this whole thing.
Doctor's appointments, Lamaze classes,
baby-proofing the apartment.
- We can do that after we get married.
- Married?
We should get married.
Because that's your answer
to everything?
No, it's the right thing to do.
Yeah, maybe, if you're in love.
But we are not in love, are we?
No, but still, I mean,
you can't possibly do this alone.
Excuse me?
Come on, you can't even eat alone
in a restaurant.
- What?
- How can you have a baby by yourself?
- I can too eat by myself!
- When have you ever?
When certain people leave the table
and I am not finished!
Certain others take two hours
to eat soup!
Please, you inhale your food.
I grew up with Monica. If you
didn't eat fast, you didn't eat!
Am I interrupting?
No, Dr. Long, come in.
This is Ross, the father.
But not the husband,
because she can do this alone.
Nice to meet you.
I'll get started on this.
- Why can't you admit you need me?
- I need you to stay near my head!
Okay. Everything looks good.
Here it is on the screen.
There's your uterus...
...and right here is your baby.
Oh, my God.
Wow! There it is, I see it.
Congratulations.
I'll give you two a minute.
Thank you.
Pretty amazing, huh?
I don't see it!
- What? What?
- I can't see it.
- You just said you did.
- I know, I lied.
I didn't want her to think
I was a terrible mother.
Come here. Sure you can.
Come here. Look, it's right there.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I see it now.
- Do you really?
- No, I don't see it!
Come on. All right. Okay. Okay.
You see this tiny thing
that looks like a peanut?
Sweetie, that's it.
That's it? Well, I saw that.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Wow, I can't believe that's our baby.
Yeah, that's our baby.
- So how was the doctor?
- It went great.
- Good.
- Show them the picture of your uterus.
I don't see the baby.
I couldn't see it either
at first. But it's right...
Ross, I lost it again.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]