[Drawer thuds]
[Clattering]
[Telephone rings]
Belinda here.
Yeah.
[Police radio chatter]
[Drawer thuds]
- Name.
- Charles McGill.
Client visit.
[Pen scratching]
[Clatter]
[Drawer thuds]
[Buzzer]
[Indistinct shouting]
Here's Johnny!
- [Laughing] Hey, I knew you'd come.
- [Door closes]
All right. You're a sight for sore eyes.
You're looking good.
- [Buzzer]
- Jimmy.
Sorry you had to come all this way.
It's a long way, right?
- It's a long way.
- Yeah. Sorry.
Only two things I know about Albuquerque...
Bugs bunny should have
taken a left turn there.
And give me 100 tries,
I'll never be able to spell it.
[Laughs]
Anyway. [sighs] As you can see,
I'm in a... A bit of a pickle.
- You certainly are.
- [Chuckles]
Forget the property damage
and assault charges.
You face being labeled
a sex offender, Jimmy.
If that happens,
it'll follow you for the rest of your life.
That is insane, okay?
Th... That is a trumped-up load
of horse crap, Chuck.
- Come on.
- Is that what I tell the judge...
"Trumped-up load of horse crap"?
I'm not the lawyer here, okay?
But it was a simple Chicago sunroof.
Sex offender? That's not even remotely a...
[Scoffs, sighs]
Let's talk strategy, okay?
'Cause I need you to work your magic
and make this whole situation go poof.
You got a plan of attack? Huh? Come on.
I know I haven't made it easy for you,
but you are... you are the man!
Right? I know you got
a million legal loopholes
that we can dance through...
Big bag of tricks, you know?
Any clever technicalities, huh?
And reasonable-doubt type stuff?
Come on, Chuck.
I haven't seen you in what, five years?
We barely hear from you.
Now that you're in it up
to your neck, you can't even
call me yourself... you have mom call me?
Mom took it upon herself to call you!
I was just letting her know where I was.
- You didn't cry to her on the phone?
- What? No.
You didn't cry and beg mom for help?
What? Jesus!
She hears what she wants to hear, okay?
I'm gonna cry on a pay phone
in the middle of cook county jail.
Jesus!
Can we... can we talk strategy here, huh?
Look... [sighs]
I know I'm a lousy brother.
[Sniffs]
I'm a lousy brother. I'm a big screw-up.
And if I was just a better person,
I would not only stop letting you down...
You know what? I'd stop letting me down.
And it's about time
that I started to make both of us proud.
Am I right?
- Guard.
- Wait.
Chuck, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no. You can't leave me. No.
If I... if I don't get
out of this, my life is over!
So long as you understand that.
Yeah.
Jimmy, if I do this...
If... Do not make a fool out of me.
I promise I won't.
Everything you're doing,
everything you're involved
with... that's over.
[Exhales sharply] Just tell me what to do.
[Voice breaking]
Whatever it is, I'll do it.
Just say it.
Please, Chuck?
Help me.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
[Sighing]
[Insects chirping]
[Vehicles passing]
[Sighing]
[Dialing]
[Ringing]
[Telephone rings]
- [Beep]
- Kim: Hello?
Jimmy: Hey. It's me.
[Grunting]
Jimmy? What's... uh...
Jesus, what time is it?
The clock says 2:00,
but I think that might be
Ho Chi Minh's time zone.
What? What's happening? Is Chuck all right?
Yeah. Chuck... Chuck is Chuck, all right?
E... everything's all right. [Clears throat]
I just wanted to call you.
So, uh [breathes deeply]
hey, what you doing?
Jimmy... No. I'm not talking dirty to you.
What?
Wait, you think that's the only reason
I would call you at this time of night?
I mean, can you just give me...
Give me a little bit of credit, okay?
And you're not talking dirty to me, either.
- Okay, bye.
- I knew it.
Uh, joking. Just... just joking,
having fun with you.
I am calling you tonight
with quality PG phone
conversation... PG-13 at worst.
Uh-huh.
Hand to God, you know?
Uh, but, uh, if you hang up now
and drive straight over,
limited time only,
I'm offering a free pedicure and foot bath.
Is that right? Well, maybe next time.
Hey, more for me. [Clears throat]
Uh, you're, uh, probably swamped
with work anyways,
what, with that big, fat, giant case
falling right into your lap.
- Which case is that?
- I don't know.
Some, uh, some county official
or something?
It was in all the papers.
Craig Kettleman.
Craig Kettleman, yeah!
The primo client your dipwad boss
stole right out from under me.
Nobody stole anybody.
The Kettlemans made a choice.
Yeah, so did the donner party
when they took that shortcut.
Come on, Jimmy. Hamlin is not that bad.
And I'm gonna be second chair
if it ever goes to trial, so...
Be happy for me.
Hey, um, how much exactly
did Kettleman get away with?
Uh, excuse me,
innocent until proven guilty?
Uh, excuse me, but I'm
a taxpayer in this county.
I think I have a right to know.
And besides, it's not like
I'm his lawyer or anything.
I have to go to sleep. So do you.
I know you have court in the morning.
He got away with $1 million,
$1.6 million, at least?
I'm not talking details
of the case with you. Goodnight.
Where do you stash all that dough?
I mean, besides for buying
that idiotic boat.
Hello, guilty.
Hanging up now.
This guy's... yeah, he's probably a target.
Somebody might get some bad, bad ideas.
You know, if Kettleman
isn't careful with that money,
I mean [sighs] his whole family
could be in danger.
What do you mean, "danger"?
Jimmy, why would you say that?
What?
You said the family might be in danger.
I did? I... oh, I, uh...
[Clears throat]
I'm... I'm drunk. [Chuckles]
So, I'm just, uh... I'm thinking out loud.
I'm... I'm up, spinning, uh...
Spinning thoughts.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh...
So, I will see you
down in the court bowels Mañana.
Goodnight, Kim.
- Goodnight, Jimmy.
- [click]
[Beep]
I'm no hero.
[Sighs]
[Bed creaks]
[Insects chirping]
[Brakes squeal]
[Beeping]
[Dial tone]
[Coin drops]
[Dialing]
[Ringing]
- [Click]
- Hello! You've reached team Kettleman!
Craig: Please leave a message for Craig...
- Betsy: Betsy...
- Warren: Warren...
Jo Jo: And Jo Jo...
All: After the beep!
[Receiver slams]
[Coin rattles]
[Dialing]
[Ringing]
- [Click]
- Hello! You've reached team Kettleman!
Craig: Please leave a mess...
[Coin rattles]
[Coins drop]
[Dialing]
[Ringing]
Craig: Hello?
[Muffled, distorted]
Kettlemans, you're in danger.
You're in danger.
- I'm s... I'm sorry. What?
- Craig, who is it?
I am not sure. Wait.
Say... say that again, please.
Jimmy: [Muffled, distorted]
They know about your money.
Watch out.
Yeah, what are you trying to say?
This is a warning. You're in danger.
They're coming for your money.
This is a friendly stranger.
Your whole family's in danger.
The money... they know about the money!
You have a terrible connection.
I'm warning you.
They know about your money. Be careful.
- Do you think...
- Can you call back on a better line?
[Normal voice]
Kettlemans, you're in danger.
They're coming for your money. Bye.
[Receiver slams]
[Coin rattles]
[Clock ticking]
What did he say? We're...
In danger. They're coming.
Who...
Who's coming?
Jimmy: Okay, how about this...
Time served plus counseling?
- Oakley: Can't do it.
- It's his first offense.
- Can't do it, McGill.
- "Can't do it." "Can't do it."
- Would you work with me here?
- [Sighs]
- I'm listening, aren't I?
- [Buckle jingling]
Well, you're kind of a captive audience.
What did you eat for lunch...
The whole roast beast?
- Oakley: Funny.
- [Toilet flushes]
Okay. Okay.
But hear me out. Wow.
The 30 he's done, which is a 60 credit,
plus 60 additional days.
Can't do it.
Best offer... six months,
plus the time he's done,
half time for good behavior... out in 90.
- That's my final.
- That's never gonna happen.
Oh! Come on. Now, are you joking?
Now, that is the best deal
you're gonna get.
- [Air blowing]
- I can't do it.
Your guy drove drunk into a shopping center
and killed three people.
Wait. Shopping center? Desmond Rojas.
Armed robbery, liquor store.
He assaulted a cashier
with a bottle of Kahlúa.
Oh.
I was thinking of Daryl Redwood.
Yeah, okay. My bad.
Desmond Rojas. Okay, go.
Start over.
I am not starting over.
I'm busting my nut here
every day for 700 a throw,
inhaling your B.M.,
which is straight from Satan's bunghole,
and you can't tell one
defendant from another?!
90 days with good behavior...
We're doing this.
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
Say it. Say the words, "I accept the deal."
Yeah, I... I accept... I accept the deal.
[Scoffs]
- [Door closes]
- [Cellphone ringing]
[Sighs]
Good morning.
W... what do you mean, what did I mean?
I... I... no, I told you.
I... I was drunk. I just...
Kim, why are you...
Why are you asking me this?
- [Tires screech]
- Oh, damn it.
Here. I'm in a real rush.
I didn't have time to get the validation.
- Fine. 9 bucks.
- [Sighs]
I... I don't have it.
I have $5. Please?
You know the drill...
Money or the validation.
Look, this is an emergency, okay?
A serious, serious emergency.
I have to get out of here.
I promise, on the souls of my forefathers,
I will get you the stickers
when I come back.
I will get you extra if you just let me go.
Fine!
Fine! You're gonna make me
walk back and get the stickers?!
I will walk back and get the stickers!
I'm not making you do anything.
Those are the rules.
Hey, whatever helps you sleep at night.
Screw you, geezer!
[Tires squeal]
[Brakes squeal]
[Police radio chatter]
[Gear shift clicks]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Engine turns over]
Man: Copy that, dispatch.
[Keys jingle]
[Engine shuts off]
[Car door closes]
[Indistinct conversations continue]
Jimmy. What brought you here?
Me? Uh...
Uh, I... I was surfing the police scanner.
I heard there was big activity
out this way.
Well, there's no business for
you here, so maybe next time.
Uh, it was a home invasion?
Uh, the Kettlemans okay?
Uh, we don't know.
A neighbor was walking the dog last night
and saw the front door wide open.
The place was ransacked.
No sign of the family.
There's no note, so...
We're still figuring it out.
I got to get back.
Yeah, yeah. Of course. Good luck.
[Police radio chatter continues]
- Why did you come here?
- [Scoffs]
I'm just supporting a friend
in her time of need.
You want to be supportive? Tell me why
you said those things last night.
I'm just reading tea leaves,
same way I knew
the Kettlemans needed a lawyer.
All that money floating out there...
It's logical somebody would come after it.
So, the same night you worry
about them, they... Disappear?
Yeah, it's crazy. It's "Ripley's."
Jimmy, it's not just Craig
and Betsy Kettleman...
It's their two kids, as well.
You would... Say something if
you could help find them, right?
I don't... I don't know
what happened to them.
Really, I d... I don't know.
The longer you stay here,
the more explaining I have to do to Hamlin.
I'll talk to you later.
Hey, you'll tell me
if there's anything I can do?
[Sighs]
Everything is gonna be fine.
It's gonna work out.
A-okay. It's gonna be fine.
[Breathes sharply]
[Tires screech]
[Coins rattle]
[Sighs]
[Coin drops]
[Dialing]
[Ringing]
Nacho: Nacho. Leave it.
- [Beep]
- Uh, yes, I'm, uh...
[Clears throat]
This is the party
you spoke to the other day.
Uh, and I sincerely
want to help you. [sighs]
De-escalate your situation,
uh, legally and otherwise.
Um, so call me at 146-8729
at your earliest convenience.
But soon, please.
- [Receiver clicks]
- [Coins rattle]
[Sighing]
[Coins jingle]
[Coins drop]
[Dialing]
[Ringing]
- Nacho. Leave it.
- [Beep]
Yeah, Nacho, hi.
Uh... Just to clarify,
look, I don't know anything.
Uh, I have spoken to no one,
and, uh, there are no rats on this ship.
But [sighs] for the sake
of everyone involved,
I would just like to open a dialogue.
So... 146-8729.
Call me when you get this.
- [Receiver clicks]
- [Coins rattle]
[Breathing heavily]
- If I didn't say it before,
time is of the essence on this matter,
so, uh, I'm gonna hang up now...
If you're trying to call.
Uh, there's no call waiting here
if you get a busy signal.
146-8729.
- Just keep trying. I'll be here.
- [Receiver clicks]
I can put out this fire,
if there is a fire.
By hope of hopes, this is all
a big misunderstanding.
146-8729.
[Coins rattle]
[Sighs]
[Telephone rings]
Hello?
Hello? Nacho?
Nacho?
- [Click]
- [Dial tone]
[Receiver clicks]
[Sighs]
[Keys jingling]
[Door creaks]
[Engine sputtering]
[Sighs]
[Door creaks]
[Exhales sharply]
Walking. Just walking.
Just strolling along.
[Panting]
- [Siren chirps]
- [Tires screech]
- Oh, thank God! Help! Help!
- Down! Show us your hands!
- Stop! On the ground!
- Oh, you guys are cops?
- Show us your hands!
- I got bad knees! Ow! Ohh!
[Grunting] Come on, officers.
You're making a mistake.
My name's McGill, James McGill.
- [Handcuffs click]
- I'm an attorney.
Easy, easy!
[Police radio chatter]
It's his lawyer.
Whose lawyer?
[Indistinct conversations]
[Telephone rings in distance]
You sure he asked for me?
Going in or what?
[Beep]
[Sighs]
Hey. [Clears throat]
You asked for me, and I have come.
I want to tell you this was a wise move...
Very smart, because I'm here
to help... Everyone...
All parties, but mostly you.
Uh, those two detectives... [stammers]
They just gave me an earful. [sighs]
And what they were telling me
is... it's problematic.
I'm gonna pitch it back to you
so I know we're on the same page.
A neighbor lady saw a suspicious van
parked across the street
from the Kettlemans' house
two nights in a row.
She wrote down the license plate.
It was your license plate.
Cops tracked your van and you,
searched it, and found blood on the floor.
So... Here we are.
[Smacks lips]
Um... Um... They're calling
the FBI in on this,
which makes it federal.
That's a bad thing, Nacho.
That's... that's very bad,
but if you tell me where the family is,
if... if you give them up now...
Full cooperation, deep remorse...
I feel very good
about knocking your sentence
down to the minimum... 18 years.
[Chuckles nervously]
They take this good-behavior
thing very seriously,
so start here, right here.
[Sighs]
Tell me the family is okay.
Tell me the kids are okay.
Y... you want to tell me
your thoughts and weigh in?
Does this sound like a plan
that you can get behind?
You miserable piece of shit.
- You set me up.
- I what?
You gave my score to another crew,
and now you're setting me up.
I... what the what?
D... did the cops beat you?
'Cause you're talking
like a person with head trauma.
- You think you're funny?
- What are you saying?
Are you saying that you
had nothing to do with this?
That was your van outside the house.
- Y... you weren't there?
- Yeah, I was there.
I was casing the place,
figuring out the best way in and out,
what time they went to bed... all that.
They were fine when I left. That's it.
You had nothing to do with the Kettlemans?
I was never in the house.
[Scoffs]
What about the blood in your van?
They DNA my ride,
all they're gonna find is the
blood of your skate-rat twins,
plus whatever piss and shit
you leaked out when you were in there.
Nobody's been in the
back of that van since.
[Sighs] I... I don't understand.
Here's what I understand, counselor.
I told my plan to one other person.
One... you.
Now here I am, under arrest.
- Go figure.
- [Sighs]
I don't know anything
about a setup or another crew.
[Chuckles]
[Chains rattle]
You know what? I don't even care.
The cops are out there right
now, poking into my business,
and if they find something on me
or my partners, for real,
it's gonna be bad for you... really bad.
Bad? Bad as in...
You get me out of here, today...
Or you're a dead man.
[Knock on door]
[Beep]
Oh, hey.
I asked if you knew anything.
You didn't tell me you were
representing the lead suspect.
I didn't know it at the time.
Dunst: He give up anything?
- What?
- Did he tell you where the family is?
[Sighs] H... he doesn't know.
What does that mean... he doesn't know?
He gave them to somebody else?
He... he doesn't know
because he didn't do it.
Ah, Christ. Give me a break.
Guys, can you give us just a minute?
Jimmy, that family is in real danger.
You don't have to stand behind
attorney-client privilege.
I'm not.
These people can be buried in a box,
sucking air through a straw right now.
And I'm sorry if that's where they are,
but my guy didn't do it.
How are you so sure?
[Sighs]
You know what you're gonna do?
You're gonna get
your special CSI people, right?
And you're gonna test the
blood from that van,
because I guarantee you,
one billion percent,
it's not the Kettlemans'.
Whose is it?
I... It's not the Kettlemans'. Just test it.
That'll take weeks,
if we could even get
a DNA sample to compare it to.
Well, isn't that convenient?
You've got an innocent man
in there right now,
who I demand you release with an apology!
Dunst: Look, there are no other suspects.
There's no evidence
that points to anyone else.
Well, then, I want to see the crime scene,
'cause you guys are missing something.
Screw you, "missing something."
No, detectives, I, um...
I think that's a good idea.
- A good idea?
- Yes.
I think we should invite
Mr. McGill to the house.
[Scoffs] Why?
Yeah, why?
So, what did we miss?
[Clock ticking]
[Sighs]
This is the son's room...
Warren. 12 years old.
[Sighs]
Jo Jo's room.
She's 7.
[Sighs]
All right, you wanted me to crack?
Mission accomplished.
But I'm telling you...
My client didn't do this.
We know Varga was outside the house
the night the family
disappeared. That is a fact.
Advocate for the guy all you want
after we get these people back safe.
In the meantime, help us.
Where's the doll?
Where's the what?
Uh, got little shoes, a bunch of clothes,
a table and chairs, hairbrush,
but where's the doll
that goes with all this stuff?
In every picture of this little girl,
she's holding the same doll.
- So, where's the doll?
- What does it matter?
Doll is gone... girl is gone,
which means doll and girl
are most likely together,
which means...
I have no idea what that means.
Which means the kid
wasn't dragged out of the house.
- Ipso facto...
- Wait. Wait.
What are you saying?
Maybe the Kettlemans kidnapped themselves.
That's it. You're...
You're... you're done. Let's go.
- I... it makes perfect sense.
- How does it make sense?
Why would they do that?
They stole a million dollars-plus, right?
You... you want to get away
with all that yummy cash,
what do you do? Run? No, you can't.
If you run, everyone knows
you're guilty. Ah!
But if you're kidnapped,
you're a victim, right?
They staged this to throw everyone off.
[Scoffs] You guys are
looking in the wrong place.
Who knows how many miles into
Mexico or Canada they could be?
You... you got to put the word out.
Oh, co... come on.
You don't think it's possible I'm right?
It's possible... unlikely.
- Unlikely?
- All their cars are here.
There's no record of a taxi
or car service to the house,
and they didn't get on any
planes or buses or trains.
- You checked all that?
- Yes, we checked it.
And the doll... it's not news.
We saw it was missing.
So where is it?
The girl was scared, crying.
Bad guy lets the kid
take the doll to shut her up.
What?
You don't think that's possible?
I need to talk to you alone.
I've got to tell you something on the Q.T.,
and promise not to be upset with me.
No way am I making that promise.
I called the Kettlemans.
After I hung up with you,
I gave them a warning call.
A warning call?
Yeah, I was worried my guy Varga
was going after their money.
And he was. He was gonna rip them off.
I deduced it from a
conversation that we had.
It was lawyer to client,
so there was, you know,
confidentiality issues.
But I called the Kettlemans
anonymously to warn them.
Anonymously?
You didn't... oh, God, you didn't...
You didn't do the sex-robot voice, did you?
I did, with the tube and the whole thing,
which probably scared
the living shit out of them,
and they took off, which, you know,
file that under "unintended consequences,"
but you... you believe me now?
- Uh...
- Great.
Now we have to find them.
I mean... or, better yet,
get the cops to let Varga go
because right now my ass is
on a highway to the danger zone.
Well, why are you in danger?
Nacho Varga... he didn't kidnap the family.
But he's a bad guy. He's a very bad guy.
And if the cops keep pushing him,
they're gonna find something.
And when that happens, Nacho blames me,
and then his guys turn me
into a meat piñata.
Jimmy, tell the police.
No, there's n... there's no way
I'm gonna rat on this guy.
I will never be safe.
No, I have to convince the cops
that I'm right,
get them to stop looking at Nacho,
and catch the Kettlemans on the run.
And if they never catch them?
The Kettlemans?
Well, you've met these people, right?
They're... they're not exactly
masterminds, right?
They will be caught if the cops
are looking for them,
so you tell them to, would you?
The FBI, too... I heard
they're getting in on this.
Why would the FBI listen to me?
Well, Hamlin...
They'll listen to him, right?
APD, at least. Y...
You... you talk to Howard.
You explain things to him.
He has clout with these people.
What? Is... is that a no or...
Hamlin will never agree to it.
The Kettlemans are our clients.
This would mean incriminating them.
Oh, you... you see? This is why
people hate lawyers. [scoffs]
It's Hamlin's call,
and Hamlin will never agree.
And even if it were up to me,
you know I couldn't.
I'm sorry. I just...
I get it.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go talk to Nacho.
I'll try to make him see reason.
To beg!
[Brakes squeal]
[Beep]
Come on.
Come on!
[Button clicking]
[Sniffs]
Right. Yeah. Hey. [Clears throat]
I was a jerk, okay?
So, I will...
I will pay you what I owe you,
plus interest,
if you just let me come through.
I suggest you find parking somewhere else.
Somewhere else, as in...
Where somewhere else?
Not my concern.
Uh, actually, uh, this is your job,
so, by definition, it's your concern.
So pump out the ticket and open
the stupid gate already, please.
I mean, I don't have time for this.
- [Horn honks]
- [Scoffs]
All... [sighs]
All right!
[Horn honking]
Hey. I'm gonna...
I'm gonna park right here.
I don't think you want to be doing that.
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do? You got
a poop-filled diaper in there?
Are you gonna throw it at me?
You gonna gum me to death, huh, geezer?
Ohh! Whoa, ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ohh! Ohh!
Ow! Ow!
We're talking about a family...
Mom, dad, two kids.
Lawyer's got this bullshit theory
about them staging this
and running off with the money.
You know the story?
Yeah, county treasurer embezzled funds.
I read the paper.
Yeah, well, we got this
gangbanger dead to rights.
Only problem is your guy over there.
He needs to help us get
his scumbag client to talk.
So, what do you say? You on board?
Help us do some good.
Sure.
Okay, here's the deal...
You assaulted this man.
Give me a break. I barely touched the guy.
But you laid hands on him first.
Finger... I laid finger on him.
Well, whatever your interpretation,
it was still an assault.
Now, this gentleman
is willing to let this go,
not press charges, if you help us out.
You got to get your client
to tell us where he has the family stashed.
Wait, guys, I'm the definition
of a broken record on this one.
Nacho is "not-cho" man, comprendo?
Nobody took the Kettlemans.
The Kettlemans took themselves!
You're gonna keep playing
that line, it's gonna go rough.
[Sighs] You know what? Do your worst.
All right, let's go... to booking.
Yeah, sure.
- Fine.
- [Claps hands]
Perfect end to a perfect day.
Hey, guys, wait a second.
I changed my mind.
- I'm sorry. What?
- I don't want to press charges.
We talked about this.
You want to press charges.
No. No, I don't.
What are you doing, buddy?
I thought you had our backs.
No, I don't think I said that, buddy.
So, what... you get a chance to do
the right thing and you puss out?
Mm...
Yeah. Well, I guess it's my loss.
Hey, Cagney, Lacey.
When you realize how wrong
you are about all this,
I'll take an edible
arrangement as a "sorry."
Heavy on the pineapple.
[Sighs]
Hey. Hold up.
How come you let me
off the hook back there?
Look, I'm going back to work.
Why don't you quit while
you're ahead and go on your way?
No, I refuse to believe it's because
you have something resembling
a heart inside your body.
You're not gonna have
a heart inside your body
in about five seconds.
Okay, don't tell me, all right?
I already know why you did it.
Yeah? Why is that?
'Cause you believe me.
That family kidnapped themselves.
[Chuckles, clicks tongue]
All right, I believe you.
I knew it! I knew it!
Finally, someone believes me!
[Laughs] W... why do you believe me?
I heard the details.
Your story makes sense.
Of course it does! But... [snaps fingers]
Devil's advocate... like the cops said,
uh, the Kettlemans' cars
are still at their house.
There's no record of them leaving.
H... how'd they get out of the country?
They didn't.
Odds are, they didn't
get out of their neighborhood.
What? What? They... come again?
Look [sighs] when I was still
on the job back in Philly,
we had this case...
Whoa, hold up. [chuckling] Hold up.
Now, wait. "On the job," as in
you were a cop on the job?
This bookie disappeared
after the super bowl...
Cowboys/steelers... took $6 million in bets
and skipped town
when things didn't go his way.
Now, everybody thought he was
on the beach in the Bahamas
or dead in the Jersey
pine barrens... wasn't the case.
He was two doors down from where
he lived in a foreclosed house.
Hid there for six months
without anyone suspecting.
But... but why? Why not run?
Now, that's what everybody expects.
It's human nature
to want to stay close to home,
and if this Kettleman
figured out how to do it,
that's what he did.
Nobody wants to leave home.
[Car door closes]
[Birds chirping]
[ "Find Out What's Happening" plays]
♪ Baby, you know me well ♪
♪ you know I mean what I say ♪
♪ before I say farewell ♪
♪ I'll give you one more day ♪
♪ so you can find out what's happening ♪
♪ find out what's happening before long ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
-♪ ahh, ah-ah-ah ♪
- ♪ if you don't find out what's happening ♪
♪ you're gonna find out that I'm gone ♪
♪ gone, gone, gone, gone ♪
♪ tell me what you're gonna do ♪
♪ you'd better make up your mind ♪
♪ it all depends on you ♪
♪ oh, I'm leaving you behind ♪
♪ you'd better find out what's happening ♪
♪ find out what's happening before long ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
- ♪ ahh, ah-ah-ah ♪
- ♪ if you don't find out what's happening ♪
♪ you're gonna find out that I'm gone ♪
♪ gone, gone, gone, gone ♪
♪ baby, you know it's true ♪
♪ we've been through thick and thin ♪
♪ but if you don't come through ♪
♪ you won't ever see me again ♪
♪ you'd better find out what's happening ♪
♪ find out what's happening before long ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
- ♪ ahh, ah-ah-ah ♪
- ♪ if you don't find out what's happening ♪
♪ you're gonna find your daddy gone ♪
♪ gone, gone, gone, gone ♪
♪ find out what's happening ♪
[Insects chirping]
Betsy: I know. It's pretty exciting.
Let's really sell this one. Okay?
Let's do this. And...
All: ♪ There was a farmer had a dog ♪
♪ and Bingo was his name-o ♪
♪ b-i-n-g-o ♪
♪ b-i-n-g-o, and Bingo was his name-o ♪
♪ there was a farmer had a dog ♪
- [Panting]
- ♪and Bingo was his name-o ♪
- [All clap]
- ♪ I-n-g-o ♪
♪ and Bingo was his name-o ♪
- [Dialing]
- ♪ there was a farmer had ♪
♪a dog, and Bingo was his name-o ♪
- [All clapping twice]
- ♪ n-g-o, n-g-o ♪
Hey, it's me. Listen to this.
- [All clap twice]
- ♪ n-g-o, and Bingo was his name-o ♪
♪ there was a farmer had a dog ♪
You hear that?
I found your dumbass clients.
- [All clapping three times]
-♪ g-o, g-o, g-o ♪
- I... It's a long story.
- ♪ and Bingo was his name-o ♪
Look, I'm... I'm taking them
back to their place.
We'll meet you there.
G... give me a couple hours.
- [All clapping four times]
- All: ♪ o, o, o ♪
[Beep]
- [Sighs]
- ♪ and Bingo was his name-o ♪
[Laughing] Hey. Yay!
That was great, guys.
Yeah, I think we have time
for one more before bed.
- Do we have to?
- Oh.
Oh, hey, I don't know about you,
but I would love a little
"John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt."
[Laughs] Yeah, and... and you know what?
Let's really have fun with
this one, okay, Kettle team?
- Let's do this! And...
- [zipper opens]
Here's Johnny!
- [All scream]
- Hey. Hey, Warren.
Hey, Jo Jo. Uh, sorry about that.
I'm your uncle Jimmy, all right?
Now, your parents are gonna
take you down the mountain,
back to your house. That sound good?
- Uh, we...
- Yeah, see? They're excited.
M... Mr. McGill, can we talk about this?
No, we can't, okay? You're done here.
Pack up your stuff, bury your
scat, 'cause we're heading back.
- Civilization awaits.
- Finally.
- [Chuckles]
- [Snaps fingers]
Uh, look, could... please, could we just
- talk this through, okay?
- It's not an option.
You either do this on your own recognizance
or the cops come
and drag you by your heels.
- I...
- let's go.
- Kettlemans.
- No.
- Time to ship out.
- No!
- Yes, you are!
- This is happening!
- No, this is not happening!
Yes, it is! [grunts] Yes! Kettlemans!
- No!
- [grunting] Yes, you are doing this now!
[Grunting] No!
[Breathing heavily]
Yeah.
[Sighs]