Old place hasn't changed much, has it?
Samuel Richards.
- Should I know him?
- He robs banks.
- And?
- And...
you and I together are going to catch him.
I think you have me confused
with someone else.
Do you play chess, Michael?
I prefer snakes and ladders.
- It's my great passion.
- I'm happy for you.
I've an IQ of 157.
So when I get the chance to lock horns...
with the great Mickey Bricks...
It's an opportunity too good to miss.
It seems you have me at a disadvantage.
I was in the Fraud Squad for 19 years.
- And now?
- Head of Security at Moores Bank.
Ex-cop becomes Head of Security at bank.
It's hardly original.
Original no, but lucrative, yes.
I find it very easy
to negotiate my contract...
with a 100% Conviction rate.
Impressive.
I have left every grifter I have ever met...
in my wake.
Including Albert Stroller.
Victor Maher.
Albert's mentioned me, then?
Once. I'm not sure
if I recall the exact words.
Go on, paraphrase.
"An unprincipled reprobate
two-faced son of a bitch."
I do miss Albert.
Friend of yours?
Cut?
I didn't know you could do that.
There's a lot of things
you don't know about me.
Such as?
I could tell you.
But then I'd have to kill you.
That might be worth it.
Are we playing cards or flirting?
I thought we could do both.
Yeah, well, that's why
you'll never grow as a person.
Unlike Mickey?
Is that your professional opinion
or is that just because you fancy him?
- Game?
- Dealer's choice?
Of course.
Strip poker.
When he was 17,
Danny's uncle used him as a lookout...
while he and his crew
robbed a casino in Windsor.
Good job. Professional.
They cleaned the place out...
and they took the CCTV tapes with them.
Anyway, last week
one of these tapes turns up...
and Danny's uncle's long gone...
but one of his crew
wanted to make a deal.
Old friend of mine in the squad
showed it to me.
He knew that Danny was a grifter now,
and he wanted my opinion.
Which I assume
you're about to share with me.
If I show that tape to Robbery,
Danny Blue goes to prison.
And by helping you
I can stop that happening?
Only by helping me
can you stop that from happening.
Now, we've got branches in Edinburgh,
Liverpool, Birmingham, and London.
And Richards has hit every one of those
except London.
He arrived here last night.
He's about to find out
that the alarms expert...
he expected to meet has been arrested.
A favor from an old colleague.
So he's gonna be looking
for a replacement.
That's where you come in.
Set a thief to catch a thief.
I am not a thief.
Think of it as a way of stopping your pal
from going to prison.
Danny's a big boy now...
he can look after himself.
Three sevens.
Nut straight.
We don't need to take the...
I mean, you wouldn't.
To the victor the spoils, Danny.
- Fancy another game?
- You're sick.
Albert's on his way...
Just killing a bit of time.
Albert's on his way to Eddie's Bar.
The mark's going to be another week.
So everyone hang loose.
It's not complicated, Michael.
Either you help me catch him...
or I'll have Danny put away.
When I've got him, you get the tape.
I'm going to need some more information.
You can find me there.
We have to send Danny away.
Come on, Albert. For how long?
A month, a year?
You can't deal with this man, Michael,
he's poisonous.
We have to give Danny the choice.
I don't like being manipulated.
Victor Maher is a freak of nature.
I know him.
He doesn't care about the bank or Danny...
it's all about the game.
He's thrilled at taking on the best grifters
in Europe and out-grifting them.
Jimmy Cohen, Mitch Peters,
and Carl Taylor.
You can't outsmart him,
you can't outmaneuver him.
He knows every trick we do
and more, besides.
I do believe you have a bogeyman.
Don't go there, Michael.
- He's already winning.
- How so?
If he's studied you like I think he has...
he knows that you have
three weaknesses.
He'll use them against you.
Three weaknesses?
Loyalty...
that extraordinary ego of yours...
and a psychopathic hatred of being told
what to do by anyone.
I watched my father
doing exactly what society told him to.
And then I had to watch
as that same sense of duty crushed him.
I know.
Whatever the origins,
Maher knows about them.
He's using Danny right now
to spark your loyalty.
Your ego is beginning
to relish the challenge...
of taking him on.
He'll goad you next...
then belittle you enough to suck you in.
Don't do it.
Look, there's an easy way out of this.
I'll just get the tape.
Excuse me. Is that yours?
Thank you.
Michael, you disappoint me.
You must have known I'd try.
Yes, of course.
I just didn't expect you to be so clumsy.
Now, what's it gonna be, Michael?
Are we to play more games
or are you gonna do as you are told?
And so, the deal.
You'll find out when and how
Richards is gonna rob this bank.
If by some strange chance
he changes his mind...
the tape goes to the police.
If he sprains his ankle...
or his wrist
or any other part of his anatomy...
then you will drag him
into the vault yourself.
Or the tape will go to the police.
When he opens the vault...
and only when he's opened the vault...
and only when you and I
have watched him open the vault...
will you get the tape.
And how do I know
you haven't made a copy?
Because that would suggest...
that I have considered the possibility...
that you can outwit me.
Which you haven't.
After this last performance,
the only possibility I would consider...
is that I have overestimated you.
So now, be a good boy, will you?
Go catch my thief.
Are you still here?
If it's any consolation...
even I have a boss.
You see, Michael, sooner or later...
everybody has to serve someone.
Even you.
Check.
Did you get it?
He was waiting for me.
So what now?
Work on Sam Richards.
I'll do what Maher wants.
Let's brief the others.
Sam Richards has now hit
four branches of Moores Bank.
We got a tip-off
he's due to hit the London branch.
I don't get it.
- Since when do we rob banks?
- We don't. Richards is going to.
So what's the con?
It's going to happen anyway.
We just take a slice after the fact.
Well, that still sounds
like robbing banks to me.
Since when did we ask
where a mark got his money?
If it's going down anyway,
then it makes him fair game.
Yeah, and it makes us accessories before,
during, and after the fact.
The cupboard is bare.
Guys, we need a score and we need it fast.
I'm with Michael.
Okay, so what do we know about him?
Not much, except that
he seems to dislike banks.
Who doesn't?
So what's the in?
He needs an alarms expert.
We use Ash as the bait.
What do you know about alarms?
- I know about everything.
- You know about everything?
Okay, if you know about everything...
what's the capital of Luxembourg?
Luxembourg City.
- You're good, you're very good.
- Thank you very much.
You're not helping, Danny.
Don't start having a go at me, girl,
just because you've seen me naked.
Don't ask.
Okay, this is what we do.
Richards is staying
at the Royal Lodge Hotel.
Albert will hook him in from there.
Once he's made contact...
he introduces him to me as a local fixer...
and I pass him on to Ash.
What about Danny and me?
We keep you two floating, plug any gaps.
Okay, come on, let's do it.
Naked?
- Strip poker.
- Right.
- You were jealous.
- No, I wasn't.
- Yes, you were.
- No.
I was just concerned you may have been
taking advantage of him.
Of course you are.
Can you do something for me?
Yeah, I'll go and get the cards now
if you like.
No, I need you to...
keep Danny out of the way for a while.
It's important. I'll explain why later.
Is he in trouble?
Just keep him occupied.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
I don't believe this.
What is the Bank of England interest rate?
3.5%?
They've charged me 10 times this...
for a credit card I didn't want
in the first place.
What's all this?
Alarms.
- I thought you knew about alarms.
- I do. I'm just a bit rusty.
- We're on a clock here.
- I know.
Floating? What's that all about?
Are you going to bitch all day?
Albert, okay, he's the roper.
Ash does the fixing. Mickey, inside man.
Me? I'm a floater.
To me that sounds like a turd.
And we do like to be center stage,
don't we, Danny?
I have a talent.
It's my duty to share it with the world.
- That's very thoughtful of you.
- Hey, I love it.
So what's wrong with that?
You're telling me you don't?
- It's a means to an end.
- What end?
Saving enough money to buy a small
place in the Caribbean one day. That's it.
So you're saying it's just a job to you?
I didn't say that.
So you love it really?
Is there any point to this?
Yes. You know, indulge me.
I tell you what.
Why don't you tell me about you?
Hello, again.
We met briefly at breakfast.
Yeah, I remember. Sorry.
- George Cooper.
- Sam Richards.
- Can I get you a drink?
- Scotch. Thanks.
You look like a man
who's had a tough morning.
I was expecting someone,
but they've gone AWOL.
- Is there anything I can help you with?
- No, I doubt it.
Just remember:
There are no such things as problems...
simply opportunities for solutions.
Thanks. I'll try and remember it.
- Cheers.
Okay, mate. I love all the old cons.
You know, stuff they wrote about
in books...
in the '20s and '30s.
People like Charles Ponzi,
"Yellow Kid" Weil.
- Danny, you're an old romantic.
- See...
I knew you'd take the piss.
No, I'm not. I promise.
I don't know.
I just always wanted to try one.
- See what it'd feel like.
- Well, then.
You shall.
Take my game. Insurance.
We had a claim last year...
that I was damn certain was an inside job.
There was a burglary at a stately home.
State-of-the-art security.
They were in and gone...
with the family jewels
without so much as a footprint.
Trouble was,
not only did we need an alarms man...
but a crooked one
to tell us how it was fixed.
Did you find one?
Well, fortunately, I had a contact for that.
Terribly unethical,
but needs must and all that.
- Can I get you another?
- Yeah.
Yeah, Albert? Bring him in.
No, I meant to do that, don't worry.
Can you hear me?
I'll quiet it down for you.
What?
Danny boy, well done.
Let's get out of here.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Have you lost a dog?
- Yes.
- I think he might be in that pub.
- Thank you.
This is Vincent Cole.
Vincent, this is Sam. Sam Richards.
No offence, gentlemen,
but I get the distinct impression...
that I don't want to hear this conversation.
- Thank you, George.
- My very great pleasure.
George tells me you have contacts
in a field that I need help with.
- Which is?
- Alarm systems.
And what kind of help are you looking for?
- Does it matter?
- Lf you're straight up, no.
But if you're a cop,
I need to hear you say the words...
so I can plead entrapment
when I'm arrested.
Okay, I have other things to do.
Sorry.
Coffee, thanks.
I'm planning to rob a bank.
And a bell man is an afterthought?
I've been let down.
I can get into the bank.
I can deal with the outer security
until I get to the vault.
That's where I need help.
It's a Locheim system with retinal scan.
That needs a specialist.
I had a guy lined up,
but he was arrested last night.
- Can you bypass it?
- No.
The only one with the security override
is Victor Maher.
The Head of Security.
Okay, so when are you going in?
- Tomorrow night.
- Here you go, pal.
Thanks.
So? Can you help?
No.
But I know a man who can.
It's a piece of cake.
You hack into the retina scans
and reprogram new settings.
What are these new settings?
You take your own scanner,
replace their retinal scans with your own.
I can give you the software
and talk you through the process.
Whatever you do,
remember to wipe both scans...
on the computer memory
before you leave...
otherwise it's like
leaving your fingerprints behind.
Hang on. Both scans?
The Locheim's been updated at Moores.
It's a double scan, two people,
eight feet apart.
- How many in your crew?
- One.
- You're doing this on your own?
- That's how I work.
The scan's the least of your worries.
You won't even be able
to carry the bleeding money out.
I won't be taking any money out.
My dad was 47 when he took a shotgun...
placed it under his chin
and pulled the trigger.
He ran a small diamond-cutting business
started by my great-grandfather.
By the time Dad took over...
bigger companies
were buying new machines...
making stones quicker, cheaper.
So he took out a loan to keep afloat.
When the bank called the loan in...
he felt he let down his entire family.
He was too ashamed to face us.
Moores Bank?
They're a cancer.
- Playground bullies.
- What? So this is revenge?
Have you any idea what it's like
to watch your father die?
Watch your whole family...
everything you've ever known and loved
disintegrate in a second?
All he ever wanted to do
was play it straight, you know?
Toe the line.
I know this sounds stupid...
but this isn't about the money.
Go on.
In the '20s,
my grandfather bought a stone.
Still uncut...
but even then
it must have been worth £250,000.
The bank took it to recoup my dad's loan.
But instead of putting it up for auction...
they kept it for themselves
and wrote off the loan.
That loan was £40,000.
I've taken back every penny
that they stole...
and caused as much damage as I could
in the process.
But now I'm gonna get the diamond.
Then that's it. Then it's over.
And that's what's in the vault?
Yeah. But they're moving it
the day after tomorrow.
That's why I have to do this now.
Only, if what you say about them
updating the alarm is true...
I can't do it on my own.
Have you any idea what it's like
to watch your father die?
Watch your whole family...
everything you've ever known and loved
disintegrate in a second?
My dad worked, ate, and slept.
Paid his taxes on time, toed the line.
The only dream he had was retiring.
Worked himself to death
three days before his 60th birthday.
Everybody has to serve someone.
Even you.
Oh, my God, can you take a chip?
- Come on.
- Bingo.
Hello.
You were married before this, right?
That's how I got into the life.
He was a smalltime hustler.
I'd play a whore, pick up a mark...
Jake would burst in
as the irate pimp or boyfriend...
- and threaten to tell their wives.
- Classy, isn't it?
I thought we were building a future.
Then five years ago...
he cleared out all our savings
and he disappeared.
You ever seen him since?
Do you miss him?
Of course I did for a while, yeah...
but no, not anymore.
I'm not even angry anymore.
Things are what they are.
So where does Mickey fit into all this?
He helped me out when Jake left.
You knew him before, though, right?
- Can we talk about something else?
- Lf you want.
What about...
What about you and me?
What about us?
I don't know about you, okay...
but I really enjoyed today.
Yeah, it was fun.
I just got the feeling
that you wanted to be with me.
You know I like you.
Down, boy.
I know you like me, too.
I must say,
when you're not being obnoxious...
you can be really quite sweet.
So?
- How was it for you?
- Sorry. I can't.
- What do you mean, you can't?
- All right. I won't!
I told you once before,
I don't screw people I work with.
People? Or is it just me?
What makes him so special?
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
- Danny?
- Don't ask me.
I'm just floating.
Someone to see you.
Albert Stroller.
Victor Maher.
It's been a long time.
It certainly has.
- You're looking well.
- Why, thank you.
You look as though
you're doing pretty well yourself.
You went to see Maher. He sent me this.
He taped it. I didn't see that coming.
You begged him to leave me alone.
I didn't beg him, I asked.
What makes you think
I need yours or anyone else's protection?
You've no idea what you're getting into.
- I'm keeping Danny out of prison.
- You're putting yourself back in.
- What?
- Sit down.
Swallow your pride and sit down.
Now think.
Yes, of course I am.
No, sir. I understand, sir.
Richards has been plaguing Maher's bank.
He's hit branches in four other cities.
They haven't even come close
to catching him.
It's driving him mad.
He goes for a beer with some
of his old friends from the Fraud Squad...
and all he hears about is you.
He set you up to catch Richards.
Why?
To prove he can.
There's that ego again.
He set me up to catch Richards...
to put us in the same place.
And why would he do that?
To...
Please tell me you haven't.
I'm going into the vault with Sam.
- Because?
- His father...
It's a long story.
I'm sure there's a bleeding heart
in there somewhere.
And I guarantee that Maher knew
that's what you'd do.
Am I that predictable?
He plays to your weaknesses.
He gets you both in the same place...
he leaves you no way out,
then he calls the police.
Then he gets what he desires most.
To be the man
who outsmarted Mickey Bricks.
Danny stays out of prison
and you go down instead.
You taught me
there was always a way out.
Because I never thought
you'd run into Victor Maher.
He lures you into the game,
plays you like a violin.
Every grifter he's sent away
made the same mistake:
They all thought
that they could outthink him.
But they couldn't.
I love you like a son...
but I don't think you could, either.
- You want to play?
- No, I want to win.
I give up.
Help me?
Okay.
What makes you strong?
What I know, what you taught me.
That's not enough.
He beat me, remember?
The others.
And where are they?
Ash doesn't know anything, wonders why.
He thinks you don't trust him.
Stacie's bright as a button...
the best ally you've ever had.
Have you asked her advice?
And Danny's grift sense
could put even you in the shade one day.
Have you used him?
No. And why not?
Because you're too proud to ask.
You think the whole world is better off
resting on your shoulders.
You've got a good brain.
Use it.
You two not talking, then?
He's impossible.
So you're angry with Danny
for being Danny?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I mean it.
And I really did enjoy today.
Stacie, Mickey wants you.
So you knew all this
and never said a word to me?
That was wrong, Danny. I'm sorry.
And that goes for all of you.
We're strongest as a team.
I tend to forget that.
So if you don't set this guy up,
Danny goes to prison.
And if you do, you go instead?
That's about it.
That's a good deal.
Aren't we all missing the point now?
- Which is?
- Lf I go away, so does the problem.
That's not an option.
Because of the whole family,
musketeer thing.
Listen, I'm the new kid. I'll let you off that.
No, because it means he'll have beaten us.
You don't get the tape
till this guy's opened the vault?
Right.
And he can't open the vault
without one of us.
Right, too.
At which point you both get a tug.
I don't see how we can win.
If we get you inside,
can we get you out another way?
No, there's one way in, one way out.
It's like one of them things.
It takes three blokes
four hours to dig a hole.
How long does it take six men
to dig a smaller hole?
Shut up, Danny.
The question is, do we have any ideas?
I don't think I've ever had so much fun.
I'm glad to have been of service.
It ain't all over till the fat lady sings.
Don't you disappoint me by giving up.
The options you've left me
are rather limited.
I haven't left you any options.
That's how this thing works.
So, when?
- Tonight.
- How?
He's hacking into the mainframe
and resetting the retina scans.
Clever.
But there's a problem.
- It takes two people.
- No.
What are you going to do?
I'm going in with him.
But you already knew that, didn't you?
Seemed like the logical thing.
Albert will be there. Give him the tape.
When I see your face next to Sam's,
and the vault door open.
It's been a pleasure
running rings round you.
The bank.
Stacie, you and Danny
go and set up the first phase.
We'd like to see the manager, please.
Can I ask what it's in connection with?
Police.
Albert next.
They know who he is,
so we'll need a disguise.
Peregrin B. Winterhill III, I think.
Perfect.
That should provide enough of a diversion
for me and Sam to get in.
I'll pick up the materials
and meet you there, Danny.
Can you sort out the present?
Okay, let's do it.
Oh, my God,
I'm so embarrassed, you know.
I'm sorry, I can't bend over.
Right, phase two.
Two gates at the side.
Mickey will take care of the locks.
Which will bring you to this door.
By that time,
Albert will just be arriving to meet Maher.
You guys should be in position
by this time.
If Maher's as smart as Albert says he is,
it won't take him long to figure it out.
From this point, he'll be running.
That will give you
three and a half minutes.
All right?
We know they'll be coming in,
nothing we can do about that.
So they'll be using this direction
to get out. You understand me?
This direction, so you stay alert.
We'll be one step ahead.
You ready?
Albert, just in time for the show.
They're in. Switch to the vault cameras.
- Get your men in position.
- Yes, sir.
This must be very galling for you, Albert...
watching the downfall of your protégé.
Gotcha.
That's the one. Come on.
They're in the vault.
Seal the outer door. I'm coming down.
Care to join me, Albert?
Watch my moment of glory.
Just give me the tape.
Say "please."
Please.
Sir.
Smoke. I repeat, smoke.
Get the gas masks.
Unlock it.
They won't get through, sir.
Where's the smoke? I smell smoke.
What's going on?
Security override.
Move!
Move out of the way!
They've rerouted it. Oh, shit.
Come on, quickly!
They must have routed it next door.
What's going on?
What's in there?
You can't go in there.
It's police surveillance.
Quick, back to the vault.
Fancy meeting you here.
Two minutes.
Got it.
- Let's go.
- You are joking?
We're not thieves, Danny.
Listen, speak for yourself.
I'm very versatile.
Mickey said to take the diamond and go.
- Mickey says...
- Danny.
Let's go.
What's up with him?
He's just having a personal crisis.
It's got millions in there.
Milk train leaves in half an hour.
- I don't know how to thank you.
- Then don't.
You actually did me a favor.
- Really?
- I learnt a lot about myself.
What's important.
My dad was important to me.
Mine, too.
You take care.
Well, that went rather well, right?
Like the man said:
It ain't over till the fat lady sings.
Which reminds me.
Yes?
Nice try, Victor, but no cigar.
But as I enjoyed
playing the game so much...
we've arranged a little present for you...
if you'd like to look out
of your office window...
courtesy of our friend, Mr. Albert Stroller.
- I'd love to have seen his face.
- Me, too.
Right, in the office.
I'll turn in. I'm absolutely knackered.
What?
- Was he left alone in the vault at any time?
- Now, wait a minute.
He forgot to leave the chess piece,
had to go back.
- I didn't do anything.
- Oh, dear.
Danny, is there anything
you'd like to tell us?
- What're you talking about?
- Want me to frisk him?
I haven't done anything.
Good, then you won't mind
unbuttoning your jacket.
- You don't trust me?
- Unbutton.
Go on, show us.
That is unbelievable.
What have I ever got...
- Turn around.
- Go easy.
All right, do what you want.
Hold on, you didn't take any money?
No, I didn't, mate. But you know what?
I'm shocked and a little bit upset
that you thought that I did.
Thanks, guys.
Well, just must have been me then.
You?
- Expenses.
- You're the thief.
One each.
Except...
I've got two.
Thief.
- 50 pence.
- There you go.
Thanks.
Hang on, the rest of your change.
Sorry.
Four makes five and five's £10.
I've got a £1 coin.
Give me my £10 back, will you, Eddie?
I'll give you £5 and five £1.
Help me lose this change.
Better check it.
- Hang on, there's only £9 here.
- Sorry.
- What have you got there?
- £9.
I'll give you £11, you give me £20.
All right.
Thanks.
Wait a minute.
Did you do something funny there?
Of course not.
English