A lot of the time, you don't register
important moments in your life
as they happen.
You only see that they were
important when you look back.
Fuck seat belts.
What should we do?
We need to find somewhere nearby.
Somewhere nice.
Holy shit!
Is breaking and entering
the best way of lying low?
Do you think that's him?
The guy that lives here?
We can just chill here,
take our time.
Sometimes James feels
like a boy I could love.
Like, really love.
Being with Alyssa
had started to make me feel things.
How did you get in here?
Please don't.
MUSIC: The Snare
by Graham Coxon
He was gonna hurt you, Alyssa.
Fucking drive!
I killed him.
She didn't do anything.
Tell them that I did it all,
then you'll be OK.
Armed police! James!
GUNSHOT
MUSIC: How Glad I Am
by Nancy Wilson
# My love has no beginning
My love has no end
# No front or back
And my love won't bend
# I'm in the middle
# Lost in a spin... #
CAR DOOR SHUTS
# Loving you... #
DOOR OPENS AND CHIMES
# And you don't know, you don't know
You don't know, you don't know... #
HE CHUCKLES
Bonnie!
It is you!
It's Ray. From St Joseph's.
We were in the same class.
I had, like,
a medical eye-patch for a bit.
Oh, yeah.
SCANNER BEEPS
And one of those.
So how are you?
You got kids? No.
Married? No.
So what have you been doing?
Prison.
Oh, right.
Why were you, er...?
What did...? What did you do?
I killed someone.
HE GULPS
On purpose.
Right.
HE LAUGHS
Shit!
THEY LAUGH
Properly got me there.
HE LAUGHS
You got me.
You always had
a weird sense of humour. Yeah.
I'm gonna go kill someone else now.
Do you want a bag? No, thanks.
Bye, Ray.
# And you don't know, you don't know
You don't know, you don't know
# How glad I am. #
I learnt about punishment
from a young age.
I learnt it happens because of love.
Austria. Vienna.
China. Beijing.
Democratic Republic of the Congo.
Kinshasa.
Latvia.
Kiev?
I feel like
you've punched me in the face.
My mum always wanted me
to go to university.
MUSIC: My Special Angel
by Bobby Vinton
She couldn't go
because she got pregnant.
With me.
She always put me first.
Cod?
Again? It's good for the synapses.
Dad spent a lot of time
in the garden.
When I was 17, he lost his job.
He didn't wanna tell us,
so every day he got in the car
and drove around
until it was time to come home.
When Mum found out,
she was quite upset.
# You are my special angel
# Right from paradise... #
Dad left soon after that.
I'm...
..just getting some milk.
# Heaven is in your eyes... #
Mum said we were better off
without him.
MUFFLED SOBBING
Mum?
It meant she could focus
all her energy on me.
Where did you get this?
I found it.
Do you know what kind of women
wear this?
Hookers.
Hookers don't pass exams.
Eat it.
What?
Eat...
..it.
All of it.
Life can be hard.
Make sure you chew.
Mum taught me how to cope with it.
Fucking weirdo.
How to cope with people.
BELL RINGS
I'm gonna have to suspend you.
OK.
Can I keep that? No.
When I was 18,
I failed all my exams.
Mum was actually OK about it.
Three As.
Good.
And it didn't stop me
from going to university.
Thanks.
I got a job there.
Are you a student here, as well?
Sometimes a small decision
can lead to something big.
Yes. Cool.
Something really big.
MUSIC: The Old Man's Back Again
by Scott Walker
# I seen a hand
# I seen a vision
# It was reaching through the clouds
# To risk a dream
# A shadow across the sky
# And it crushed it to the ground
# Just like a beast... #
NECK CRACKS
# The old man's back again
# The old man's back again. #
HE SCOFFS
Er, may I?
HE SIGHS
This is your textbook for the term.
HE CLICKS HIS FINGERS
Don't move.
Let's begin.
Foucault is an embarrassment.
He has no class.
THEY LAUGH
"Freedom is what you do
with what's been done to you."
Sartre.
Be the protagonist
in your own story.
And that story begins with an act
of intellectual defiance.
Read Max Weber, Erving Goffman.
Or if you want a more contemporary
perspective, this guy's pretty good.
You're not a student, are you?
You just work here.
People have earned the right
to come to my class.
You haven't.
I don't want to see you again. OK?
Sometimes people
don't see your potential.
So you have to show them.
Was this you?
Is this human...
QUIETLY: ..shit?
Yeah.
Yours?
Maybe.
HE LAUGHS
You can come to my class.
On one condition.
What?
You have a drink with me.
Once a week.
OK.
MUSIC: Wondrous Place
by The Last Shadow Puppets
Finally I could see
a future for myself.
And it felt good.
# I found a place full of charms
# A magic world
in my baby's arms... #
Go ahead.
# Her soft embrace
like satin and lace
# A wondrous place. #
DOOR SLAMS
MUSIC: Above Suspicion
by Mel Tillis and Sue York
HE SIGHS
# We're above suspicion
# Both you and I
# They say that I'm a good girl... #
Take a seat.
# And I'm a good guy... #
Do you like this?
Not really.
So...
..tell me about yourself.
No.
OK.
Why did you want to take my class?
I was interested.
In what?
In what the point is.
Of anything.
Why aren't you a student?
You're clearly bright.
Failed my exams.
Ah.
Exams rank different levels
of mediocrity, that's all.
Exceptional people
don't do well at them.
I didn't.
You are very pretty.
THEY LAUGH
Do you know that?
Do people tell you that?
You're a little salmon. Aren't you?
What?
You want to swim against the tide.
Shall we take our clothes off?
Take a taxi.
Thank you.
Do you know something?
What?
I could fall in love with you.
MUSIC: He's A Keeper Of The Fire
by Buffy Sainte-Marie
# He's as heavy
as a lead weight, baby
# He's as skinny as a wire... #
Has it happened yet?
What?
The love?
Nearly.
But, er, we're finished for tonight.
# He's got a heavy
kind of hoodoo, baby
# And he can lay it on you
# Ohhh, he can say it like... #
MUSIC STOPS
# I gave you my heart
# Long, long ago
# I can't take it back
# Darling... #
HE SIGHS
# And though you treat me mean... #
Just, er, returning these
and, um, getting this one out.
SCANNER BEEPS
This is really good.
Yeah. It's my favourite.
Yeah.
So do you speak German, then?
Yeah. Oh, cool!
HE SPEAKS GERMAN
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
OK. Great.
Thanks.
SHE CLEARS HER THROAT
Who was that?
He wants to be my boyfriend.
He asked me
to a fondue night tomorrow.
Are you going to go?
I like cheese.
WHISPERS: I'd like to take
some photographs of you.
What?
WHISPERS: Come and see me
tomorrow night.
How about tonight?
I can't do tonight.
When you want something,
it's hard to wait.
CAR DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS
You can get impatient.
GLASS SMASHES AND CAR ALARM BLARES
Who is she?
Oh, I didn't want to worry you.
What?
I'd only seen her in lectures.
I didn't know her name till she came
to see me a couple of weeks ago.
I was stupid...
..agreeing to talk to her alone.
She said she was worried
about her exams. I believed her.
She's clearly in love with me.
And now she's...made up these lies.
She's threatening me.
She's gonna say I attacked her.
She wants to destroy me -
my life, my work, everything.
The girl's mad.
So it isn't true?
How can you ask me that?
No, look, I... No, I didn't...
Get out!
GET OUT!
Love makes you feel quite clear
about what is right
and what is wrong.
And when someone
has done something wrong,
they have to get punished.
# Go
# Down the road
# With me
# Walking out of what I'm here for
# Getting out of my head
# Making plans for a better
# Beginning... #
ENGINE ROARS
TYRES SCREECH AND GLASS SMASHES
GLASS CRUNCHES
PHONE KEYPAD BEEPS
Ambulance.
There's been an accident.
ACOUSTIC GUITAR PLAYS
# There's a long
# Road... #
You asked me to tell you
about myself that time.
And I said no.
I want to tell you now.
I learnt about punishment
from a young age.
I learnt it happens
because of love.
# Fly away
I used feel
like I maybe wasn't real.
Like I was made up of nothing.
But when you fall in love,
the nothing feeling is eaten
by a something feeling,
which is eaten
by an everything feeling.
You swallowed me.
And set me free.
How do you know this one's safe?
No obvious burglar alarm.
Dust everywhere,
so no cleaner to worry about.
Post.
At least a week's worth.
Is breaking and entering
the best way of lying low?
# Fly away... #
What?
SHE SCREAMS
MUSIC: How Glad I Am
by Nancy Wilson
# My love has no beginning
My love has no end
# No front or back
And my love won't bend
# I'm in the middle
# Lost in a spin
# Loving you
# And you don't know, you don't know
You don't know, you don't know... #
Hi.
Is Alyssa in?
# My love has no bottom
My love has no top
# My love won't rise
And my love won't drop
# I'm in the middle
# And I can't stop
# Loving you. #