Numero uno.
-You're on.
-Send him over to me in two minutes.
Although the joker could turn out
to be the ace in the pack.
Get in there, my son!
Can't win them all, Joe.
Problem?
That's my husband.
Thank you, chaps.
So?
The casino score's on hold.
We've got ourselves a new mark.
-Who?
-Jake Henry.
My husband.
He walked out on me five years ago...
with pretty much everything I owned.
Everything?
Apart from a few thoughtful touches,
he took all the things that mattered to me.
-Even my home.
-Bastard.
He left me a Phil Collins CD
that wasn't even mine.
-Twisted bastard.
-The point is, it's payback time.
So what do we know?
-Ash?
-Well, I haven't had that much time.
But I have found out he's only in town
from Amsterdam for a few days...
to play poker. Texas hold 'em.
And he's got another game
at the casino tonight.
He playing for real or pulling a con?
-Probably the latter, knowing Jake.
-Well, it looked like it was for real.
And word is he's one of the best.
Is he, now?
-Where's he staying?
-The Aylesham.
So either he's worth a few quid
or he's planning not to pay.
What's our in?
We'll have to move fast,
so it'll have to be the poker.
Going on previous performances,
Danny can play our hopeless drunk...
-without too much difficulty.
-Yeah? Thank you.
I'll have you know it does take
a lot of hard work and dedication...
to be that convincing.
So we'll convince Jake to join us
in a holdem competition.
-Anything else we should know?
-lf someone's got something Jake wants...
he'll do whatever he can
to take it off them.
So we'll rekindle his desire for something.
In this case, Stacie.
You watch he don't get carried away.
Okay, same routine as last night.
Albert, you'll rope.
Stacie and I will wait for the signal.
Danny, as you were. Ash, dig around,
see what else you can find out.
Yeah, that's right.
You lot do the glamorous stuff...
and leave me to do the serious graft,
why don't you?
Let's get started.
Stace, can I have a word?
-Yeah.
-Look...
I understand if you don't want to do this...
but you know him better
than anybody else.
I just need a bit more going.
Twenty-nine! Big 29! Big 14!
Big nine! Come on, baby!
I saw you winning earlier.
You're quite a player.
Thanks.
Ben Morgan. Sometime poker player,
sometime blackjack player...
-sometime a winner.
-Jake Henry. All the time winner.
That I can believe, yes.
Benny the Ball, all right, son?
Hang on, just get our little drinky-poos.
Cheers, babe.
-I didn't catch your name, mate.
-I didn't give it out.
I've not seen you round here before,
have I?
Unlikely. I only arrived here yesterday.
This is Jake Henry. And he's an excellent
poker player and a very busy man.
-Having a good night, are you, Jake?
-I was.
Like I said, Mr. Henry is a very busy man.
All right, whatever.
Anyway, catch you later, Jack.
I'll see you later, Benny.
Tomorrow night, don't forget.
I know what you're like, Mr. Forgetful.
Nightmare. Don't tell him anything.
All right, sweetheart?
I wouldn't have thought you and he
moved in the same circles.
Oh, we don't. I know his father...
or rather, made his acquaintance
at a golf charity function.
He's a terrible bore, but a billionaire,
and therefore useful to know.
His son thinks he's one of the hotshots
on the poker circuit.
He's always trying to mingle
with the best players.
If the joker's dumb enough
to think he can beat the best players...
he deserves to lose every penny he's got.
Although the joker could turn out
to be the ace in the pack.
Richie Blake.
Richard to his father...
-Dick to anyone else.
-Hit me.
His dad has been funding
his son's gambling for years.
He's finally had enough.
He confided in me last week...
the next time he helps
his wastrel of a son will be the last.
Now, when Richie's bluffing, he's got a tell
that no one else seems to have spotted.
He does a little variation each time.
People think it's because he's drunk.
Are you wondering
why I'm telling you all this?
The thought had crossed my mind, yeah.
Well, I'm getting up a little competition
tomorrow evening, winner take all.
£25,000 sit-down money. I'll be the dealer.
Chip Lacey mentioned something about it.
Yeah, he's in, and Snake Eyes, too.
But, you see, I had to get them in,
otherwise Richie wouldn't be interested.
I could have done with more time...
but his father told me
it'll be the last drop he gives to Richie.
So I had to find a good player, and fast.
Stick your casino up your ass.
So, what are you saying?
I want to get you in the game.
I'll put in half of
the £25,000 sit-down money.
You put in the other half,
then give me 10% of your winnings...
and you get to keep everything else.
-What if I lose?
-Well, you won't.
A: because you're an exceptional player...
and B: because you've got a sure-fire tell...
courtesy of me.
Why not bring Snake Eyes or Lacey
in on this with you?
They're good...
but from what I saw this evening,
you're even better.
Nice plan, but no, thanks.
In case you change your mind.
Right?
I doubt it. I'm flying home to Holland
tomorrow. Thank you anyway, Ben.
Pleasure.
Stacie.
Jake.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
-Are you alone, or are you with--
-No.
She's with me.
Well, well. Mickey Stone.
I heard you were dead.
Wishful thinking.
So what's the story, Mickey-boy?
You pulling casinos now?
No, I was here to play poker.
-I hope your game's improved.
-It has.
So how are things
in the small-con world, Jake?
Still taking £50 scores?
I wouldn't know. Some of us managed
to get out a long time ago.
And some of us got out with something
that didn't belong to them.
Leave it, Mickey. He's really not worth it.
Are you serious, after what he did to you?
I think I came out of it pretty well,
considering.
Albert, he's on the hook.
Good.
-He's gone for it.
-Nice one.
Come on, come on.
That is all double Dutch to me.
Come on, come.... We're in.
-Forgotten your key?
-Hello, Stacie.
Goodbye, Jake.
I've come to apologize.
-You're five years too late.
-Please.
I thought I'd keep you company...
seeing as though it looks like
Mickey's neglecting you.
-He'll be back soon.
-It won't take long.
Lovely view.
You've done well for yourself.
How long you had this place?
The show apartment, please.
Couple of years.
Nice to see at least my money went
on a decent suit.
Although I don't recall
the marriage vows saying:
''Love, honor...
''and do a runner
with your wife's savings.''
Okay. I deserved that.
And that.
So what's he been up to
in Amsterdam all this time?
Well, put it this way, he hasn't exactly
been tiptoeing through the tulips.
He made a mint
on the poker circuit out there...
and it looks like he's given up grifting.
Couldn't take the pace.
This is why I had to leave.
I owed Davey Canning
a lot of money in a poker game.
A lot of money.
This was a little taste of what was
to come if I didn't get him his money.
-Acid?
-I was lucky.
It was meant for my face.
I couldn't get all the cash together...
not even after selling the house.
I was desperate.
A phone call would have been nice.
-A postcard, even.
-I couldn't call you.
I couldn't get you involved in the mess.
Would have been dangerous for you.
I couldn't believe it,
seeing you in the casino tonight.
Must be fate, eh?
Or seriously bad karma.
You don't think
Stacie would fall for him again?
He once had quite a hold on her.
Once bitten....
Just because I couldn't call you...
didn't mean
that I stopped thinking about you.
Where's yours?
Bottom of the Thames.
Nice.
That where you wish I was right now?
I didn't know you could mind-read.
I don't blame you for hating me.
Aren't you going to get that?
It can wait.
-Twice bitten?
-No.
Not Stacie. I'm sure she's playing it fine.
I'm asking for a second chance.
Good to see
your jokes are as warped as ever.
I still love you, Stace.
Really warped.
I'm not joking.
We're good together, you know we are.
That was a long time ago.
Doesn't have to be.
I know Mickey's not right for you.
How?
Because....
You wouldn't have
kissed me like that if he was.
I think it was time you were going, Jake.
Any idea how much
Jake took Stacie for, Mick?
£25,000.
-So, do we have him?
-Looks like it.
You okay?
Or are you sick of being asked that
since Jake showed his face?
''Yes'' to both those questions.
I'm not sure if I'd have the bottle
to do what you're doing.
-How do you mean?
-Well, trying to take out a mark...
when the mark just happens to be your ex.
Things can get, you know, a bit messy.
Old feelings come to the surface,
all that, you know.
Except I don't have any feelings for Jake.
Good of you to fit me
into your busy schedule.
-Five minutes.
-Certainly, sir.
I haven't got long, Jake.
What do you want?
Done well for yourself, Mick.
Can't take all the credit.
Wouldn't have got where I am today
without Stacie.
Mind you, you haven't quite got
all the trappings, have you?
You and Stace still not hitched yet.
What's the story with that?
You got cold feet?
You haven't exactly made it easy for us
to find you, to get the divorce papers.
Perhaps Stacie doesn't want a divorce.
I must admit, she didn't sound so keen
on the idea of marrying you.
And how the hell would you know?
She didn't tell you
I was in your apartment last night?
I think you've outstayed your welcome.
You haven't heard my proposition yet.
Not sure I'm interested.
I think you might be.
-I'm gonna give you a second chance.
-Second chance at what?
There's a big poker game tonight.
Winner takes all.
A few other players involved.
I thought you might like another chance
at trying to beat me after all these years.
What makes you think I care?
Guy called Ben Morgan set it up.
He's gonna be the dealer.
£25,000 gets you a place at the table.
Why would I play in a game
with a dealer of your choice?
You think I'm gonna try and cheat you?
-Once a grifter, always a grifter.
-No, Mickey. I don't need to cheat you.
I use this.
You think you're smarter
than the next man...
that you can outplay him,
that you can outwit him...
but the truth of the matter is...
you're still a two-bit loser...
pulling cons on stupid marks
to get what you want.
-I'm out of that game.
-I didn't have to con Stacie.
True.
Then again, I wasn't around,
so there wasn't any competition.
And the competition's back now?
You flatter yourself, Jake.
You just can't handle
me being around Stacie.
No problem. You give me a call
when you get your bottle back.
If that's what it takes to get rid of you,
then yes, you count me in.
Ben Morgan.
Jake!
No, no! It's not too late, no.
Okay. Let's meet.
We're on.
Okay, holdem it is.
Are we all clear on the rules?
I hope you're paying attention.
Thank you.
At the start of the game,
every player gets two cards, face down.
Then comes the flop.
Burn one, place three up.
At each stage,
you place a bet to stay in the game.
Next, the turn card, or fourth street.
Then the river.
Now, the idea is:
between the cards you've got in your hand
and the cards on the table...
you make the best five-card poker hand.
Tricky thing is:
you've no idea of knowing
what two cards every other player has.
So you bet that you've got the best hand...
and once you bet, the other player
has to put in the same amount...
raise, or fold.
Of course,
if you think you've got the best hand....
All in.
Easy, tiger.
I've gone all in
because I believe he's bluffing.
He's got a nothing hand,
whereas I have pocket queens...
and with the queen in the flop,
that makes three of a kind.
He thinks I'm bluffing...
but listen, I can read this kid like a book.
Good thing is, I got pocket 10s.
Which is not bad at all.
I'm sure I've got him beat.
Now, if he loses....
Now, if he loses this, he's out,
'cause he's put all his chips in.
He ain't just lost the hand,
he's lost the whole goddamn game.
So I win.
You going to play the hand or not?
Touchy sod, isn't he? Right, I'll call.
-He's bluffing.
Three queens...
beats a pair of 10s.
Here's the deal.
I'm gonna come in on this con with you.
Con? But isn't that rather ungentlemanly?
I'd like to think of it as an opportunity.
I've decided to use this ''opportunity''...
to bring someone else
into the competition tonight.
Mickey Stone.
And who is Mickey Stone?
Someone who's got something
that I want.
The more players in the game,
the more money in the pot.
-All the better for you and me.
-Exactly.
Which is why I'm only interested
if we make the pot bigger.
-How much?
-£50,000 sit-down.
£50,000?
I'll have to see if the other players
can come up with that in time.
Well?
-Yours and my stake, that's £100,000.
-Plus Ben Morgan's stake, £25,000.
We've already put
all our reserve capital into this.
-Not quite. There's my pension fund.
-No, Albie, don't even think about it.
This one was for you, remember? I mean,
you're worth every penny, my dear.
And there's the money I set aside
for June's hospital bills.
You can't do that, Ash.
I can if I think I'll get it back,
which I know we will.
Think of the returns, Stace.
Yeah, but if we lose,
we lose everything we've got.
We won't lose.
So, if Albert can convince
Snake Eyes and Chip Lacey...
to come up with an extra £25,000 each
for a place at the table....
-Already done.
-Then we need to find....
With what we've got so far,
we're still short by £20,000.
Three hours to find it.
I'm coming in to collect my boss' dog.
His wife brought her in this morning.
Yeah, that's her.
Mitzi.
I'll be around to collect her shortly.
Okay, yeah. I'll see you soon.
Thank you ever so much. Bye.
-This is going to be tight.
-I thought you liked a challenge.
Yeah, I do. I like Cameron Diaz as well.
Don't mean I stand a chance
of copping off with her, does it?
-Mind you, I don't know.
-Come on, beautiful.
Here you go.
All right, thanks a lot.
They're all divine.
Please take as long as you need to decide.
Perhaps you'd like to have a look at these.
Unfortunately, time is of the essence.
We do have a plane to catch.
I just can't make up my mind, darling.
Pumpkin, you have 30 seconds.
We have to go to Harrods
and get the playpen and the crib.
I'll have this one.
Or this one?
Okay, that's it. Come on. We have to go.
-Come on, I'm sorry.
-Sweetie?
You've been most helpful,
thank you very much.
-Look, I'll be two minutes.
-No, I said 30 seconds.
-You can't hurry a decision like that.
-Yeah, well, maybe we'll come back.
I promise, darling.
-I'll decide this time.
-Okay.
Come on,
you said you'd made up your mind.
Perhaps madam would like to try one on?
I knew you should have been
taking it easy.
No. I'm fine.
-Mitzi. Be careful with her.
-All right, Mitzi, all right, baby.
-Sorry.
-Stay.
-How you feeling?
-I'm fine, I just need some air.
Okay, then you can wait in the car.
-Here we go. Come on.
-But my....
It's been a heavy day.
-Mitzi!
-I'll take care of the dog.
Would you mind just escorting her
to the car? Thank you.
I am so sorry to have wasted your time.
Maybe we'll try to come back
when we're next in London.
If it helps...
I believe your wife was about to opt
for this one.
You think?
Could be a very expensive mistake
if you're wrong.
Tell you what, why don't I go and ask her?
Shouldn't take a second. Yeah?
Of course, sir.
I'll be a second.
-Told you we'd do it.
-Okay, game on.
Stage one:
we need to take the other two players
out of the competition first.
They won't want to leave the table.
If they leave before the game is over,
they forfeit their chips...
so they'll need a push.
Danny, you're taking care of Snake Eyes?
Yeah, me and Eddie
got a little something sorted.
Let's just say his mind will be
on more pressing matters.
Okay. Ash, Chip Lacey?
Yeah, everything's in place.
He's in for a small surprise.
Good. Then we move on to stage two:
the false tell.
What is the tell?
-Oh, God!
-Please tell me he's not serious.
Nothing to do with me.
I thought it was bordering on genius,
myself.
Well, think of something else, genius.
All right, it'll be something, I don't know,
a little bit, you know, twitchy.
Okay, I suppose that's a bit more like it.
We let Jake win on a few of Danny's tells,
so he'll know he can trust me.
Good.
Once Danny's let Jake beat him,
he'll be out of the game...
and it'll just be Jake and me.
At which point, we'll play our joker.
Stacie?
I think that I should pay Jake
one more visit before the game.
Is that really necessary?
I think so.
Well, you've already reeled him in.
We're gambling everything we've got
on this. I need to be sure.
Excuse me.
Ja. Hello.
Yes!
I can't believe I'm doing this
for £3 an hour.
All you got to remember, yeah,
is you ain't seen me or any of us before.
-Got it?
-Got it.
So tonight this is just a regular bar.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
You ain't seen me, right?
-Right.
-Good lad.
Ed, did I leave my pen here
the other night?
It's a gold one. Very expensive.
I shouldn't think so.
I've never seen you in here before.
-No, really, I think I left it.
-Nope. Never seen you.
No, Ed, stop pissing about now, yeah?
Sorry, lad.
Does Mickey know you're here?
No.
Has he told you about the poker game?
Yeah.
I'm gonna beat him, you know.
-Why so sure?
-I bother him.
Why do you think
he's taking the game on?
I get to him, always have done.
Mickey's always gonna be second best...
especially where you're concerned.
Why are you doing this, Jake?
I want you back.
That's not gonna happen.
I know every inch of you, Stace.
I know the way you smell.
I know the way you think.
And I know the way you put your hands
through your hair when you're lying.
There's no way Mickey's gonna beat me.
I know every con, every move.
Whatever he comes up with,
I'm gonna beat him, and you know that.
Don't you?
Well, then call it off.
Why?
Because I don't want him hurt.
Too late.
Please, Jake. I mean it.
-Call it off.
-That's why you've come here, isn't it?
To save lover-boy.
-He was there for me when you left.
-I bet he couldn't believe his luck.
What you said,
when you said you still love me.
-Did you mean it?
-Yeah.
On my life.
-Does that make a difference?
-No.
Not even a maybe?
Not even a maybe.
-Here's my £25,000.
-£25,000 from me.
-Do you wanna buy in, lads?
-Game on.
There you go.
-Nearly had to stand down.
-How come?
My wife's going crazy,
me coming out playing cards...
two weeks before the baby's due.
I'm on call, 24/7.
That's Mickey.
Relax, Ben, you make it obvious.
I'm sorry.
-Evening, sir. What can I get you?
-Just an orange juice for me, please, and--
I've ordered you a Kir Royale, Stace,
just for old times' sake.
Ben, this is Mickey Stone
and the lovely Stacie.
-Stacie.
-Stacie and I go back a long way.
-Really?
-Yeah. Still, that was a long time ago.
A lot's changed since then,
including Stacie.
I used to love you in that color.
You stacked?
This is Chip Lacey.
Hi, Chip.
And the guy in the specs there:
Snake Eyes.
-Did you pack your bags yourself, sir?
-Absolutely.
It doesn't look like
your friend is going to turn up.
Why don't we just start without him?
Don't worry, he'll be here.
He's just a little tardy.
Why don't I keep the change?
I could have swum here
bloody quicker than that!
Bit late. Sorry, lads.
Interesting euphemism for ''drunk.''
-Decent of you to turn up.
-Oh, I've managed.
You know what they say, lads.
No show without Punch, is there?
Anyway, it took me bleeding ages
to find this place.
Hello, love.
I didn't realize there was ladies present.
You all right, sweetheart?
Cor, that's cute, isn't it?
So, what kind of a poxy old joint is this,
then?
I'm the owner of this poxy joint.
Right. Listen up, squire, I want
a large Scotch, nice and big, bit of ice.
Stick it on a tab, get one yourself.
All right, Jim?
It's Jake.
Yeah, whatever. Tell you what, lads.
Hope you got your lucky boots on,
'cause I'm feeling lucky tonight.
Are you feeling lucky tonight? Yes, I am !
All right, name of the game is
Texas hold 'em. Winner takes all.
Leave the table or you lose your stake,
you're out of the game.
Only after each player is out
will I call a break.
-Clear?
-Crystal clear.
Ready, gentlemen?
Raise you.
-Fold.
-All right.
Call.
Calling, are we?
Start as you mean to go on.
I'll raise £1,000.
You know what they say.
You gotta make action to get action.
Isn't that right, sweetheart?
Fold.
All right, Ray Charles is out.
Call.
A pair.
Three of a kind wins the game.
Mr. Lucky.
Flush.
Now would be a good time for coffee.
Yeah, and I'll have another large Scotch.
Come on, Benny,
deal me something lucky, son.
Think I'll have another one.
Thanks, cowboy.
Shit.
Take your glasses off,
you might be able to see better.
£600.
Snake Eyes to bet.
-Call.
-All right.
It's a pair. Wow, good deal.
To my left.
£1,000.
To the Mick.
Call.
Oh, well, that's something.
Raise £14,000.
£14,000?
That's a lot of money, ain't it, Snakey?
-You all right, mate? You look a bit--
-I'm fine.
Call.
Yeah, I'll have a bit of that.
Thanks, mate, keep the change.
Black jack.
All in.
We have lift-off.
Call.
Ace high.
You must be joking.
-You went all in on that?
-Flush takes it.
Sorry, Snake, you're out of the game.
Don't I know it.
Well, he seemed in a hurry to leave us.
Two-minute break before the next hand.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, Ed, it's me.
What are they up to? Is it time?
Okay, I'm on it.
-Leave it alone.
-Sorry, I gotta take it.
Hello?
Who is this?
She's not far off now, Mr. Lacey.
I think you'd better get over here.
-She's asking for you, yes.
-Yeah, all right.
Shit, shit.
Fold.
All in. £20,000.
You're out of the game.
Break.
Glass of water, please.
Do you think Mickey suspects anything?
-Such as?
-Between us.
There is no ''us.''
Isn't there?
Do you know what I wish, Jake?
What?
That you'd never shown up at all.
I'd almost managed to forget about you,
and yet here you are...
messing up my life again.
How exactly am I messing it up?
Because you've got me so confused.
About what?
Mickey.
They're trying to con you.
That's why I came
to your hotel room earlier.
To try to get you to stop playing.
They all know each other,
apart from the two who are already out.
Richie's gonna give you a false tell,
then they'll wait till you've gone all in.
Richie will have a better hand than you...
but you're supposed to think
it's a poor hand.
The ''sure-fire tell''
isn't so sure-fire after all.
So, once Richie's out,
I'll stand behind Mickey...
and indicate to you
what cards he's got in his hand.
Why exactly are you telling me this?
Because I believed you
when you said you loved me.
I do.
Don't tell me.
You're catching up on old times?
Something like that.
Jake, give it up.
Sorry?
Trying to take what doesn't belong to you.
You're wasting your time.
£30,000.
-I think you're bluffing.
-Call me, then.
I'll call you.
Give it to me, boy. Oh, yeah.
I'll go all in.
Call.
-Suck on them.
-Three sixes.
Straight flush.
It's a fix.
You're out, Richie.
I've never seen
anybody get a straight flush.
Get him a champagne, please. On me.
Benny, you're a bottom-card dealer
and a bum.
I'm not playing any of you amateurs.
Just you and me, Mickey.
You feeling lucky?
Jake, I don't rely on luck.
Two-minute break, gentlemen.
Time, gentlemen.
Just like old times.
You're really feeling that confident, Jake?
Only when I'm playing someone
who thinks he's better than me.
I think you're the one
who's about to go down.
I'm really gonna enjoy this.
Well, you know what? So am I.
Stace, that thing we talked about.
Forget it. I don't need any help.
I feel like playing this thing for real.
What?
Go and take a seat at the end of the bar.
Go on.
If there's any suggestion of impropriety,
I'll call the game off.
No, you will not.
Deal the cards.
Come on, deal!
£10,000.
Call.
£15,000.
£40,000.
Call.
Red lady.
Painted yourself in a bit of a corner there,
haven't you, Mickey?
You think so?
I know so.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you go all in and I'll call?
Yeah, all in.
Call.
Straight.
Nine, ten, jack, queen...
king.
It's a straight.
A ten, a jack, a queen...
a king...
and an ace.
Bad luck, Mickey.
Ben?
-Thank you, Ben.
-Anytime.
Michael, if you're ever in Holland,
do call me.
I'll teach you how to play properly.
You coming?
Stacie?
What's going on?
I just think that this is for the best.
Please try to understand.
It's my second chance.
I don't know what to say. I still love him.
And let's face it, Mickey...
you never really wanted me, did you?
And Jake does.
This is a wind-up, right?
I mean, it has to be.
-Let's go.
-Stacie?
I'm sorry, Danny, Albie.
I will make sure
you get your money back, I swear.
Eddie, can I have my coat, please?
I can't believe it.
Is that it?
Stacie's gone, and so is the money?
Mickey, this can't be happening.
Heathrow, mate, as quick as you can.
Shouldn't we pick up
some of my stuff first?
And let Mickey catch up to us?
No, Jake!
I swear I didn't know.
I didn't know they were going to do that.
Change of plan.
I think that belongs to me.
Nice try, Mickey.
Mickey...
give it to him.
I can't believe you're doing this.
Stacie, whatever he's promised you,
don't fall for it.
Stacie, I'm asking you, I am begging you...
please do not do this.
What the hell are we going to do
without you?
I'm sorry.
Not the only thing I won off you again,
is it?
You ''won'' me?
Makes it sound like
I'm a prize in some raffle.
Yeah, but you'd be the first prize.
-Thanks.
-It's a joke. Does it matter?
The main thing is
that we're back together again.
It matters to me.
Is that how you see me, Jake?
As a trophy you can show off
to your friends when it suits you?
Come on, Stace.
That's what this has all been about,
hasn't it?
-What?
-Money, winning...
getting one over on Mickey.
You're both as bad as each other.
It wasn't about wanting me back at all,
was it?
Of course it was.
I mean, really wanting me.
Prove it.
-How?
-lf I mean so much to you...
get rid of the money.
Go on. If you love me,
throw it out into the river.
What?
I didn't think you would.
All right.
Satisfied?
There was a moment there...
when I thought that you were genuine.
And if you had been...
who knows what might have happened
between us?
I was stupid enough
to think that you'd changed...
but you will never, ever change.
That was the case full of fake money,
wasn't it?
Goodbye, Jake.
-At least let me give you what I owe you.
-I don't give a damn about the money.
I never did.
Just get out.
My coat, please, Eddie.
Danny, does her taking one of these
mean anything to you?
Hang on a second.
I know what she's doing.
No, Jake!
I swear I didn't know.
I didn't know they were going to do that.
Change of plan.
Good to have you back, my dear.
You always could think
on your feet, Stace.
Stacie knew what she was doing.
-I never doubted her.
-Glad to hear it.
Shouldn't we wait for the kid?
Yeah, better had. He'll only sulk.
Yeah, he might be a little while.
He's gone fishing.
-On his way up.
-Here we go.
So, what exactly have you been up to?
Let's just say I've been dotting the ''I's''
and crossing the ''T's,'' that's all.
Ash?
I understand if you don't want to do this...
but you know him better
than anybody else.
Go on.
First, what were these
thoughtful touches that Jake left you?
Well, after selling the house...
and cleaning out the bank account...
all he left me was a cactus...
a Phil Collins CD...
and a moldy piece of cheese.
You did all that for me?
Yeah, well, it's not like
he didn't deserve it, is it?
-To absent friends?
-Why not?
-Cheers.
Very funny. Who nicked me clothes?
Poor Danny!
Did you have to walk
past the receptionist like that?
Yes, I did.
I did get her phone number, though.
-Well done, all.
-Well done, boys.
Open it up.
Hello!
English