Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ Know that it's not
for naught ♪
♪ You were beaming once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪ Round up the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that they're not
for naught ♪
♪ You were willing once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so... ♪
♪ sure of? ♪
Be quiet.
What the hell?
Shh!
Get up.
It's 1:00 a.m.
Come on. Hop to it.
Carl's awake.
I'll get Debbie.
Come on.
Is that our Halloween candy?
Who wants candy corn?
Me.
Movie night.
We have school in the morning.
Paranormal Activity 3.
Right?
My buddy Edgar shot
this at the AMC.
Ooh.
Why is the camera so shaky?
Ah, Edgar's got palsy.
It's rated "R."
For "really
fucking scary."
So sit there and learn.
I'm gonna get Fiona.
She wouldn't like this movie.
This is gonna be
our little secret.
Hmm.
Die.
Ooh.
Don't go there.
I'd trade my left nut for
one more hour of sleep.
- You're gonna be late for school.
- Hey,
I hope you're hungry--
most important meal
of the day.
Carl,
sit.
House could use a spring clean.
It's November.
It's like Dawn of the Dead in here.
What's with you guys?
Debbie, can you get
your father up?
He's out in the alley by
the Chopiaks' garbage cans.
Help him to bed.
Ian left for work early.
Did you hear,
I kicked Terry Milkovich's ass?
Not the first time
someone's come in here
fists first.
Why don't you go for a run?
When's the last
time you did that?
Got too much to do.
Like?
Uh, make lunches,
get Liam dressed,
take him for his checkup.
Made lunches already.
I'm here.
Doesn't all have
to fall on you.
I'm doing better,
I promise.
Carl.
Carl Gallagher.
Okay, if you're not
going to eat,
I want your teeth
brushed in two minutes.
Come on, wear this.
- You Febreze it first?
- Washed it last night.
Why don't you go for a run?
I remember
when you used to run six miles
before school every morning.
She did.
Steve, is Lip okay?
Got great news.
Can I come over?
No.
I'm right outside the house.
Of course you are.
My wife is in love
with another guy.
- Congratulations?
- Marco.
I'm importing him to the States,
I'm gonna surprise her.
Yeah, what's her dad
got to say about it?
Nothing can stand
in the way of true love.
He finds out,
you're going to be Hoffa'd.
He'll remain blissfully
in the dark down in Rio.
Can I come in?
- 'Cause we got nothing else to work out.
- Like what?
Like you still being married
and harboring my brother?
He's a truant, not a terrorist.
Come on, Dad.
Morning, Debs.
Bring any coffee?
- Hmm, sorry.
- Step up.
Wife's boyfriend ain't here yet.
So when he gets in, so do I?
Deal.
Don't make plans tonight.
I'm picking him up right now.
I never said "Deal."
All right, Mandy, third try.
Look, I'm really bad
at taking hints,
so I'll hit double digits
if you don't call me back.
Look, I need you to get
your dad to back off.
Coming!
Package.
Signed for it.
Oh, oh, y-you don't
have to get my mail.
Oh, i-i-it's
the body pillow.
I, I, I ordered it for Karen.
Butane?
Crème brûlée.
Father Pete's bringing
a guest over.
Hospice?
Poor guy's been living
in the church basement.
You, uh... need a hand
bringing the bed down?
Oh, no, no, no. I
can, I can do it.
I can help.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck.
Hey.
The skinheads again?
Mandy's dad heard the news.
You and Mickey?
Mandy-- pregnant.
Oh.
Well, congratulations.
- I didn't know you switched teams.
- Yeah.
Or was it
just a late night--
- stuck it in the wrong Milkovich?
- He told Linda
he's gonna put my feet
in that meat slicer,
work his way up.
Linda call the cops?
Think she wants the
place firebombed?
Huh.
Mandy say whose it is?
Won't call me back.
Try checking the school.
Yeah, Linda assured me that
if I leave the place how it is,
then I'm gonna be out of a job,
and anyway, she's not going
to be there.
She usually goes into hiding
until her dad cools off.
Spider hole in Tikrit?
Relatives on South Justine.
Went by, but
her aunt wouldn't let me in.
How's the homeless shelter?
On the 14th floor of
the Ritz, so not bad.
Staying with Steve.
Great view.
- Skyline?
- That, too.
Ah, right, Steve's wife.
Surprised you can
still lift that arm.
That's gonna come
out of my pay.
Relax.
Got to go meet Steve.
Try not to knock up
any more chicks while
I'm gone, all right?
Steve's flying in
the wife's boyfriend?
Can't say he hasn't been
working his elfin ass off,
trying to win you back.
Holy shit, bury the lead.
Something you want to tell me?
My morning ritual--
get mounted by Kev,
pee on a stick.
He won't leave
for work without it.
- Weeks now.
- Jesus, these things
- are expensive.
- Tell me about it.
Thought anything involving
his dick and my honeypot
would be the easy part.
You worried?
Thought Kev had defective balls,
but he got it checked out.
Little swimmers could qualify
for the Junior Olympics.
When was the last
time you spread 'em?
For a doctor?
Been forever.
Couldn't be me.
I've had so many abortions,
the next one's free.
Isn't there a neglected child
that needs you somewhere?
Thinking about
taking the day off.
Who's running the asylum?
Monica.
Seems like she's doing better.
Taking her meds?
She says so.
I know it's not gonna last,
but maybe I can get
a few good months
- before she crashes.
- You should go see Meg.
Down at the club?
Didn't she say she had
something for you--
a regular job?
Yeah.
That lady doctor still at
the clinic-- Sausage Fingers?
Liam,
you did such a great job
with your... shot.
What did I promise?
Brave boys...
...get a sucker.
Frank!
I'm back!
You up?
How about pancakes?
Hungry?
"Squirrel fund"?
Hello...
- Frank.
- I don't give a shit
what you make for breakfast.
Ow!
What the fuck, Monica!
What? Where the hell
did you get all that?
I found it.
Thinking we could pay
a visit to Raoul.
Snort or swallow?
Both!
Oh, nine, four,
three-eight...
So, when was Marco
supposed to arrive?
Should be here by now.
Oh, nine, four, three,
eight, four... four, one, six.
There's got to be an easier way
to smuggle him in.
A billion Chinese
can't be wrong.
Man, how long
is this gonna take?
Really? Is there
somewhere you need to be?
Yeah, Ian's in some trouble.
Here. Thought you wanted this.
Quickest grand you ever made.
What's that,
for the phone hacking?
Oh, buyer was thrilled, said you
should moonlight for the NSA.
Use it as a down payment
on your own place.
Why do that when I could have
a rich father-in-law
to leech off of like you?
Seriously,
you want to be on your own,
you got to start saving.
Ricky, there's no more
containers in this aisle.
10,000 easy get lost
at sea every year.
Well, is it possible
the container could have got put
in a different lane?
Let me see that?
Yo, Steve, you sure
these are fours?
They look like nines.
Yo, Marco, bit of a problem.
Uh, you want to call me back
when you get this?
Marco!
Yo, Marco!
Fucking Raoul.
12 hundred dollars
for an ounce of coke.
- For his shitty coke?
- Yeah.
It's like Drano
going up your nose.
Offered it for
$1,150 if I blew him.
What else... What else
did you get?
Oh.
Wheels?
It took six security guards
to kick us out of there.
It took three just to climb
over the rail and get you
away from that zebra.
I thought it was a unicorn.
I swear, I saw a...
What were we on?
Hit me.
Oxy or... Bennie?
- Bennie.
- Bennie?
There you go.
Why anyone
- would go to the zoo sober...
- Hey.
You having fun back there?
Where's the Special K?
- I skipped it.
- Skipped... Why?
If I wanted to feel dead,
I would take my meds.
It was the one thing
I asked for!
You selfish bitch!
God...
Stop the car!
You're fucking driving!
- Get out!
- No!
Then I'm fucking getting out!
This is just like you!
Excuse me for fucking sharing!
Always your conditions!
I had to deal with Raoul.
Oh, there it is.
Trying to cut my nuts off.
No! Don't you talk
about cutting!
Not my fault your parents
did a number on you.
Oh, like the psychotic bitch
who raised you
- was Mother of the Year!
- May that psychotic bitch rest in peace!
Fuck you!
Oh, yeah?
Well... fuck you!
Wait. Where you going?
Monica?
Monica?! Fuck! Christ!
Get the fuck back, Terry.
I've got a shotgun!
Not Terry.
Fuck you want?
Hi. I'm-I'm...
I'm Lip, Mandy's friend.
- Mandy ain't here.
- Oh, yeah.
I-I need to talk to her.
No visitors.
Could you just go inside
- and tell her it's me?
- Could you step back
before I spray your organs
all over my goddamn yard?
Now, fuck off!
Mandy?
Look, you got to call
your dad off, all right?
Get him to leave Ian alone!
Just.
Tell him the truth,
you know, even if it mine.
If your dad needs
to kill someone,
tell him he can come after me!
I thought you had kids
- to take care of.
- The situation changed.
Oh, I wish it had changed
before I hired someone else.
Got to give them the
spiel. Hey, no nips,
no lips, no handies.
This isn't a strip club.
You still opening
that new place?
Belle Epoque.
More Gucci,
less Axe Body Spray.
- Is there anything for me there?
- I wish.
I can do more than waitress.
I've bartended.
We're staffed up.
Completely?
Just need someone
to run the upper bar.
Well, I can do that.
Looking for someone who
can promote a night.
Well, I'm getting my GED.
Look, no one's gonna pay
1,000 bucks for a
$20 bottle of vodka
unless the service
is impeccable.
You ever managed? Overseen
inventory, budgeting?
Look, I got too much
on my plate to baby-sit.
- Sorry.
- Worth a shot.
Thanks.
Deb? Debbie?
Hi. How was school today?
Who'd you steal it from?
We bought it.
Come on, get in!
Now!
Come on!
Where's Frank?
Do you want to go shopping?
Oh, pretty girls day out!
Sure.
Come on, let's go.
Whoa!
I got it.
Come on!
Fucking NAFTA!
Ah...
No.
No. No.
Ooh!
Marco?
Where the fuck am I?!
I've been trying to reach you.
Take small breaths.
Have anydea where you are?
Can you hear anything?
I'm trying my best, Marco.
Okay? Ration your food,
like those Chilean miners.
Only needed a couple bites
of tuna a day to survive.
Hey, beautiful.
Don't pass that one
up right there.
Do a twirl.
No.
Hello. Marco?
Hey.
Oh.
Surprise.
- Sheila, Ruben.
- Oh.
- Got shot by his pimp.
- Ooh.
- Infection in his spine.
- Oh.
- Hi.
- Oh, he can't hear you.
- Oh.
- Deaf since birth.
Says that's why he started
sucking a crack pipe.
I'm proud to say young Ruben's
come to see the Lord does not
accept excuses in
exchange for first-class
transportation upstairs.
Been clean a year now.
- Father, just a moment, please?
- Of course.
He came to us three years ago
during one of our winter
nights for the homeless.
- Yeah. - Hung on a lot longer
than any of us expected.
Saints be praised.
No, that wasn't what I...
Weust can't afford
to keep him any longer.
- Oh.
- State cutbacks.
You'll receive
$50 a day for food
and whatever else he needs,
but let's just say,
I'm not going to be making
any surprise visits.
Father, I've...
I've... done a
terrible thing.
I don't...
recognize myself anymore.
When I look in the mirror,
it's like another...
person is staring back at me,
and I'm...
I'm just...
I'm lost.
Your purpose in life was
to build a happy family,
and you achieved that.
And now, your husband's passed,
and your daughter's
ready to fly the nest,
but you're still needed.
This is your purpose now.
Hi, Ruben.
I'm Sheila.
Okay, great.
Yeah, this will be great.
Hey, sweetheart,
is everything okay?
Mandy's dad came looking for me
at school.
Are you all right?
Managed to duck out
before he saw me.
What's with the dolls?
Took Debbie shopping;
I missed her last birthday.
And we couldn't decide which
doll to get, so we got them all!
I'll get the other load.
There's more?
Didn't have
the heart to tell her,
I don't play
with dolls anymore.
She practically filled the car.
Car?
- You bought a car?
- Hey, how was
your trigonometry midterm?
C-minus.
Great, you passed!
I can kiss West
Point good-bye.
West Point?
I was hoping to get in,
not that I'll live
long enough now to go.
Well, if you know
you want to be in the Army,
why are you wasting
your time with school?
Join up.
What are we waiting for?
Happy birthday.
Come on, let's go.
The ship's called the Bonita.
It's based out of Mexico.
- Lip?
- Yup?
- Focus.
- I am focusing on the nude woman
getting a spray tan
in your bedroom.
She's trying to lose
her tan lines
- before Marco gets here.
- It's a noble endeavor
- I fully endorse.
- And a complete waste
of time if we do not track
down Marco's ship and find out
where he is; he is
calling me in four hours.
I need to give him good news.
What, you didn't telt her
we lost him?
No.
Well, it would be a shame
if he didn't make it,
but, you know,
naturally, I'd step up,
- be there to comfort her.
- All right,
cut the shit, Lip;
I lose Marco,
I lose Fiona.
Okay, okay, okay.
Um...
All right, so the ship
- should be stopping to pick up extra cargo.
- Where is it?
Uh, be in Cleveland tonight.
Cleveland! Cleveland?
Yeah, so take him to the Rock
'n Roll Hall of Fame, but now,
do me a favor,
get the fuck out of my way?
Thank you.
Ever been outside of Chicago?
Army sent me all
over the world.
I ate a croissant
outside the Eiffel Tower
and pizza in Rome.
So the other branches
are here, too, huh?
Yes, ma'am.
And we'll train you, too,
so when you finish
your service,
you can secure a
good-paying job back home.
So, what're they playing?
That looks fun.
America's Army 3.
We could use more
bright, young men like you.
How soon can I ship out?
Okay.
So,
U.S. citizen, right?
- Ever been convicted of a crime?
- Uh, no, sir.
What year you graduate?
I'm a junior.
In high school?
Gonna have to come and see me
when you got your diploma.
What?
You're turning him down?
He needs to be a
high school graduate.
- Why?
- The rules, ma'am, I'm sorry.
- Fuck the rules. Sign him up.
- Ma'am, I'm sorry, but it's really....
He wants to serve his country!
Finish school.
- Let's stay in touch.
- Since when do you have to know
trigonometry to get killed
for your country?
You gonna send him out to do
multiplication
or kill towel heads?
- All right, Mom...
- Geez,
no wonder you can't
win a fucking war.
- All right, thanks for your time.
- Because of shit heads like you
that we're all gonna be eating egg
rolls and speaking slant-eye.
Army too chicken shit?
Fuck you! We're
going to the Navy.
Veronica, I got
20 minutes left in my break.
That should give us enough time
to go three times, easy.
I just ate.
Mmm, that's okay.
I'll do all the work.
- Maybe later.
- Oh, come on,
the best part
about making a baby
is, you get to have sex
while we're doing it.
Not likely.
What're you talking about?
Making a baby.
Baby, I told you,
the ball doctor said
- we're good to go.
- Talking about me.
Went to the clinic today.
Said me having kids--
"not likely."
PID.
Is that bad?
Bad enough.
It's gonna be okay, baby.
Never really wanted them anyway.
What? What do you mean?
I like things the way
they are. Why change?
- It's what we wanted.
- Not what I wanted.
We talked about it.
I was just telling you
what you wanted to hear.
Oh, so you were lying?
You calling me a liar?
Maybe if you lied about it.
Maybe you were too busy thinking
about what you wanted.
Oh, so now you're
calling me selfish?
You know what, congratulations.
You just got everything
you wanted all along.
Fuck, that hurt!
All right, GED
practice test next week,
and remember
knives count as weapons,
so please leave them at home.
I'm looking at you,
Miguel and Shontasia.
Who? Me?
Hi.
- Fiona Gallagher, uh...
- Mm-hmm.
Wondering if there's anything
more I should be doing.
Only the second class.
Anything I could
be studying at home?
Why'd you drop out
of high school?
I didn't have time.
Mm-hmm?
Family thing.
What are you going
to do with your GED?
I was tossing around the idea
of club restaurant managment,
but I found out
I'm under qualified.
I'm afraid the GED only
takes you so far nowadays.
Didn't mention that
in your opening remarks.
They encourage us not to.
Guess I need to aim
a little lower.
Massage therapist?
You're here because there's
a gap in your education,
not your intelligence.
You live near Daley College?
The JC?
They offer a range
of business courses.
They have scholarships,
financial aid.
You can take classes while
holding down a full-time job.
You have the time now?
I might, yeah.
Don't have to aim low.
You're only my second patient.
My first one died.
So, one for one.
Aw.
Do you, um...
Do you want me to...
to... end
your suffering?
You want me to...
You st say the
word, and I'll...
Yes? Was that a yes?
Yeah, it was just hard to hear.
Maybe if you
plug the hole with your finger?
Okay, bit of a whistle.
Maybe try the thumb.
Hungry?
Oh, yes!
I have something special.
Yes, you just wait right there.
Um, hey!
Look what I have.
Crème brûlée.
Would you like some?
Okay.
Let's see.
If I put this in your mouth,
is it just gonna spill
out that hole?
Monica!
I'm in here.
I'm replacing the shelf paper.
It's gonna look great in here.
What?
Want to apologize?
For what?
For leaving me in fucking
Indiana somewhere!
I should've hit
you with the car.
Walked ten, 15 miles.
You must be tired.
Froze my ass off.
How about a bath?
I'll run you a bath.
And then after, we can do
what we do best.
We don't have an eight ball.
Not that.
Sex?
A kid.
Oh, Frank.
Let's do it;
who are we
to deny the world another
shining Gallagher star?
We had one kid on coke.
- Debbie.
- It was Carl.
No, Carl was E.
Thought Liam was E.
Liam was acid.
- Don't you remember?
- Yeah.
Christmas Eve,
I got it from that
bail-bond guy?
We had our own rave.
Till the kids came downstairs
asking for fucking gifts.
But we've never made
a little rug rat on GHB.
Aw...
Yeah.
Yeah, let's do it.
Not in my room.
Need to get shit-faced;
don't want to do it alone.
I'll pour, you talk.
I'll get the cups.
What do you want?
I have to cancel our date.
- What date?
- I'm sorry.
Just keep tomorrow
night free, okay?
I-I got to go.
You find the ship?
Thank you.
There's nothing on it.
I guess they
unloaded it already.
Where are the containers?
How the fuck should I know?
Fuck.
Easy.
Is that Linda's?
It already shot one Milkovich.
Look, I think I got a way
we can get rid of Mandy's dad.
Don't even have
to fire a bullet.
He's on parole, right?
Kidnapping and grand theft auto.
All right, so what do you
think the cops would do
if they found one of
those in his house?
Linda will know if we took it.
Grammy's 9mm?
He could get six years.
Yeah, or life.
Serial numbers aren't
scratched off.
Gun's bound to have
racked up a body count.
All we have to do is plant it.
I got nothing to lose.
Bombed the trig midterm.
How bad?
I tried to enlist.
- What?
- Monica took me.
Figured Mandy's dad
couldn't kill me in Kabul.
Yeah, well, there's plenty
of fucking Muslims who could.
Well, they all turned me down.
The Army, the Navy,
Marines, Air Force.
Still got the Coast Guard.
It's my fucking funeral.
Look, just... lay low until
tomorrow morning, okay?
Don't forget the gun.
On top of managing
the upstairs bar,
I could've gotten my
own night to promote.
Why are we talking about
a job you didn't get?
- I really wanted it. - Don't spend time
thinking about things you can't have.
Doctor didn't say
it was impossible.
Close to it.
Since when do you take
no for an answer?
Since when do you?
♪ How can I just
let you walk away? ♪
♪ Just let you leave
without a trace ♪
♪ When I stand here
taking every breath ♪
♪ With you, ooh. ♪
Sheila, you're the only one
who really knew me at all.
Wake up, baby, come on,
Mommy needs your help.
Where is Ian?
Come on, it's going to be fun.
Debbie,
don't forget your father.
Thanks for letting me talk
your ear off last night, Fi.
I'll tell her
when she gets back.
Where the hell did
she go this early?
Hey, he's still in there.
- They leave a key anywhere?
- Door's unlocked.
- Who would be crazy enough to break in?
- Right.
You bring Grammy's gun?
Remember to wipe
your prints off.
There he is.
Where should we plant it?
Maybe beside all the others.
Jesus.
It's like bringing a joint
to a crack house.
What the fuck?
Huh?!
Gonna fucking waste
- your Peter Pan ass.
- Put it down.
What the fuck you doing?
- Let him go.
- The little shit broke in.
- Wait, he's not the dad.
- He knows.
The fuck I do.
I told you whose it is.
Let him go, Dad.
This is between us.
Your dad?
Another word and I'll
blow your brains all over
the fucking linoleum.
What are you doing down here?
I didn't want to sleep
in our bed without you.
Your eyes are red.
I couldn't sleep.
You?
I'll go first.
No, me.
I called you a liar.
Only 'cause I am.
Said I didn't want kids.
I did.
Yeah.
You know, there are lots
of kids who need a home.
Fucked up foster kids like me?
Exactly.
We could build up our own army
like Wesley Snipes,
take over the neighborhood.
You know, no one said
that we have to stop trying.
Oh...
- Come here.
- Whoo!
I am going to slit your throat
with a motherfucking can opener!
I have no food.
My fucking phone is dying, man.
I am trying to find you!
Estefania, please!
You were on your way
to a Costco
in Georgia but got rerouted.
I don't care, man,
don't fucking care.
Listen, I just finish an hour
conversation with my brother,
and he's dead 12 years.
Get me out of here!
Will you give it a rest?!
Hello?
Fuck!
You--
dead man.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
I'm steam-cleaning the rug.
I rented it
from Jewel-Osco.
When's the last time you
think this has been cleaned?
How many miles did you run?
Uh, four.
You'll be up to six in no time.
Yeah, take a shower while
there's still hot water.
Hey, Carl.
Carl?
Hey, just want a second
with Mandy, okay?
Will you need this?
I'll see you later.
Yep.
So...
When'd you get home?
Last night.
Hmm.
He drinks
and mistakes me for Mom.
Only once in a while.
Not like it's a big deal.
Watch the fucking look
on your face.
A Gallagher looking down
on me-- I don't think so.
Why'd he think it was me?
He blacks out... forgets.
Lip better keep his mouth shut.
He will.
I just wish the whole thing
would go away.
We can make it.
You got $600 lying around?
We can raise it.
The money, not the baby.
You'd do that?
You're my girlfriend.
Anthony Bourdain?
Sanjay Gupta.
Nancy Grace!
There's got to be
a missing white girl somewhere.
Oh, Ruben, I'm trying.
No?
You don't want TV,
you don't eat.
Do you have a wish
before you go,
anything I can get you?
Yeah?
Oh, oh, I don't,
I-I'm not sure what you mean.
Oh...
Milk, eggs.
Aw.
Hey, bro.
He can't hear you.
Is it getting cold out there?
Could use a shower.
Oh, uh, that's not a good idea.
Hey, I...
Uh, okay, I'll tell her.
So I spent the last few months
learning baby sign language.
He says he hates crème brûlée.
- Gives him the runs.
- Oh, I noticed that.
Is there anything
he does like?
Uh, what do you want to eat?
Know how to make cake?
Strawberry shortcake.
Strawberry shortcake?
Oh.
No, he says, "Fuck that."
Vanilla cake
with a shitload
of Grand Marnier.
Hey, you need to
watch your language, bro.
Uh, there's one more thing
before he kicks it.
Uh...
Want to fuck.
Hey, out of line, bro!
That's a lady right there.
What'd he say?
He's sorry.
He'll settle for something else.
Oh.
Put everything but the
Cristal in the cooler.
I want the job.
Fiona...
You asked if I've
managed before.
Yeah,
a houseful of kids.
Taught me how to
smack with one hand
while giving a pat on
the back with the other.
Inventory, budgeting.
Go grocery shopping for a family
of six with what's in my pocket,
then let's talk.
At some point, somebody saw that
you were more than a cage dancer
and they took a chance on you.
I can do this.
I got a pre-opening
event tonight.
Things move fast,
got to keep up.
I will.
All right,
let's give it a shot.
That's what managers wear.
Pick out your size.
I got to go audition DJs.
I'm gonna kick ass, Meg.
All right, I'll see you at 9:00.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, thanks, man.
Kev says we're all set
- for the Alibi.
- Why do we even have to do
- this stupid fund-raiser?
- Mandy needs our help.
Got more chocolate chip cookies.
Every buck counts, right?
Who wants another batch?
Peanut butter, toffee?
Where is the tape?
Can't find anything
in this kitchen.
When are we moving
the furniture back?
Oh, Debbie, I love your poster.
Who did you get your
artistic talent from?
Who wants to sample a cookie?
Me.
Uh, they're for
the fund-raiser.
Blood sugar is dipping,
trying to keep up
with your mother.
She is wearing me out.
I'm done with the flyer.
Uh, it's "fund-raiser,"
not "fun razor."
Want 'em to show up, make 'em
think someone's getting cut.
All right, make copies, man.
Oh, I'll take him.
Come on, you and me, Carl.
We can take the new car.
Can't get enough
Carl and Mommy time.
Do you need some new clothes?
We could stop at JCPenney.
I can drive.
Do you have a license?
Mom's never going to
shampoo the rug, is she?
Will you calm down, okay?
Just will you sit
down and take a seat?
Okay, if I hear what you
were saying, I'm sure
that it's great,
but can you see
that I am trying my best?
You! Where have you been?!
I'm not on fucking retainer.
Okay, Marco's disappeared.
He's on a truck somewhere,
no idea where.
That's not good.
Whoa, you know Portuguese?
Yeah, it's like Italian.
She says if you don't
find Marco alive,
she's gonna call her father.
Okay.
I hope you're not wed
to your eyes or your...
tongue.
Or your dick.
Here, hold this.
No, no, no, no, no.
Who are you calling?
I got a Teamster
friend in local 710.
Yeah, yo, Tully.
I'm looking for a container one
of your drivers is hauling.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, sure I can hold.
Oh, shit, Carl. Carl.
Come on. Switch places.
Quick. Quick.
Hi.
You're supposed to
have your seatbelt on.
Think these'll match?
- Mm-hmm.
- What are you looking up?
Nothing.
It's my computer.
You don't know how to do
private browsing.
I'll check the history later.
Richard Daley College?
Just seeing what's out there.
You got to get Lip back
in high school first
before you got any shot
of getting him to college.
Actually, it's for me.
I pass my GED next month,
I can enroll for January.
I could fit in
two classes a day
before I'd have
to be at the club.
Study up on marketing,
I could be
promoting my own night
before the end
of the semester.
Good for you, Fi.
Why didn't you just say so?
I thought you was looking
at Kev dick pics.
Hey, Gallagher.
Seen Fiona? I've been
looking for her.
Why, what's up?
Your mom's down at the station.
Bring bail money.
Dying wish.
How are we gonna
feed it to him?
Oh.
Think he wants another hit.
He worked so hard to get clean.
Sometimes it's not worth
holding out.
Life's too short.
Why not just give in?
Christ.
I'm not here for your stash.
I need bail money.
I only have a grand.
You have a grand?
- Where's the Squirrel Fund?
- What the hell
is a Squirrel Fund?
Empty your fucking pockets.
You talk to your
father that way?
Get the fucking key
and get me out of here!
I want my phone call!
Get my lawyer, Rodney
King your asses.
Your brother was driving.
He got a nasty bump,
but he'll be fine.
I told my captain
your mom was driving
under the influence.
You feel powerful
locking me up?
She's not making it easy.
I'm not invisible!
Hey, buddy, you doing okay?
Do you hear me?
I'm right here.
I'm right here. Here!
What the fuck is this?
We're raising money.
For Mandy.
$25, all the well
drinks you want.
Hey, guys,
you got ten minutes to sign up
for the pool tournament,
five dollar entry fee;
bragging rights are at stake.
Hey, thanks for all
your help, Kev.
Yeah, too many Gallaghers
in the world already.
Lip, now you?
Instead of passing
rubbers out at schools,
they should be passing
them out at your house.
Hey, Debbie. Cookies?
Oh.
We have dollar a cookie,
buck 50 a brownie,
70 for the gun.
Oh, hey, how'd you get
so many people here?
Told them the proceeds
go to a great cause.
It's for a church retreat.
Kids with cleft palates.
Here.
The NRA.
The resistance against
the Zionist occupation.
Hmm.
Hey, wow,
you look great.
Where's Pele?
Florida, sunshine state.
Heading to the airport,
just wanted to stop by
and ask for another rain check.
Rain check?
Yeah.
Tomorrow I'm all yours, okay?
Who says I want you?
Where the fuck have you been?
Oh, what, you back for
good or just visiting?
Just bailed Monica out of jail.
What? Why?
Cops and their
fucking quotas,
why do you think?
She let Carl play bumper cars
with a Buick.
Is he okay?
"Is he okay?"
What about your mother?
She birthed
your ungrateful asses.
I'm late for a meeting.
They said Carl's gonna be fine,
but it's hard to tell
because he's
- normally concussed more than he isn't.
- Well,
don't let him fall asleep.
What, you're AWOL
this whole time,
now you're giving orders?
- I was around.
- Really?
So you know Monica spent
all the Squirrel Fund money?
You know what, I wouldn't
have even had the cash
to bail her out if I
didn't return a bunch
of dolls I found
in Debbie's room!
The first rule
you learn in this house,
you hide the goddamn money.
- She seemed better.
- Look at this place.
The sofa is in the kitchen.
For fuck's sake, she tried
to get Ian to enlist.
She what?
What did you think
was gonna happen, Fiona?
Thought it might
be different this time.
Hm, well, how'd that Kool-Aid
taste going down?
Where is she?
You could've gotten
Carl killed!
You tried to get Ian
into the army?!
You promised me.
Get out of bed!
Get out of bed, Mom!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Get me out of here! Please!
Help!