Ooh, look pretty sharp tonight, Earl.
You going somewhere special?
Max, I'm free, black and 75.
Who knows what the night will bring?
Well, here's a 20.
Can you break this the way
you just broke my heart?
Pop, pop! Ha, ha!
Look at all this.
People really tipped well tonight.
Don't get used to it.
Thanksgiving is almost here.
Soon as people realize how much
they have to spend on holiday gifts...
...their wallets snap tighter
than Kim Kardashian's legs...
...after the wedding check cleared.
I always love this time of year.
Spiced pumpkin lattes,
bringing my winter furs out.
Then bringing my winter furs to the dry
cleaners to get the red PETA paint out.
For me, it was jumping into a pile
of leaves and finding a used condom.
What's up, Children of the Corn?
I will stay tonight and decorate diner for
American holiday of Thanksgiving.
Wow. I'm surprised you got
the right holiday decorations.
Last month you put out
Easter bunnies for Yom Kippur.
So many Jewish holidays,
I cannot Wikipedia them all.
What, like I don't got a life?
My father and I had a special
Thanksgiving tradition every year.
Let me guess. You'd fly someplace
like the Bahamas, lay by the pool...
...and he'd light other people's
stolen money on fire?
No. We'd rent out the Waldorf Astoria
ballrooms and feed the homeless.
Don't look at me right now.
And after, we'd fly down to our home
in St. Barts for two weeks.
Okay, you can look at me again.
I stayed at the Waldorf Astoria once.
Beautiful hotel.
Fifty dollars for a hamburger.
For that money, it should eat me first.
Okay, ready to go?
If you'd like to do something
to honor the spirit of Thanksgiving...
...open your doors, feed the homeless.
Yeah, put your money
where your cornstalk is.
- Caroline and I will work for free.
- Isn't it enough that...
...when I see them on the street, I smile
and pretend to fumble for change?
No, it isn't. You can afford
to open the diner for one night.
You can't put a price tag
on those emotional rewards.
Yes, I can. Eighteen dollars for 16-pound
turkey, and I will need many of them.
There. Price tag.
Here. I will pay for turkeys.
Jeez, dude, where'd you get that?
I sell cigarettes from New Hampshire
to school kids in New York.
It is a good profit.
And beautiful drive. I love the leaves.
All right, I'm feeling y'all.
I'll bring the pies.
My mother used to make the best
chocolate pie.
She got so mad at
this white woman she worked for...
...she took this pie into the bathroom--
No, hold up, that was from The Help.
I know it's not Burberry
like we're used to, but I'm telling you.
Used moving blankets
are gonna be in this year.
Who's a trendsetter?
We're really lucky November
is so warm.
Another thing I'm giving thanks
for this Thanksgiving? Global warming.
I think the three remaining polar bears
would disagree.
Max, it's time to teach me how to bake.
Okay, well, if we're doing that,
first I have to go get baked.
I'm serious.
It's the beginning of the holiday season.
With all the Christmas cupcakes
and festive gift baskets...
...you're gonna need help.
Festive holiday gift baskets?
- No way. I'm not into all that crap.
- Oh, no. Are you one of those...
..."I'm too cool to believe in the wonders
of Christmas" type of bitches?
I am so many types of bitches,
I've lost count.
The only wonder of Christmas
I'm aware of is...
...I wonder how you're gonna keep
that attitude through Christmas.
Why, because this is my first holiday
without any money?
Uh, yeah.
Money isn't what makes
the holidays special, Max.
Uh, yeah.
The holidays are totally about money.
About spending money to buy things...
...to stuff into the giant black sucking
hole in the center of each of us...
...that reminds us life is hard
and then we die.
And that's my Christmas card.
Max, I'm aware this holiday season
will be challenging.
Will I miss my 20-foot Christmas tree
decorated by ten gay men? Yes.
Will I miss those ten gay men outing my
cousin Steven before he was ready? No.
My holiday spirit is bigger
than my money. Teach me how to bake.
- We only have a couple weeks.
- Fine.
- Pour a cup of milk into the mixer.
- This will be fun.
When I was little, I used to make
my father cakes in my Easy-Bake Oven.
My Easy-Bake Oven was repossessed.
So, uh, speaking of your father,
are you doing okay?
This is a hard time of year
for people who have feelings...
...and with your father in prison,
how are you doing?
I'm great. I found out
that since it's Thanksgiving...
...they're allowing me to see him
for the first time.
Well, that excitement will probably taper
off after the full-body cavity search.
I don't know, I might like it.
It's been a while since
I've had any cavities searched.
All right. Pour the milk, slut.
One cup milk.
- There. How's that?
- Good.
Now into the mixer.
- There. How was that?
- Uh-uh.
We're not playing "rich girl gets a trophy
every time she does something normal."
Just cover the bowl with the towel
so it doesn't splash out and turn it on.
- Oh, it's not plugged in.
- Oh, right.
No, not without the towel.
Christmas comes but once a year,
and I think it just did.
Wow, high-end mixers are a lot of money.
I thought if we came to a big store...
...there'd be a lot of them
and better prices.
- We can't afford these.
- How much did you think they'd be?
I don't know.
I guess I'm not used to looking at prices.
I usually just point, pout
and it's purchased.
I had a version of that,
only it was more like point...
...and when they look the other way,
stuff steaks down your pants and run.
There has to be a mixer here
we can afford.
There is.
Here.
A $5 spoon?
That's what we can afford?
Yeah, if we put it on layaway,
work hard for a few years.
I'm used to being poor around your stuff,
but not around stuff that I want.
What happened to all your
"money's not important" holiday spirit?
Max, it feels like you want me
to be depressed about the holidays.
I'm just saying it's okay for you not to be
all up around me if you're not feeling it.
It's all right to let your dark side out.
Come to the dark side.
Oh, my God, look.
They're hiring elves.
Why would I go to the dark side
when I could go to Santaworld?
Let's go get in line.
I've always loved Santaworld.
Me too, as a David Sedans story...
...not as an actual real-life option.
If we get hired, we could use
our employee discount...
...to get one
of the really good cake mixers. Oh!
And then it'd be like it came from Santa.
Come on, Max.
We'd be great elves.
I have the holiday spirit,
you're great with kids.
And we're both so desperate for money,
we'll wear other people's tights.
I've been coming to this store
at Christmas since I was little.
I'd get all dressed up in my fanciest
winter coat and hat...
...and then stand in line to see Santa
with my hands in my muff.
And they didn't throw you out?
There is nothing Christmas-y
about this hallway.
The place Santa sends promiscuous
elves to get the results of their STD test.
That kind of comment almost got us
knocked out of the first round.
- You're lucky I edited your application.
- Why? What was so bad?
You requested to work in Santa's
sex-toy shop.
Max, that's not even a thing.
Tell that to my candy-cane
shaped vibrator.
Max.
I call it "Santa's big helper."
Heh-heh.
Please try
and get into the holiday spirit.
I know. If we get hired, we'll go right
home and watch Miracle on 34th Street.
It'll be a miracle on 34th Street...
...if we make it out of the bottom
of this slave ship without elf scurvy.
Hi. I couldn't help but overhear you
mention Miracle On 34th Street.
That's my absolute favorite
Christmas movie.
Mine too.
Second favorite is
It's a Wonderful Life.
- Mine too.
- I've got Schindler's List on Blu-ray.
- Hi, I'm Mary.
- I'm Caroline.
Hi. I'm Mary.
It's cool. We don't need to talk.
That's Max.
She's kind of a Grinch about Christmas.
Oh. Like my brother Patrick.
He's always teasing me about
loving Christmas.
He calls me Mary Christmas.
Get it? Ha, ha!
It's because my name is Mary.
Ha, ha!
I can't help it,
it's my favorite time of year.
- Mine too.
- Yo. Disconnect before it's too late.
Don't be so cynical.
Especially Christmas Eve.
It's an O'Brien family tradition,
all seven of my sisters and brothers...
...we line up on the staircase
in our brand-new Christmas PJs...
...and have our picture taken.
- Bitch is 30.
- Max.
It's my father.
Hi, Daddy. You'll never guess
where I am right now.
Applying for a job at Santaworld.
No, it's not depressing at all.
The man's in prison
and he thinks this is depressing.
Oh.
Are you sure? It's really not that far.
Okay, if that's what you want.
Call me on Thanksgiving. Love you.
He thought about it and doesn't want me
to come. He can't face...
-...having me see him in there.
- You okay?
Fine.
Quiet, please, people.
I have an announcement.
Everyone in this corridor
has been chosen to be an elf.
Mazel.
Yay, we're elves.
Report to work at 3 a.m.
the morning of Black Friday.
Ooh! This is so exciting. Ha, ha!
Fa la Ia la Ia
La la la Ia
Okay, well, I'll see you both then.
Okay, Mary
Great, 3 a.m.
You, me and Definitely-A-Virgin Mary.
Good night. Get home safely.
Oh. Maybe I should not
have said that to homeless.
That is it, 2 a.m. Freebie Thanksgiving
dinner is now officially over.
According to my calculations,
we served over 300 turkey dinners...
...and only had two knife fights.
Thank you, Caroline.
This experience taught me
that rich or poor, home or homeless...
...we are all the same.
Wait. Where's my wallet?
They took my wallet.
Those dirty sons of--
Oh, here it is.
Yes, we are all the same.
Well, I have two things to say.
First, I'm proud of us for spreading
the spirit of Thanksgiving together.
And secondly, someone left an adult
diaper in this booth...
...and I am not dealing with that.
What's with the sad face?
You saw the bathroom?
We fed the homeless, but it doesn't
feel like Thanksgiving without my father.
You made a lot of people
happy tonight.
- You should feel pretty good about that.
- Yes, I do.
Come on, elf. Clear these tables.
We have to be at Santaworld in an hour.
You have to be there
in the middle of the night?
Because it's Black Friday.
The doors open at 5 a.m.
We wanna be there right on time...
...to see the first person trampled
to death by Uggs.
We work all night
and then all day tomorrow.
- How are we gonna do this?
- I got the answer right here.
Max, I'm not doing cocaine.
If we could afford cocaine,
we could afford a mixer.
- Nine-Hour Energy shots, a.k.a. Elf Juice.
- I've never done these. Do they work?
Millions of wired-off-their-asses
college students can't be wrong.
Whoa, whoa, wh--
- Did you just drink that whole thing?
- Yeah. Why?
Nothing. I'm sure it's not too much.
They suggest sipping it,
but who are they?
All right, we'd better go.
We gotta go, go, go.
Oh, you should've sipped it.
How do I look? Because I kind of feel
like I look like a north pole-dancer.
You actually look cute. You look good
in red and green together.
You can pull off anything. You're
so beautiful. I don't tell you that enough.
Whoa!
Whoa, slow down, Speed Racer.
I can't stop.
What was in that stuff you gave me?
I don't know.
The ingredients are in Spanish.
Well, my corazón
is beating muy rápido.
- Why aren't you in your elf costume yet?
- I was talking to those people.
There's a slight chance, but a chance,
I could move to the strolling carolers.
Their ethnic mix is short a token blond.
And I'm blond, baby.
No, no. Look, forget it.
You got me into the underbelly of
the elf beast. You are not bailing on me.
Those period costumes
are so much prettier.
I'll knock you to Rudolph's house
if you abandon me.
We're in this together. Get your bells.
I didn't wanna tell you this
because it's gross.
The last elf who had the tights
they gave me?
Let's just say her little lady elf
friend visited unexpectedly.
Ew. Talk about a period costume.
You're right. It's disgusting.
I can't do this anymore. I'm leaving.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
I feel tired and wired at the same time.
This was an awful, awful, awful idea.
All right, calm down. Jeez, you're
like a Christmas crack monkey.
Look, we are not
going anywhere, okay?
You got me all elfed up
and now we need these jobs.
Talk to someone and tell them
why you need a new pair of tights.
I can't. It's embarrassing.
Look, either you ask her
or you rip out the crotch...
...and risk showing 6-year-olds
your winter wonderland.
And now I'm sad.
You. The one with the dark hair.
Come with me.
Where? And is there
a drug test involved?
Change of plans.
I need for you to be Mrs. Claus.
The other one had to leave.
Blamed menopause.
Menopause, please. Heh.
I had my uterus yanked out on my lunch
hour and I was back at my desk by 2.
Follow me. Oh, unless you don't want
that extra $2 an hour.
Oh, no. You are not leaving me here
alone when I'm crashing on elf juice.
If I can't be a singer,
you can't be Mrs. Claus.
Well, I'm sorry, but I'm throwing you
under the sled, sister.
That extra $2 an hour will bring us
closer to the really good mixer.
And the way my life is going...
...this might be my only chance
to be married to a rich guy.
I'd double-check those tights
if I were you.
- Look over here.
Unh. These tights suck.
Hi. Hi, elf. I just got assigned
to the front of the line with you.
Oh, crap.
It's me, Mary.
Mary Christmas. Ha, ha.
- Like my brother Patrick always says.
- Yeah, you said that.
Look at how cute we look, Jingles.
I just named you Jingles.
Heh-heh.
Get it? Because of all your bells.
Oh, listen.
Ah. This is my number one favorite
Christmas song. Ooh!
- What's your favorite?
-"Silent Night." Get it?
Because I want you to be silent.
What's the matter with you?
You're acting like an elf-hole.
- Oh, hello, children.
- Yeah!
- Who's next to see my husband, Santa?
- I am so mad at you right now.
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Um, hold on, children.
Mrs. Claus is just having an issue
with one of her elf employees.
- What are you doing? What's wrong?
- You abandon me on Christmas...
...the day after my father abandons me
on Thanksgiving? You have balls.
Christmas balls, like on Santa's tree.
Or a Hanukkah bush.
Look, I've got
my own problems, okay?
Santa is kind of handsy.
And you leave me here with this one...
...when I'm coming down the bad side
of Nine-Hour Energy Mountain?
I don't know what's at the bottom, but
so far, not the miracle on 34th Street.
- Well, elf--
- Her name is Jingles.
One more word, Mary. Seriously.
Listen, Bipolar Express...
...you need to jingle
up that mountain...
...because all these kids
are looking at us.
Hello. You got your list for Santa?
Yep. Got it right here.
Well, he's waiting for you,
so go right ahead in.
Yay! Let's go.
Hi. Oh, you look so pretty
in your hat and your coat.
Thank you very much.
I used to have a coat like that.
But she gave it to a reindeer
because he was very cold.
Oh, you have your list for Santa?
Let's see what you want.
- Oh, a pretty doll.
- Had it.
- An Easy-Bake Oven.
- A Barbie Dreamhouse.
- Oh. Had that too.
Had all those things
and now I have nothing.
- Nothing to stick in my big hole.
- Okay.
Jingles, what are you doing?
- Tell them, Max.
- No, no, I'm not Max.
I'm Mrs. Claus.
Mrs. Beyoncé Claus.
And I'm married to Santa.
No, tell them what you told me.
That it's all just stuff we buy
to stick in our big holes.
I've been married for 50 years.
I don't even think
about holes anymore.
Why is she talking to children
about holes?
- I'll get her
- Caroline--
- No, Max.
You were right.
They should know the truth.
Mrs. Claus, have a little elf control.
Jingles, come into my little house.
No, Max, they should know.
There is no miracle on 34th Street
and it's not such a wonderful life.
If it were, I wouldn't be standing here
in crotchless tights in Santaworld...
...with a father in prison,
too broke to buy a mixer.
- Stop it. You're gonna ruin Christmas.
- Christmas is all about money.
If you want stuff from Santa,
you gotta buy it, because there is no--
Merry Christmas.
Get her out of here now.
And you, put your knees together.
Hope I didn't ruin Christmas
for all those sweet children.
No, you didn't. All they saw
was a crotchless elf freaking out.
But Mary Christmas
will never recover.
They'll find her in her studio apartment
in two weeks...
...hung from the chimney with care.
This is all kind of your fault.
You told me to come to the dark side.
I didn't think you'd turn
into Darth Caroline.
Once I went, I couldn't get back.
- And chugging that elf juice didn't help.
- It wasn't just the drink.
Before those presents came
crashing down on me, reality did.
I have no money
and a father in prison...
...who didn't wanna see me
on Thanksgiving.
Yeah, well, there are a lot of people
way worse off than you.
Yes, your father's in prison, but at least
you have one and you know where he is.
And you have a home and a job.
And you have a freaking horse.
So happy holidays.
It is a wonderful life.
You're right. I am so lucky.
Well, since right now is the closest to
the Christmas spirit we're gonna get...
...Santa wanted me to give you
your Christmas present now.
It's our new mixer.
We're gonna old-school it.
Oh, you spooned me.
I feel bad, I didn't get you anything.
Max, you got me everything.
Before you, I was living on a subway,
and now look.
I'm living near a subway.
So did you buy this?
No, it's from Santa.
Jingles, did you steal this?
Yeah. Ha, ha.
I grabbed it
when they were throwing us out.
Wow, Caroline Channing.
You keep this up, you won't have to ask
permission to visit your father in prison.
But I did give $2 of our cupcake fund
money to the Salvation Army Santa.
So, God bless us everyone.
It's a wonderful life.
It's times like this
I really miss Darth Caroline.