The Big Bang Theory -
it's a funny show.
Who's Adam West?
What do you two talk about?
We're going to relive some of the
show's most memorable moments.
What's going on?
It's not what it looks like.
Oh, it's a tiara!
I love you so.
I love you too.
Jim, hello.
And, how are you?
I'm here on set with the cast to get
them to tell us their favourites.
I'm kind of a fan girl
about this show.
And, let us in on a few secrets.
I'm not a big Star Trek fan, so...
Are you excited?
I'm really excited.
I'm a fan of the show.
Welcome to The Big Bang Theory,
it all started with a big bang.
Boom!
This is the opportunity of a
lifetime for a Big Bang Theory fan.
Full access behind the scenes.
And a chance to talk to the cast
and crew to ask them the questions
that we fans, by which I mean me,
are dying to know the answers to.
Here we go and background, action!
Leonard, promise me,
when our new waitress comes over,
you will not start a complicated
on-again, off-again relationship
with her because
I'm very, very hungry.
It's such a simple idea.
Too geeky guys get a hot neighbour.
Guess, I'm your new neighbour, Penny.
Leonard, Sheldon.
Hi.
- Hi.
And yet that simple idea
has created a comedy supernova,
one of the biggest
shows in the world.
Wow, you really are a genius.
Not really,
I Googled how to do that.
The show has some truly
legendary characters.
In our rag tag band of scientists,
with nothing to lose,
I am the smart one.
Wolowitz is the funny one
and Koothrappali
is the lovable foreigner
who struggles to understand
our ways, and fails.
Now, we all know these geeks
and girls so well after five years
that they hardly need
any introduction.
What do the cast think of them?
How would you describe
Leonard as a character?
Struggling.
One Tequila Sunrise.
Thank you.
This drink is a wonderful example
of how liquids with different
specific gravities interact
in a cylindrical container.
Thank you.
That's what's fun
about playing him,
he's struggling to evolve.
You have assured my ability
to tolerate idiots.
Now, come with me.
Where are we going?
We are going to have sex.
Why? I mean, OK.
Sheldon's first and
foremost a genius.
Are you familiar with mean theory?
I'm familiar with everything
but go on.
He is doing his best to stick
to his guns of what he wants,
while having small moments
of learning
how to be a more normal human
being, for lack of a better word.
What kind of doctor removes
shoes from asses?
Depending on the depth,
that's either proctologist
or a general surgeon.
How would you describe Penny?
Adorable.
Mm-hm.
Look, guys, for the future
I don't mind killing the big spiders
but you have to at least try
with the little ones.
I love that she has become
so sarcastic and funny.
The last morsel
is called the greng jai piece
and it is reserved
for the most important
and valued member of the group.
Thank you all for this high honour.
How would you describe Howard?
I would say a bit
of a delusional Casanova.
May I say, Penny,
not a lot of women could look as hot
as you do with such greasy hair.
More confidence
than is good for him.
Or, maybe ignorance is bliss,
I don't know.
We just got back from that exhibit
of those plasticised human cadavers.
And some of those skinless
chicks were hot.
Raj is like the Tom Cruise
of the sitcom world.
He is, he is. It's the looks.
It's the...
You know, erm, Raj
is the foreigner on the show.
He comes from
India, New Delhi, India.
What, just because I'm Indian
I can't be a Norse god?
No, no, no,
Raj has to be an Indian God.
He's obviously pathologically shy.
He can't talk to women
without drinking alcohol.
OK, look, this never happened.
Do you understand me?
Really? Still can't talk to me?
I think on the surface,
Bernadette is your
typical microbiologist,
kind of nerdy.
In microbiology, the most exciting
thing I get to work with is yeast.
Erm, but what I love about her
is the fact that we've discovered
these layers to her.
She's kind of got a dark side.
Yes.
She's got a temper.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You are always so nice to me,
I thought maybe you liked me.
I'm nice to everyone!
So, what you see necessarily
isn't what you get with her.
If you and Leonard
get back together,
Sheldon and I will finally have
someone to go on double dates with.
What about me and Howard?
Fine, we can double with you too.
So insecure.
How would you describe
your character Amy?
She's straightforward,
she's dedicated
and she also knows
how to have a good time.
Oh, I know!
We'll go to a sweat lodge,
take peyote, roll around in mud
and paint fertility symbols
on Bernadette's naked body.
That's happening!
So I think she's a pretty
well-rounded person, considering.
Yes, all things being...
The only person who
signed my yearbook was my mother.
Aww.
"Amy, self-respect and a hymen are
better than friends and fun. Mum."
The Big Bang Theory has just hit an
important milestone - 100 episodes.
That's impressive for any show.
The fans loved it from day one,
but did the people
who were actually making the show
have an inkling it would go on
to be such a huge success?
Chuck Lorre is the man who,
along with co-creator Bill Prady,
is responsible for the show.
In the past 20 years, he's brought
us some of the biggest shows on TV,
including Roseanne
and Two And A Half Men.
What gave you the idea for the show
in the first place?
It started with Prady telling me...
Bill Prady,
the co-creator of the show...
telling me about his life in the '80s
in New York as a computer programmer.
Uh huh.
And the guys he was hanging out with
and working with
were all brilliant guys,
but they were entirely incompetent
in all other aspects of life.
Yeah.
Oh. Hey, guys.
Hey, sorry we're late!
Late?
It's 7.05!
And you said
the party starts at seven.
Well, yeah.
When you start a party at seven,
no-one show ups at, you know, seven.
It's 7.05.
And that struck us both
as really funny
and as a good starting place
for a group of characters
who were extraordinary
but were struggling to get on
with the mundane task of living.
Why on earth are you telling me
all this?
I don't know.
Sometimes your movements
are so lifelike,
I forget you're not a real boy.
When you first wrote the pilot,
did you have any kind of sense
that it could go on to be
as successful as it has been?
None. None whatsoever.
When Johnny Galecki
and Jim Parsons first read together,
that was
when we started to have hope.
Put this in the bathroom.
What for?
I need to measure
my fluid intake and output
to make sure my kidneys
aren't shutting down.
I mix pancake batter in this!
I auditioned twice,
and didn't get hired both times.
And they did a pilot
and it didn't work!
We did the pilot twice.
You know,
we had two chances to get this right.
And they revamped the script
and made it different,
and I came back in
and I guess it was all about timing.
Mm.
And I just - clonk! -
knocked it out of the ballpark.
It was like, "Oh, God!
Something's happening here."
You could feel
something special was happening.
It was very apparent that it
was better than we'd hoped for.
I knew it was a true ensemble,
that everyone was just fantastic.
You could sort of sense
where it was going to go,
that it was going to kind of
not be making fun of nerdy people
but sort of give them the voice...
Yeah.
And make everybody else
sort of the laughing stock.
Who's Adam West?
"Who's Adam West?"
Leonard, what do the two of you
talk about after the coitus?
The first night shooting,
I think really...
in front of an audience...
is what cemented it for me.
Because they knew the characters
immediately and they pulled for them.
I'm sorry, do you speak English?
Oh, he speaks English.
He just can't speak to women.
Really? Why?
He's kind of a nerd.
Juice box?
The show, ultimately,
is an underdog story
and people like to
root for underdogs,
because everyone, in their life,
has felt like an underdog.
What did I ever do to
Jimmy Mullins in the third grade?
He still punched me in the face
with my own fists.
That transcends...
cultures, religions, language.
That's why it's such
an international show,
why it's popular all over the world.
Whether you're watching the show
and saying, like, "That's me!"
or you're watching it going,
"What's up with these guys?"
There's always something...
Everyone can relate to being
an underdog at some point.
Hi, Amy. Can I talk to Penny?
A guest in my trundle bed
and a boy at my door?
I wish I could tell 13-year-old me
itdoesget better!
These characters are very lovable,
and I'm not talking about Penny,
even though
she's the most lovable.
But the guys, truthfully...
I mean, from day one,
you just fall in love with them.
I feel they've made nerdy
and goofy kind of sexy.
♪ Da-daaaaaaa! ♪
I don't think
it's the specific geekiness
or science
or Star Trekky stuff,
cos none of us are really
into that stuff in real life,
and I know a lot of people
that aren't that love the show,
so I think there's a human connection
to feeling like an outsider
or trying to figure out,
sort of, the...
the rules, the handbook of life.
I love that it's
a show about smart people,
I love that it's a show about
the quirks of smart people
and sort of
the social dynamics of people
other than the Beverly Hills 90210,
Friends, attractive people
hooking up in different permutations
kind of show.
Last night, I was strong-armed into
an evening of harp music and spooning
with an emotional
Amy Farrah Fowler.
This on a night that
I had originally designated
for solving the space-time geometry
in higher-spin gravity
and building my LEGO Death Star.
There's no denying that the
gang on The Big Bang Theory
get themselves into some
peculiar pickles.
Over 100 episodes, we've seen some
outrageous behaviour.
But what keeps us watching
isn't the wacky antics,
it's the relationships.
The friendships and romances
on the show
have grown and developed
over the years.
The guys have actually made
friends with some girls.
Howard grew out of his bromance with
Raj and found love with Bernadette.
Sheldon has a girlfriend
and Leonard and Penny,
well, they're just
Leonard and Penny.
It's been an interesting
ride for these two.
From their first kiss in episode six
to their break-up in episode 59,
to whatever it is they have now.
It's been an on, off, on, off,
delight to watch.
Forgotten the details?
Here are the highlights.
New neighbour?
Evidently.
What about if you went out with me?
Yes, I will go out with you.
Leonard has no business being
involved with a waitress/actress
who felt so insecure that she lied
about finishing community college.
What about that really long hug.
What did that mean?
It means I wish you were going.
Leonard, you're back.
Yes, I just stopped by to say...
Let's slide over to Sheldon's spot
and make out.
You're a dirty girl.
I love you, Penny.
Thank you.
So we're in two different places
emotionally, so what, that's fine.
In fact it makes sense
because let's face it,
I've been in this relationship
two years longer than you.
That isn't fair to you, Leonard,
I'm sorry.
I screwed up.
Leonard's a great guy.
Never should've broken up with him.
What's going on?
It's not what it looks like.
Do you have plans for dinner?
Why, you guys going somewhere?
No, I mean just you and me.
Have you thought this through?
Yes and I think we should go anyway.
I think if I could choose,
I would love them to end up
together at the end of the day.
Not any time soon,
but you know how relationships are,
they go on and off,
you date someone, you break up,
you become friends,
your friends deal with it.
Because they're so close, it's
always going to affect everyone.
I like the ride that the writers
are taking them on.
I think it's really fun
and it's real.
I have a real soft spot
in my heart for those two
and I think they are the loves
of one another's lives.
They just don't have it together
in other areas of their life.
There's a real visceral thing
between the two of them
and they both just have
a whole lot to learn.
Our babies will be smart
and beautiful.
Not to mention imaginary.
One couple, who despite all odds,
do seem to have it together,
are Sheldon and Amy.
I love the Amy and Sheldon
relationship
cos I think
it's a very different kind of sweet.
It's a very different kind
of tender.
Possible explanations
for your symptoms are,
in descending order of likelihood,
hyperthyroidism,
premature menopause,
hosting an alien parasite...
Or, and I only include it
for the sake of covering all bases,
sexual arousal.
Where would I have picked up
an alien parasite?
Amy and Sheldon are in
the relationship agreement phase.
A binding covenant
that in 31 pages enumerates,
iterates and codifies the rights
and responsibilities
of Sheldon Lee Cooper, here and after
known as "the boyfriend',
and Amy Farrah Fowler, here and
after known as "the girlfriend".
It's so romantic.
It's just this beautifully
odd situation,
he seems to really enjoy her company.
And, erm,
there's obviously slight
attraction/attachment there.
That has just sort of come upon him.
You're a vixen, Amy Farrah Fowler.
There was a lot of pressure from fans
that he be in a romantic
relationship.
But... I didn't want to
miss out on an opportunity
to have a character
living life on his own terms.
That's what wonderful
about these characters,
particularly Jim's character,
he's living life on his own terms.
Proposal...
one wild night of torrid love-making
that soothes my soul
and enflames my loins.
Whether you agree with it or not.
Whether you agree with how
he's having a relationship with
Amy Farrah Fowler...
that's the relationship.
They've established a relationship
that works for them.
And... I think that's admirable.
Counter proposal...
I will gently stroke your head,
and repeat, "Aw, who's a good Amy?"
Rounding out the trio of couples
on the show
are the pint-sized
Howard and Bernadette.
When the show started did you ever
think that Howard would get engaged?
Ha! No.
You know, I thought
he would be killed off or something.
Erm, yeah,
he's certainly not
the first to find love.
Yes, I will marry you.
You will? I will!
Oh, I love you so much.
I love you too!
It was erm, just a perfect storm of,
for whatever reason,
these two people balance
each other out.
Don't take him too seriously,
a lot of what
he says is intended as humour.
Yeah, well I don't think
it's very funny.
Me neither.
But he just lights up when I laugh.
I think that, these characters,
there's so much love between them,
so whether they actually marry or
they don't, I think it'll be great.
What is that behind your ear?
Look, it's a condom.
Well, ladies, we killed the bottle.
The Big Bang Theory is about
more than romance, of course.
It's about friendships
and those can be the most
entertaining relationships
on the show.
My favourite... come on, easy...
Howard and Raj.
To friendship.
How would you describe
Raj's friendship with Howard?
It's a bromance.
It's a classic bromance.
All right, honey, if we're going to
make the movie we should go.
This may be hard for you to hear
but when I say, "honey",
I mean my fiancee.
Yeah, well, now it means her.
I think it can be misconstrued
into a physical relationship,
that they have the physical
hots for each other.
That's not happening.
There are a lot of girls out there
who want to kiss you.
Where?
You just have to look.
N-o-o-o-o-o.
Well, this was fun!
There have been so many memorable
Big Bang Theory moments.
Some of my personal favourites are
Sheldon dressed as a Doppler
Effect...
I don't care if anybody gets it,
I'm going as the Doppler Effect.
Howard's robot arm...
incident.
You slipped
and fell into a robot hand?!
Yes.
Penis first?!
That's not important.
Which moments stick in the minds
of the cast and creators.
There was an episode where I... they
wanted Sheldon to learn to drive.
There was this simulation exercise
he had on the TV with the video
game to practise driving.
Slow it! Hit the brake,
hit the brake!
The commitment of everybody
as one group to get it done,
it was sheer joy.
I liked the one where Howard cries
to Penny, and then tries to kiss her
and gets punched.
Hm.
Obviously the tiara scene...
Sheldon, you are the most shallow,
self-centred person I have ever met.
Do you ever think that another
transparently manipulative...
Oh, it's a tiara!
A tiara, I have a tiara!
Put it on me, put it on me,
put it on me!
Put it on me! Put it on me!
Do you have a favourite
scene or episode?
Oh, goodness, erm,
I'm kind of a fan girl
about this show.
The scene where Penny gave Sheldon
a letter Nimoy autographed,
I think was one of my most favourite
moments.
"To Sheldon, live long and prosper...
"Leonard Nimoy."
He came into the restaurant,
sorry, the napkin is dirty,
he wiped his mouth with it.
The gift was a wonderful gesture,
but the moment that everybody
was struck by was, we had this
character who was so disaffected
and so, you know, alienated from
people, hugging her in that moment
cos he was so overcome with joy.
We're making a situation comedy here
and we have to make one
every week but you know,
everyone on set is crying!
It got very emotional.
Leonard, look,
Sheldon's hugging me!
Now, just because there are
so many great moments in the past
doesn't mean there won't be lots of
great moments in the future...
on the contrary... there will be.
What they'll come up with
is anybody's guess.
Here we go, into the future.
Do you have hopes and thoughts
for Sheldon in the future?
What would I want for him?
That he wins the Nobel finally?
I mean, that's like getting a couple
together at the end of an episode.
Where's his fight then?
Do I want him
and Amy to have test tube baby?
I don't want to have to work with a
child ever week on this set, so no...
That's important!
Do you have hopes
and aspirations for Howard's future?
For the better of his own
being I hope
he can manage to get out from under
his mother's fat thumb.
I don't know if they'll actually
make it down the aisle,
if they will or won't.
I want them to get married
because I think if we see that scene
then presumably Howard's mother
will have to be there.
At the actual wedding,
she could serve us, I guess. Yeah.
I hope Penny gets another job...
Mm-hm... than working at
The Cheesecake Factory.
She's good there, though.
She is really good
at The Cheesecake Factory
but I'm kind of sick of the uniform.
So I'd love to maybe work at Sushi.
Do you feel like Raj will eventually
be able to talk to girls?
Without the aid of drink?
I don't know.
If not drink it'll be something else.
Hard to believe we've already had
100 episodes of the Big Bang Theory.
But we have. Here's to 100 more.
We're not writing Lost.
We have no idea where this is going.
Big deal,
not knowing is part of the fun.