She's in her room.
She won't come out.
[ Grunts ]
Assuming the dead drops
are real,
Feds are going to be on them.
-Feds?
-They're gunning for arrests.
If there's no money in those
dead drops, Lalo will know.
The dead drops remain.
If we'd have had a house, I
never would've wanted to leave.
You'll say anything
to get what you want.
Woman: Help you
find somethin'?
Uh, no, thanks.
I'm just browsing.
[Grunts lightly]
[Exhaling sharply]
Woman:
That still works.
You can plug it in
if you want.
Oh. Thanks.
How much for this?
That?
I could let that go
for $30.
Um...
$75 for all three?
¶¶
[Bells dinging]
[Birds chirping]
[Alarm beeping]
[Beeping stops]
[Inhales sharply]
[Groans lightly]
[Exhales sharply]
[Birds chirping]
[Groans]
Yeah,
don't worry about it.
Building
will take care of it.
That's whatcha
pay rent for.
What's your day
look like?
I got MDC
in the morning
and, uh,
court in the afternoon.
Oh, and I'm finally doing
that lunch with Howard.
Yeah?
See what he wants.
Hopefully it will be
short and sweet.
You?
Uh...
yesterday was bad.
Today
I'm gonna fix it.
Sounds like a plan.
[Smooches]
See ya.
[Car door opens]
Pull the initial research we did
on Lot 2375.
Yeah.
Yeah, all of it.
Uh, permit status,
costs, projections.
Uh-huh. Are they on digital?
Good. How are you on PowerPoint?
Great. I'll walk you through
what I need when I get in.
I should be there in 20.
I'll see you when I get there.
[Broom clatters]
[Glass clanks]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door closes]
[Lock engages]
[Sighs]
You gentlemen have had
a busy week, huh?
[Both chuckle]
Bail has been denied.
No mystery there.
Okay.
Let's start at the beginning.
Somehow you two
are short on priors,
so I think I can get the DA
to knock the drug charges down
to simple possession.
We can lay responsibility
for the felonies
at the doorstep
of your unfortunate dependence
on hard drugs,
but we're gonna have to argue
for rehab
as part of probation --
Hells naw.
I hate rehab.
Alright.
Don't get
all in a twist, okay?
I've heard
that there exist
certain less-than-reputable
establishments
that will
provide certification
without the pleasure
of your actual attendance.
You know a place
like that?
I could conceivably find such
a place for an additional fee.
Alright, 'cause I ain't
going to no rehab.
Mnh-mnh.
You go,
you don't go --
that's between you
and your God.
But you got to tell the judge
you'll go,
and you got to sound like
you mean it, 'kay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Well, all that's left is
your many, many misdemeanors,
which include
graffiti, vandalism,
littering,
public urination.
[Laughs]
Nature's calling you,
you got to answer it.
H-Hold it too long,
you get kidney-stoned.
[Sighs]
Be that as it may, um,
even misdemeanors add up.
So, if I can get you
concurrent sentences,
you're looking at...
12 months in stir.
Now, with good behavior
and overcrowding,
takes it down to six,
maybe five months.
That's minimum security.
It's gonna be like
taking a cruise...
[Sighs heavily]
...only less danger
of drowning.
Christ, man,
five months?
Down from five years,
consecutive,
or worse if they get
this heavy stuff to stick.
Now, come on.
You do your months, you do
a little community service,
maybe a year probation,
and you're gold, Ponyboy.
Sound good?
Yeah, okay.
We -- Yeah, we --
we can take that.
No doubt.
Great.
So, all that's left
is my fee.
[Clears throat]
Okay, so, for my time,
court costs, filing fees,
you're looking at,
oh, let's say about...
four grand, all-in.
S-Say what?
Yo,
d-don't play us like that.
What about 50% off?
That is 50% off.
Now, my normal rate
would be 4K each.
Dude,
this is B.S.
They got lawyers here
they gotta give us.
You pay nothing.
Free lawyers?
Public 'fenders.
Four grand, we can get
a lot of scante, man.
I'm sorry. Free lawyer?
Y-You saying that you want
a free lawyer?
We're just
talkin' over options.
And, you know,
free is, you know, free.
Did you ever hear the phrase
"you get what you pay for,"
you nudnik?
Without me,
they're gonna lock you up
and throw away the key.
I'm sorry.
Did I say five years?
You -- You go ahead
and play Russian roulette
with a public pretender,
you're gonna end up doing
a decade in Los Lunas.
You twerps
even know who I am?
I am Saul Goodman!
Okay?
You think 4K is too much?
Yesterday I got paid 8K
just for the afternoon.
That's how good I am.
I am the real deal.
You're lucky
I'm even talkin' to ya.
Y'know what?
[Chuckles]
[Pounds on door]
Hey, c-c'mon, man.
Hey, alright.
D-Don't be like that.
Hey, we're sorry, yo.
We're sorry.
Y-You --
w-w-w-w-we wanna go with you.
Hunny-percent.
Please, sir.
Okay.
We're back on the same page,
though -- payment.
Yeah.
Before you make my headache
even worse,
no, you cannot pay me
with the money you stole.
Okay, that cash is Exhibit A
for the prosecution.
So, relatives?
Anybody you haven't
already fleeced?
My grandma maybe?
Yeah,
she -- she got a house...
Yeah.
...and a car
and shizz.
Yeah, grandma.
She's perfect.
Okay, so, you tell granny
faster she gets me my money,
faster
I work my magic.
My wire info
is on the back of that card.
I look forward
to hearing from her.
[Pounds on door]
Coming out!
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door closes, lock engages]
[ "Spirit of Birdland" playing]
Man: Fantastic.
[Sighs]
[Indistinct conversations]
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's just
one of those days.
No problem.
Let me introduce you.
Judge Lawler,
this is Jimmy McGill.
Uh, it's actually
Saul Goodman.
I changed my name.
But Lawler --
now you're Federal, right?
Uh, District of New Mexico?
That's me.
Thought so.
Your gavel work
is legendary.
Uh...thank you?
I'll let you get back
to your lunch, Ian.
Catch you on the back nine
next week.
See you.
Jimmy?
And I'll have
the sole and --
No butter,
side of steamed veggies?
You got me.
Creature of habit.
[Chuckles] Great.
I'll put this in,
and I'll be right back
with your drink.
¶¶
[Chuckles, sniffles]
So.
"Saul Goodman."
Am I allowed
to call you "Jimmy"?
Uh, Saul Goodman
is my professional name,
but my friends
still call me Jimmy.
You can, too.
Well, tell me about
"Saul Goodman."
[Clears throat]
Whaddya mean?
Well,
what I mean is,
if he's not Jimmy McGill,
who is he?
What's he about?
Uh...hmm.
Well...
Saul Goodman is,
uh --
he's the last line of defense
for the little guy.
You getting sold
down the river?
He's a life raft.
You getting stepped on,
he's a sharp stick.
You got Goliath
on your back,
Saul's the guy
with the slingshot.
He's a righter
of wrongs.
He's friend
to the friendless.
That's Saul Goodman.
[Chuckles] Wow.
[Chuckles]
¶¶
Couldn't Jimmy McGill
do all that?
¶¶
Maybe he could,
but, uh, Saul Goodman is.
[Sniffles]
I get it.
You do?
Yeah.
I understand why
you changed your name.
Is that right?
Hamlin Hamlin McGill
did you wrong.
Your name
is a part of that firm.
Now it's tainted.
We took your legacy
away from you.
You say so,
Howard.
No, no, I've been
thinking about this a lot.
And you know what?
We should have hired you.
I mean,
don't worry about it.
That's ancient history.
You deserved a shot.
And I could've given it
to you...
when you got barred or
when you brought us Sandpiper.
Both times,
I should've shown some backbone.
It would've been
the right thing to do.
Well,
I am glad you had
this cleansing moment
of clarity, Howard.
Good for you.
[Chuckles]
¶¶
Let me be clear.
I'm not interested
in yesterday.
I missed an opportunity
with you,
and I think it's time
to correct that.
¶¶
I'd like you
to come work at HHM.
¶¶
[Clears throat]
[Ice cubes clinking]
[Slurps,
exhales sharply]
You want me
to work for you
after all the shit
that's happened between us?
Oh, as far
as I'm concerned,
that's between
you and Chuck.
¶¶
[Scoffs]
Hey, look,
before you offer me a job,
you might want to call
your buddy Cliff Main.
He'd have a unique perspective
on employing me.
This isn't a spur-of-the-moment
decision, Jimmy.
I have been considering this
for a while.
At the scholarship committee,
you spoke about
that young woman.
Kristy Esposito.
Yes. Kristy.
Yeah.
You stood up
for her.
And that
got me thinking...
about judgment...
and honesty.
¶¶
[Chuckles]
And when you kicked my ass
last year,
you weren't wrong.
You say
what you mean.
Listen, you don't wanna be
surrounded by liars, Howard,
you might be
in the wrong profession.
[Chuckles]
Look,
it's simple for me.
You're smart.
You're scrappy.
You're a go-getter.
You don't wait
for things to happen.
You make 'em happen.
HHM is growing again
and could use
someone like you.
¶¶
I could use you.
"Charlie Hustle."
[Inhales sharply]
Howard, I --
You don't have to answer
right now.
Let's just enjoy lunch.
But do me a favor.
Live with it
for a bit.
Okay?
¶¶
[Slurping]
[Horn honks]
Ah. That's me.
Well, Howard,
this was, um...
Thanks for lunch.
I'll get the next one.
Thanks for
taking the time.
[Car door closes]
Good to see you,
Jimmy.
[Chuckles]
[Air brakes hiss]
[Engine rumbling]
[Car door closes]
Paige: If you glance
at the package,
it'll give you a clear idea
of what we're talking about.
There's a raft
of TCPA compliance issues,
but they're
fairly straightforward.
We've been in touch
with the FTC, the FCC.
OSHA, same.
By the time
construction's complete,
we'll be able
to hire able bodies,
and we'll be
ready to go.
Exciting to expand beyond
the ol' brick and mortar.
We've hit
all the key benchmarks
for the Tucumcari
call center.
And we remain
well under budget.
You know
I like to hear that.
[Chuckling] Alright.
If you turn
to the next tab,
there are some
mortgage opportunities --
Sorry.
Paige, there's one more piece
of call center business
I feel
we need to discuss.
Oh...
Stef?
Okay.
[Screen clicking]
Kim: We decided
to put this center here,
on this parcel of land,
Lot 1102.
But I think we need to
reconsider the other contender,
Lot 2375.
Paige: 2375 -- the vacant lot
with the flooding problem?
Yes,
that's right.
Initially, we did have concerns
about the infrastructure,
but I spoke with Alex Amadeo
on the Council this morning,
and she told me the city
has recently shored up
all of the drainage
along the arroyo.
And they have repaved 10 miles
of roads in the vicinity.
So that would not only
speed up our construction,
but make for a more efficient
operation overall.
And over the long term,
it seems to me
that these improvements
will pay dividends
and more than offset
any delays.
Since we won't need
a redesign,
we could be back on track in
a matter of two to three weeks,
maybe less.
Are you saying
that we lose three weeks
and, what, eat the cost
of the land that we already own?
I know this isn't really
my department,
but according to
our own projections,
the land we already own
will more than double in value
in the next five years.
This could be
an excellent investment.
There's potential here
to turn Tucumcari
into a real Mesa Verde
company town.
And when you add in
the -- the reputational risk
with Lot 1102 --
"Reputational risk"?
You're talking about
Everett Acker?
[Inhales sharply]
Ousting a man
from his house --
it's never
a good look.
Kevin: Kim, let me ask this
real plainly.
Is Lot 1102 our land
or not?
Are we in the right?
As far as the law goes,
yes.
Alright, then.
Well,
that settles it.
I'm not gonna let anybody
chase me off.
This fella wants to make a fuss,
well...
it's our land and our right
to do with it what we want.
I agree.
We've already offered him
a sum for relocation
far greater than what we've paid
any of his neighbors.
Kim...
thank you for the thought,
but I say we move forward
with Lot 1102.
How 'bout
we get the lights?
Yeah, alright then.
That's that.
I just
had to mention it.
[Clears throat]
I've got a call in
to the sheriff.
Come Friday at noon,
Acker will be out
and construction will proceed.
Now, as I was saying --
mortgages.
Our institutional clients
are strong,
but if we want to penetrate
the retail market,
there are some opportunities
that we should explore
as we develop
the business.
[Keys jingle]
[Birds chirping]
[Vehicle approaching]
[Brakes squeal]
[Engine shuts off]
Pop,
what are you doing here?
It's Thursday.
It's my day.
You didn't get
my message?
I called you
to see if you were coming.
You never called me back,
so I had Emily come.
It's okay.
Send her home.
I'll pay her
for the night.
Well...
maybe it's better
if you just sit this one out.
I mean, they're already off
playing dolls.
I scared her.
I lost my temper.
That's it.
If you just
let me talk to her,
tell her I'm sorry --
No, no, no, no.
Kaylee's fine.
She forgot all about that.
Then what's the problem?
[Sighs]
I love you,
Pop,
but tonight I think
you should let Emily babysit.
Honey, I'm okay.
I wouldn't tell you I was okay
if I wasn't.
And if Kaylee
brings up Matty?
I'll be okay.
You're getting worked up
over nothing.
I'm fine.
Look, what if maybe you come
for dinner sometime next week?
We can have those pork chops
you like.
You've been working
so hard.
You deserve
a little break.
Let you
get back to yourself.
"Get back to myself"?
[Exhales sharply]
Something's going on
with you.
I don't know what.
But I'd be
more comfortable
if you didn't sit
for Kaylee.
For tonight.
[Sighs]
[Birds chirping]
[Dog barks in distance]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door closes]
Harkness:
We were hopping
'cause of that Kiss show
at the pavilion.
I had those leather guys
in makeup
coming in and buy Slim Jims
and beers all night long.
Ko: Thank you,
Mr. Harkness.
Is the person who robbed you
present in the court today?
Yes.
And could you point him out
to the court, please?
There.
Let the record show
that the witness has identified
the defendant,
Mr. Sakey.
Thank you,
Mr. Harkness.
Judge:
Your witness, Mr. Goodman.
[Inhales sharply]
Thank you for coming in today,
Mr. Harkness.
I just want to clarify a few
things from your testimony,
if that's okay.
'Kay.
So, you were working
at the Sandia Mart
the night
of the 30th.
Is that correct?
Got in at noon,
left at midnight.
That's a long day.
Mm-hmm.
Good for you.
Nothing wrong
with a hard day's work.
So,
you say a man came in
and he reached
across the counter
and, uh, quote,
"He grabbed up the money
from my register
and run off."
Yeah.
And there was no one else
in the store?
Not at that time,
no.
And since the camera system
wasn't working at the time,
you're the only one
who saw the perpetrator.
Yeah.
I guess so.
[Sighs]
Yeah.
So, this person came in,
and they bought something.
I think
it was an Almond Joy.
And they bought
an Almond Joy.
And when
you rang them up,
that's when they snatched
the cash from the register.
Sounds like it happened
pretty fast,
but you say you got
a good look at 'em, correct?
Yes.
[Exhales sharply]
You must drink
stronger coffee than I do
'cause after 11 hours
on the job,
I can barely
see straight.
And it was dark out.
Well, he was the only guy
that came in that night
that wasn't made up like
a bat or a cat
or whatever the hell
those guys are.
A-And he was
right up in my face.
Right in your f-- A-And
according to your testimony,
you feel confident that
you can identify this person.
That's what
you're saying.
I can, absolutely.
It's him.
Your client.
Are you sure
that's the person?
There's no doubt in your mind?
Take your time.
I don't need time.
That's him.
[Chuckles]
Now, would you be surprised
to learn, Mr. Harkness,
that the person you just
pointed to is not the defendant?
Wh-What?
My client is
in the back of the courtroom.
Mr. Sakey,
would you please stand up?
Ko: Objection!
The person you ID'ed
is named Hollis Earley.
He's a bartender
down in Belen.
He has a very good alibi
for the night in question.
Your Honor, objection!
[Spectators murmuring]
Oh, Mr. Goodman!
Really?
You didn't recognize him,
either, Your Honor.
Alright, settle -- settle down,
everybody. Settle. Settle.
[Gavel banging]
[Murmuring stops]
[Sighs]
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
we're gonna call it a day.
I will have very specific
instructions for you tomorrow.
As always, please refrain from
discussing the case until then,
and I will see counsel
in my chambers now.
[Gavel bangs]
Adjourned.
[Door opens]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door creaks, closes]
You're still here.
Yeah.
You saw the fireworks.
It was
a bit unorthodox.
But, uh,
check this out.
Two sweetest words
in the English language --
"miss," "trial."
Not bad, huh?
Not bad.
[Stammers]
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's just...
I have a case
in Tucumcari.
And there's something
I want to discuss with you.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Metal clanging]
Lyle: Fry pit looks good,
Deshawn.
You can take off.
Night, Tiffany.
Good work.
Juana,
very good work.
Crap,
I forgot to cover the fryer.
Uh, y-- don't worry.
I'll get it.
[Engine starts]
Thanks, man.
Sure.
See you tomorrow,
Deshawn.
[Lock engages]
[Keys jingle]
[Vehicle departing]
[Metal clanging]
[Sighs]
Everything alright,
Mr. Fring?
This is acceptable
to you?
Uh...
I thought
Deshawn did a good job.
Uh...
I'm not
seeing anything.
It's...
I understand.
Uh, you know...
like,
now that I look closer,
yeah,
I think I see maybe...
Yeah. Okay.
I'll take care of it,
Mr. Fring.
Alright.
Yeah.
Sorry about that. Sorry.
[Metal clangs]
[Breathes deeply]
[Metal clanging]
[Sizzling]
[Train whistle blows]
Who puts a dead drop
in a culvert?
I mean, rain comes
and -- fsssht! --
your money's on its way
to the, uh, Rio Grande.
So you use a different drop
during the monsoon season.
"Culvert." [Chuckles]
That's a weird word.
What do you think that is,
like Dutch?
Maybe French.
It's not French.
In Spanish,
it's "alcantarilla."
Well, it --
it doesn't come from Spanish.
I mean, you ever hear anyone
walk around
talk about the majestic
"culverts of Spain"?
Who the hell goes around talking
about "majestic culverts"?
Man: Target is approaching
position two.
Stand by.
Copy.
Standing by.
[Exhales sharply]
Well...
only one drop left.
That's us.
You think
he'll do all three?
Well, Molina's info
has checked out so far.
Long as we don't
spook the target,
I say he, uh,
rounds third
and goes straight for home.
You know
how to use that thing?
Point it at the bad guy,
press the button.
[Chuckles]
Don't miss your shot,
Ansel Adams.
We need this guy.
Position two,
we have the target.
Looks like
he's headed inside.
Copy.
[Exhales heavily]
"Culvert."
"Cullll-vert."
Sounds like a Dutch word
for crotch rot.
[Chuckles]
Target is on the move,
headed toward position three.
Alright, guys,
keep your distance.
Hey, Byers and Vacca,
roll back 30 yards.
If I can see ya,
he can, too.
We don't want him
to get nervous.
Want to keep him
nice and relaxed.
[Radio thuds]
Like your mom
on date night.
Like your left hand
every night.
[Metal clangs]
Is it okay,
Mr. Fring?
You can go home,
Lyle.
I-If it's not right,
just let me try again.
I-I can get this right
for you, sir.
Please.
If you would like to take
another crack at it,
then go ahead.
Thank you.
[Metal clanging]
¶¶
Here's our guy.
Cap off the lens there,
Gomey.
Screw you.
[Camera shutter clicking]
¶¶
[Metal clanging]
[Camera shutter clicking]
¶¶
Shit.
He make us?
¶¶
I think we're good.
[Camera shutter clicking]
¶¶
[Water running]
[Engine starts, rumbles]
[Tires screech]
God damn it!
Hey, uh, yeah,
our target's in flight.
All units, uh...
[Engine starts]
...going West on Bobby Foster.
We're in pursuit.
¶¶
What're you doin'?!
Getting ahead of him.
Got to skate to where
the puck's gonna be.
But you don't know
where he's goin'!
I got a feeling.
¶¶
[Tires screech]
[Gun cocks]
¶¶
[Tires screech]
Federal agents!
Come on out!
[Engine rumbling]
Nice and slow!
Hands!
Show me your hands!
¶¶
Damn it.
[Engine revving]
[Tires screech]
¶¶
[Sighs heavily]
Schrader!
[Water dripping]
[Sirens wailing in distance]
Well,
what do you say, Gomey?
Let's spelunk.
[Engine rumbling]
[Crickets chirping]
[Grunts]
[Car door closes]
[Speaks Spanish]
Vamonos.
[Gearshift clicks]
$696,000, $698,000,
$700,000 and some change.
Damn.
We sure took a bite
out of crime tonight, McGruff.
Mnh,
booby prize.
C'mon, man.
We got the money.
We got the douchebags
who did the drop.
We got
three assholes in cuffs.
And we put Molina
back out on the street.
Who knows what else
he's gonna scare up?
Yeah, I wanted to go upstream,
Gomey, not downstream.
[Breathes deeply]
[Police radio chatter]
Here goes.
Alrighty.
Everybody, circle up!
Circle up!
Come on!
Bring it in!
I just want to thank y'all
for a successful operation.
Great work across the board.
APD -- hey,
you guys are first-rate.
We're putting bracelets
on three shitbirds as we speak.
And better yet, we got ourselves
a buttload of money, alright?
Just shy of $1 million.
So some major dickwad
of a dealer's hurtin' tonight.
And that's because of
all of you.
So, to show my appreciation,
we're all going to O'Neill's,
and first round's on me.
Yeah! Alright!
[Cheers and applause]
Thank y'all!
[Cellphone vibrating]
Victor:
All clear.
And the money?
They got it.
Went down
like it was supposed to.
[Metal clangs]
Mr. Fring.
I was just about
to come find you.
Thank you, Lyle.
You can go home.
Um, but is it,
like...
You think it's okay?
It's clean?
It is acceptable.
[Metal clanging]
Have a good night,
Mr. Fring.
[Birds chirping]
[Sniffles]
[Exhales sharply]
[Knock on door]
[Footsteps approaching]
[Lock disengages]
Who the hell are you?
Mr. Acker,
my name is Saul Goodman.
I'm an attorney --
I've had it up to here
with you Mesa Verde scumbags.
Get bent!
I'm not
representing Mesa Verde.
In fact,
I'd like to represent you, sir.
I don't need a lawyer,
I don't want a lawyer,
nothin' you can say
is gonna change my mind.
Now,
move your damn foot.
Sir,
if you would just -- just --
Please just take a look
at my proposal, okay?
Because I think
you'll find it persuasive.
I don't want it.
Just look at it, sir.
Just look.
What do you see?
A man...
...f-fuckin' a horse.
Sir,
I hate Mesa Verde.
I hate them.
Looking down on us
from their glass tower.
They think they can shit on
whoever they want
and we just have to smile
and say, "Thank you"?
Look, picture me as the man
and Mesa Verde as the horse.
I'm the guy who'll do
whatever it takes
to stick it to them.
Guess who's got a new client
in Tucumcari.
Kim: Wh-What?
That's right.
Put some beers on ice.
We'll celebrate when I get back
from the hinterlands.
[Laughing] Yes.
That's the best news
I've heard all day.
How the hell
did you convince him?
Uh...
uh, visual aids.
You'd be surprised what
you can find on that Internet.
So,
Chinese tonight?
Yeah, sounds good.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
What'd y'all get into
last night?
[Scoffs]
Absolutely nothing, G.
Yo, G,
pass that lighter, G.
Hey, yo, yo, your girl
came by. You need to
keep her in check, fam.
She trippin',
man.
I've been telling you
about that, man.
Black her eyes.
Hey, yo, yo, yo.
Ain't that...
Yo, that's...
Yo, Gramps!
[Grunts, coughs]
Ugh!
[All grunting]
First one was free,
dickhead!