This sandwich is an
unmitigated disaster.
I asked for turkey and roast beef
with lettuce and swiss
on whole wheat.
What did they give you?
Turkey and roast beef
with swiss and lettuce
on whole wheat.
It's the right ingredients
but in the wrong order.
In a proper sandwich
the cheese is adjacent to the bread
to create a moisture barrier
against the lettuce.
They might as well drag
this thing into a car wash.
I don't believe it.
I know, it's basic culinary science.
Some guy is actioning up a
miniature time machine prop
from the original film
and nobody's bidding on it.
A time machine from the
movie "The time machine"?
No, a time machine from "Sophie's choice".
Boy, Sophie could have used
a time machine in that movie
Did you see it? It's rough.
Oh that's cool.
It's only 800 dollars?
Yes, and that's my bid.
You bid 800 dollars?
Yes, it was a spur-of-the-moment thing
I figured it would go for thousands
and I just wanted to be a part of it.
There's only 30 seconds
left in the auction.
Do you have 800 dollars?
Not to blow on a
miniature time machine.
Oh don't worry, the way
this thing works
is people waiting till
the last seconds to bid
and then they swoop in and get it.
It's called sniping.
15 seconds.
Come on snipers.
Ten, nine, eight...
Where are your snipers?
- Five
- Snipe!
- Four
- Three
- Snipe!
- Two
One...
Congratulations!
You are a proud owner of
a miniature time machine.
You lucky duck.
I wonder why no one else bid
This is a classic piece of
sci-fi movie memorabilia.
I know! I still can't afford it.
Why don't we share it?
Well each put 200 bucks and
we'll take turns having it in our house.
A time shared time machine.
I'm in. Sheldon?
Need you ask?
But I still don't understand
why no one else bid.
I understand why no one else bid.
Our whole universe was
in a hot,dense state
then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... wait!
The Earth began to cool
The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools
We built the wall
We built the pyramids
Math, Science, History
Unraveling the mystery
That all started
With a Big Bang!
Bang!
www.wikisubtitles.net
The Big Bang Theory S01 E14
The Nerdmabelia Scattering
Did the listing actually
said "miniature"?
I just assumed.
Who sells a full size time
machine for 800 dollars?
In a Venn diagram that
would be an individual located
within the intersection of the sets:
"No longer want my time machine"
and "Need 800 dollars".
It's actually a tremendous bargain.
Even with shipping it works out
to less than four dollars a pound.
Cocktails shrimp at 12.50.
How are we gonna get it upstairs?
If we take the dish off
it might fit in the elevator.
Yes but the elevator has
been broken for two years.
I've been meaning to ask you
Do you think we should
make a call about that?
Not necessarily.
I have a masters in engineering.
I remotely repair satellites
on a regular basis.
I troubleshoot space
shuttle payloads.
When the Mars Rover started
pulling to the left, I performed
a front end alignment from
62 millions miles away.
No, that baby's broken.
Come on guys, push!
If I push any harder
I'm gonna give birth to my colon.
I can't feel my fingers!
Hurry up!
It's the same amount of work
no matter how fast you go.
Basic physics.
- Sheldon?
- Yeah?
If my fingers ever work again
I've got a job for the middle one.
Oh hey guys.
Hi Penny.
Take a break guys.
What are you doing?
We're just, you know,
moving something upstairs.
What is it?
Just, you know, a time machine.
Yeah, ok, neat, but I
really gotta get to work, so...
- Just give us a few minutes.
- I don't have a few minutes.
I'm running really late.
I have a sample solution.
Go up to the roof, hop
over the next building
There's a small gap
- don't look down if you suffer the vertigo -
and use their stairway.
You're joking, right?
I never joke when it comes to vertigo.
Damn... Ok, I'll just take the roof.
Hey, if you wait for us to
set up the time machine
I can drop you off to work yesterday.
Time travel... jokes.
Nevermind.
For what it's worth,
I thought it was humorous.
Let's just do this.
Guys, ready to push?
In a minute.
Howard stepped outside to throw up.
I don't know what you're worried about.
I think it really works in the room.
Yeah.
It is by far the coolest thing
I've ever owned.
The exact time machine that
carried actor Rod Taylor
from victorian England
into the post-apocaliptic future
where society had splintered
into two factions:
The subterranean Morlocks,
who survived by feasting
on the flesh of the gentle
surface-dwelling Eloi.
Talk about you chick magnet.
Oh, yeah.
The guy who lives next to me is always like
"I have a Jacuzzi on my balcony"
Wait until I tell him
"I've got a time machine on my balcony"
Stuff that in your Speedoes,
Jacuzzi Bob."
Gentlemen, I know we
said we'd take turns
but I think you'll agree
that practicality dictates
it remain here.
You can't just keep it here
What if I meet a girl and say
"Do you wanna come up
and see my time machine?
It's at my friend's house"
How lame is that?
- He's got a point.
- All right.
I think we're going to need
some ground rules, in addiction
to the expected
"No shoes in the time machine"
and "No eating in the time machine"
I propose that we add
"Pants must be worn
at all times in the time machine"
Second it.
I was gonna put down a towel.
I still want it on my balcony.
I say we move it on a bimonthly basis.
- Yeah, that sounds fair
- Hold on.
"bimonthly" is an ambiguous term.
Do you mean moving it every
other month or twice a month?
- Twice a month.
- Then no.
Ok, every other month.
No.
Sheldon, you can't be selfish.
We all paid for it so it belongs to all of us.
Now get out of the way so
I can sit on my time machine.
Ok. I'm setting the dials
for 10th March 1876.
Good choice, Alexander Graham Bell
invents the telephone and
calls out for Dr. Watson.
Wait a minute, I want to see that too.
So when it's your turn you can.
But if you all go back to
the same point and time
Bell's lab is going to get very crowded.
He'll know something's up.
Also, since the time machine
doesn't move in space
you'll end up in 1876 Pasadena.
And even if you can make it
to Boston, what are you gonna do?
Knock on the door and say to Mrs Bell
Hey, Mrs Bell, I'm a big
fan of your husband
Can I come in and watch him
inventing the telephone?
Mrs Bell was deaf
She's not even going to hear you knock.
I have a solution.
First, go into the future
and obtain a cloaking device.
How far into the future?
If I remember correctly
Captain Kirk would steal a cloaking device
from the Romulans on Star Date 5027.3
Which would be 10th January 2328
by pre-federation reckoning.
Ok, I'm setting the dials
for 10th January 2328.
Here we go into the future.
That was fun.
My turn!
Ok, first of all
what you call a gap was
nearly three feet wide
- I slipped and skinned my knee.
- Are you ok?
Second of all, the door to the stairway
of the other building was locked.
so I had to go down the fire escape
which ends on the third floor
forcing me to crawl to the window
of a lovely Armenian family
who insisted I'd stay for lunch.
That doesn't sound too bad.
It was eight courses of lamb.
And they tried to fix me up with their son.
- Sorry.
- Not done.
By the time I finally
got to work they'd given my shift away.
Yeah, that's right
I've lost an entire day's pay thanks to this.
- this...
- time machine
The lights flash, the dish spins,
do you wanna try it?
No!!
I don't wanna try it
My God, you are grown men.
How can you waste your lives with these
stupid toys, and costumes
and comic books and...
and now that!
- That...
- Again, time machine.
Oh please, it's not
time machine
If anything it looks like something
Elton John would drive
through the Everglades.
It only moves in time.
It would be worse than useless in a swamp.
Pathethic! all of you!
Completely pathethic
My turn
Leonard, it's 2:00 in the morning
So?
So it's my turn.
Why did you set it for the day before yesterday?
Because I wanna go back and keep myself from
getting a time machine.
You can't. If you would prevent
yourself from buying it in the past
you wouldn't have it available in the present
to travel back and stop yourself
from buying it. Ergo, you'd still have it.
This is a classic working
time-travel mistake.
Can I go back and prevent you
from explaining that to me?
Same paradox
If you were to travel back in time
and, say, knock me unconscious
you would not then have the conversation
that irritated you
motivating you to knock me unconscious.
What if I knock you unconscious right now?
It won't change the past.
But it'd make the present
so much nicer.
Are you upset about something?
What was your first clue?
Well, that was a number of things.
First, the late hour.
Then your demeanor seems
very low energy
- Plus your irritability...
- Yes, I'm upset!
I don't usually pick up on those things.
Good for me.
Yes, good for you.
Oh, wait.
Did you wanna talk about
what's bothering you?
I don't know, maybe.
Wow, I'm on fire tonight.
Here's the thing.
Girls like Penny never end up
with guys who own time machines.
I disagree.
Your inability to successfully woo Penny
long predates your acquisition
of the time machine.
That failure clearly stands on itself.
Thanks for pointing it out.
In addiction, your premise is flaw.
In the original film Rod Taylor
got Yvette Mimieux
in that very time machine.
in "Back to the future" Marty McFly
got the opportunity
to hook up with his extremely
attractive young mother.
Those are movies.
Of course they are movies.
Were you expecting me to
come up with an example
involving a real-life time machine?
It's absurd.
Come on, guys, push!
If I push any harder
I'm gonna give birth to my colon.
Hi guys.
Hi Penny.
Take a break guys!
What are you doing?
Oh, you know... just moving
a... time machine.
Yeah, ok, neat, but I really
gotta get to work, so...
No problem
Hang on.
But, what about your
time machine?
Something more important
than the toys
I'm scared
Don't worry baby.
I've got you.
It's still my turn.
What are you doing?
I'm packing up all my collectibles
and taking them down at the
comic books store to sell.
Was that really necessary?
If you need money you can
always sell blood.
and semen.
Not about money
We brought food!
Lox and bagels, the breakfast
for time travellers.
Terrific
Does anyone want to buy my
share of the time machine?
Why?
I don't want it anymore.
just...personal reason
My spidy sense tells me this
has something to do with Penny.
Look,
- Do you want to buy me out or not?
- I'll give you
100 dollars, which will
make me half owner
and we'll put it on my balcony.
Screw his balcony
I'll give you 120 and we'll put it in my garage.
I paid 200 dollars for my share.
Dude, everybody knows
a time machine loses half his value
the minute you drive him off the lot.
I go for 200 and that time
machine stands right where it is.
300, and I'll throw in my
original 1979 Mattel Millennium Falcon
with real light speed
sound effects.
No, no more toys or action figures
or props or replicas
or costumes or robots
or Darth Vader's voice changers.
I'm getting rid of all of it
You can't do that.
Look at what you've created here.
It's like "Nerdvana".
More importantly,
you have a Darth Vader's
voice changer?
Not for long.
Oh, I call dibs on the Golden Age Flash.
Hang on, I need that
to complete my Justice Society
of America collection.
Too bad, I called dibs.
- You can't just call dibs.
- I can and I did
Look at "dibs" on the Wikipedia.
Dibs doesn't apply in a bidding war.
It's not a bidding war.
I'm selling it all to Larry
down at the comic books store.
Why Larry? Did Larry call dibs?
Would you forget dibs?
He offered me a fair price
for the whole collection.
What's the number? I'll match it.
I'll match it plus 1000 rupies
- What's the exchange rate?
- None of your business.
Take it or leave it.
Mom, my Bar Mitzvah bond
how much have I got?
Thanks.
I can go 2.600 dollars
and two trees in Israel.
Forget it.
If I sell it to one of you
the other two are gonna
be really mad at me.
Who cares?
As long as you pick me!
Okay Leonard, put down that box.
- Let's talk.
- Sorry Raj.
My mind is made up
No
I can't let you do this
Sheldon, get out of my way
None shall pass
Okay
I did not want to do this
but I have here the rare,
mint condition, production error
Star Trek: The Next Generation
Geordi La Forge
without his visor in
the original packaging.
If you do not get out of my way
I will open it.
Okay man,
be cool
We're all friends here
What the hell is going on?
You Hypocrit!
What?
Little miss "Grown-ups-
don't-play-with-toys".
If I went into that
apartment right now
would I not find beany babies?
are you not an accumulator
of Care Bears and
My Little Ponies?
And who is that japanese feline
I see frawn looking at your shorts?
Hello, hello Kitty!
Okay.
Okay,look this is about yesterday,
Leonard.
I'm really sorry about what i said
- I was jus upset
- No, i needed to heard it
No, you didn't
Look you're great guy
it's the things you love
that make who you are
I guess that makes me
"Large breasts"
Still I think it's time for me
to get rid of this stuff
and, you know
move on with my life.
Really?
Oh
Wow, good for you
Thanks
Hey, do you want...
I don't know, later...
Excuse me..
Hi Penny
Hi Mike
You're ready to go?
yeah, i just have to change
I give you a hand
Stop it!
Bye guys
My turn on the time machine!
It worked
It really worked
They said i was mad,
but it worked!
Oh no!
Not Morlocks!
Not flash-eating Morlocks!
Help!
Sheldon, you okay?
We have to get rid
of the time machine.
It's too little big for
the living room, isn't it?
yeah, that's the problem.
It's too big.
I'm glad you agreed
I hired some guys
to help us move it.
Come on in fellas
Oh no, Morlocks!
Eat him,
eat Him.
Leonard!
www.wikisubtitles.net