Okay, are you from
Star Wars universe?
Yes
You were in the original trilogy?
Is there a picture of you in my wallet
using a metal bikini?
God, I hope not.
And no, I'm Princess Leia.
Okay, okay, my turn ...
Are you in the six
Star Wars films?
- Yes
- Interesting.
Are you a Droid?
Yes
¿Sheldon look like a shiny?
- C-3PO.
- You got it.
That is ridiculous.
Do not I look like C-3PO.
Do not misunderstand me. I Alagoas,
just do not see the resemblance.
Leslie Winkle.
Talk to "Friends with rights."
For a call
sex, press one now.
Exactly what ¿
means that expression,
"Friends with rights?
Do you provide a health service?
No.
Watch ...
Imagine that you hold
a friendship with someone
with whom you have sex, but you are
free dating anyone.
Sorry. I can not imagine anything like that.
Okay, back to the game.
I think it's my turn.
They can start with
questions when they are ready.
Are you Spock?
I do not like this game.
So, where were we?
Is not going to have sex?
No, it was something else.
Why everything has to be
about sex with you? Come on.
Who plays?
We were with you.
Great, just start.
Okay, let's see.
Are you a TV series?
I made it!
I bet that someone from Babylon 5
never guess.
# All our universe was
in a hot and dense state ...
# Then for about 14 billion
years, the expansion began ... Wait!
# The earth began to cool,
# Autotrophs began to drool the
Neanderthals developed tools,
# Build the wall ...
we built the pyramids,
# Math, science, history
unravel the mystery
# That started it all with
a Big Bang!
wWw.Subs-Team.Tv
P r e s e n t a:
The Big Bang Theory S02E21
"The Renormalization Vegas
Translation and  synchro: PolloDH
What happened to Leslie?
Why are you leaving?
I do not know, just said,
"Howard, Mom is a free spirit."
Then another call came and went.
I do not understand.
If you were in a relationship
not emotional, then
Why do you have what appears
be an emotional response?
Sheldon, obviously
I felt something for her.
Of course I felt something for her.
I saw her naked, for the love of God.
Okay, you just need
sacártela of mind.
Want to go to the comic shop?
Maybe go see a movie?
I do not want to go anywhere.
You know,
I understand that there are
a city in Nevada
specifically designated
to help people like Howard
to forget their problems.
Can replace them with
new problems such as alcoholism,
addiction to gambling, and
sexually transmitted diseases.
Am I, or that was how
Sheldon said, "Vegas, baby!"?
Never ido.
And you?
Me? No.
Just remember "Vegas, baby!"
by Vince Vaughn in Swingers.
Could be fun. My order
week is free, now that ...
Okay, let's do it.
Let's go to Las Vegas.
- Now? Now do the same?
- Why not?
People do things now
same all the time.
Why can not we be
people "now" as well?
Go home, pack a suitcase,
and let people "now."
That is, should I stop at the pharmacy
to fill a prescription, but
after that, we will now.
What do you say, Howard?
I mean ...
"Vegas, baby!"
What would you say to your mother?
"Sea World, baby!"
Hey, Sheldon, are you going to come?
Would prefer a fly
scavenger put eggs
and hatched larvae in my ear canal.
Great, you bring a jacket.
Thank you.
Hello, neighbor.
Hello, Sheldon.
And how are you doing this pleasant evening?
- Great.
- Well, I'm happy.
Really?
Are you drunk?
I'm just in a good mood.
While my compatriots
are in Las Vegas,
I enjoy
a wonderful night
in my Fortress of Solitude staff.
That's the great thing of
Ice Superman, right?
You know, I am such a good mood,
this day in fact
find your poor knowledge
language and enchanting folk.
What smells so good?
Such is the intoxicating
Kadhai paneer flavor,
a perfect representation culinary
of freedom which is tonight.
Indian cuisine is not just,
which Koothrappali hate
contains a generous portion of nuts,
thus reduced to a Wolowitz
wheezing ampoule of 44 Kilograms.
And finally, its main
ingredient is paneer, a cheese
that would cause Leonard
any habitable room
in a matter of minutes.
Well, enjoy your big night.
Penny.
I realize that you
are also single tonight
then, if, at some point
you find yourself with nothing to do,
please do not bother me.
Have fun, Sheldon.
Oh, I will.
No!
What happens, Superman?
Are you staying out of
your big ice thing?
Look at that.
Rinse, lotion, body soap,
shampoo and conditioner
together in one bottle.
I love Las Vegas.
Howard, Could I have some
after shave lotion?
Black briefcase, upper compartment.
That is a lot of cologne.
The first row are  musk, the
second is forest aromas,
skins and botanical.
The third is a variety of pheromones.
Use it with care.
That is the spirit, Howard.
Yes, we can.
Go on, come on.
You adelántense only
I have to finish a post.
That is not an email is
Leslie Facebook page.
Okay, okay. I
reviewing their Facebook page.
Watch your status update.
He says he left me.
People should know that I left her.
But she left you.
Madura, Raj. There is no place
for truth on the internet.
Just go, after the catch.
Okay.
We should have a plan in case
that one of us get lucky.
Okay, if I have luck, take
majestic my personality
the outskirts of Gotham, y. ..
if you're lucky, sleep on the moon.
It seems a good plan.
Wait, I think the key
emergency is somewhere around here.
We have a bowl.
Our keys are in a bowl.
You should get a bowl.
So how was that
brilliant mind of Sheldon Cooper
forgot your key in the first place?
I left it in the bowl.
I just remember where
emergency is the key.
- Where?
- In your apartment.
- What do you do in my apartment?
- Well, I was a few weeks ago
when you were not
at home and forgot it.
I entered ...
Why ...
What?
It is not so important. Was
making coffee and I ran out of milk.
You're the thief of milk!
Leonard said he was crazy, but
knew that the board was light.
Okay, Sheldon.
Just calm down.
Call administrator
building and will open your door.
Just eat your dinner here while waiting.
Why, my dinner?
In your department?
Yes, why not?
Sure, why not
And after you get off the sun,
We can get in my truck
and we can go to swim
naked in the stream.
Because today is the day of
fail to make sense.
Thank you.
I tell you, Leonard,
with video slot machines,
brought us free drinks
by a waitress big breasts
and all the shrimp
can eat for $ 3.95.
Disneyland can go to hell.
This really is the place
happiest of the earth.
My friends, look!
That's the laundry a month!
Hello.
What is your name?
Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali.
Hi, Rajesh Ra --
Hi, Rajesh.
I'm Michaela.
Hello, Michael.
So, are you interested
a small party?
Why? Yes, I love the holidays.
Fiesta is my middle name.
Or it would if it were not Ramayan.
Raj, can, can
talk to you a moment?
Not now, Leonard.
Michaela invites me to a party.
You better call the moon
and you make sure that
have a bed for you.
Yes, I really need to talk to.
Sorry, back away.
Do not go anywhere.
Do not move, only
stay there as the beautiful
American natural flower you are.
What's the matter, buddy?
She wants all my jammy.
Okay, hate to have
to tell this to yourself
and to what is around you "Jammy"
but I'm pretty sure
she is a prostitute.
What?
No. ..
Let me put it like this:
Throughout your life,
How many beautiful women
have walked straight to you in a bar
and you have asked if
want to go to celebrate?
Maybe I can save her.
Maybe, but I bet it will cost you
as $ 500 for an hour of trying.
It was lovely to meet you.
The best of luck in your future.
Whatever.
And strange.
Howard is going crazy.
Watch his last message on Twitter.
"I'm at the bottom of a black hole
"noting the abyss.
My life has no meaning. My
future has no hope. "
Why do not we
to see the Blue Man Group?
Do you think that would help?
USA Today called, "Fun
lush for the whole family. "
I do not know. Howard is not really
class subject
of family fun.
What a pity that no
was here for that bitch.
She is exactly the kind a bitch.
You know, I bet that if the
hired, we encourage them.
We will not get
Wolowitz to a whore.
"I'm just hot,
may open this bottle of $ 20
dollars nuts and end all. "
I guess that would not harm
get an estimate.
And how was your day?
Trying to talk?
Honey, is not really necessary.
No, the agreement is accepted.
How was your day?
Well, they changed my shift
in the restaurant, so my
hours is a little different ...
Sorry, that does not interest me
at all, just eat.
Hi again.
Hello.
Yeah, hey, listen ...
if you're not busy,
we were thinking
that you could ...
we wondered ...
whether you are a prostitute.
- Are they cops?
- No.
I am a prostitute.
Okay, great.
The thing is, we have a friend
and is somewhat sad that I left him.
And we think that maybe
you could cheer him up.
With sex.
I think he knows what I mean.
How could it when
you walk around the bush?
She is the tough streets
where everything is fast and true.
Do not worry, I can
take good care of his friend.
Okay, great.
Listen, Is there any way
we can do this
he knows that without
you're a, you know ...
Prostitute.
They want the experience of a girlfriend.
Yes, Yes, exactly.
The experience of a girlfriend.
In fact, if it is not much to ask,
Could be
experience of Jewish bride?
Okay, that is the question 20.
Must guess.
I do not know, Sheldon.
Are you a Star Wars?
How can a person
be a movie?
Okay, I give up.
Can we just do something else?
Well.
It was Spock.
You are friends with Leonard and rights?
What?
Whence came this?
He said they were?
No, Leonard said nothing.
But who knows that happens around here
when he pretends that your mail
was mistakenly delivered?
Mail only, no benefits.
I see.
Why you ask?
I am curious about the whole
social construct.
At the hearing, the idea
satisfy the sexual appetites of their own
assuming that it affects such
without any emotional entanglement,
That seems remarkably practical.
But what I observed,
Howard Wolowitz is crying
as a little girl.
Well, some people simply do not
can handle such relationships.
You can?
Excuse me?
Are you able to have sex with men
are to develop an emotional attachment?
Sheldon, I really do not want
talk to you about this.
Is conversation makes you uncomfortable?
Of course it makes me uncomfortable, do not you see?
I really have no idea.
I'm not particularly good
reading expressions
facials, body language ...
I'm uncomfortable, Sheldon!
Thanks, that's very helpful.
Well, where are
these fantastic shrimp?
Contemplated.
Seriously, do you think this is
the size of a baby's arm?
A small baby.
I am going back to the room.
Heck, would you kill
put a little skirt?
Hello, Howard Wolowitz.
Esther Rosenblatt.
I do not think the manager comes
tonight, then shot.
¿It suggests that sleep on the couch?
Well, it was not the first
suggestion that occurred to me,
but what I have to choose.
I can not sleep in your
sofa, sleep in a bed.
And given its size
I have no intention of
experience the children's book
of E.M. Snickering, The
tall man in Cornwall. "
What?
"It was a tall man in Cornwall
"whose height exceeded his bed.
"My body is, but just above it,
no room for me
English large head. "
Okay, I'll give you my
bed with a condition:
that promise to seal your mouth
for the following eight hours.
Can I say one last thing?
Only if you do not rhyme.
Agreed.
Good night.
What excites me?
Let me see.
Read a good book in front of the campfire
Long walks on the beach ...
and getting rare in the Sabbath
a burger with bacon.
Really? Also yo!
Oy gevalt, you are burning.
Yes
Excuse me a moment.
Hey, how are you going?
The devil, fix this, right?
Yes
It's a bitch, is not it?
A prostitute, yes.
You gave him the money?
Yes
Thanks!
Penny  ¿
What?
I can not sleep.
Perhaps because
your mouth is still open.
Strange home.
Your house is about 6 meters from here.
6 meters, 6 light years, never mind.
It's in a galaxy far, far away.
Damn.
What do you do?
Sing, "Soft kitten."
That's just when you're sick.
Long for the home is
a type of disease.
Come on, is it really necessary?
I guess we can
stay awake and talking.
# Soft kitty,
loving kitty
# Small ball of hair,
# Kitty Happy ...
# Kitty sleepy.
- # Gatito sleepy ...
- No.
Begins again.
# Soft kitty,
loving kitty
# Small ball of hair,
# Kitty Happy ...
Sleepy kitten.
- Penny?
- Yes?
Thanks for letting me stay here.
Nothing, honey.
Okay, I got sleepy.
Out.
Well.
Finally at home.
What were you doing at the home of Penny?
Well, dinner,
play some games
and then spent the night.
Be happy to know that I now have
a much better understanding
"Friends with rights."
wWw.Subs-Team.Tv