Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Maybe you haven't noticed,
but I'm in love with you.
Victor caught
Gaby by surprise...
Why would a four-star chef
wanna slum at a pizza joint?
Lynette took a gamble...
-He has a history using cocaine.
-No, no way.
Well, but he's been
clean for almost a year.
Mike bet on love...
I win, you leave me
and Susan alone.
And lost...
Don't panic.
But still came
to Susan's rescue.
You okay?
Yeah.
And Mrs. McCluskey
revealed her secret
for a lasting relationship.
It was late on
a Tuesday night
when the power went
out all over Fairview.
For most of the residents,
it was a minor inconvenience.
But for those with secrets,
the darkness proved
quite useful indeed.
Millie Russell was
able to indulge
in another night
of midnight binging.
Timmy Cooper was able
to sneak another peek
at his father's
adult magazines.
Marilyn Quinn was able
to steal a few more puffs
of her forbidden tobacco.
But these secrets paled
compared to the one
a certain old woman was
hiding in her basement.
You sit tight, Ida.
I got batteries here.
No, I keep them in the freezer
for just such an emergency.
I'll run 'em over to you.
By the way, yowouldn't happen to have
any extra ice laying around, would ya?
No, I've just got some
stuff in my freezer
I don't want thawing
out anytime soon.
Yes, as a rule, darkness helps us
keep our secrets safely hidden.
Oh, crap!
But every rule...
Karen, what's happened?
Are you okay?
Has its exceptions.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by YDY
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
When the lights went
out on Wisteria Lane,
Karen McCluskey wasn't the
only reside left in the dark.
Everyone else felt the pain of
going without power as well.
Ow! Damn! Thumbtack!
Susan, please let me help.
No, no, I got it.
Oh, wait.
Here we go.
But it's hardly
a long-term solution.
Well, at least it'll keep me from
stabbing myself while I look.
But this is silly.
Why don't we just borrow
a flashlight from Mike?
Mike?
He's a plumber.
He's bound to have a spare.
Sure, but we can't keep leaning
on him for everything.
"Mike, we're drowning. Save us."
"Mike, it's dark.
Give us a flashlight."
Let's go ask Gaby.
Actually, I wanted to
talk to him anyway.
I thought we might ask
him over for dinner.
Dinner?
You know,
as a thank you gesture.
Well, Ian, you've
tasted my cooking.
It's not a thank you.
It's revenge.
Well, then I'll cook.
You know, you told me I should
put my jealousy behind me.
I think breaking bread together
would be a great start.
Well, let's not
bother him tonight.
You know, I don't really
even need a flashlight.
My eyes have totally
adjusted to the dark.
What was that?
Don't walk in the kitchen.
Anyway, where is your
sense of romance?
It's a blackout.
You have a defenseless lady.
Getting any ideas?
Well, I'm starting to, yes.
It's funny.
All that time I wasted worrying
Mike would come between us...
It seems so laughable
now, doesn't it?
Kiss me.
Hey, Carlos,
we had a blackout.
You need a flashlight?
Carlos, you okay?
Sorry, man.
I thought I heard a thud.
I just, um,
bumped into a chair.
I didn't think that you were
coming home till tomorrow.
Nah, fish weren't bitin'.
So, uh...
You got a girl in here?
No. Why?
'Cause when I came home,
I thought I heard sex nois.
No, that was just me.
Okay.
Night.
Oh, God,
that was close.
All this sneaking
around is ridiculous!
Mike and I dated for...
five minutes.
He's not gonna care.
What if Travers finds out?
Look, I don't want
him to be confused,
and until we figure out
where this is going,
I just...
think we should keep
things on the down low.
Hey, I didn't say
we had to stop.
I just said
we had to quiet.
What?
I suppose we should tiptoe
around like schoolchildren
so our parents don't
catch us doing it?
I feel like I'm 12 again.
I'm just saying, I don't think that
the whole world needs to know our...
12?
Okay, look...
I will find us another
place to rendezvous.
But I'm not gonna
skulk around forever.
And no one's
asking you to.
I respect you too
much for that.
If you don't mind...
Oh, for God sake...
I'm gonna be right there.
Here you go.
So can you still cook
with the power out?
Of course!
Absolutely!
Please, please, tell me
we can still make pizza.
No dice.
Some genius installed pizza
ovens with electric starters.
This is awful.
On a good night,
we barely break even.
Tonight is gonna kill
the whole week.
Not necessarily.
The stovetop's gas.
I bought pasta for
the staff dinner.
You give me
ten minutes,
I'll whip up a spaghetti carbonara
that'll knock their socks off.
Oh, my God!
You are a lifesaver!
And, uh, since
it's not on the menu,
you can charge
whatever you want...
Say, 20 bucks?
For pasta?
Are you crazy?
Won't hurt to ask.
I don't wanna
scare them away.
Okay.
So...
Good news!
Our chef is preparing his
special spaghetti carbonara.
Oh, yummy!
And we're offering
that for $12.
Great!
For the appetizer portion.
The entrée is $20.
-Fine.
-2.
22.
Okay.
Shouldn't there be
an emergency light?
Sometimes in these
elevators there's a...
Ta-da!
Well, aren't you clever?
I'll just call hotel security
and let 'em know we're...
No, wait!
This is the first time I've had
you to myself all night.
I'm sorry.
It's those fund-raisers.
Everybody wants a piece
of the candidate.
What are you doing?
Taking my piece.
Are you insane?
We're in an elevator.
Exactly.
Going down...
No! Come on.
Cut it out.
The power could come
on at any moment.
I know. That's what
makes it so exciting...
the risk.
But I'm kind of running for
mayor here, remember?
It's an elevator, silly.
It has an emergency stop button.
I don't.
Oh, my God, that's amazing!
What are you doing?
That's my phone.
It's on vibrate.
Man, I was just
starting to get into it.
Less talking,
more dressing.
You two okay?
Yeah, fine, thanks.
Must've gotten
pretty hot in there.
You have no idea.
Karen, don't worry
about a thing.
I'll collect your mail
till you get back.
Well, how long's this
blackout supposed to last?
Well, they say
it may last for days.
Days?!
Hey, blondie, come here.
Come here.
Listen, I don't really need
to go to the hospital.
I'm fine.
You fractured a rib,
and you might ve a concussion.
You need looking after.
No, some of the stuff in
my freezer might melt.
How about I just run out and get some
ice and then meet you at the hospital?
Ma'am, you can
replace groceries.
You don't understand.
Some of my groceries,
they have sentimental value.
Sorry.
Yeah, well, I don't need
to ask your permission.
Ma'am, no!
Get your hands off me,
you big ape!
Get the restraints.
I'm gonna sue your ass!
Well, what are we waiting for?
Get me to the hospital.
I'm not a well woman.
What was that all about?
Your friend's afraid the stuff
in her freezer is gonna spoil.
Well, thank God
the power's back on.
Now she won't
have to worry.
I made you waffles!
Eat 'em while
they're hot.
What?
Will you marry me?
They're just toaster waffles.
Ah, that was just the
pre-proposal, actually.
The real one will be
much more romantic
with a big diamond
the size of a doorknob.
But just so you're prepared,
I do wanna marry you.
Well, just so you're prepared,
consider this my pre-refusal.
Come on. What's wrong?
You're wearing my shirts.
You burn my breakfast.
You're here every night.
It's like we're married already.
We're having a good time.
Why risk ruining it?
See, what happened to the thrill seeker
that seduced me in the elevator?
She wouldn't be afraid
of taking a little risk.
Oh, you don't wanna marry her.
She's a tramp.
Hold out for a good girl.
No, no, no.
I've found what
I'm looking for.
Come on. What gives?
Look, Victor...
Getting divorced really
kicked my ass.
I'm sorry. Just...
Next time I get married,
I've gotta be sure.
Okay, I get it.
I just wish there was
a way I could prove
how much I love
and ore you.
Well, if you canhoke down
that lousy waffle I made you,
that'd be a start.
Oh, there's Mike.
Should we see if
he's free Friday night?
Yeah. Yeah, why not?
Sure.
You know what? Do you wanna run
this ice cream side before it melts?
Look, Ian is going to come
invite you to dinner Friday,
And you are not, I repeat,
not going to accept.
Why is Ian inviting
me to dinner?
He wants to thank
you for saving us,
and he wants to show that
he's not jealous of you.
How's that for irony?
I didn't plan to kiss you,
but you didn't exactly resist.
I was in shock.
Why were you so upset
when you mentioned Ian?
Because we had
just had a fight...
about you.
Really?
You talk about me a lot?
Mike, I am marrying Ian.
We have hired a caterer.
We are going with the salmon,
so just back off!
Hey, Ian.
Hi, Ian.
I just asked Mike.
He can't make it.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I've got plans tonight.
But didn't we say Friday?
Friday?
Friday I'm wide open.
Splendid!
Shall we say 7:30?
It's a date.
Edie!
Mrs. Epstein!
Listen, I'm late for
my Hadassah meeting.
Here's the key.
Take your time.
Oh, and don't be shy.
Check out those closets.
They're very spacious.
Edie, what are
we doing here?
Checking out a house.
I told you, I'm not looking
to buy right now.
Well, who's talking
about buying anything?
I...
am giving it away.
Edie, we cannot
have sex in here.
It's someone else's bed!
That's just wrong!
We can't use my place.
We can't use yours.
But I'll be damned if I am
gonna pay for a hotel room
when there are all of these
empty houses all over town
that I have the keys to.
Though reluctant at first,
Carlos soon saw the
wisdom in Edie's plan.
Secret affairs are
a lot like real estate.
The three keys
to success are...
Location...
Location.
Careful. I can't sit
down that fast.
Sorry.
But it's gonna be worth it.
Okay, so tell Tom the
secret of your risotto.
Well, I sauted spinach and
onions in white wine...
No, no, the profit margin.
Basically, it costs
a dollar to make...
And we charge $20!
So four people who would've shared a $15
pizza are now spending 80 bucks.
Okay, kids, dig in!
There's just one little
problem with that, Lynette.
Those families you're
talking about have kids,
and there's no kid that's gonna
eat anything with spinach in it.
Um, Tom...
It's delicious, huh?
Yeah?
Rick learned how to
make this in Italy.
Go ahead. Try it.
I wanna see
what you think.
It's good.
It's awesome!
But?
But it's just not us.
Us?
What is us?
Look, we're a neighborhood
pizza place.
We serve pizza.
I like this better.
I'm getting bored of pizza.
Porter, the adults are talking.
Look, we serve good
food at good prices.
We're not looking to be the next,
you know, trendy flash in the pan.
That's not what
I'm looking for either.
See, my food, it's not trendy.
It's classic.
Rick...
Obviously you're
a great cook,
and when you have your own
place, I will definitely eat there,
but I see no reason
to change my menu.
More, please!
Hi! Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm here
to see Mr. Lang.
He's not here.
Is that for him?
Yeah.
But it's very personal.
Okay.
I don't think I should
leave it with the maid.
Do I look like the maid?
Give me that!
You!
Blackmailer!
Oh, man, you weren't
supposed tlook!
Get off of me!
$50, 000?
Are you insane?!
No, that's not for
you to decide!
I want all the negatives of those photos,
or I start breaking fingers!
No, you can't
break my fingers!
Give me the pictures!
Break it up! Break it up!
Come on! Come on!
She's crazy!
That's for calling me a maid!
He works the hotel
security monitors.
That's how he got the photos.
That miserable cockroach.
If you wanna smack
him around a little,
I can go inside and
turn up the radio.
Again, no, thank you,
but I will need those photos.
Oh, no, no, I'm gonna
hang on to these.
They're a little revealing.
Ma'am, we can't charge him
without evidence, and if he walks,
he can do what he wants
with the originals.
Okay, yeah.
But guard them
with your life.
Yeah, especially that one.
We've been open for
three months now,
and we've barely
turned a profit!
We are building a customer
base! That takes time!
Go on, ask her.
No, you ask her!
Why are you
being so stubborn?
And you would rather see the restaurant
fail than succeed with Rick's idea!
And I can't believe that you two
are ready to toss out my concept.
You know, why don't you just rename
the restaurant "Lynette and Rick's"?
Can we have fudgsicles?
-No!
Sorry, Lynette, but the menu is
not changing. End of discussion.
I don't think so.
I'm giving it a try.
That's not your
decision to make.
Yeah?
Well, then why don't you come
down to the restaurant and stop me?
Oh, that's right.
You can't.
I told you she'd say no.
Ms. McCluskey always
has some fudgsicles.
Yeah, but she's
in the hospital.
Where's the ice cream?
She didn't have any.
Oh, man!
There wasn't anything
good in there?
No.
What the hell
were you thinking?
How was I supposed to know the cops were
gonna release the photos to the press?
Everybody in town knows the police chief
is the mayor's brother-in-law, everyone!
Enough, Jerome!
I want you to organize a press conference,
and then I want you to help me prep for it.
Well, this is gonna be a bloodbath.
I don't know how you're gonna prep.
Just get me a bucket of piranhas,
and I'll stick my head in it.
You know, you're a single guy.
Maybe people won't care.
I'm running a family values campaign,
and I had sex in an elevator.
I think they will care.
Look, I know this is my fault, so if you
wanna bite my head off, go ahead.
You know, Gaby, there are only two
things that matter to me these days.
My campaign and you.
And if I had to
lose one of them,
I'd rather it was
the campaign.
Is there anything I can do?
Yeah, you can stick
around on election night.
I have a feeling I'm gonna
need some serious consoling.
God, that is so good!
I know. It's hard
to decide, huh?
No. No, I'm gonna go with the crab
cakes and the little quesadillas.
Well, all we need is a wedding
cake, and we're done.
You are the most decisive
bride I've ever met.
I just guess I'm in a rush.
Gotcha.
Well, don't worry.
You are not showing at all.
No, no, no.
No, I'm not pregnant.
No, I just know know
what I want, which is Ian.
So I'm just eager to...
you know, not get it over
with, per se, but just to...
get to the good part,
which is the marriage...
to Ian.
Seems like a great guy.
I don't suppose
he has a brother.
Oh, so you're not seeing anyone?
No, I'm between
disappointments.
Well, are you free
for dinner tomorrow?
Is this some lame setup?
Please say yes.
Well, there's this guy
coming to dinner, and he is
single and handsome
and charming and...
You had me at "guy."
So how do
you know him?
He's just a neighbor.
Hey, buddy,
whatcha doing?
Nothing.
You seem a little mopey lately.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Can we go see
Mrs. McCluskey?
You guys didn't have
to come down here.
No matter what that C.A.T. scan says,
I'm breaking out tomorrow.
Well, Parker really
wanted to come visit you.
I'm gonna put a little
water in these.
Don't tell your brothers.
You were always my favorite.
I saw the man
in your freezer.
-Lynette!
-Yeah?
Could you run down to the snack bar
and get me some green jell-o?
Oh, sure!
Okay, time for a little
grown-up talk.
So can you understand now
why I had to do what I did?
And how you can never tell
anyone, not even your Mom?
Hey, they didn't have jell-o,
so I hope pudding is okay.
Yeah, let's give it to Parker.
A good boy like him
deserves a treat.
What are you thinking about?
Just...
this room doesn't
really work.
It's just too sterile.
Can we go back to that
Spanish colonial on 3rd?
Sure.
Fine.
You know what
I was thinking?
I'm really happy,
and I haven't felt this
happy in a long time.
How about you?
Are you happy?
Oh, my God!
Oops, sorry.
Bed's not made.
Russell!
Why don't you check out
the subzero in the kitchen?
It's to die.
Well, I see you can't close a sale
without opening something else.
Oh, please, I heard about your
open house on holly drive.
They're still disinfecting
the jacuzzi.
Slut.
Bitch.
You think he's
gonna tell anyone?
He's a gay realtor.
He's speed-dialing as we speak.
Then go stop him.
What's the big deal?
Who cares if people find out?
-I do.
-Why?
Are you embarrassed
to be dating me?
No! It's...
You know, if Gaby finds out,
she's gonna hit the ceiling.
Why would she care?
She's dating
that Victor guy.
Please, that's not gonna last.
Oh, my God.
You're still in
love with her.
No, I just...
I mean, we've been getting
along, and don't wanna...
I don't know who
the bigger moron is.
You or me.
Hey, don't be like this.
Look, we're having fun, right?
Apparently that's
all we're having.
Edie, come on!
No, fun's over.
Ah, Mike.
Thanks for coming.
Thanks for asking me.
Susan.
Hi.
Um, Mike,
I want you to meet
Maggie Gilroy.
I don't believe this.
You're setting me up?
You need to
move on, okay?
I don't wanna move on.
I came here to see you.
Well, I'm not available,
so if you feel like
kissing someone tonight,
point those lips at Maggie.
Here we go.
Your beer.
Did I mention that Maggie
is an amazing chef?
We're embarrassed to
be cooking for her.
Stop.
So, Mike, do you have
a favorite type of cuisine?
Nah. After three months of prison food,
everything tastes good to me.
So you were in prison?
He was totally innocent.
Yeah, a woman was
bludgeoned to death,
and her blood wound
up on my wrench.
Oh, my God.
But he was cleared.
All charges dropped.
Here. Eat this.
It's just so awful.
To go to jail for a crime
you didn't commit.
Oh, it was just a few months.
Now my first stretch
for manslaughter...
That was brutal.
My worst cellmate was
this guy called "Stilts."
When they arrested him,
they found a bowl full of ears.
I think that was
meant for you.
Sorry.
So why don't I just go
and brew some coffee?
And I brought a little
surprise for dessert.
Wedding cakes for
you to sample.
Great.
Thanks a lot.
Now maggie thinks
you're Charles Manson.
I don't care. I love you.
Don't say that.
It's true. I remember
everything now.
When I got run over,
I was on my way
to propose to you.
-I don't wanna talk about it.
-I do.
What would you have said?
You know what I would have said.
It doesn't matter now.
The hell it doesn't. Susan,
If you can look me in the eye and
tell me that when we kissed,
you felt nothing,
then I'll just go.
But only if you can say
that and really mean it.
Can you?
Who wants wedding cake?
Maggie, these
cakes are fantastic.
Great. Well, all you have to do
is choose one, and we're done.
Did you notice the themes?
Themes?
Yes.
This one is very british:
fondant icing and
toffee ganache.
And this is your
classic american:
white cake with
buttercream frosting.
So which one do
you like the best?
Wow. It's kinda
hard to decide.
Well, that depends on
what you're looking for.
Rich and elegant?
Or down-to-earth
and sweet?
I don't know.
You want to
taste 'em again?
No, I know what
they taste like.
I'm just torn, okay?
There's no need to get
upset. It's just a cake.
It's not just a cake.
It's a major decision!
Well, hey, if you like 'em both so much,
why don't you have two cakes?
How would that look?
"Oh, hey, everybody!
Here's my wedding cake.
Oh, and what's that over there?
It's my other wedding cake."
I have to pick, and I will!
So just stop pressuring me, okay?
I'm sorry.
I think I was just having
a little sugar rush.
Thanks again, and sorry.
Seriously, just put it on hold
for just a month or two...
Excuse me.
Am I interrupting something?
No. It's nothing.
I think it's time
to level with him.
I just told Susan
I want her back.
Excuse me?
Look, I know it puts
a crimp in your plans,
and I'm sorry,
but I love her.
Well, that's too damn bad, isn't it?
Because she doesn't love you.
Really?
She didn't seem to mind
when I kissed her.
What?
Did he just kiss you?
No. It was days ago.
-And you let him?!
-No! He pounced.
It was hardly a pounce.
You bastard. We...
We had an agreement.
Susan doesn't have to rry you because
you won her in a game of cards.
What, he didn't tell you how
we played poker for you?
You bet me in
a game of poker?
It's not how it sounds.
I merely suggested that
if I won the hand,
then he would
stop badgering you.
And if he won?
Well, I forget the exact terms,
but the point is, he lost,
as I knew he would.
I never would
have wagered you
if I didn't have
a very good hand.
Get out!
Susan, please.
-You heard her.
-You, too.
I've had it with
both of you.
You're tugging at me like
I'm some kind of wishbone.
You're just upset.
No, I am beyond upset.
You two want a decision?
Well, here's what I decide.
There will be no kissing,
and there will
be no wedding,
be no damn cake!
What's this?
Pumpkin sage ravioli.
It's a little thank you for
taking a chance on me.
Are you kidding?
I should be thanking you.
We took in three
grand tonight.
Candles, too?
Yeah, I think we should
use 'em all the time.
It softens up
the ambience.
So, come on. Eat.
Oh, my God.
If we serve this for
tomorrow's special,
will will clear four grand.
Great.
Just be sure
to run it by Tom.
Why? You know
he'll just shoot it down.
I mean, I get it.
He's in pain.
He doesn't like being sidelined,
but that is no reason to...
You know what?
Let's talk about something else.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, unless you'd like to go.
You're here so late all the time.
No. No, I like being here.
It beats going home
to an empty apartment.
Don't you have any friends
to hang out with?
My friends come
in two varieties.
The ones I drove away
before I got clean and
the ones I should avoid
if I wanna stay clean.
Yeah. I gotcha.
You ever wear
your hair down?
What? Yeah.
Sometimes. Why?
It looks really good.
You should do
it more often.
Oh, well...
Thanks.
This is delicious.
Do you want some more wine?
Sure.
Daddy!
The paper has a story
about your restaurant.
You're kidding!
Well, come here.
What does it say?
"When Scavo's pizzeria
opened its doors,
you could almost
hear the city groan,
'Just what we need,
another pizza joint.'
But with an updated menu
from new chef Rick Coletti..."
Is he the man who
cooked us that really...
Yeah, that's the one.
What else does it say, honey?
"There's more than just
crayons on the table.
The veal piccata is divine,
and the mushroom
risotto is an...
-E-X-Q-U..."
-Exquisite.
"An exquisite treat.
Scavo's has been transformed
from a mundane family eatery
into the area's hottest..."
That's enough, Kayla.
Daddy's tired.
Okay.
Okay, I know you guys
like a good scandal,
but I think the citizens of Fairview
are more interested
in the real issues.
Mr. Lang, given your
15-point drop in the polls,
what do you have to say
to your constituents?
Well, I would ask them
to not base their view of
me on a single lapse of...
-It's not going very well, is it?
-You picked up on that, did you?
Who is she, Mr. Lang?
Give us a name.
No, I will not identify
the woman.
What are you hiding?
Is she a prostitute?
No! She's not a prostitute.
I'll answer questions
one at a time, people.
That does it.
What are you doing?
Gaby, stop, please.
Please, stop.
Excuse me.
I am the woman
in the photos!
What are you doing?
Standing by my man.
My name is Gabrielle Marquez,
and I want you to know, right
before those photos were taken,
Victor asked me to marry him.
What did you say?
I said, "yes.
I would be thrilled
to be Mrs. Victor Lang."
Are you gonna get married?
Have you set a date?
Are you really getting married?
In fact, I was so overcome, that when
we were trapped in the elevator,
I seized the moment to...
express my joy.
So this is a love story?
The only reason Victor kept it
from you was to protect me...
Because he's the kind of man who puts
a woman's honor before his own,
and that's the kind
of man you marry.
That's the kind of
man you vote for.
Where are you honeymooning?
What's that smell?
Ma'am.
Are you Karen McCluskey?
That little bastard gave
me up, didn't he?
Today, at the mayoral
candidate's press conference,
a woman identified as Gabrielle
Marquez, a former model,
surprised reporters by announcing
her engagement to Mr. Lang.
The only reason he didn't tell you
was because he was protecting me.
Carlos?
I don't know if you've heard...
Yeah.
I heard.
In a few months,
I will be Mrs. Victor Lang.
I just heard on the radio the power
company is still having problems,
and there might be another
rolling blackout today.
Do you want me to leave Ida's
number in case something happens?
I'm sure I'll be fine.
Did you read our
review in the paper?
Yep.
Okay.
I'm off.
Power.
It's the type of thing most
people don't think about...
until it's taken away.
Whether it's the political
power of the many...
Or a lover's influence
over just one.
We all want some sort
of power in our lives,
if only to give
ourselves choices.
Yes, to be without choices,
to feel utterly powerless, well...
It's a lot...
like being alone...
in the dark.