Previously on...
The scavos prepared
for a grand opening...
This could be
the best thing
That's ever happened
to our family.
While gabrielle had
a few too many drinks...
I'm gonna take
a little nap, okay?
And a cry for help
made orson lose his cool.
Suicide is the worst thing
that could happen to a family!
Mike got arrested...
Oh, thank god.
And a friendship
hit the rocks.
For the sake
of our friendship--
Make no mistake,
Our friendship is over.
Orson's mom was determined...
In the eyes of god,
you're the other woman.
To bring alma and orson
back together.
(Bree) she raped you,
and your mother helped.
I think it's time
I told you about the night
about monique died.
Alma became a prisoner...
Gloria?!
Bree...
Aah!
...was set up to take a fall,
And mike was finally able
to remember the past.
Uhh! Uhh!
Aah!
(Mary alice)
orson hodge had always assumed
That the moment before he died,
His entire life uld flash
before his eyes,
But as he fell from the roof of
the fairview memorial hospital,
It wasn't his life he saw.
It was one night in particular.
Monique?
I've got wonderful news.
Bonnes nouvelles!
Monique?
There's been an accident.
Oh, my god.
What have you done?
It was self-Defense.
I came to tell her to stay away
from you. She attacked me.
Mother, she's dead.
I know.
And i'm sorry,
but what's done is done.
What are you doing?
I'm lling the police.
No! I'll go to jail.
You killed someone!
I'm your mother!
You've got to help me!
But i loved her.
I once lost someone i loved,
thanks to you.
You owe me.
(Mike) hello?
Ms. Polier?
I've got that part
for e sink.
Hello?
Ms. Polier?
Ah, i'm sorry.
I'm monique's boyfriend.
She's upstairs lying down.
She wasn't... feeling well.
I'll just finish up the sink
and get out of your hair.
Uh, look, why don't you
let me take care of that?
I mean, i'm pretty handy,
and it's getting late.
Oh, i don't mind staying.
Oh, i've, uh,
i've got it under control.
Um, here, let me, uh,
let me pay you.
That should cover it
Thanks.
Oh, hey, uh...
Don't forget your wrench.
You handled that
very well, son.
Now help me find a tarp.
Ugh!
What are you doing?
You don't want her identified
through dental records, do you?
Ugh!
I must say, i never realized
your job was so difficult.
It's not enough to kill her.
You have
to desecrate her body, too?
Get away from her!
Aah!
(Groans)
now look what you've done!
I think my damn hip's broken.
Help me.
Yes...
Orson hodge had always assumed
That his life would flash
before his eyes
The moment before he died.
Uhh!
Luckily, for orson...
(man) hurry! Come on!
That moment...
I got a pulse!
Let's get him inside!
Was noscheduled for today.
Dh315
The first light of sunrise.
The sound of the cat purring.
The smell of fresh coffee...
Yes, there are many things
A housewife
likes to wake up to,
But an unexpected guest
in her bed
Is not one of them.
Zach?
You're... in your underwear.
Well, i-I needed
to put on something
To get the morning paper.
You've been here all night?
Sure.
I'm not one of those guys
Who gets up and leaves
right ter.
Right after what?
Do you wanna hear me say it?
Fine.
You were amazing.
Okay, listen to me
very carefully,
And this is no time
to be vague.
What exactly
was i amazing at?
Please tell me
that once contained a mint.
After a few drks,
you told me how lonely you were
And that i was the kindest man
you'd met in a few years,
And, uh, then you kissed me.
(Gasps)
And then you took off your--
Okay, okay, stop talking.
I'm getting nauseous.
This is so great.
I have so many
awesome plans for us.
"Us." (Chuckles) oh, man.
It feels so good to say that.
Oh, god. Here it comes.
Would you like me
to hold your hair, honey?
No!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm lying in bed, inking about
the opening tonight,
When it hits me...
We could
run out of breadsticks.
Oh, honey,
you have had, what,
Four hours sleep
in the past three days?
You need rest. Who cares
if we run out of breadsticks?
I do!
Tonight's the most important
night of my life.
Everything's
gotta be perfect.
Here. Try that.
It's good.
No. Too salty.
If they're salty,
we'll sell more beer.
See? You're a genius.
Don't patronize me!
Oh, my god.
This is gonna be a disaster.
Hey, chill out.
You're acting like i did
when i was six months pregnant.
Uh, excuse me.
You were hitting people.
Only two, and the mailman
had the good taste
Never to bring that up again.
Come on.
Let's go get some sleep.
The dough maker
And the chairs
get delivered at noon.
I know. I'm the one
that put in the order.
I will handle anything
that needs to be done.
And you, take these
and get some sleep.
Come on. We need you
at your best tonight.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Crazy. (Chuckles)
Ooh! Honey glaze.
Honey glaze will cut the salt
in the breadsticks.
Tom, i do not need
to be pregnant
To kick your ass.
Now go. Go on.
Andrew, you're here.
Oh, what happened to me?
You--You kinda had
an accident.
You fell off our ladder.
Oh, that's right.
(Sighs) is orson here?
Um...
Yeah, he's--
He's at the hospital,
But he's
not exactly visiting.
Suicide?
No. Orson would never
try to kill himself.
The police are wrong.
It must have been an accident.
But they found his footprints
on the trunk of his car.
The only reason
he'd be up there is to jump.
But why?
Maybe he was feeling guilty.
For what?
Mom,
i-I looked at that ladder.
Someone
sawed through the rung.
And you think...
I heard you two
in your room the other day.
The next day,
you fall and nearly die.
You-Ou think
that's a coincidence?
And you say
he's just down the hall?
Yeah, but don't worry.
I-I told them
not to let him near you,
And we're gonna get you home
as soon as wcan.
Can i help you?
I'm here to pick up
my wife's belongings.
Uh, jane hainsworth?
Oh, yes.
I'm so sorry
for your loss.
I'll be right back.
You doing okay?
Not really,
but having you here helps.
Oh, hey, mrs. Mayer.
Andrew, what are you doing
at the hospital?
You--You haven't heard?
Hey.
Susan.
I just heard from andrew
what happened.
I had to come see you.
If you want me
to go, uh...
No, no. Come in.
I know we've been fighting.
Something like this happens,
It just puts everything
into perspective.
I am so sorry.
It was all my fault.
If i hadn't got so caught up
in protecting mike--
Susan, stop.
Mike is innocent.
He had nothing to do
with monique polier's murder.
Do you know something?
Yes, and i intend
to go to the police.
Oh, my god.
Does this have something
to do with orson's accident?
I can't tell you
right now.
You're just gonna have
to trust me.
Can you do that?
Of course.
I should let you rest.
So we're back
to being friends?
We never really stopped.
Um, excuse me. These--These
things don't belong to jane.
Are you sure?
Oh, every couple
has their secrets,
But i'm pretty sure
she wasn't a closet whittler.
"Mike delfino."
Oh, these are mike's things?
Yep. Someone made
a big mistake.
Helen, you screwed up
the labels again!
Oh! He had an engagement ring
with him.
Ooh, that's pretty.
You know,
mike and i are good friends.
I-I could return these things
to him, if--If you like.
Sorry. He'll have
to pick 'em up himself.
It's hospital policy.
It's also hospital policy
To put the right labels
on the right boxes!
Ian! Ian, you're not gonna
believe this.
Bree just told me
she can prove mike's innocent.
What?
It's true.
He's gonna be a free man.
Isn't that great?
Yes,
it's bloody fantastic.
Oh! Whoops.
Here. I'm gonna go get bree
some flowers.
I'll be right back.
No, no, that's great news.
Thank you, doctor.
(Telephone beeps)
so orson's
gonna pull through?
You'd rather he didn't?
No.
I just don't know what
he's gonna tell the police
When he wakes up.
It wasn't your fault.
Orson falling off that roof
was an accident, right?
Well, sort of.
Sort of?
Depending on what
orson tells them,
I could get charged
with attempted murder.
Well, so i'm so glad she has you
to take care of her,
And of course
your mom comes first, andrew.
And i wouldn't even ask except,
you know,
We're opening tonight--
Chairs are here.
Uh, uh-Huh.
Oh, god. Seriously?
Fantastic. Thank you.
It's just two quick hours,
And then we'll get you
right back home with your mom.
Thank you, andrew.
Okay. Bye-Bye.
(Telephone beeps)
Did you finish folding
the takeout menus?
You never asked me
to do that.
I shouldn't have to tell you
every little thing, you know.
Show some initiative.
Wait. Wherare my chairs?
I didn't order these.
You lynette scavo?
Yes.
Well, then you ordered these.
No. Why would i order
50 high chairs
For the opening
of a pizzeria?
I don't know.
I thought it was one of those,
uh, kiddie pizza places
With the games
and the animatronic rats.
Give me that.
Easy there, sally.
"Animatronic rats."
Where do they find you people?
Okay, okay, here it is.
See? I ordered 50
of item number 7-3...
Oh, huh.
Did we find the mistake?
I, um, i switched
the 7 and the 1.
Mm-Hmm.
So... we're both wrong.
Now this place opens
in five hours.
How long will it take
to fix this?
Hi. I need to rent 50 chairs
by tonight at 5:00.
(Blows air) what?
Why not?
What do you mean,
it's bar mitzvah season?
There's no such thing.
Oh! You still have five.
I will take those. Scavo.
Okay, that brings us to 22.
Javi, rico,
we got chairs to find. Move it.
Wow.
Looks like someone crawled into
a bottle of merlot last night.
I sort of threw myself
a little birthday party.
So if you don't mind, i'd like
to get back to my dry heaving.
Quick question--
Was that zach young
I saw leavinyour house
8:00 this morning?
Uh, oh, yeah. Um...
He just came by to, uh...
Drop off a birthday rd.
Really cute little cat
with balloons. (Chuckles)
All right, bye.
Follow-Up.
Why was zach in your driveway
at 7:00 this morning...
In his underwear?
We had sex last night!
What?!
I mean, i think we did.
That's what he told me.
Weren't you there?
No, i don't remember
anything!
I just woke up,
and he was in bed next to me.
Thanks again, gaby.
Hey, carlos.
If you don't remember,
Then how can you be sure
that you and zach had sex?
Well,
we were both half-Naked,
And--And there was
a condom wrapper.
And he said i was amazing,
which totally sounds like me.
He thinks we're a couple now.
You have to help me.
(Laughs)
i am not getting involved.
God, i can't believe you bagged
another neighborhood kid.
Where are you going?
To warn the scavo boys.
I wanna speak to my wife.
She's resting. If we can
get back to these questions...
I fell off a roof. I need
a physician, not a psychiatrist.
Well, i'm afraid
it's hospital policy
When there's
a suspected suicide attempt.
I didn't try to kill myself.
But you do have a certain...
History?
You spent most of 1976
in a psychiatric hospital.
I don't care
to discuss that.
You won't be leaving here
until we do.
My parents
were very regious.
When i was 16,
my fher had an affair,
Caused quite a scandal
at our church.
(Orson) he became depressed.
He started drinking heavily.
My mother grew concerned.
She didn't like
leaving him alone.
One night,
she had to visit a sick friend,
And she asked me
to keep an eye on him.
But i had made plans
with friends.
I thought i could
duck out for a while.
When i got home,
i found him in the bathroom.
You blamed yourself?
Ah, i didn't need to.
Mother blamed me enough
for bo of us.
That must have
caused quite a strain
In your relationship.
Yes.
But now and then,
She suggests little ways
i might make it up to her.
Yes, i'm calling to check
on the status of a patient.
Last name hodge.
What do you mean,
"which hodge"?
Gloria! Thank god. I thought
you'd forgotten about me.
When are you
letting me out of here?
It won't be long now.
In fact, something interesting
happened last night.
Orson
tried to kill himself.
Oh, my goodness.
Is he okay?
He'll be fine.
My point is,
Suicide is hardly the act
of a happily married man.
Gloria, for god sake,
give it up.
He doesn't love me.
He will, dear.
Bree will be gone soon,
And he'll need a good woman
like you to console him.
What are you gonna do
to bree?
(Alma) gloria?
Gloria?
Oh, hey, hon.
Hey.
Did you get some sleep?
Yes. I'm still kind of groggy
from those pills, but...
And now i'm awake.
Okay, little mix-Up
with the new chairs.
Which you were in charge of.
Okay, okay,
we could point fingers,
But what's important
Is forgetting about
what we expected
And focusing on what we have,
which isn't so bad.
I mean, all the different
kinds of chairs
Give the place
a kind of bohemian vibe.
Plus, if we get
a lot of babies--
Look,
we're just totally set.
Tom, i'm sorry.
I am. I'm sorry.
I just--I realize
it's not... perfect.
But...
Please say something.
What can i say, lynette?
It is what it is.
Why do i
have to babysit mom?
All my friends
are gonna be at the opening.
Austin was gonna
sneak us beer!
Damn it, danielle,
i have to work!
Our mother's
lying helpless upstairs
'Cause her husband
tried to kill her.
Now for just one night,
could you try toe responsible?
I liked you better
when you were a psychopath!
Here you go.
Ah.
Wow, you're... here.
I wouldn't have missed it.
You know how i feel
about lynette and tom.
Uh, look, zach,
i'm glad you're here.
I've been wanting to talk
about us.
Me, too. You, uh,
being in my life now,
Having the connection
that we do,
This is really the--The first
time that i've been happy
Since my mother
killed herself.
Would you excuse me a send?
Huckles)
Of course, baby.
Hurry back.
Yeah, okay. All right.
I am in hell.
I just tried
to break up with zach,
And the little twerp
played the dead mommy card.
Well, u can't let him
make you fell guilty.
But i am guilty.
I don't remember how
we ended up in bed together.
Maybe--Maybe i led him on.
I gotta be sensitive here.
Cod you
threaten him for me?
What?
You know, intimidate him.
Do the whole jealous,
latin ex-Husband thing you do.
Tell him if you can't have me,
nobody can.
Forget it. I'm not gonna
Hey, i am looking t
for zach, too.
If i dump him,
it'll destroy him emotionally.
Better to scare him off.
(Sighs) please?
Fine.
Thank you!
Okay, look, there he goes.
Go! Go get all cholo
on his ass.
Hey, mr. Solis.
Hey.
Look, i need to talk to you
about something.
It's a little awkward,
but...
Mr. Solis?
What?
You were just saying
that something was awkward?
Never mind.
Forget
that i said anything.
(Urinal flushes)
Hey. So how'd it go?
You did not have sex
with zach young.
Really?
Did he tell you that?
He didn't have to.
What?
I was standing next to him
at the urinal.
I don't care
how drunk you were.
If you had sex with him,
you'd remember.
(Gasps) little zach young?
Well, just how much
would i have remembered?
Uh, hey.
What are you doing here?
I thought bree
might like some soup.
It's my own special recipe.
I'm surprised
to find you home.
I thought the whole street
was going to scavo's tonight.
Well, i was supposed to go,
But, uh, andrew said i had
to stay home and babysit mom.
Well, that's just silly.
A vibrant young lady like you
should be at the party,
Turning boys' heads.
You go.
I'll look after
your mother.
You mean it?
Just take
her dinner up first.
I don't think i can
manage the tray with my cane.
Thanks, grandma.
You're t best!
Mm.
This soup smells so good.
You wanna score some points?
Don't say i brought it.
Tell her
you made it yourself.
Hey!
Hello?
Over here!
Aah!
Honey, there is a line
out the door.
We are gonna
make a killing tonight.
I'm happy for ya.
For us.
Now it's "us"?
Because i thought
i was the one
Who was trying
to ruin everything.
Hey, look,
i know i overreacted--
Yes, you did.
But i have customers.
Oh!
The place
came out great, huh?
Sure did.
Looks like, uh,
the whole street's here.
Yeah.
Except for orson,
who fell off a roof.
You know anything
abouthat?
Why would you think that?
I heard you talking to carlos.
Now answer the question.
I-I can't
talk about it here.
It's complicated.
It always is with you.
Hey. I just had a slice
of pizza. It's pretty good.
Is it really good,
Or are you just pretending
you had a slice?
You and i did not have sex.
Admit it!
Of course we did.
Zach! How can you claim to care
about me and lie to my face?
I'm sorry.
I'm tired
of just being your friend.
I thought if you saw me
as a lover,
You can think of me as a man,
not--Not a boy.
Zach, a real man is honest.
All you've ever tried to do
Is bribe and trick me
into falling in love with you.
A little advice next time?
Don't play games.
Just stand up
and be the kind of man
A woman would be proud
to share her life with.
(Singsong voice) hello!
I think it's high time
to make a toast.
(Woman) all right!
(Man) sure!
Um, tom, where are you?
Where--Ah. Tom, you did it.
There are a lot of people
in this room
That didn't think
you could pull it off.
Okay, well, maybe just me.
Anyway, congratulations.
The pizza is excellent,
and the service is sublime.
Cheers.
(Carlos) speech!
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
It means
everything in the world to me.
I-I gotta tell you, when i
arrived here this afternoon,
I saw all these weird chairs,
Um, i thought the evening
was gonna be a total disaster.
But now when i look out,
i can't even see the chairs.
I just see people eating,
Laughing
and having a great time.
It's absolutely perfect.
And none of this
would've happened
Without
my amazing partner lynette.
Who, uh...
To...
I'm sorry.Laughs)
i'm--I'm a little, uh...
(Laughs) i think what
my husband is trying to say is,
If you really want
to test a marriage,
Open a restaurant together.
Anyway, um,
thank you for coming.
Eat a lot and come back,
'cause our kids need braces.
Actually, as long as everyone
has their glasses raised,
I have something that--
That i wld like to say.
I, um, well,
i-I thought of waiting
For the perfect romantic spot
in which to ask this question,
But being here tonight,
Enveloped by so much love
and warmth, i realize that, um,
This is
the perfect romantic spot.
Susan mayer...
Drop the pizza.
Will you make me
the happiest man in the world
And be my wife?
Mmm.
Absolutely, yes!
Whoo!
(Cheering)
Ladies and gentlemen,
Please, i-I have something
that i'd like to say also.
Gabrielle solis...
Will you marry me?
(Man) oh. Should i clap?
No, there will be
no clapping!
You, moron, come with me!
Time for your pills,
mr. Hodge.
Hmm? Oh.
Oh, it's after 6:00?
Mm-Hmm.
I need to speak with my wife.
What room is she in?
Oh, uh,
your wife checked out.
Already?
She was very eager to get home.
Don't worry. She'll be fine.
I-I have to talk to her.
Oh, that reminds me.
Your mother called.
She said she didn't want
to wake you up,
And she wanted to make sure
we'd be keeping you overnight.
Ms are like that--
So protective.
(Orson) bree, it's me.
Are you there?
Please, pick up.
Bree?
Please, somebody,
pickp the phone.
I know that you're mad--
I'm not mad, zach.
I'm done!
But you said to be honest.
I did not say
to humiliate me!
I'm sorry. All right?
I-I was just trying--
What do you want from me?
I want you
to leave me alone!
This friends thing
isn't gonna work
'Cause you're always
gonna want more,
And i'm never
gonna love you... ever.
20 years from now when you're
all middle-Aged and alone,
You'll regret this.
Okay, i'll take my chances.
Thought
you might need this.
Bless you.
So how did it go
with seabiscuit?
He's devastated.
Of course.
It's my fault.
I should've known
He couldn't handle the whole
"let's be friends" thing.
I don't blame him.
I'm having kind of a hard time
myself being just your friend,
Watching you with other guys,
being your confidant.
Really?
I think it's been nice.
For you, maybe.
Look, seriously,
i don't know how much longer
I'm gonna be able
to keep this up.
Wow.
Well, hang in there
as long as you can,
'Cause i still need you.
I'll do my best.
What are you doing here?
I have better things to do
than babysit mom.
She's fine.
Gloria's watching her.
What? I told you mom's ready
to go to the cops about orson.
How could you leave her at home
with his crazy mother?
She brought soup!
Gloria?
What are you doing here?
I came
to take care of you.
I'm so sleepy.
Good. En the pills
are working.
Andrew? Danielle?
They're gone.
It's just us.
Now...
You rest, hon.
I'm gonna draw you
a nice, warm bath.
Oh, bree...
I wish i could
make you understand
How deeply i regret
having to do this.
Monique... that was easy.
She was a slut.
You're a good woman.
You didn't know
orson already had a wife.
But he did,
And he made a vow to her
before god.
What sort of mother would i be
if i let him break it?
I'm sorry.
But i will not let him be
his father's son.
Wake up, mr. Hodge.
I've got dinner.
That water's not too hot,
is it?
No. It's just right.
Mom? Are you all right?
Andrew?
You've done this before,
haven't you?
Ow! Oh! Aah!
Uhh!
Ane drops to floor)
No!
Aah!
Is she all right?
She will be.
Get her some blankets
and some dry clothes.
(Gloria) orson?
Orson!
Something's wrong.
(Weakly) i think
i'm... having a stroke.
You need an ambulance,
mother.
It's too bad
there's no one here
Who'd dream
of calling you one.
What are you doing?
I don't want her dying
in our house.
Hey there.
Are you all right?
(Weakly) your mother...
She tried to kill me.
Don't worry about her.
She's never gonna
hurt you again,
And neither will alma.
Alma?
She's dead.
What?
I don't know what happened,
but she's gone...
Oh.
And she's taking our troubles
with her.
(Orson) tomorrow morning,
one of our neighbors
Will stumble
on a gruesome surprise--
Two bodies side by side.
The police will conclude
that alma fell from the roof,
And when my mother found her,
she suffered a stroke.
When they search the house,