Previously on The Originals...
Klaus: I assume I have the misfortune
of speaking to my mother.
I have come to heal our family.
I will undo everything that has been done,
thereby giving you a new life.
I don't believe I've had the pleasure.
You mean you don't recognize me?
It's been a long time, finn.
Cami: I have to get back to campus.
I'm meeting my new advisor.
- Mr. Griffith?
- Call me Vincent.
Elijah: Aiden, you and Oliver
escort the children.
We'll handle the rest.
Elijah: Uh! Ugh!
No more.
Lenore: Oh, I'm afraid we've just begun.
What is it, hayley?
Something has happened to Elijah.
He's vanished.
Lenore: Stop fighting, Elijah.
I want you to rejoin our family,
take the body of a mortal.
We can all be happy again.
Get out of my head.
The only way to find peace is my way.
[Chanting]
[Creak]
[Panting]
Sister...
I've come to beg for your help.
What for?
You know I've always wanted
children of my own.
Then go. Have your viking children.
It's been almost a full year,
and I'm still not with child.
I fear I'm cursed.
Dahlia, please.
Your magic, it could help me.
You come to me needing favors.
If you hadn't abandoned
your talents with witchcraft,
you could help yourself.
I was never as strong as you.
I know that just as I know
you will not turn me away.
You are my sister, and
whatever our quarrels,
we are bound by blood.
Please help me.
What you ask of me,
it requires a heavy sacrifice.
I will do whatever you ask.
Oh...
I could never refuse you...
My precious, little Esther.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.Addic7ed.Com
why don't you just kill me
and get it over with?
Speak to her again,
I'll feed you your tongue.
Spread the word from here to the bayou.
Midnight tonight, he's to be put to death
for his part in aiding
the escape of deserters.
For now, chain him up in the lycee.
Tell the other wolves to come
and have a look
and see what happens to traitors.
Well done.
Now, I believe you have a meeting.
Good. I'll tend to your brother.
Still sleeping, lost in visions
of horror and dreams of love...
And still so strong, so full of life,
too willful to take my offer.
I remember you as a little boy...
Innocent, kind.
If that boy had known the creature
he would one day grow up to be,
he'd have leapt into my arms
and begged me to save him.
I'd do anything for that little boy...
As I would for you.
Aagh!
[Chanting]
Man: Aagh!
[Saxophone playing]
Hayley: Ah, I see your
interrogation went well.
Turns out, these witches
are delicate creatures.
No matter.
As suspected, my mother has Elijah captive.
Great. Let's go find them.
Esther is too powerful.
She won't easily be found.
I need to draw her out.
Wait. Where are you going?
I'm going to change my shirt,
and then I'm gonna find my brother.
Klaus, let me come with you.
I know you want to help, Hayley,
but you can't.
My mother is wretched.
She will target you in order to thwart me,
and I can't very well save Elijah
if I'm busy saving you, can I?
Gia: I did like you said...
Kept a low profile,
went all over the city.
There's no sign of Elijah anywhere.
Yeah. The humans I know
said the same thing.
Maybe Klaus is having better luck.
Hayley: No. He's not, which sucks,
considering how low the bar is around here.
Hayley: Listen. You two
up for a rescue mission?
Are we going after Elijah?
Nope. That's all Klaus.
I'm talking about Oliver.
He and Elijah were fighting
the werewolves together.
I've heard that Oliver has been captured
and he's about to be executed.
Now, look. If we can save Oliver,
then we might be able to find out
where Elijah is.
Ok. So what do you want from us?
Just a little distraction.
Esther's son finn, he's the one
that's controlling the werewolves.
If you can keep him out of the way,
I can go get Ollie myself.
Can't take on all those wolves by yourself.
You'll get killed, and then I'll
get killed for letting it happen.
I'm not going in alone.
The werewolves may be
answering to the witches,
but they still have an Alpha.
I just have to find him.
Fancy seeing you here.
Ha! Not that fancy, seeing as I work here.
I thought I mentioned that.
Cami, half my patients work in bars.
Can't avoid them all.
You ok? Let me guess.
More drama with Klaus.
Is that right?
Yeah, actually. He has family in town.
They don't really get along,
and he's kind of flipping out.
I got sucked into the crazy.
Seems unfair that he would rely so heavily
on you for support.
Doesn't he have anyone else?
His sister left town.
His brother has been... Occupied.
Rest of his family I wouldn't
say has a healthy dynamic.
So I guess I just feel
a professional obligation to help him.
Cami, this is a person
whom you've described
as being dangerous.
Not to me.
I don't want you to put yourself
in a position where he can harm you.
I know it's your job to give me advice,
but can we save the shop talk?
I mean, it is happy hour.
You're right. Now is not the time.
Bartender, I'll have a whiskey, neat,
and for the lady, a sazerac,
two spoons of honey.
You know what? Better cancel that.
I actually have to run,
but I'll see you Monday.
[Shovel digging]
[Bird calling]
Are you watching this, mother?
Nothing says, "I loathe you,"
quite like desecrating a corpse.
Elijah: Niklaus.
[Continues playing random notes]
You seem troubled.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were worried.
What has she done to you?
1,000 years of murder, mayhem,
and mother believes she
can still save our souls.
[Glissando]
She wants to talk.
Perhaps we should listen.
Enough...
Of the petty illusions, Esther.
Where is Elijah?
Lenore: He's preoccupied at the moment.
I'm helping him find his way,
but not to worry.
I'll return him to you.
All I ask is that you hear me out.
You expect me to sit through
a sermon of your lies?
I have lied in the past, to my shame,
but I'm going to tell you the truth.
I'm in the process of making Elijah
into the man he was meant to be,
and I intend to do the same for you.
Lenore: This plantation, ruined by fire.
How sad, not to mention symbolic.
After all, you never intended
to build a true home here.
Even as Hayley carried your child,
as Rebekah and Elijah sought to defend you,
your thoughts were focused only
on your conquest of the quarter.
Tell me, how did that go?
I'm sorry. Is this some
sort of motherly critique?
Please feel free to choke on it.
I mention your failures
only to make a point, my dear.
You've endured several lifetimes of misery,
never mind the suffering
you've caused others,
even to your own blood.
You yourself remain trapped
in a perpetual state of despair.
I have come to offer you
a means to escape that cycle.
And that's about all
the hypocrisy I can take.
I suggest you give me my brother
before I get angry.
Such hatred.
It breaks my heart to see you like this,
the boy I loved.
Your love was a curse,
an affect you feigned.
The truth is, you're no better than Mikael,
and like him, you seem to have crawled back
from the grave simply
to ruin your own children.
Oh.
You didn't know. Yes.
The destroyer has risen, brought back
to kill me by the witch Davina.
Surely Kol has revealed everything to you,
or has mother's loyal, little boot licker
not quite so loyal, after all?
Marcel: I bet you want a new
advisor right about now.
Who is he, Marcel? I mean, really.
Long story short is... Impossible.
I checked the school's website.
Vincent Griffith has no
other academic credentials,
and, according to my uncle Kieran's
big book of New Orleans bloodlines,
Griffith is a family of witches.
Oh, it's worse that that.
Your therapist has a 1,000-year-old,
dead vampire inside of him
named Finn Mikaelson.
My advisor is Klaus' brother?
Oh, God, Marcel, he came
into Rousseau's today
asking questions about Klaus
and ordered my favorite drink
like he's been watching me.
Why?
Probably to get the scoop on Klaus,
maybe to use you as bait for a trap.
I don't know. It doesn't matter.
Either way, you're done with that guy.
No. I'm just getting started.
If Mikael has returned,
we will need to deal with him.
Ho ho! We? Is that a joke?
Am I to forego centuries of hatred
for my evil mother in order to join her
in besting the very demon
she herself allowed to raise me?
I am not evil, Niklaus.
I am your salvation, and Mikael,
he was not always a demon.
Lenore: Long ago, he loved
his children with all his heart.
He doted on your brother Finn,
but it was our first-born Freya
who was the apple of his eye.
Do you really think that
saccharine recollections
of ancient history will
have any effect on me at all?
What I think is that you have gone mad
from centuries of hating your parents,
but if you join me now,
I can grant you peace...
And should Mikael return
with the intent to harm you,
I will strike him down myself.
That's quite an offer,
but, you know,
I've never needed any help
when it comes to killing parents.
You reject me out of hatred,
but I have something stronger.
I have the truth about your father...
Not Mikael, your real father.
[Arrows release]
Hayley: Is that your best shot?
You're gonna have to do
a lot better than that
if you're gonna kill a hybrid.
Jackson: Stop.
Jackson.
Hayley.
I see you met my friend Ansel.
You know her?
Yeah. Actually, I do.
She was supposed to be my wife.
Lenore: 1,000 years ago in a fit of rage,
you wrapped your bare hands around my neck
and squeezed until I died.
Do you even remember why?
Let's see.
You turned us all into monsters.
You cursed me, denied me
of my hybrid nature.
You lied about my father.
It's that one above all.
You killed me because I kept you
from ever knowing your true father.
My hatred for you runs so deep,
it's difficult to pinpoint its origin.
Maybe I hate that I'm the
product of a whore's lechery.
Watch your mouth.
You would do well to remember
that you are still my son.
You judge me evil, yet it was your lust
that made me what I am.
Not once have I ever regretted
the love I had for your father,
and you have never known the truth
of how that love came to be
or what happened in the months
after Mikael and I lost your sister Freya
to the plague.
There are no words for the loss of a child,
as you well know.
After Francesca Guerrera
took over the wolves,
she offered me a moonlight ring
as long as I'd call her Alpha.
I declined.
So a couple of her brothers dragged me
out here and left me for dead.
By the time I healed up,
work had spread about what happened to you
and to your baby.
So I knew it was over,
and I just drifted,
and that's when I met Ansel.
See, he's been teaching me the old ways,
the traditions,
what it means to be a wolf.
You mean, by living out
in the ass end of nowhere?
Hey, easy.
Your kind makes him ornery.
My kind?
Jack, whatever you and
your friend think of me,
my kind is the wolves.
Even if they did pledge
allegiance to a witch,
all that means is, they need an Alpha.
All I need is one, too.
Yeah. I heard about that.
Thing is, Ollie betrayed me.
He plotted with the Guerrera's.
He spilled his own people's blood.
He was trying to make up for that.
It doesn't matter. Witches have him.
He's dead, not that I care.
You don't want to be the Alpha, fine.
I'll save Ollie myself.
You got a problem, old man?
I have no love of vampires,
but I will not allow a wolf
to be killed by witches.
At least someone is interested.
After Freya died, Mikael was inconsolable.
Compelled by his grief, we were forced
to pack our things and set across the seas.
Eventually, his despair
would drive us apart,
and that's when I saw
him for the first time...
Your father.
I'd never seen a man like him,
powerful yet wise but loved by his people,
and... Because Mikael had chosen
to leave me alone in his grief,
shunning me from his life...
I found myself drawn to another.
Spare me the sordid details
of my origin.
I only speak the truth.
Then tell me this, mother.
Why did your adonis abandon his son?
Why did he allow me to be raised
by a monster who hated me?
Why not claim me for himself,
raise me among the wolves,
or was he as ashamed of his bastard
as you were?
No, no, no. He loved you.
It was I who forbade it.
I knew if Mikael had
learned of my infidelity,
he would've destroyed us in his rage.
I had no choice.
Marcel: So, what, you're gonna spy
on a witch with a 1,000-
year-old grudge match
against Klaus?
Uh-uh. I'm not gonna let you
go anywhere near that guy.
I can handle myself.
Look. Ok. I get it.
You're mad at the guy,
and you want to get even.
It's not about getting even, marcel.
Look around.
Everything in this room,
this is my family's legacy,
and if I had just embraced it
the first time around, I could've uncovered
Francesca Guerrera's secret, and the wolves
would never have taken over the quarter,
and Klaus' baby would still be alive.
So don't tell me not to get involved.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Hold that thought.
Tell me you got your Alpha.
Hayley: He's out of commission,
but I got the next best thing.
I'm assuming you have
a plan to keep Finn occupied.
Yeah. Yeah. I think I might have an idea.
When I learned I was with child,
I went back to Mikael.
I told him I was having his baby.
He showed no joy,
but neither did he suspect the truth.
Lenore: When you were born,
it renewed his spirits.
We had Kol, Rebekah, Henrik.
Because of you, we were a family again.
Oh...
A family built on secrets and lies.
Oh, you were my secret joy,
and to protect your secret,
I denied you a life with your father,
but what if I could make up for all that
by curing you of this sickness
that's infected your soul?
Whereas I put Kol and Finn
into the bodies of a witch,
you I shall place into
the body of a werewolf
so you can live out your days as what
you were always meant to be.
What could possibly make you think
I would agree to such a thing?
With mortality, you could start over.
You could have a family of your own,
happiness, and peace,
all the things you've long been denied.
Enough!
Tell me where Elijah is, or I will kill you
in this body or any other you choose
to jump into from now
until bloody Armageddon.
I had hoped there was some part of you
that yearned for an end
to your vicious ways,
but if you are determined
to perpetuate the cycles
of violence to which
you have become accustomed,
well, then I'll have to accommodate you.
[Distant wolves baying]
Uh!
Lenore: Apologies for the headache.
Were you dreaming?
I was remembering the day I found out
who my real father was
only hours after Mikael slaughtered him.
My darkest hour.
Had you yourself not killed me
soon thereafter,
I doubt I ever would have recovered.
You woke earlier than I expected.
No matter. It is time.
Time for what?
You said you wanted Elijah.
He's sleeping, chained to the wall
of a tomb in Lafayette cemetery.
I've lifted the spell that hides him.
You are free to take him home.
Now his own mind will work out
his choice for him.
When he wakes, he will
make his own decision.
Every single thing I've said to you tonight
is the truth, Niklaus.
Whether you choose to believe it
is up to you.
[Music playing]
All good, not a werewolf in sight.
I appreciate you being here.
How's blondie doing?
She'll be fine.
Just keep an eye out for wolves, all right?
All right.
Cami: Thank you for coming.
I feel bad about being so abrupt earlier.
I'm sorry. That was my fault.
I was being unprofessional.
My apologies.
You're sorry. I'm sorry.
Let's call it even and have a drink.
Ollie, Ollie, wake up.
What the hell are you doing?
Who the hell is that?
We're here to save your ass.
Please tell me you know where Elijah is.
They know we're here.
[Barking]
Sorry. No time to be gentle.
- Uh!
- Let's go.
Ooh, ha ha!
So how would you diagnose
my friend Klaus, if I may ask?
Well, he's clearly depressive,
low self-esteem, paranoia, impulse control.
Wouldn't you agree?
A lot of it is beyond me,
too much history I don't know,
like all the stuff with his siblings.
How do you manage it?
I beg your pardon?
In one of our first sessions, you mentioned
that you don't get along very well
with your brothers.
Do you stay in touch with them?
In a manner of speaking.
Cami: And your parents,
are they still around?
Am I prying? I'm totally prying.
All this talk about my family
when you so recently
scolded me about boundaries.
Just searching for coping methods,
trying to learn from the master.
Is that so?
You must be lost.
Vampires caught in the quarter
are to be killed on sight.
Go. Run as fast as you can.
Just leave me here. Go.
To hell with that.
If they want a fight,
I'll give them a fight.
No. I came with you to save one of my own,
not watch as you kill scores of them.
Take your friend out the back.
Move as fast as you can.
I'll hold them off here.
Look. If I've offended you, I'm sorry.
You haven't offended me.
It's just, you seem on edge.
Perhaps it's this Klaus business.
Is there something you
haven't shared with me?
[Clears throat]
I guess I'm just nervous around you.
I mean, I keep badgering you
with my dumb questions.
Your questions are quite smart.
They're just personal,
and your interest is unexpected.
Maybe this is my passive-aggressive way
of trying to change the subject
from where I'm afraid you're headed.
Which is?
I think you're going to tell me
to stop spending time with Klaus.
Cami, you're an intelligent woman.
You're articulate, poised.
I think you can tell
for yourself what's best.
Oh!
You know, sometimes I ask myself
why I let people like Klaus into my life.
I have this destructive pattern.
I'm always drawn to the bad boys.
Maybe deep down,
I feel like that's what I deserve.
Hey, Cami, I'm an expert
in unhealthy patterns.
I've broken some of my own,
and I can help you do the same
if you'll let me.
Aagh! Aargh!
Run. Uh!
Aagh!
Agh...
Marcel: Ah...
Aiden: Come on out!
We know you're here.
Why don't you just let us go,
and we can call it a day?
No. I don't think so.
Then we do this the hard way.
Oliver: You idiots.
You're lining up to fight a hybrid?
For what, so you can kill me,
all because some witch gave an order?
I know I ain't innocent,
but I never lost sight
of what I was fighting for.
We were gonna be a pack.
But now...
We are turning on each other,
killing your own people.
We do that,
we're nothing.
You.
- Niklaus...
- No. No.
- You're not real.
- Niklaus...
No! You're a phantom conjured by Esther.
That is all you are.
Mother, stop this charade.
I know that thing is not real.
Look at me, Niklaus.
I am flesh and blood...
Your flesh and blood.
You've been dead 1,000 years.
Through that time,
I lingered on the other side
watching you let the world fall apart
until I woke 4 moons past
in a land of wolves like myself.
No. No. No. You're just in my head.
You're an illusion meant by my mother
to sway me to accept her bargain.
I do not speak for Esther.
I know nothing of her bargains...
But you are my son.
Even if what you say is real...
You are nothing to me.
For all I care, you can crawl back to hell.
You sure this is gonna work?
Klaus' blood is the only
cure for a wolf bite.
Thing is, I'm running low.
So new rule... Don't get bit.
I got bit saving your ass.
Yeah, and you did good, too.
I got to admit, though, when you took off,
I thought you were gone.
All my life, when things got tough,
that's what I would do.
I would run because I never fit in, anyway,
but this place, what you're building here,
it fits.
So I'm in, no running, no matter what.
And thanks for sticking it out.
Yeah.
[Cell phone rings]
I got to take this.
- [Beep]
- You ok?
Cami, on phone: Yeah.
To be honest, not the worst
date I've had in this city.
Yeah. Seemed like you had him
wrapped around your finger
by the time I left.
More than that.
Vincent, Finn, whoever he is,
I think he likes me.
I don't know if I'd call that good news.
Don't you get it? I'm his blind spot.
If he's distracted, he's vulnerable,
which means I can help take him down.
Jackson: Well, you got him. Great.
Where's Ansel?
He was busy being a man.
He should be right behind us.
Jack, I have to tell you...
I already know, Ollie.
You sold me out to Francesca.
Look.
I know that I can't make up for that...
But you need to hear this.
You're the one.
You're the Alpha.
Our people are not meant to be slaves.
You can free them.
[Coughing]
Ollie? Ollie? What is wrong with him?
It's the witches.
Ollie?
They said he only had until midnight.
Stay with me.
[Coughing]
Jack...
Oh...
Wake up, brother.
Elijah...
Lenore: He won't wake, not yet,
which gives you and I one last chance
to discuss my offer.
You promised me Elijah's safe return...
Or was that a lie
just like that ghoulish atrocity
outside claiming to be my father
back from the dead?
Your father's return is real.
I pulled him from the other
side before it collapsed,
left him in the bayou to join the wolves,
and I used the execution of one of his own
to draw him here, where
I knew he'd find you.
To what end besides my torment?
I brought him here to be
the father you never had,
to teach you to become the man
you always longed to be.
Once you are remade as a werewolf,
you can join him.
[Music playing]
His return
changes nothing.
It changes everything.
It is my gift to you, Niklaus.
This offer is your last
chance at salvation.
Reject me now, and you will live out
your endless days unloved and alone.
Do not refuse me out of some ancient spite.
Not spite, hatred,
a pure and perfect hatred that's
greater now than the day
I first took your life.
Why?
After all I've done to explain to you,
why must you persist...
Because you came for my child,
my daughter, your own blood!
You don't understand.
My child!
Niklaus, I had to...
You declared war when you
came after my family, and for that,
I will make you suffer as only I can.
After all, I am my mother's son.
Esther: Please do not do this.
You wanted a family.
Fate said otherwise, and so you came to me,
and for a price, I granted your wish.
Now I must collect.
When Mikael returns
from his journey, I swear...
You will tell him Freya grew ill and died.
No, Dahlia.
You were forced to burn her
body to stop the spread of plague.
Sister, please, I cannot give up my child.
You've already offered me more
than just this one child.
Our bargain was for this firstborn
and every firstborn of each generation
that is to come for as long
as your line shall last.
You do this, if you take my daughter,
I swear to you, I will return
to the black arts, and I will grow in power
as a witch, and I will make you pay!
Your power is nothing against mine.
Foolish girl, you knew
the bargain you made,
and should you defy me,
then I will take all your children,
including little Finn,
even unborn Elijah.
No. Dahlia...
- Mommy...
- Freya. Wait!
Mama!
Help! Mama!
Mama? What happened?
Niklaus... Refused my offer.
Lenore: He's still burdened
with hatred for me...
For what happened to his child.
He's a fool.
Your action saved this family.
If that child had lived...
Dahlia would return...
And she would come for us all.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com