You wanna know what happened
on Shameless last year?
- Brothers...
- Doctors.
- I came out.
- He came out!
[Overlapping chatter]
Fiona!
He's not breathing!
Oh, my God.
He got into my coke.
Fiona Gallagher, you
have the right to remain silent.
I'm not guilty!
Liam almost died!
- How do you plead?
- I'm guilty.
You will be under house arrest
until further notice.
[Beeping]
My liver's finally giving up.
Want me to steal you one
from the grocery store?
Not ready to punch
my ticket yet.
We're not a match.
Even my own daughter
isn't a match.
Daughter?
This is Amy, and that's Gemma.
The nurses just left me like
we know what the fuck
we're doing.
I'm not a little girl.
I'm ready.
Does this make you cray?
- Uh-- you're too young.
- Oh, my God.
- Where the hell were you?
- The army.
Why'd you even go there
in the first place?
Relationship issues.
You're sick of living a lie,
aren't you?
I just want
everybody here to know
I'm fucking gay.
You happy now?
College is a lot
fucking harder than it looks.
You actually have to apply
yourself.
Who exactly is Amanda?
My roommate's
ex-girlfriend
who tried to blow me
in my sleep.
She buys me shit.
Sounds like a keeper.
No more bullshit about baby.
You help.
Yo, it's after 5:00.
- How can you--
- Jesus, leave me alone!
It could be bipolar disease
like our mom.
He may have to be hospitalized.
No fucking way!
He's staying with me.
Fiona never came home.
She violated probation.
I fucked up.
It is my honor
to declare you man and wife.
- I need everybody to move!
- Is he dead?
- He's getting a liver.
- Mrs. Gallagher?
- We're married?
- Let me see my father,
- you bitch.
- No!
You're camping in my yard?
The vacant lot
next to your yard.
Get your stuff.
You're out.
20, 30-- Can't be about how
much they screwed us up anymore.
Sounds kind of like AA.
Attendance is a condition
of my parole.
Come on, let's go.
You gonna be late for work.
Thanks.
Are you gonna go inside?
No.
I'm alive, motherfucker!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
[High Strung's
The Luck You Got playing]
♪ ♪
♪ think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ know that
it's not for naught ♪
♪ you were beaming
once before ♪
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
♪ you're so sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ round up the friends
you got ♪
♪ know that
they're not for naught ♪
♪ you were willing
once before ♪
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
♪ you're so sure of ♪
[Christian & The 2120s'
Smile At Trouble playing]
♪ ♪
- Sheils.
- Hmm?
What's he doing in our bed?
Who?
Him. His pecker's poking me
in the back.
Oh, Sammi picked up some guy
at the Alibi last night
and kicked Chuckie
out of her trailer.
Karen's room?
I tucked him in there.
He must've crawled in
in the middle of the night.
Well, he's got to uncrawl.
- [Grunts]
- [Thud]
Ow.
Oh, Chuckie, why didn't you
stay in Karen's room?
I had a bad dream.
Well, you might as well get up
and get ready for school.
And you mister,
meds and vitals.
Can't.
Got to work on my project.
Busy.
Frank, meds and vitals now!
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
[Cheers and applause]
Why they tearing it down?
Asbestos.
[Cheers and applause]
All right, I'm leaving.
I've seen enough.
Wait, give me a ride home
on the back of that thing.
Can't. Got to run an errand
then going to school.
- I'm not.
- It's the last day.
- You have to go.
- Why,
so I can figure out how
to flunk sixth grade again?
Yeah, I'll do that next year.
Come on, just give me a ride.
You can't even fit on my bike
with that giant gimp leg.
These crutches
are killing my wrists.
I can't even jack off
that well.
Should've thought about that
before you busted up
your ankle
on your stupid skateboard.
See you.
Looks pretty good, huh?
It's perfect...
Except for one thing.
What?
- Uh-oh.
- Mm-hmm.
Looks like we're stuck in here
- forever.
- Yep.
I guess we-- we trapped?
- Yeah.
- No way out.
That's right, we're trapped.
You're never gonna
see any one of
Patsy's pies ever again.
Oh, Liam,
- this is our new home now.
- Okay.
[Laughing]
[Mellow rock music]
♪ ♪
I'm gonna get the ladder.
Mm-hmm.
Don't twist an ankle.
Please.
Don't worry.
- Ah!
- [Laughing]
[Screaming]
- Impressive.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
You ready to fill
this sucker, Liam?
Yeah!
- Right on, here you go.
- Yep.
All right, attach this end
to the fire hydrant.
How are we gonna
open the valve?
Gallagher ingenuity.
You got one
of those lying around?
You don't?
Come on.
All right.
Here, step aside.
This goes here.
- You want to help?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, watch your fingers.
Here it comes.
Ooh.
- [Laughing]
- [Screaming]
No, no, now, come on.
I'm your fucking boss.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, no, no.
I may not have hired you,
but I sure as hell
can fire you.
- No, no, no.
- Yes.
- [Screaming]
- [Laughing]
Hold it-- Give me that.
Give me that.
No, no.
[Screaming]
Sean, no, no.
Ah! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna hurt you.
- [Screaming]
- Boom! Boom, I say, boom!
- How did you get so wet?
- [Liam screeching]
- Don't you got to go?
- I do.
In fact, I got to go
take my son to school.
Come on, I got to get Will.
All right,
tell him I say "Hi."
I will, I will.
I'll see you for dinner.
- Okay.
- All right.
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
[Cheering]
We get it, morons.
School's out.
- You're not even packed?
- You look cute.
It's summer.
You have a suitcase?
- It's right there.
- Louis Vuitton?
- No, it's a Gucci.
- What are you doing?
I'm filling out an application
to be an RA in the fall.
- Really?
- "Resident Asshole."
- [Laughter]
- Why not, you know?
It's free room and board,
all the beer I can confiscate.
Well, you could just stay with
me at my off-campus apartment.
My dad's paying.
That makes it free.
You mean, like, live together?
Well, isn't that
what we've been doing
for the last four months?
Yeah, but you got
your own dorm room.
I'm gonna miss my plane.
Look, have a good summer,
man, yeah?
You too, dude.
It's been real.
Let's get out of here.
It's the only one I could find
in all the crap out in the yard.
Put it in the window.
You want scrambled or fried?
I like those puffy eggs
you make.
Nika, we got baked eggs today.
Food is food.
- [Baby cries]
- All the same to me.
Why's the baby crying?
Look at you.
Ooh, diaper full of poop.
- [Gasps] Da?
- Oh...
- Is that what happened?
- [Speaking Russian]
Don't want him covered
in baby shit
on his first day of work.
We have baked eggs in the oven.
- Hey, moron, truck ready?
- Yeah.
You stare any longer,
I chop your dicks off.
Time to go play nicey-nice
with surrogates,
meet them at the ultrasound.
They still think
you're a kindergarten teacher?
Wheels on the bus
go round and round.
Amazing what people
with money will pay for.
After ultrasound,
I go open Rub 'n' Tug.
You feed Yev breakfast,
and you go to grocery store.
Got it.
Hey, Patel hit
one of the girls yesterday,
left without pay.
- Dry cleaner Patel?
- Uh-huh.
I'll take care of it.
Let's go.
No, no, no, guns.
Look, no hardware.
It's not that kind of job.
We're respectable now,
remember?
Do you want this?
I'll meet you at the place
later, okay?
I'll be there.
Better be.
Mm.
What the hell?
I'm in here.
Gotta pee bad.
What's the point?
Nothing's happening anyway.
Are you taking
your medications?
Yes!
[Chuckie urinating]
What are those for?
Anti-rejection,
ulcers,
hypertension,
high blood pressure,
depression, headaches,
diuretic,
and apparently I need one
for constipation now too.
A lot of pee.
Held it all night.
Are you weighing yourself?
I don't hear the scale.
I hear the scale now.
155.
It says 147.
- You lie to your notebook?
- Your grandmother
doesn't need to know
I've lost some weight.
- Blood pressure.
- Oh, Jesus!
[Crying]
Oh, why can't you girls just
make this easy for me just once?
Girl, here, give me that thing.
Here.
Mama, stop.
I'm not a cow.
Look, you got to grab this tit,
and you got to massage it
till you get the milk ducts
flowing, girl.
I know how to do it.
Stop.
How are my four favorite
ladies doing and my little man?
Well, I got them big,
brown flying saucers working.
That's right, Dominick,
our job here is done.
- Bye-bye, D.
- Say, "Bye-bye."
Bye-bye, D.
Ow. Amy,
you biting me again.
What are you doing?
Do not hit our daughter.
- It's just the nipple.
- Just the nipple?
Let's see how you like it.
- Ow! What are you doing?
- [Crying]
- Now look what you did.
- What I did?
You're the one titty twisting
and moving her all around.
- Shh.
- Don't shush me.
Your turn.
Hi, Gemma.
Here we go, baby.
We're gonna be good.
Let's try it, okay?
You gonna do better
than your sister?
You okay?
She hit you?
- Mommy hit you?
- Okay.
- Ow! Now she's biting me.
- V!
No, I'm done.
No more breast feeding.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm done.
The milk bar is closed.
We can go to formula.
No. No, no, no,
absolutely not.
We are not doing formula.
They will grow up with asthma,
and be short,
and have no friends.
Kev, kids in this neighborhood
are raised on Kool-Aid
and powdered milk.
Formula's a step up.
Gemma hasn't pooped
in five days.
Formula will make it worse.
Oh, God!
I'm just so sick of this.
It's "Baby" this
and "Baby" that.
You get to go to work all day,
and I'm stuck here with "Whiny"
- and "Screamy."
- [Crying]
Just-- Here,
she's driving me crazy.
I'm done.
I need some air.
[Crying]
What just happened?
Hey, sunshine.
Liam and I are meeting Ian.
You want to come
for a run with us?
No, I don't want to go
for a run. I can't go for a run.
I probably won't be able to go
for a run for another 18 years,
not that I even ever went
for a run, but if I wanted to,
these milk jugs
would give me two black eyes.
Rough morning?
I am covered in puke
and piss and vomit.
The other day I rubbed my eye,
and I realized
that there was baby poop
underneath my fingernail.
I want my boobs back.
I want my life back.
I want my husband back.
You haven't gotten laid
lately, have you?
You're one to talk.
You even fucked Sean yet?
Nah, just friends.
I'm too gun-shy
after going to jail.
What's your excuse?
I'm too tired.
Kev's too tired.
One kid is screaming.
The other one is colicky.
I don't even know
what colic is,
but everybody says it.
Go home, take a shower,
put on something slinky,
and seduce your man.
A little sex is gonna put
everything into perspective.
Ugh.
I'm not in the mood.
Fine!
I will go home
and fuck my husband.
Maybe with a little more
enthusiasm?
Sure you don't want to take
my Beamer for the summer?
And what, park it
in my neighborhood?
Yeah, not unless you want it
back fully stripped.
Too much of a commitment, huh?
Off-campus apartment, car.
I got you something.
Thank you.
- It's a watch.
- Fossil.
They tried to get me to engrave
something queer like,
"Until The End Of Time."
Or
"Make Every Second Count."
Are you gonna date
other people over the summer?
Don't know.
You?
I don't know.
I guess it's settled then.
I guess so.
Bye.
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
- Here.
- Oh, thank you, Frank.
I need a clamp or something.
Look at you.
You've done a wonderful job
maintaining your weight, Frank.
Yeah, a regular blimp.
How are your headaches?
You can't feel a person's
headache by touching his head.
[Chuckles]
That's true.
How's the depression?
The doctor says
exercise could help.
- I could do it with you.
- Sheils, Sheils, stop.
Every morning, okay?
Okay.
That's what I need.
I made breakfast.
No, do we have any bacon?
I need it for my project.
No, just French toast.
Would that work?
I'm not hungry.
Are you experiencing
a loss of appetite?
No, I-- Christ!
Oh.
What happened
to that socket wrench?
Frank, what-- what is
this secret project of yours?
Well, it wouldn't be
a secret if I told you.
I like French toast.
Oh. Ah, well,
you know what?
I bet your mom
is home making breakfast.
Why don't you go see?
- Morning, dad.
- [Sighs]
Want me to go
get you medications?
Oh, he did that ages ago.
I could help you
with your blood pressure,
take your temperature.
Done and done by those of us
who didn't have a man
in our trailer
- and kicked their son out.
- [Knocking]
That's Rinaldo.
I left him alone in the RV to do
his morning constitutional.
Come in!
Dad, come say hi.
- Hey, babe.
- Mm-hmm.
Dad, you know Rinaldo.
- Frank.
- Hi.
Well, we don't have
enough food for your friend.
Oh, that's all right.
I'll just take Java.
You can have some of mine.
- Are you my father?
- Don't think so, kiddo.
[Whispers]
Frank! Frank!
You have got to do something
about your daughter.
She's dying
for parental boundaries.
Dad, can you take
your grandson to school today?
Uh, can't.
Work.
I could come down
and help you--
Guess Rinaldo and me
will have to find
something else to do then.
- Oh.
- [Laughter]
Uh, hello?
Um, hi.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
Um, I know that you're acting
out your father issues
by dying your hair
with that trashy peroxide
and dry humping
that man on my couch,
but I don't think it's nice
to expose your child
to this behavior.
You're not my mother.
- [Porcelain shattering]
- [Gasps]
My hummel!
I could go for a hammer.
It's a hummel, not a hammer.
You know how
expensive this was?
[Giggling]
What's in here?
You know what?
Why don't we, um--
Why don't I just
take you to school?
- [Moaning]
- Mm.
A yoga studio
in this neighborhood?
Probably just a front for
some drug laundering operation.
Hey, did you have a chance
to call that doctor?
- Which one?
- From the clinic.
No, no.
I'm good.
Well, probably the best time
to go when you're feeling good.
- Why is that?
- Just to have a plan of action
for when things
aren't so good again.
Just a one-time thing.
Don't you want to have
a doctor tell you that?
Just give you some meds,
do a few tests.
Look, I don't have
what Monica has.
I know.
It just seemed similar.
Mood swings, depression.
There's too much coke
down at the club.
I mean, that shit makes you
crazy-- highs and lows.
I've cut way back.
Good. Good.
Odds are one of us
is gonna get it, right?
It's not our fault, just fucking
genetics Russian roulette.
I'm betting it'll be Carl.
Race you to the lamp post!
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
Um, excuse me,
may I give you one of these?
Uh, no, thank you.
I already accepted Jesus
as my lord and savior.
Try three houses down.
They're Muslim.
[Knocking]
Good job, Debs.
Yeah.
We said a dollar, right?
Yeah, if I were still
five years old.
10 bucks, cough it up.
All right.
But for this amount,
I'm gonna need
your help tonight.
Can't. Family dinner
at Fiona's restaurant.
Lip finished his first year
of college.
Hey.
I'll be there.
I don't think you're invited.
Do you know if we have
any bacon at home?
Maybe.
What are you doing down there?
You'll know soon enough.
Meet me in the park later.
We'll go to the
restaurant together.
[Both moaning]
Oh, daddy, you caught me.
Am I in trouble?
Hey, babe, you feeling better?
Shower did me good.
What you doing?
Just online before
I have to go to work.
I've got something better you
can do before you go to work.
Ooh, @bensmommy
just responded to my question.
What?
Yeah, I'm in a Mommy
And Me chatroom,
and I'm asking these women
how to get the twins
to stop biting your nipples.
I know how to get 'em
to stop-- Feed 'em formula.
It says here
that if you rub your nipples
with a loofah 20 minutes a day,
- it'll toughen them up.
- Ken.
I'm gonna ask them how to get
Gemma to start pooping.
- Kevin Ball.
- Yeah, what?
Put the computer down
right now.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait-- wait a minute.
[Distant crying]
- You hear Amy crying?
- She'll calm herself.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
I read it in a Mommy
And Me chatroom.
Are you fucking with me?
A little.
But I'd like to fuck
with you more.
Mm. Oh.
Yes, please.
Mm.
- What are you doing?
- What?
You're not even getting hard.
I-- I don't know
what's wrong with me.
You're more into the babies
than you are me.
- No, it's not true.
- I bet you
if they were here sucking
your dick you'd be into it.
Jesus, V, do not talk
about our angels like that.
You'd rather be on a website
than let me suck your dick?
Ugh. I'm sorry that
I care about their well-being.
- What about my well-being?
- Look, we had two babies.
Life is different now.
I'll show you different.
What are you doing?
I'm going to work at the Alibi.
You can stay here.
- What?
- Good luck taking care
of your babies.
And we need formula!
[Pop/Rock music]
♪ live, live life ♪
♪ reconcile you to the night ♪
♪ going out having fun ♪
♪ yeah, this is
gonna be the one ♪
♪ the one time it feels right ♪
♪ going naked
take it all tonight ♪
♪ come on, come in the fight ♪
♪ yeah, you know you wanna
come on, come on tonight ♪
♪ yeah, we know we wanna
come on and feel alive ♪
♪ 'cause we're going out, yeah ♪
♪ we're going out tonight ♪
♪ ♪
♪ 'cause we're going out, yeah ♪
♪ we're going out tonight ♪
♪ la, la, la, la, la
la, la, la ♪
♪ la, la, la, la ♪
♪ again take a ride ♪
♪ like a team taking sides ♪
♪ rolling up having fun ♪
♪ yeah, you're gonna
be the one ♪
♪ the one spark to ignite ♪
♪ going naked
take it all tonight ♪
♪ tonight ♪
♪ la la la la la la la la ♪
♪ la la la la la la la la la ♪
♪ ♪
Hey, careful
with those barcaloungers.
You got it, boss.
Looks like you have everything
under control here.
Yes, ma'am.
We're gonna head
up to the Bridgeport house.
Okay. Shouldn't take us
much longer.
We'll meet you there
in a few hours.
You will be careful
with the piano?
Absolutely.
Hey, tie those down.
We don't want
them moving around.
[Mellow rock music]
♪ ♪
Bye, little guy.
Debs, Carl, what's going on?
I hate you stupid bitches!
Well, how was your last day
of school, Debs?
Is there anything you want to
- talk about?
- No.
Yo, Fuck Wad.
Hey, what's going on, Stumpy?
- I got some new piercings.
- Yeah, I can see that.
And I picked up some herb
for our guys.
- You want to come?
- Eh...
Yeah, sure. Look,
I'm just gonna be over there
if you need anything, okay?
Look who I found
trolling the streets.
Yo.
- There he is.
- Oh, there he is.
Lip, heard you been
up at college or some shit?
Yeah, yeah.
I've been over there a while.
What's going on with you guys?
- Same old crap.
- Yeah.
Did you bang a bunch
of coeds up at school?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, you still
at your dad's chop shop, Wayne?
Ah, when he gets the work.
Towelheads are getting most
of the scrap now.
- Stumpy knocked up Gloria Hu.
- Oh, shit.
She squirted a kid out,
like, two months ago.
I ain't convinced
it's mine though.
I'm saving up
to get one of those DNA tests.
Right.
- Look at that fancy watch.
- Ooh.
They giving those out
up at college?
No, I swiped it
from a kid's dorm room.
It's the rich prick's fault
for leaving his door unlocked.
Oh, look at this pretty lady,
some dust my uncle
scored for me.
Put that shit on the weed.
Holding out on us.
Yo, guys,
I got to split, all right?
- No, no, come on.
- Hey, it's good shit,
did some last night
at Lauren Chambers' party.
No, I'll hang later.
I haven't been home yet.
All right, pussy,
see you later.
Hook that shit up, Stump.
Here's your check.
Be right back
to take your order.
Gonna have your food right out.
Hey, Angela.
- Hi, Fiona.
- You know what you want?
I do.
I'll take the blueberry pie
this time.
You got it.
Cup of coffee?
Yep.
How's life?
Been seeing anybody?
Nah.
I'm boring these days.
- Doubt that.
- [Laughs]
Polo, can you get Angela
a cup of coffee
- and a slice of blueberry?
- Yes, Miss Fiona.
Adam, I swear I ordered it.
It's on the check,
chicken parmesan.
No, come on.
The customer's already
so pissed at me.
What is going on?
Here, have my chicken parm.
Can you make another one
fast, please?
Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
That oriental chick, Angela,
just asked me
how much you make here.
- I don't know what her deal is.
- I do.
She wants some Fiona pie.
Is everybody okay?
Wanda's sexually harassing me.
Well, I'll spank her later.
Her?
What about me?
Uh, the guys from Jezebel
just came in.
- They asked for you. Table 13.
- Oh, goodie.
Well, if you won't spank me,
maybe their lead singer will.
Here you go, cheeseburger,
spaghetti and meatballs
for the gentleman.
I'll get you another iced tea.
Okay, thanks.
Left you a hundred bucks again?
- Yeah.
- Got to send her to my section
at least once.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
- Hey, Fiona.
- Hey, darling.
- Leftover pie?
- Thank you very much.
You are so welcome.
Can you stare a little harder?
- Get back to work.
- [Scoffs]
Hello?
[Sighs]
[Sniffs]
Oh, God damn it!
What kind of a woman has sex
in another woman's living room?
For God sakes!
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
Oh... no... she... didn't!
♪ the king of Babel
took a fall ♪
♪ while his subjects
climbed the walls ♪
♪ all his horses and his men ♪
My sex toys?
Ah!
♪ Couldn't put him
together again ♪
♪ I'm damaged, damaged
damaged into ♪
♪ damaged, damaged
♪ love ♪
[Gasps]
Frank!
- Frank!
- I told you,
I'm not ready
to share my project yet, Sheils.
It's not about your project.
It's about Sammi.
Ever since you got better,
she is really acting out.
A grown woman
can do what she likes.
Well, she has real issues.
I mean, if you don't start
playing daddy,
things are only
gonna get worse.
I'm busy.
Got a lot of work.
Well, Frank,
if you're not gonna do anything
about it, then I don't want her
and that Chuckie thing
in my house anymore.
Well, fine.
Whatever.
Really?
That's it?
Sure.
What do I care?
Oh, well, good.
I'm glad we had this talk.
[Muzak playing]
♪ ♪
What's going on, Ian?
How you doing?
Hey, Kev.
What's up?
Just looking for something
to get Gemma to go poop.
Oh, hey, Liam.
Hey, yev, uh,
whatever your name is.
You got any suggestions?
Pureed pears and glycerin
suppository work for this guy.
Diaper aisle.
Thanks, man.
Hey, let me ask you something.
You still breast feed?
I mean, well, not you,
but I mean, you know, Svetlana.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's into it.
It's, uh, good
for the baby's immune system.
I knew it.
Plus, it's free, right?
Forgot that argument.
Are you cool with this dude
cruising you?
Yeah, I'm fine.
All right, well, let me know
if you want me to rough him up.
Okay.
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
- About time.
- Fuck you.
I didn't know she had a piano.
You know the deal.
You got five minutes to look.
It's three bedrooms,
some den thing.
It's a 60615 zip code.
It's good shit.
How much for the barcaloungers?
I got to do this
with you again?
It's not a fucking
antique road show.
You bid on the whole thing
or nothing at all.
Shit.
I like barcaloungers.
Great, buy the truck
and get your barcaloungers.
Think I'm gonna stand
around here selling each piece
for 5 bucks
like it's a fucking yard sale?
Give you 4 grand for the lot.
- 4.
- I'll give you $4,500.
- Anyone else?
- 5 grand.
$5,300.
I want those barcaloungers.
- Yeah, we know.
- Nah, I'm out.
Yeah, me too.
Sold to the man
with the barcalounger fetish.
- It's all there?
- It's there.
All right.
Need a ride?
You're late.
Grocery store was busy.
Come on, V,
free pour like Kev does.
That's why
the bar's losing money.
Yum, it tastes just like
tonic water.
Lip.
Hey, V.
- Hey, Tommy.
- Hey, Lip.
Sammi.
When did Sammi start
hanging out at the Alibi?
That girl is hornier than
a three-peckered billy goat.
[Giggling]
Stop it.
So what brings you here,
college boy?
Well, I came to get
the details about the job.
Yeah, what job's that?
Hey, get college a beer here,
- will you, V?
- Demo'ing.
- Are you still doing that?
- Yep.
About to start a big cleanup.
They knocked over Sunny Days
on Halsted this morning.
Great. I'm in.
Like hell you are.
Well, you promised me a job.
Yeah?
How drunk was I?
I-- I need the money
for school, okay?
I don't hire college pussies
like you.
Try the Gap on Michigan.
Too late in the summer
to get another job.
We had a deal.
You're an idiot.
I'm just busting your balls.
Fuck you.
First day of work
you'll be crying like a baby,
- begging to go home by lunch.
- Yeah, we'll see.
Hey, be sure to write
your blood type on your boots
for when you sever a limb.
Oh, boots?
I was gonna wear flip-flops.
[Laughing]
I'm gonna enjoy fucking
with you all summer.
Welcome home, Lip.
Thanks, V.
[Sarcastically]
"Flip-flops."
How do you not have
any tattoos?
I don't believe you
for a second.
Well, it's true.
Maybe I'll let you do
a full body scan sometime.
Come see our show tonight, huh?
- No, I wish I could.
I turn into a pumpkin at 9:00.
What if I come by after my gig?
You text me...
if you're feeling randy.
Okay.
[Funk music]
♪ ♪
Girl, Davis is all over you.
Dude is fire, and that accent?
Ugh, falls in the bad choice
category.
I should know.
God, you scared me.
- That's for you.
- Thanks, Fiona.
Yeah, see you, Fiona.
- Bye, guys.
- Take care.
Maybe I'll see you later, huh?
Mm.
Both: "Maybe I'll see
you later."
Did he leave a good tip?
Wait, he only gave you the tip?
He didn't stick
the whole thing in?
Be careful.
He's a musician.
You never know where
that tip's been.
- Aw, are you jealous, Sean?
- Who's coming with me?
- I'm heading out to the meeting.
- Yeah, I'm coming.
No, I can't.
Working double.
Fiona?
Uh, nah, family's coming
in for early dinner.
I'm gonna stick around
and wait on them.
Well, I'll be back later
to say hi and meet Lip.
Okay, great.
Hey.
Why'd you want to meet here?
Get me some
of those wood chips.
Would you?
Put them in here.
For your work project?
Yeah.
Why can't you do this yourself?
A grown man
digging at the feet of kids
looks a little pervy,
don't you think?
This is gonna cost
you more money.
What you got?
That's good.
Come on.
We're gonna be late for dinner.
Thank you.
Okay, see, Chuckie,
it's not that I don't
want you at my house anymore,
or your mom, it's just that--
Look, this is where you belong.
This is your house,
and you're welcome to come
and visit sometimes,
but you have
to call first, okay?
You have to ask your mom
and call first.
And sometimes I'll say yes,
and sometimes I'll say no,
but that's
just how families work.
See, there's boundaries that
aren't supposed to be crossed,
and somehow your mother
just never learned that.
But that's the good news
is I'm here to teach you.
But what if mom brings home
another man from the bar?
You just put a pillow
over your head
and wait for her
to be finished.
Okay, bye, Chuckie.
Chuckie, why don't you just
lock the door?
Chuckie, lock the goddamn door.
[Click]
Jesus.
- Yay.
All: - To summer.
And to Lip's first year
of college,
may you all follow
in his footsteps.
All: - To Lip.
- Yes, thank you, guys.
Frank.
To Lip.
You sure you should be
drinking, Frank?
You think a brand-new,
untainted liver's
- gonna stop him?
- After extensive research
and weeks of testing,
I've determined
my liver can support
one beer a day.
I am now a cheap date.
I'm buzzed already like
an anemic ten-year-old girl.
Who's ready for pie?
- I want to taste cherry pie.
- Ugh.
Any more of that
Salisbury steak?
Yeah, if I pay for it.
I tell you what,
get me an order,
- and we'll call it even.
- Call what even?
Her trying to kill my son
with cocaine.
Douche bag,
why would you say that?
Why are you even here, Frank?
Just don't.
- I'll just get him some more.
- To go.
I got to get back to work.
- I don't want any pie.
- What's going on with you?
First you're stabbing dolls
in the face,
now you're all mopey?
Holly and Ellie
aren't talking to me anymore.
- It's like I'm invisible.
- I hate it
- when teenage skanks do that.
- What do you mean?
Same thing happened to me
with Heidi Mitchell
and Donna Alexander.
Me too.
Leah March and Jean Kolb.
Really?
Why?
Who knows?
Jealousy, periody.
Two weeks later,
they started talking to me again
like nothing ever happened.
- Same with Heidi and Donna.
- It's not fair.
They don't get to do that.
I'm never being friends
with Holly and Ellie again.
- Screw those bitches.
- Yeah, screw those bitches.
Screw those bitches.
Sounds like
you're having fun here.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- What's up, man?
- Hey, Sean.
- Good pie, dude.
- Well, I'm glad you like it.
- You're Lip?
- Yeah, yeah, nice to meet you.
Hey, what's going on?
Sean.
Thanks for giving this one
a job.
- Oh, my pleasure.
- It's so good of you
to hire a felon.
This is my father, Frank.
Hey, Frank.
Salisbury steak, Miss Fiona?
Right here.
- That about explain everything?
- Pretty much.
I got some paperwork
in the back.
It was good to see you all.
Nice to meet you, Lip.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
What was that little squeeze?
- What?
- He just squeezed your arm.
The two of them are like that
all day with each other.
- We are not.
- Really?
Bathroom.
Hey,
he ever go see that doctor?
Nah, he refuses.
We should talk to Mickey.
[Funk music]
♪ ♪
Now, the players
in the black and white,
they're The White Sox.
That's our team.
And the pussies
in the gray and blue,
they're The Twins.
- We hate The Twins.
- [Crying]
No, no, no, no, no.
Not the baby girl twins,
the player twins.
- [Game plays on TV]
- [Knocking]
- Good evening, sir.
- Oh, Jehovahs. Not interested.
No, no, no.
We're not Jehovahs.
Everyone keeps thinking that.
Your clothes.
We're from Rothchild Realty.
Would you be interested
in selling this house?
You want to buy this dump?
Redfin named this
one of the top five
up and coming
neighborhoods in Chicago.
- [Phone ringing]
- Hey, I gotta get that.
- Oh, can we leave our card?
- Yeah-huh.
- [Phone ringing]
- [Game continues on TV]
Hey, babe.
- Hi, how's it going?
- Good, good.
- How's it going over there?
- Good.
Mom's here
if you need her to come help.
- Hey, Kev.
- Hey, no, no, no, no.
I got everything under control.
Hey, I wanted to tell you,
I talked to a woman
in My Mommy And Me chatroom.
She said I have
madonna whore complex.
- What?
- Yeah,
it's why I
didn't want to have sex.
Wait, you calling me a whore?
He calling you a whore?
No, I'm not calling
you a whore.
I mean, you used to be a whore
which I liked a lot, trust me,
but now you're a madonna,
like the Virgin Mary Madonna.
He's saying
I'm like Madonna now.
- What, like Vogue Madonna?
- The Virgin Mary-- that's
- why he don't want to fuck me.
- Oh.
V, why you telling everybody
our business?
You tell everyone in your
Mommy chatroom our business.
I don't know them.
There's no guarantee
that they're even women.
Ooh, I got to go.
I got to go.
I'll see you later.
Is that face
what I think it is?
[Inhales deeply]
Oh,
is that the face
of what I think it is,
of someone who pooped.
Yes!
Poop, there it is.
Yeah, that's my girl.
Oh, my-- That's my girl.
What are you doing tonight?
I got to look for an apartment.
Judge isn't gonna let
me have Hannah back if I'm still
in that shithole motel.
What about you?
Gonna see Davis?
I should.
I need to get laid,
or maybe I shouldn't
'cause I need to get laid.
I don't know.
Knock, knock.
You guys dressed?
Yeah, but we'll get undressed
if you're coming in.
- Is this your family's check?
- Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I don't see
any pie on it.
You charge them for it?
Family discount?
Come on, you throw most
of the pie out at the end
of the night,
especially the peach.
Nobody likes the peach.
Don't be talking
about my grandma's peach pie.
Sorry, Grandma Pierce.
Oh, it's Grandma Johnson
on my mom's side.
You can cough up
the $12.99.
Your grandma really
makes that pie, hmm?
How come I never knew that?
She's dead.
It's from Costco.
It's frozen,
but you still owe me.
Can I give it to you in trade?
I take cash or cash.
Next time,
I consider it stealing.
Won't be a next time.
Good.
Don't be taking advantage
of me because we're friends.
Sorry, boss.
Ooh, sorry, boss.
[Laughing]
You're gonna pay for this.
You locked me
out of my own house.
Since when did my house
become your house?
Since you married my father.
You're a 45-year-old
woman.
Your father's house
is not your house!
- I'm 33.
- 33?
Well, you could have fooled me.
Whatever.
Act it then!
Frank, did you see
what she did?
She crow-barred the new locks
off the door.
Grandma Sheila said we should
respect people's boundaries.
Breaking and entering,
are you out of your mind?
- That's what families do...
- I'm almost finished
with my project downstairs.
You want to see it?
- Sure.
- They assault each other.
No, they don't.
[Argument continues, muffled]
- You ready?
- Uh-huh.
I give you Frank's
Milk Of The Gods,
my contribution to mankind,
the strongest beer ever made.
Wow.
I'm telling you, I have
a new lease on life, Fred.
This liver of mine may only last
six or eight years.
I have no control over time
anymore,
but this-- this will live on.
It's spectacular.
They can try
to stop me from drinking,
but they can't stop me
from helping others to enjoy
the finest brew ever made.
With its woody,
bacony flavor...
Frank's Milk Of The Gods
will redefine the way
people enjoy their grain-based
fermented beverages.
But don't get me wrong,
my intentions
are not all altruistic.
If I can only enjoy one beer
a day,
why not make it 130 proof?
Can I taste it?
Oh, it has yet
to kiss my lips, my friend,
but the time is upon us.
Let's take our business
elsewhere to some place
more righteous than here.
Beautiful.
[Knocking]
"Sell your home
at a premium price."
Jeez, how much
are they possibly offering
for in this neighborhood?
20 dollar make you holler.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Can we talk to you for a sec?
Does no one
use a fucking phone anymore?
Honey, he's gonna
close in five minutes.
Yes, I'm going!
I'm going!
I got to run an errand.
You want to talk,
we got to walk.
Well, how far are you going?
I-- I've got a ticking time bomb
on my ankle.
Just across the alley.
What you want to talk about?
Can you get Ian
to see that doctor
- I told you about?
- He's not sick anymore.
- But he will be.
- You don't know that.
If he's anything
like our mother, we do.
What's this fucking
shrink gonna do to him anyway?
Mental health assessment.
Prescribe him some meds.
Yeah, see,
you said that before.
That's the fucked up part.
Why are we giving him meds
if he's not sick?
It helps the mania
not be so crazy.
Yeah, and he won't
be depressed as long.
Like last time?
All right, hold up.
Hold up.
Stay here, all right?
Yo, brown ass.
- Oh, shit.
- "Oh, shit," is right.
You like hitting girls, huh?
- Come here.
- [Whack]
Uhh! What the--
Ugh!
- [Grunting]
- Curry says what?
- This is his errand?
- Stop it!
You ever hit one of
my girls again,
I'm not gonna go so easy on you,
do you hear me?
Yes.
Good.
Hey!
Mrs. Patel,
can you jerk your fucking
husband off once in a while
so he doesn't come back
to my Rub 'n' Tug ever again?
All right, let's say he gets,
like, depressed, or manic,
or whatever the fuck,
how do we know it's not
just from living
in this shithole ghetto?
- He has signs of bipolar.
- Like?
Recklessness, impulsiveness.
Fast-talking,
barely sleeping.
Hyper sexuality.
Hyper se--
You mean horny?
What 17-year-old gay kid
isn't horny?
Kev?
Kevin?
You awake?
[Mellow rock music]
♪ ♪
Ow.
[Whistle]
Yo, Gallagher, you up there?
We got chronic.
Get your ass down here.
- Ah, he's not home.
- Let's get out of here.
- Ow!
- [Laughing]
♪ ♪
_
Hey, you awake?
I am now.
- I can't sleep.
- [Chuckling]
Again?
- Whoa.
- Why?
You got a problem
with that? Huh?
No, I don't need to now
and not at all
'cause you're so tough--
Come here.
Wake up. Wake up.
[Laughing]
You dog, you're going down.
You are going down, army.
Come here, army.
I wanted him to fail.
- I thought he'd be overwhelmed.
- And?
Jackass is a better mom
than me.
[Phone chimes]
_
Who's that?
Nobody.
You know what we should do?
Pool party!
What's going on?
Go tell your brothers.
We're gonna party up
Gallagher style.
Hey, it's me.
Pool's ready.
Bring Will over.
What time is it now?
It's 12:03 AM.
So it's technically tomorrow.
Yeah, uh-huh.
My quota resets.
We can drink.
Frank's Milk Of The Gods.
[Burping]
[Coughing]
[Mumbling]
Oh, Jesus.
[Coughing]
All right, Carl, get him!
I've got a day
full of rage inside of me.
- Get her now!
- Take him down.
- Go get him, Debs, get him!
- All you all must die!
[Screaming]
- Oh, yeah.
- [Laughing]
- Oh, hey, now.
- You guys are cheaters.
Look who's a sore sport.
Look who's madly in love.
You got room for one more?
All: Ian!
- I got your text.
- Where's Mickey?
I wore him out.
All right, come on,
it's our turn in the pool.
- Let's go, Will. Are you ready?
- Go, Liam, go.
Okay, Will.
- Come on.
- Liam.
All right, Liam,
you're going down.
Hey, shut up down there!
Oh, you shut up!
It's summer!
[Vocalizing]
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
♪ hey, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ uh-huh
hey ♪
Ow.
The fuck?
Woman:
Please, don't move.
Huh?
Where are my clothes?
We found you like this.
Came out to draw the summer
flowers, found you instead.
Oh, Jesus.
Your body, it is so beautiful.
You're perfect.
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
♪ gonna
gonna make you feel good ♪
♪ good, good ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ hey, uh-huh ♪
♪ feel good ♪
[Vocalizing]
♪ all right ♪
♪ make you feel
make you feel good ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ feel good yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ make you feel good, uh-huh ♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪