When I returned
to Baker Street
from a short holiday
in the spring of 1891,
I had seen little of Holmes
for some time.
I saw in the papers
that he had been engaged
by the French government upon
a matter of supreme importance
but I could hardly foresee
that it would have
so violent
a consequence.
It lies with me now
to tell for the first time
what took place between
Mr. Sherlock Holmes
and Professor Moriarity
in that fateful year.
Ah, Mrs. Hudson
has Mr. Holmes returned?
Oh, he has indeed.
He came in early.
Must have been
before 7:00.
"Morning Mrs. Hudson"
he says,
"Have you anything nice
for my breakfast?"
as if he hadn't been away
for four months.
You could have knocked me down
with a feather.
And he's gone
out again I take it?
Yes, yes he had his breakfast
and then he went out again
just after
his visitor left.
Visitor?
An elderly
gentleman.
They had words.
I didn't like the look of him,
not at all I didn't.
He had a face like, like
the wrath of God
or should I say
the devil.
Indeed.
Should we open a bottle
of the best claret
to celebrate
Mr. Holmes' return?
Why not?
Very good.
Thank you,
Mrs. Hudson.
I learned later that Holmes
had survived three attempts
on his life
that very day.
But as I waited for him
to reappear
Baker Street looked to me
as safe and secure as ever.
Holmes you...
Wait, wait.
What is it?
Air guns, a rather special
air gun in fact.
Watson would you have
any objection to drawing
the blinds casually as if
you were alone in this room?
Watson I think you know me
well enough to understand
that I am by no means
a nervous man.
But it is stupidity
rather than courage
to refuse to recognize danger
when it is close upon you.
Damn!
Watson,
might I have a match?
Holmes,
you're hurt.
Scratches, nothing,
nothing to signify.
You don't look well
Holmes.
Well I have been using myself
rather too freely.
I have been somewhat
pressed but late.
How pressed?
Well as I am unable to leave
this room until after dark
and then most likely
on the way that I came,
we do have some time
on our hands.
Also I owe you an explanation
for my unceremonious departure
the last time
that we met.
I'll take some notes
if I may?
Oh, by all means.
This case...
This case,
it is unique
in the annuals
of crime.
You will recall that it was
a cold morning early in the year
when I last left
Baker Street.
I had no idea where I was going
or who my client was.
All I knew was
that it was important
and abroad.
My destination was the museum
and the Louve was in Paris
and my client none less
than the French government.
Surely this Louve is near
to the very heart of France.
It was here that
the great Musele held court
and here that
Napoleon Bonaparte
was married to
the Archduchess Madam
Marie Louise of Austria.
Indeed it is a history lesson
in stone.
And now this gallery
contains our finest paintings.
Gentlemen,
shall we come to the point?
I presume the Mona Lisa
has been stolen.
When I see two hooks
and the place where
the Mona Lisa used to hang
and then this talk
of...
and scandal.
Yes, now I begin to understand
the delicacy of the matter.
The Louve is closed on Mondays
for maintenance.
The fact that the Mona Lisa
was not hanging
in her usual place was no doubt
due to the fact
that she was in
the photographic studio.
It was only later in the day
that a workman found the frame
in a little storeroom
under the salon care.
We put the glass
over the painting
only a month ago.
We feared an acid attack,
there was such a one
in Florence recently.
How very fortunate.
Pardon?
Two good
thumb prints.
Many artists come here
to make copies of the paintings.
This one seems
well done.
Yes, that artist
is particularly clever
and makes a good living
from his copying.
I should like
to meet him sometime.
To make a bad copy
is very easy but a good one,
it takes
years of practice.
For instance De Vinci
used Italian popular wood
to paint on.
It is very difficult
to find.
To match the original color,
nearly impossible.
It is, uh, full mature,
the smooth blended tones,
very subtle
and his brushwork
is left-handed.
The crack work,
this fine network
of cracks,
left, ah.
that is the most difficult
to achieve of all.
And you can
achieve it?
How?
That is my secret.
It seems to me
that this is something
near to a
legitimate forgery.
No, no, no
because the copies must never
be the same size
as the original.
And, and who would buy
one of my copies as the original
when the real Mona Lisa
is in the Louve.
But if by chance
the Mona Lisa
is no longer
in the Louve?
But of course
you are joking Messier.
Happily the French police
are well ahead of the British
when it comes to
fingerprints.
The great Bantion himself
was kind enough to refer
to my little pamphlet
on the subject as his bible.
As I suspected,
our man had been involved
in petty crime in the past,
a Spaniard named Mendosa.
There, there
is your thief.
Not a pleasant
specimen.
Mr. Holmes,
France owes you a great debt.
We have not got the man
and more important,
the painting.
But he must
be arrested immediately.
He may have already
sold it.
No, no, gentlemen
it is my belief
that the painting
is still in Mendosa's keeping.
He is only a pawn
in a much bigger game.
This robbery
has been carefully planned
over months, even years
by a master criminal.
But what professional
criminal would want
to own
the Mona Lisa?
That is madness.
He can't sell it.
I believe the master criminal
is not interested
in the original,
if he can pass off
the forgeries as originals
for the same price.
Gentlemen we must
alarm Mendosa,
get him on the move
so he leads us
to the center
of the web.
But how?
First we must announce
to the world
that the painting
has been stolen.
Oh,
but that would create
a great scandal both myself
and the director of...
Minister,
please if I may explain.
It would be announced
that owing to the brilliant
and tireless efforts of
yourself and the director,
that the criminal
is about to be arrested.
Mr. Holmes, we must
arrest him now.
No.
Now!
Holmes, I understand that
the recovery of the original
would make it impossible
for the thieves to sell
any copies however excellent
those copies were,
but did you have any clue
to the identity
of the mastermind behind
the whole scheme?
I was satisfied
that I had recognized one of
Professor Moriarity's
agents.
Moriarity?
Notice the subtle modeling
of the features,
beautiful hands,
mood,
that smile.
As Walter Payton described her,
the head upon which all the ends
of the world
are common.
The eyelids
are a little weary.
No one else has ever had
the genius to paint this masterpiece
except De Vinci.
But if you look at
the paint work sir.
Leonard's signature at large,
the brush work,
the bloom,
the technique.
Will you
excuse me?
I would say without hesitation
that the general opinion
of the art world
is that this
is the greatest portrait
ever painted.
I very much regret
to have to tell you sir
that this painting
is no longer for sale.
I don't understand
Professor.
I mean,
the price maybe?
Well now look,
I'll reconsider.
I'll give you a cool
four million and how's that?
I'm sorry
Mr. Walker,
the painting is no
longer for sale.
Hey,
what you guys up to?
Take your hands off me
you nick!
Thanks for nothing.
That wretched Holmes
has recovered the original.
These are worthless.
Destroy them,
burn them.
Do it
yourself,
and let no one else
see you.
Yes,
Professor Moriarity.
I must
congratulate you, Holmes.
Such an honor
and so well deserved.
There was no
great problem.
The case practically
solved itself.
I hear you had a visitor
this morning.
Ow!!!
I had not been back
in Baker Street
more than
half an hour when...
But you cannot
go up there sir!
You have less
frontal development
than I should have
expected.
It's a dangerous habit,
a finger loaded firearms
in the pocket of one's
dressing gown.
You evidentially
don't know me.
On the contrary I think it's
fairly evident that I do.
I can spare you five minutes
if you have anything to say.
All that I have to say
has already crossed your mind.
And possibly my answer
has already crossed yours.
You stand fast?
Absolutely.
You frustrated me
in the affair
of the French gold.
So it was you behind
the Red Headed League.
A very ingenious
and welcome tried idea.
High praise
from you.
You crossed my path
first on the 4th of January.
By the middle of February
I was seriously inconvenienced
by you and at
the end of March
I was absolutely
hampered in my plans.
And now with this last business
in France you have placed me
in such a position
by your continual persecution
that I am in positive danger
of losing my liberty.
The situation is becoming
an impossible one.
Have you any suggestion
to make?
You must drop it
Mr. Holmes.
You really must
you know.
And what if
I refuse?
I'm quite sure that a man
of your intelligence
will see that there can be
but one outcome to this affair.
It is necessary
that you should withdraw.
You have worked things
in such a fashion
that we have only
one resource left.
It has been an intellectual
treat to me to see
the way in which
you grappled with this matter.
But I say unaffectedly
that it would be a grief to me
to be forced to take
an extreme measure.
Oh, you smile sir
but it really would
I do assure you.
Danger is part of
my trade.
This is not danger.
It is inevitable
destruction.
You stand in the way
not merely of an individual
but of a mighty organization,
the full extent of which
even you with all your
cleverness have been
unable to realize.
You must stand clear Mr. Holmes
or be trouble under foot.
You know I'm afraid
that in the pleasure
of this conversation
I am neglecting business
of importance
which awaits me elsewhere.
Well, well,
it seems a pity
but I've
done what I could.
This is a duel
between you and me Mr. Holmes.
You hope to place
me in the dark.
You hope
to beat me.
If you are clever enough
to bring destruction on me,
rest assured
I shall do as much for you.
You have paid me
several compliments,
Mr. Moriarity.
Let me pay you one
in return when I say that if
I were assured of
the former eventuality
I would, in the interests
of the public,
cheerfully accept
the later.
I can promise you the one
but not the other.
He is the Napoleon
of crime Watson.
For years
I have endeavored
to break through
the veil which shrouded him
and at last
I have seized a thread
and followed it
to Moriarity himself.
And now I'm ready
to close on him.
If he doesn't
close upon you first.
On Monday next,
matters will be right
but the Professor
and all the principal members
of his gang will be
in the hands of the police.
Then will come the greatest
criminal trial of the century,
the clearing up of
over 40 mysteries
and the room
full of them.
I cannot do better
than to get away
for the few
remaining days.
It would give me great pleasure
Watson if you would come
onto the continent
with me.
The continent?
I'd be delighted Holmes,
but where?
Anywhere.
It's all
the same to me.
Yes, but won't
we have to dispose of
Professor Moriarity
first?
It seems to me that we're
under siege in this very room.
And that reminds me
I must be on my way.
Won't you
stay the night?
No, it's too dangerous for you
if I stay here.
I will leave the way I came
and find lodgings
with my brother
Mycroft.
We start
tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning?
Oh, yes,
it is most necessary.
Now here are your instructions
and I beg of you
to follow them
to the letter.
We are now playing
a double-handed game with me,
Watson against
the most powerful syndicate
of criminals
in Europe.
You will dispatch
whatever luggage
you intend to take by
a trusted messenger unaddressed
at the Victoria Station
tonight.
In the morning you will send
Mrs. Hudson for a handsome cab,
desiring her
not to take the first
or second which may
present itself.
You will drive to the Strand end of La Famules,
handing the address
to the cabman
but with a request
that he will not throw it away.
Have your fare ready
and the instant that your cab
stops move speedily through
the muse and time yourself
to reach the other end at
exactly a quarter past 9:00
where you will find a small
broom waiting close to the curb
driven by a fellow
with a heavy black coat,
tipped at the collar
with red.
Into this you will stay
and you will reach Victoria
in time for
the continental express.
Excuse me sir, I
wonder if you speak Italian.
No,
I'm afraid not.
I'm looking for the gentleman
who reserved this compartment.
Not a sign of him
sir.
If you're traveling
you better get aboard.
My dear Watson
you haven't even condescended
to say good morning
to me.
Good heavens Holmes,
how you startled me.
It is still necessary
to take every precaution.
I did rather fine,
Watson.
I see that this express runs
in connection with the boat
so I think we've shaken off
Moriarity very effectively.
Well what will
he do then?
What I
should do.
Engage a special
train.
But he'll arrive
too late.
You'll observe from your
Bradshaw that this train
stops at Canterbury
and again at the boat.
Moriarity will
catch us there.
Good heavens anybody would think
that we were the criminals.
Let's arrest him
as soon as he arrives.
No, that would ruin
everything.
If we should catch the big fish
then the smaller
would dart right and left
out of the net.
No, no,
and the rest is invisible.
Well what then?
We shall
get ours at Canterbury.
But Holmes
our luggage.
We must give Moriarity
something to follow.
What will
we do?
We shall go
across country.
Here we are Holmes, Bradshaw
shouldn't let you down.
From Ashford Junction
we can take a 1:00 slow train
to Hastings,
then onto the dear old
London Brighton
and South Coast line,
Bax Hill on to Lewis non-stop,
then onto New Haven,
evening boat
to Vienna.
I think we've got time
for an early lunch.
So soon.
There are limits you see
to even our friend's intelligence.
And now Watson,
we shall treat ourselves
for a couple of carpet bags,
encourage the manufacturers,
the countries through which
we travel and make our way
at leisure
into Switzerland
via Brussels,
Luxemberg...
It fell out as Sherlock Holmes
had predicted.
We stayed two nights
in Brussels,
then began to make our
leisurely way southeast.
For a charming week we
progressed towards the Alps.
What do you
think?
A common enough occurrence
in the mountains.
Ah, nothing like drinking
the wine where it's grown.
Hmm.
All gang safely secured,
only Moriarity escaped the net,
signed Mycroft.
He's given them
the slip.
I think it would be better
if you were to
return to England
Watson.
Why?
You will find me
a very dangerous companion now.
Moriarity will devote
all his energies to taking his
revenge upon me
and if I have a companion...
Would you be
rid of me?
No, except for the reasons
I've given.
We've been in tight places
before together.
Never as tight
as this one.
I'm not leaving you
Holmes,
not unless
you order me to go.
I've never been
to Switzerland before
but the beauty of the landscape
reminded me irresistibly
of the northwest frontier
provinces of India.
But in spite of the lovely
scenery all around us,
it was clear to me
that never for one instant
did Sherlock Holmes
forget the shadow
that lay
across him.
I could tell by his
sharp scrutiny of every face
that he was well convinced
that go where we would
we would not be clear
of the danger
that was dogging
our footsteps.
What was that?
See anything?
No, nothing.
It's time
we went on our way.
Hans,
we're on our way.
At last we reached the heart
of the burnice overland
and came to the village
of Mirengland
where we put up
at the Englisher Hall
then kept
by Peter Steiler the Elder.
Uh, Steiler?
The walk over to the hills
to Rosenlawry is very beautiful.
You can stay the night
there and come back the next day
but you must not on
any account miss
the falls of Reichenbach
which is only a small detour.
Uh, there it is.
It is indeed
a fearful place.
The torrent, swollen
by the melting glacier,
plunges into a tremendous abyss
in which the spray rose up
like the smoke
from a burning house.
Herr, Dr. Watson.
Yes?
Herr Steiler told me
to give you this.
It is very urgent.
It seems an English woman
was taken to the hotel
after we left on her way
to friends in Lucerne.
She's had
a great hemorrhage.
Tuberculoses.
Oh, no doubt.
It appears
she's dying.
An English doctor
would be a great consolation.
I'm afraid
I must go back Holmes.
Of course.
Steiler suggests
that this lad shows you the way
to Rosenlawy
and I'll join you there later.
A good plan.
Hey!
I trust
she's no worse.
You didn't
write this?
There is no sick
English woman at the hotel?
No, but it has
the hotel mark.
Of course, there was
a tall old Englishman
who came here after
you had gone.
He said...
It was the sight
of the Alpine stalk
that turned me cold
and sick.
He had not gone
to Rosenlawy.
I stood for a minute or two
to collect myself
for I was dazed
with the horror of the thing.
And then I began to think
of Holmes' own methods
and to try
to practice them.
Holmes,
Holmes.
My Dear Watson,
I write these few lines
through the courtesy
of Mr. Moriarity
who awaits my convenience
for the final discussion
of those questions
which lie between us.
I'm pleased to think
that I shall be able
to free society from any further
affects of his presence.
Though I fear
that it is at a cost
which will give pain
to my friends
and especially
my dear Watson,
to you.
As you know, my career
had in any case
reached a crisis.
And no possible conclusion
to it could be more congenial
to me
than this.
Indeed if I may make
a full confession to you,
I was convinced
that the letter...
was a hoax.
I made every disposition
of my property
before leaving
England
and handed it
to my brother Mycroft.
Good bye
and good luck
and believe me
to be my dear fellow,
very sincerely yours,
Sherlock Holmes.
In this situation
I have little doubt
that a personal contest
between the two men
ended as it could hardly
fail to end.
Ahh!
It's with a heavy heart
that I take up my pen
to write these last words
in which I shall ever record
singular gifts
by which my friend
Mr. Sherlock Holmes
was distinguished.
I shall
ever regard him
as the best
and wisest man
I have
ever known.