♪ We face the music together ♪
♪ And throw our hats
in the ring ♪
♪ Facing all kinds of weather ♪
♪ And not afraid of anything ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When the sun comes up,
we'll be on our way ♪
♪ And we don't care
where we land ♪
♪ And the waves are high,
but we won't turn round ♪
♪ 'Cause your hand
is in my hand ♪
♪ And, oh-oh ♪
♪ You make me feel invincible ♪
♪ 'Cause it's you and me ♪
♪ Through the wind and hail ♪
♪ Setting sail into the world ♪♪
I mean, look, even if you're
a total noob at investing,
you'll still reap more
with the 30-year mortgage.
Good to know.
It's such a great house.
Thanks. Of course,
you'll qualify
for a VA loan,
you lucky son of a gun.
Sounds like a pretty fair trade
for risking his life
for his country.
So, uh, you ever killed anyone?
Well, Nick,
my first time downrange,
I started as a gunner in Ramadi.
After BRC, I got deployed
with 1st Recon
to find a terror cell so
deeply embedded with civilians
that we couldn't
tell the difference,
so what do you think?
Excuse us.
Was that really necessary?
Who asks that to somebody
they just met?
Oh.
You ready to head out?
Spence, it's not even dark.
The plan was to stay an hour.
We can't miss the fireworks.
I'll look bad
in front of my boss.
All right, sundown's
at 2100 hours.
Leave at 2120?
Fine.
Uh, the kids are out
of sparklers,
so I'm gonna make
a quick run with Nick.
I'll go with you.
I'll be five minutes. Okay?
[garbled radio transmission]
[bomb whistling]
Coming in. Clear.
Right perimeter clear.
Is left perimeter clear?
Left perimeter clear.
- Get him out! Get him out!
- Hey! What the hell?!
Quick time!
[Spence] You don't need
more sparklers.
There's plenty back there.
Thank you, baby.
You're so sweet.
I love you.
[rock music playing quietly]
♪ ♪
[hissing]
I think it's been
going on for a while.
Between my husband
and your wife.
- My wife wouldn't do that.
- Why not?
Because that's not
part of the plan.
[loud firework explodes]
Believe what you like, but...
I'm declaring July 5th
my Independence Day.
[fireworks popping, squealing]
Babe, have you seen my phone?
Can you call it?
- [phone ringing]
- [dog barking]
[phone continues ringing]
Uh...
why is my phone
in Charlie's dirty diaper?
That's a good question.
And I could ask you why
you put your other mobile device
in places it doesn't belong.
Now...
tell me the truth.
[sighs]
At least he admitted the affair.
He didn't have a choice.
- [Nick] Every day. Every day.
- [Charlie crying]
Yes, he's awake.
I can't believe you woke him.
[Alison] What happened next?
[Isabelle] I said
all my worst fears.
That we'd still be doing great
if I hadn't gotten pregnant.
But a baby reminds Nick
that he's not young anymore,
and he can't handle
the responsibility.
Sometimes you throw
accusations out
that you want someone to deny.
And then they don't.
[Charlie cooing]
[Alison] So what do you want?
I'm...
I'm very tired.
- I need a teammate.
- [Alison exhales]
Well, it sounds like
you have more to work through.
[man and woman grunting
in video game]
Yeah!
- [grunting continues]
- [phone chimes]
♪ ♪
Jeannie, can we talk?
The last time we talked,
it didn't go so well.
Can't you understand why?
At this point, I don't know
what else there is to say.
I saw you went back
to your maiden name on Facebook.
[grunting]
Are you gonna leave me
another angry voice message?
Does that make you feel better?
[yelling]
Nothing makes me feel better.
Spence, sign the damn papers.
[woman on phone] Sit tight,
Mr. Boyles. Help is on the way.
Thank you, ma'am.
[engine clicking softly]
[typing rapidly]
[pen clicks]
Please have a seat.
Your appointment's
not for another hour.
[scoffs softly]
Excuse me.
Are you the wife of the guy my
wife is having an affair with?
We're not together anymore.
- I'm Isabelle.
- Spence.
Thanks, uh,
for the heads-up...
at the barbecue.
I'm not sure you should be
thanking me, but you're welcome.
[door squeaks open]
Oh, my God.
Oh. I am so sorry.
This is something.
Want to go get coffee?
That might not be the best idea.
You, uh... you look well.
Thanks. I think
I'm having a good hair day.
He vomited into it,
so I washed it.
Sorry.
About what? My life?
So, how'd you find Dr. Alison?
She's okay. I...
I had some things
I needed to get off my chest,
but I think I'm done now.
- [Charlie cries]
- [phone buzzes]
He keeps texting me
about Charlie.
I wish he'd just get over
his guilt and leave us alone.
Do you think they're in love?
I don't know.
And I don't care.
Why? Do you?
If she was, I'd feel better
about her giving up on the plan.
You've mentioned that before.
What was the plan?
We were gonna have a baby.
And then, five more years,
a second.
And then, if I could manage,
the house would be paid off
in 15 years.
Then we'd go on a cruise,
see the glaciers, and...
If they're still around.
You know you can't really
plan life like that.
I guess not.
I prefer to control
the controllable.
After you have your first kid,
you'll let go of some of that.
You're right.
Maybe I won't have
children anymore.
Hey, you never know.
A goal without a plan
is just a wish.
Huh?
I wanted to get coffee because
you're the only person
who understands
what I'm going through.
But at the same time, you know
how completely ordinary
this situation is.
I was devastated
when it happened,
but now I'm more...
embarrassed.
- You feel embarrassed?
- Yeah.
Like I was robbed.
I don't want to feel
like this again.
We should probably get going.
We got to go home.
[Charlie crying]
[clears throat softly]
I'm glad we met.
Why do you look so surprised?
I can't remember the last time
someone was glad to have met me.
We're not them.
At least we have that.
Take care of yourself.
[Charlie fussing]
Hmm.
[Adam] Okay, Boyles,
your profile's set up.
Just click on who you like.
You make it sound so easy.
[Adam] Give it a try.
Um...
[♪ Gold Star:
"San Francisco Good Times"]
Hmm?
Uh...
[both chuckling]
Oh, all right. Uh, now what?
Man, you write her.
And if you hit it off,
you meet up.
[indistinct voices in distance]
[siren wailing in distance]
- So we agree?
- Definitely.
This is definitely not a date.
I saw your profile...
And it... it would have been
rude not to message.
Exactly.
It's my first night out
in a while.
Mine, too.
Do you know...
do you know what you want?
Hey, you mentioned
you lost power after the storm.
Yeah. And then
when the power came back,
I couldn't get
some of my lights working.
I bet I can fix that for you.
Right now?
We don't have to...
Okay.
[speaking indistinctly]
[chuckles] Yeah.
Let's get out of here.
- [clicks]
- No.
How about now?
No.
Yes! [laughs]
Hey.
Since you didn't get any dinner.
[door closes]
I can't believe
you finally hung the curtains.
Did Nick help you?
Definitely not.
I have a friend.
It's not that military guy
from therapy.
Girl, that is so weird.
Wasn't he married to...
Yeah, you don't need
to remind me about his ex.
So what, he's kind of, like,
a handyman with benefits?
We haven't actually...
We're...
we're friends.
I know it hasn't been easy
for you, with Charlie...
You have no idea.
But you should not lead a guy on
because you want
your tiles re-grouted.
Maybe I want a man
to re-grout my tiles.
[laughs]
Have you always been this handy?
No way.
When I, uh,
got back from the Marines,
I hadn't lived in a house
in a while.
You want to do it?
Just run it slowly.
[Isabelle] So,
when did that change?
I threw myself into becoming
the best solider that I could.
Until I wasn't
a solider anymore.
And then when I got married,
I wanted to be
the best husband I could be.
And that includes
teaching yourself
electrical work and plumbing?
Okay, bring it up.
- Oh! I made that.
- [Spence laughs]
And now...
it is gone.
You need a haircut.
Hey.
Where are you?
Oh. Sorry.
I wouldn't call myself
a creative person,
but sometimes my mind
takes me places.
Bad places?
Not always.
But sometimes.
How much experience
do you have up there?
I've cut Charlie's hair
his whole life.
He's never complained.
I wanted to do something nice
for you, for once.
I like making your life better.
I mean...
I like trying.
Do you want to go to d-dinner?
I mean, like, a real...
Yes.
♪ ♪
[ringtone playing]
Oh, hey.
- [Charlie crying]
- Hey. I'm sorry to do this
last-minute, but Charlie's sick.
What?
His fever won't break.
I've been trying all day.
Can I bring you anything?
Nope.
We have everything we need.
- I could take you
to the hospital.
- No, we're really fine.
I just can't leave him
with a sitter like this.
- Oh. Okay.
- I'm so sorry.
Um...
No, no.
Please don't worry about me.
- Okay. Rain check?
- Rain check.
[over speakers] Avery,
you have a call on line four.
Spence.
- It's, uh...
- I know who you are.
Yeah, uh, sorry,
I'll-I'll get out of your way
in a minute.
I... don't know what to get.
Are you asking my advice?
No.
No, sorry, man.
My-my kid is sick.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah. I mean,
his fever is sky-high.
I-I wanted to take him
to the doctor,
but his mother didn't want
to drag him to the ER
and get stuck waiting there.
She wants him to rest,
see his regular pediatrician
in the morning, and...
- I take it you don't agree?
- [sighs] I don't know.
I wanted to take him in
and make sure he's okay,
but she's the mother, right?
She knows best.
Oh, God, I...
can't believe
I'm unloading on you.
You must hate me.
That's a reasonable assumption.
Um...
are we okay?
What do you mean, "Are we okay?"
I'm not with Jeannie anymore.
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
I don't know.
Well, hey, man, not tonight,
obviously, but...
let me know if you want to get
a beer and talk about it.
♪ ♪
[distorted, echoing explosion]
[muted, distorted voices
shouting]
[distorted, echoing explosion]
[muted, distorted voices
shouting]
[distorted, echoing explosion]
[Nick] Hey, hey, please don't...
please, don't, don't, don't,
don't, please, please don't.
[amplified heartbeat]
Hey, man, now we're okay.
[echoing pop]
Sorry.
It was a stupid idea.
Anyway, have a good night.
Hey.
You need to get Isabelle to let
you take Charlie to the ER.
You know my son's name?
Don't let whatever's going on
between you and her
cloud your judgement.
You're his father.
[rhythmic beeping]
- [beeping]
- [whooshing]
Thanks for coming.
Yeah.
It was meningitis.
That's crazy.
I thought I knew best.
I thought
I could do this on my own.
Well, you were never
on your own.
- I was there... No.
- Nick is, uh...
Go on.
Nick insisted that
we bring Charlie to the ER.
It was like
he was a different man.
[crying]
He could have died,
and it would have been my fault.
My whole world would have
been over in an instant.
[sniffles]
You can't...
you can't plan anything.
Do you understand me?
Life cannot be planned.
[sighs]
Sorry. What were you gonna say?
No. Uh...
It sounds like he's finally
stepping into his role
as a father.
Mm.
Do you want to head back?
- [rhythmic beeping]
- [whooshing]
Look.
I think he's smiling.
[line ringing]
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Now you know
who you're talking to ♪
♪ You know I'm not a liar ♪
♪ I tore my pants
and learned to dance ♪
♪ On love and razor wire ♪
♪ I learned to keep on moving
when the flames ♪
♪ Were getting higher ♪
♪ When the devil's stuck ♪
♪ And you keep walking
through the fire ♪
♪ And I made friends
with the monsters ♪
♪ Growling underneath my bed ♪
♪ I held a ball and invited
all the voices in my head ♪
♪ I heard the traffic humming
and I thought it was a choir ♪
♪ Singing
when the devil's stuck ♪
♪ And you keep walking
through the fire ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh...
I wasn't sure if you'd show up.
I'm sorry I didn't
answer your messages.
Why didn't you?
Can we talk about that night?
You told me you were going
to kill yourself.
[Spence] That night
I managed to convince myself
that things would be easier
if I wasn't around anymore.
[Jeannie] You scared me.
[Spence] I think I meant to.
I'm sorry.
After you left,
I... kind of lost my purpose.
Don't you think
that was part of the problem?
I'm not a mission.
You were to me.
Are you zoning out right now?
Are you even listening?
I want you to be happy.
I want you to be happy, too.
Okay? Please?
Jeannie?
I'll sign the papers, okay?
Thank you.
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
Oh.
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ♪♪
[sniffles]
[indistinct crowd chatter]
- Hey, stranger.
- Hi.
- It's good to see you.
- You as well.
That's Nick's new girlfriend.
She's nice, actually.
I mean, she's fine.
I thought
you two were back together.
No. I deserve better
than that, don't I?
Here's my dude.
Happy birthday, Charlie.
Ah. What is that?
Is that why you disappeared?
I didn't want to get in the way.
That's silly.
You good?
I'm doing the best I can.
According to plan?
Ah, there is no plan.
- [Spence laughs]
- [Brynn] Hey.
Should we do the cake soon?
Just a sec.
Katie?
- Hi, Katie.
- [Katie gasps, babbles]
Can I, uh, help with anything?
Uh, yes, actually.
I could use a night out
with a grownup.
Oh.
Please don't feel obligated.
Thanks. I won't.
So, Friday?
Yeah?
Okay, it's a plan.
Was that a joke?
Hey, birthday boy.
Okay, let's sing.
Mm. One, two, three.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday
to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday,
dear Charlie ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪♪
Did you schedule
a joint session?
[laughs softly]
[Alison sighs]
I feel like there may have been
some changes for you.
Yes, ma'am. You could say that.
So...
where would you like to begin?
♪ ♪