Whatever you wanna do, I'm in your corner.
Lynette made a promise...
Mr. Faladi...
- I love him, and he loves me!
and Bree's daughter fell
for her history teacher.
Aah!
- While Mike's history...
He suffered
significant memory loss.
was being carefully rewritten.
- Susan Mayer.
- We were close, huh?
That tramp treated you
like dirt.
(Mary Alice)
The art of sabotage--
it's practiced every day
in the suburbs.
Sometimes it takes the form
of a Bundt cake
offered to a friend
who's on a diet.
Other times,
it's a cable cut just
as a husband's friends arrive
to watch the big game.
And then there's always
that anonymous phone call
to the city zoning department.
Yes, in Suburbia,
everyone you meet
is a potential saboteur...
absolutely everyone.
Good afternoon.
I'm, uh, Bree Hodge,
and you are?
Name's Gus,
and we're all booked up.
- Actually, Gus, um,
I'm here to see
one of your guests--
a gentleman named Faladi.
Oh, yeah,
came in about an hour ago.
You want me
to call him for you?
- No, no, no, no.
I'd like you to take me
to his room and unlock it
so I can
walk in unannounced.
(laughs) Lady, I can't do that.
Besides, he has a girl in there.
Yes, I know.
She's my daughter--
my 17-year-old daughter.
(chuckles) Yeah.
Uh, that would be, uh,
room, uh, 17.
Now there's irony for you.
(laughs)
You don't have
a gun in there, do you?
Because I just
put down new carpet.
Oh, Gus, I don't plan
anything unpleasant.
I'm simply going to inform
Mr. Faladi
what repercussions he faces
if he continues
this relationship
and trust him
to see reason.
- (Mr. Faladi) What the hell?!
- (Danielle) Mom!
What are you doing here?!
You just can't walk
right in here.
- How can you do this to me?!
What makes you think that
you can walk in here...
Yes, the art of sabotage--
it's practiced every day
in the suburbs...
(Mr. Faladi)
I told you, it's over!
(Danielle crying)
But I love you!
- Okay, didn't you hear her?!
So how'd it go?
Quite well, I think.
But few do it as well
as Bree Hodge...
Oh, and, Gus,
the carpet is beautiful.
or as politely.
www.1000fr. com present
sync:frm@¶çæêñû¶ù
Family dinner--
there was a time when
that phrase meant something
on Wisteria Lane.
Of course, this was back when
meals were lovingly prepared...
by wives who loved to cook...
for children
who remembered their manners.
But family dinners,
like the times, had changed,
and there was only one house
in the neighborhood
where dinner remained
a family occasion...
and attendance
was not optional.
I don't know when I've tasted
such tender spring lamb.
THank you, dear.
Danielle, you haven't
touched your dinner.
She doesn't like spring lamb.
She prefers old goat.
(stifles laugh)
I'm glad you guys think it's
so funny that my life is over.
Your mother was right
to end that relationship.
The man was your teacher
and married.
He's getting a divorce.
Well, that hardly bolsters
his suitability.
Danielle, please, eat something.
- Don't worry, dear.
Hunger strikes
demand self-control,
and as we've seen,
that's hardly her strong suit.
When are you gonna take me seriously?
- When you start acting like an adult.
Well, she sleeps with them.
That's a start.
I hate you!
I hate all of you!
Remind me to buy paper plates.
We'll need them till a certain someone
can be trusted with china again.
Aah!
Wow, you're pretty good
at that.
Hey, you are home early.
Hi. Mwah.
Yes... I am.
What is all this?
We are having
a celebration.
Sit.
(chuckles)
What are we celebrating?
You being the greatest wife
in the world.
(laughs) THanks.
No, seriously, though.
I mean it.
How many wives would tell their
husbands to follow his dreams,
and then
have the patience to wait
while he figures out
what the hell it is?
Oh, my God!
You know what you wanna do!
That's fantastic!
What is it?
Wait for it,
wait for it...
Okay, I knew I needed
to spend my days
doing something I was passionate
about, something creative--
yeah, have at it--**
um, something where
I interacted with the public
but I was still
my own boss,
and then this morning,
it just like--bam, it hit me!
Okay, okay, I'm dying here.
What's the dream?
You're eating it.
Excuse me?
I'm gonna
open up a pizza parlor!
I bet you didn't
see that one coming.
No, that was a real frisbee
to the head, that one.
But--but when you think
about it,
doesn't it make
perfect sense?
I mean, marinara's in my blood.
You remember uncle Vito?
He came to this country
with nothing.
He turned that trattoria
into a gold mine.
Isn't he the one that...
asked us for a loan
last Christmas?
He has a gambling problem,
but don't blame the pizza.
Trust me. I've got
this thing all mapped out.
It's gonna have, like,
a real family feel,
with, like, big portions
but small prices,
crayons for the kids.
Oh, God,
I feel good about this.
Hmm.
So what do you think?
I think...
I'm gonna open
another bottle of wine.
But we haven't
finished this one.
Well, hey,
we're celebrating, right?
Carlos, what are you doing
in my room?
Oh, hey, Gaby,
you're home early.
God, Carlos!
Strawberries and champagne?
Did you really think
you're gonna seduce me?
Never entered my mind.
- Oh, right, right.
You know,
I may be living with you
until the divorce is final,
but it doesn't mean
I have to put up
with your cheesy come-ons.
Gaby,
can I just say one thing?
What, you've been
doing some thinking,
and you realize
that I'm your soul mate,
and there's a vacancy
in your heart only I can fill?
Gaby, listen--
it's over between us.
Just move on already.
Forget me.
As I was trying to say,
I have company over.
This is Trishelle.
Trishelle, this is...
what was your name again?
I seem to have forgotten.
So the doctor said
I should use as many things
as I can to jog your memory.
And not just pictures.
He said I could use tastes
and smells and sounds,
so tonight is...
"sounds of the seventies."
Okay, uh...
Well, you know,
let me set the scene.
Um, we were at this
funky little fish joint
that you'd been dying
to take me to--Cappy's.
Do you remember Cappy's?
Okay, well,
we were there, and, uh,
we were just wolfing down
the most delicious trout ever--
How long
till the music part?
Oh, it's coming.
Um, and--and this
'70s cover band,
well, they started to play,
and... that's how
we got our song.
(Rose Royce) * at the car wash,
whoa, whoa... *
Our song was "Car Wash"?
Yeah!
See how much fun we were?
(laughs) So I dragged you out
onto the dance floor,
and, well, you were
giving me this look--
sort of like the look
you're giving me right now--
and, um,
I started to do this...
and then you did this...
I'm--look, I'm sorry,
this--this isn't working.
Oh, Mike. Come on, you're not
even trying to remember!
It was fun!
Oh, I know.
Okay, sing with me.
* car wash
* talkin' about
the car wash *
* whoo, car wash, yeah
You know, I'm really beat.
Okay, Mike, I-I am not
doing this to upset you.
I'm doing this to help.
I get that. it's just...
the music is giving me
a headache.
Okay, well...
I'll go, but I am not
giving up on you.
You know,
you are going to remember
the night that
We danced to "Car Wash,"
and not just because it was fun,
but because later that night,
we did some things
that, trust me,
are worth remembering.
That Jane Doe
from the golf course...
I think I missed something
at the autopsy.
Check it out.
- You always gotta come at lunch, don't you?
Those blue marks
on the back of her hand?
First I thought they were veins.
Now I think it's ink.
You mean,
like some kind of writing?
Yeah. I need to run
some more tests,
see if I can get
a clearer image.
I could be wrong, but...
But what?
I think
it's a phone number.
The oddest thing happened
at the club today.
Tish Atherton--
(sighs)
Andrew, would you be a dear
and make sure your sister's
just breaking her own things?
Anyway...
Hmm.
Tish Atherton...
Danielle?
Yeah, I'll tell 'em.
I'm telling you,
it was a deliberate snub.
I waved to her,
and she looked right through me.
True, I never bought
her eldest daughter a gift--
- Uh, Mom?
Andrew, please don't
interrupt me while I'm speaking.
True, I never bought
her eldest daughter a gift,
but you know my policy--
no husband, no baby gift.
Now what is it, dear?
Well, um, Danielle's upstairs
trying to commit suicide.
There's no rush.
She's not trying that hard.
How can you sit there
playing that ridiculous game?!
Your sister
tried to kill herself.
That doesn't upset you?
She tried to slit her wrists
with a spoon.
How upset
do you want me to be?
Mrs. Hodge?
- Is my daughter all right?
She's a little groggy,
but she'll be fine.
The wounds
are fairly superficial.
(scoffs)
So's the patient.
We'll release her tonight,
but you understand
that in cases like this,
counseling is mandatory.
- Of course. We'll get her
all the help she needs.
She is resisting our efforts
to pump her stomach.
She says she only took
three sedatives.
She's disoriented.
Pump her.
Andrew!
They're sticking a tube
down her throat.
Do you still think
this is funny?
Mom, this was
a half-assed bid for attention.
This was a cry for help,
and if we don't listen,
the next time she could do
something even more dangerous.
Yeah, next time she might
jump off the porch.
Stop it!
Suicide is the worst thing
that can happen to a family!
I will not have it
made light of! (exhales deeply)
Orson's right.
We need to support
each other as a family.
In fact,
I say we all...
go for counseling.
(Gabrielle) Tom actually said
he's opening up a pizza parlor?
(Susan)
Lynette, you're not serious.
Mm-hmm.
- Well, might as well
stand in a vat of tomato sauce
and tear up $100 bills.
- I know, but I said that I would support him
and help him follow his dream.
Well, he can't hold you to that,
not if the dream is pizza.
She promised
to stand by him,
and once you make
that commitment
you have to see it through.
- yeah...
How's that divorce going?
I'm done talking.
- Hey, Parker, be careful up there.
I just keep thinking
he's gonna come to his senses
and realize it's a bad idea.
That's never gonna happen.
- Why?
Because men
are genetically incapable
of realizing
that their dreams are stupid.
Care to elaborate,
Dr. McCluskey?
My husband sold insurance
for 36 years,
and one day,
he woke up and decided
he wanted to move to paris
and paint naked ladies.
I told him, "Gilbert,
you can barely paint the garage.
What makes you think
you can commit art?"
And for the rest of his life,
he despised me.
He despised you
for saying "no"?
Well, he also thought
I was sleeping with his brother,
and I'm sure
that was mixed in there, too.
Okay, so I got Kayla
all unpacked.
Oh, great. So, uh, Tom will drop
her off at your house on friday.
Sounds good. Lynette,
can I talk to you for a second?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Okay, pardon me for having
really big ears,
but I heard about
Tom and this pizza place.
Do you wanna know what I think?
- No, not really.
It sucks.
It's a sucky idea,
and your friends
back there--
they're just too nice
to come right out and say it.
Luckily, I'm not your friend,
so you can trust me.
Nip it...
in... the bud.
And make Tom resent me
for the rest of his life.
I don't think so.
Well, you better do somethin',
'cause if you don't,
you and me
will wind up working a pole
to pay for braces.
Hey, Julie.
I bought you some flowers.
Generally,
when you buy flowers,
they don't still have
the roots on them.
Okay, uh, I was hoping
you could help me
with my English Lit paper.
Hi, I'm Sarah.
- Hey.
So what do you say?
- Actually, I'm sort of busy right now.
Oh, come on.
Look, aunt Edie's gonna
give me the boot if I flunk out.
Wouldn't you miss me?
- Oh, absolutely!
Whose motorcycle would wake us
all up at 2:00 in the morning?
You drive a motorcycle?
- Hmm.
(sighs) Please?
Look, I could really
use some help here.
Normally, I charge
12 bucks an hour for tutoring,
but seeing as it's you...
$15.
Great. See you friday.
Oh, and just so you know,
I charge $15 an hour
to make out,
so I'll probably break even.
Ugh.
Hi. You're new.
Where's Marcy?
She's in Honolulu on vacation.
Can I help you?
Oh, I'm just
going to see Mike Delfino.
What's that smell?
- Uh, that's my macaroni and cheese.
I-I was hoping it would
trigger Mike's memory.
I made it the first time we met two years ago.
- You should've refrigerated it.
Edie?
Oh, you know Ms. Britt?
Uh, yeah.
What is she doing here?
Visiting Mr. Delfino.
You know, she was with him
when he came out of his coma.
And she's been here
every day since.
You!
Hello, Susan.
Long time no see.
I've been wondering why
Mike's been so cold to me.
Now it all makes sense.
- I'm sure I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Whew! for God's sakes,
take a bath.
Oh, that's my mac and cheese.
Don't change the subject.
What have you been telling him about me?
- Why would I say anything about you?
Mike has no idea
who you are.
I envy him.
Ladies,
is there a problem?
I want this woman
banned from the hospital.
She's been like this
ever since Mike dumped her.
Imagine "Fatal Attraction"...
with a much older woman.
Ma'am, Mr. Delfino
already has a visitor.
I think you should go.
Me? But why
doesn't she leave?
I-I'm the one
who's been here every day
for the last six months.
Well, I don't know you,
but I do know his girlfriend.
Girlfriend?!
Okay, you know what?
I want Marcy's number
in Honolulu,
and I want it right now.
You need to leave.
- What?!
You're disturbing the other patients.
- No, what are you--
Oh, this is ridiculous!
I mean,
who am I disturbing?
It's a coma ward!
Don't you want them to wake up?!
I didn't call you that
- yes, you did!
I have never in my life
used the word "retard."
- It's what you think.
You think I'm that immature
moron who can't be trusted
to decide what's best for her.
- Well, you did try to off yourself.
I don't think
you get to pull
the "I know what's best for me" card.
- Andrew!
(lowered voice)
Not in front of the therapist.
Actually, I think
we're making great progress.
You feel
Danielle refuses to see
you're acting
in her best interest.
And you think your mother
cares more about her image
than your feelings.
- Danielle, how can you think
I don't care
about your feelings?
Don't you know how much
your mother loves you?
When I saw you in that tub,
it was the worst moment
of my life.
The thought of losing you
is more than I can bear.
How does that make you feel?
Actually...
kind of powerful.
Powerful?
You really
don't wanna lose me?
- of course not.
I already went through
thinking I'd lost Andrew.
I can't
go through that again.
Well, then, here's
what's going to happen--
I'm going
to start dating Robert again,
and if you try to break us up
or get him fired,
then I'm going to leave,
and you will never
see me again.
- Danielle.
If that can survive
on its own, so can I.
You don't believe me?
Call my bluff.
See what happens.
So...
what do we owe you
for all this progress?
Come on, Austin.
Concentrate.
Okay, why did
Iago betray Othello?
(sighs) Uh...
because the play would suck
if he didn't?
What do you think
you're doing?
Mmm.
Sorry.
No! No, no, no, no!
No, no, we're here to work.
And if my mom came home,
she'd flip.
Now put that away.
Ahh.
You said, "put it away."
Look, if--if you think
I'm gonna sit here
and write your paper for you
while you're getting drunk--
- No, just help me get it started, okay?
This is hard for me,
all right?
I didn't read a lot
of Shakespeare in juvie.
I kind of majored
in not getting stabbed.
Ugh, fine.
I'll write your intro, but--
but then you're on your own.
THank you very much.
(sighs)
So... why did they send you
to juvie anyway?
"They" didn't. My mom did.
Why?
She had this boyfriend--
no job, big drunk,
real catch.
One night,
he pops her one,
so I break a chair
over his head, and, uh...
and she calls the cops...
on me.
But you were
protecting her.
Yeah,
that's what I thought.
But the guy said he'd leave
if she didn't press charges,
and... well, my mom
doesn't really like to be alone.
You know what?
You're tired.
Um, why don't you lay down
for a couple minutes,
and I'll just
do a page or two?
You're a rock star, Mayer.
Carlos...
no Trishelle tonight?
Ah, no.
About her--
I have a confession to make.
Does her pimp want
the rest of the money?
You know, there is
some cash in my purse.
Look, I know I crossed a line
bringing her here, all right?
But I was trying
to make you jealous,
like the way
you made me feel
when you said you slept
with John Rowland again.
Well, I think
it's more than that.
I think you really hate me.
That's not true.
- Oh, I think it is.
You know,
introducing your spouse
to someone
you're about to have sex with?
There's only one reason
to do that--
pure hatred.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, I think I do.
Phil, come meet
my basically ex-husband--
tHank you--Carlos.
Carlos, this is
my new friend Phil Lopez.
We've met, Gaby.
Really?
Well, that's weird. When?
Fairview Chamber of Commerce--
the annual dinner.
Oh, my God! That's right!
That's right! (laughs)
You were up
for the latino businessman
of the year award
that Phil won.
Well, actually,
I beat him out twice.
No!
Ooh, I remember.
Carlos was so annoyed.
What did you say, hon?
"He may have that trophy,
but I've got you."
Ain't life funny? (laughs)
Gaby,
can we talk for a sec?
Mnh-mnh, not right now.
Phil and I are
getting in the hot tub.
Ooh, Phil, did you bring your suit?
- You said I didn't have to.
Not in front of Arlos-cay!
Go outside.
I'll meet you there.
Phil Lopez?
You brought home
Phil Lopez?!
I had no idea
you hated me that much!
Well, now you know.
Aah!
Hey, good news.
My realtor found me
some sweet locations.
That's... great.
(chuckles)
Hey, can we talk about this
restaurant thing for a second?
Yeah. What's up?
I don't know if you noticed,
but when you first pitched
the whole pizza concept...
(chuckles)
I was a wee bit skeptical.
Yeah, I sensed that.
Of course you did,
'Cause you're a smart guy,
which is also why you are gonna
jump on the idea I have
to make
the whole thing work.
Okay, so you're not
bailing on me?
No. No, no, no,
I am totally on board.
(laughs) Oh, good! You had me
scared there for a second.
Okay, so, well,
what is this great idea?
I'm thinking...
catering company.
Huh?
Start small,
have an Italian theme,
create some cash flow,
and then later on,
expand into the pizza thing.
But that's not my dream.
Well, think about it.
You're gonna do
all these fun parties.
People will start talking--
"Hey, this is great food.
This guy should
open a restaurant."
"Yeah, yeah, I'd eat there,"
and then wham!
Five short years later,
you have
a built-in customer base.
But I said it's not my dream.
Pizza is my dream.
I know, I know. Catering's how you get there.
- So why can't I just skip the catering
and go straight to the pizza?
- Because you'll fail!
I'm sorry! God. (groans)
I shouldn't have said that.
But you're gambling
with our life savings,
and you have no experience.
You said that you'd support me.
I'm trying to.
I am trying to.
But are you aware
that 90% of restaurants
tank in their first year?
Which means that
10% of them make it!
Why don't you ever think
that I would be one of them?
No! No, do me a favor.
Don't answer that.
Yoo-hoo! Carlos!
I'm making a snack
for Phil.
Do you want
something to eat?
Some sour grapes, perhaps?
Maybe a little crow?
Okay, we need
to move this over there.
Why?
Uh, Feng Shui.
(banging)
(Gabrielle) Yes! Yes!
(laughs)
Hey, don't start without me.
(lowered voice) Oh, no, no,
let's get something straight--
you and I are not gonna
have sex tonight.
What?
I'm sorry.
No offense, you're a nice guy.
I'm just
not into you that way.
Oh, God, Phil!
Yes, yes, give it to me!
Okay. Oh, okay.
No, no, I'm not
talking to you. Back off!
What--but I thought--
I mean...
You know, the hot tub...
We were...
- Yes, you saw my boobs,
and you're gonna
have that mental snapshot
to use as you wish
for the rest of your life...
but that is
all you're getting!
Wait, wait,
so you're just using me?
You're unbelievable.
I'm what?!
(Phil)
You are unbelievable!
Really?
Oh, so are you, big boy!
Yes!
No wonder you're divorcing her.
She's a straight-up loon.
Oh, crap.
She's blocking my car!
Always happy
to help a brother out.
Hold on.
(Gabrielle) Oh, God, yes!
Oh, ride 'em, cowboy!
Oh, yes, God!
Take me home, Philly!
You should wear a saddle!
Yes! Yes!
Stop it, Phil.
- I told you to beat it.
No means no!
I need your car keys.
You're blocking
the stallion's hatchback.
"Oh, yes, yes, Phil!
Fill me with Phil!"
I never said that.
- (chuckles) And you moved the bed.
What were you thinking?
Shut up.
- You know, if you were trying to hurt me,
that's not the way to do it.
- Well, then enlighten me.
How can I hit you so hard
that you will never recover?
You can't.
Oh, I have to, Carlos.
I need you to give up on us.
We're not good for each other,
and I can't keep doing this.
But I can.
You proved something
tonight--
you had a rich,
good-looking guy in your bed,
and you couldn't
pull the trigger.
That means you still care,
and as long as I know that,
I can take anything
that you can dish out.
You know what? I'm tired.
Can we talk about this
in the morning?
Sure.
But you're bringing me
breakfast in bed or no deal.
It's a date.
Sarah?
What are you--oh!
Oh, Julie!
THank God it's you.
We totally thought
you were the cops.
(grunts) Oh, hey, Julie.
What are you,
on buzz kill patrol tonight?
This is why you couldn't
go to the movies with me?
Well, sorry, I thought
you weren't that into him.
But, you know, if you are--
I'm not!
I'm just--
I'm mad that you blew me off.
Well,
I would totally understand
if you wanted
to blow me off for a date.
(scoffs) You call this a date--
getting mauled in a car?
Hey, you wanna
talk about this later?
I'm losing altitude here.
Ugh, you are disgusting!
Enjoy the rest of your date.
Julie, there you are.
I think I found a way
to get through to Mike.
Let it go!
He's not into you!
Gaby, rise and shine.
I made you some waffles.
I got a second wind last night,
so I went to a bar.
That's where I met Jason.
We spent the whole night--
how did you put it?
Pulling the trigger.
So did I hurt you,
or should I keep trying?
You kicked ass
in rehab today.
Yeah, I raised my arm
over my head.
Sign me up
for the olympics.
Oh, be patient.
It takes time.
Ms. Britt?
hmm?
Phone call for you
at the nurses' station.
For me? Huh.
I'll be right back.
There's a phone call
for me?
Susan? What are you--
Shh! I thought you could use
some fresh air.
Hello?
Hello? It's Edie.
What the hell is this?
Who's he?
Oh, this is Hank,
and he has very kindly offered
to take us on
a little field trip today...
for 60 bucks an hour.
Where are you taking me?
Uh, just a little jaunt
down Memory Lane.
Oh, God, you're not
taking me to that
fish and disco place,
are you?
(laughs) No, no.
What we're doing today
is a little more low-key.
Don't worry.
You're totally safe.
We're not
doing anything wrong.
Punch it!
Hello.
- Look, Mrs. Hodge,
uh, I've only seen your daughter
once since the motel.
She told me
that you backed off.
Oh, Mr. Faladi,
I'm not here to threaten you.
I've come to give you
my blessing.
- Your blessing?
Yes, Danielle
made it quite clear
that I'm powerless
to stop this relationship,
and since she assures me
that you love her--
You do love her,
don't you?
Uh, yes, of course.
Good. Then we're all set.
Here are some of her clothes.
I'll bring her CDs and her
stuffed animals over tomorrow.
You want her to stay here?
This place is kind of small.
Well, that hotel room
was small,
and you seemed
happy enough there.
Oh, and I trust you
to be discreet.
You wouldn't want your wife
find out about this
and use it against you
in your divorce.
Whoa, whoa, Mrs. Hodge?
Things are getting
a little bit complicated.
Could you
please tell Danielle
that this is not gonna
work out and that we--
Mr. Faladi, if you want to
break my daughter's heart,
I can't stop you,
but I will not be an accomplice.
You'll tell her yourself.
Right.
- And don't even think about blaming me,
'cause if you so much
as mention that we spoke,
I'll phone the police.
Fine, I will
leave you out of it.
Oh, and one more thing...
- Yes?
Danielle is applying
to colleges.
I do hope she can count on you
for a glowing recommendation.
Sure.
And when I locked myself
out of the house,
that's where the bush was
that you found me in... naked.
Surely you remember that.
Nope.
Ouch, that hurts.
Um, okay,
remember this spot?
This is where
we sat in your truck
and had our first kiss.
Were you naked then, too?
(sighs) Mike,
why are you being this way?
Because this is pointless.
I... I'm sorry.
I can't--I don't remember
being with you.
Okay, I know it's hard,
but you gotta make an effort,
and, you know,
if your head is a little foggy,
then don't look there.
Look in your heart,
because I'm in there,
just like
you're inside mine.
Okay, um,
this is Mary Alice's house,
and this is
where we first met.
I was setting out
my macaroni and cheese,
and you were invited--
- Oh! ow! (grunts)
I'm good.
Finally, a smile.
You do that a lot,
don't you?
Well, yeah, I've been known
to take a spill or two,
but, you know, my doctor says
it's an inner ear...
Wait, you remember that?
Yeah, I think I... do.
Yes! That's progress! See?
Oh, it's all gonna come back.
We're gonna be us again!
But... what about
the British guy?
Mike...
I don't know
what Edie's been telling you,
but Ian and I--
we're just friends.
Just friends?
Yeah...
now.
Look,
you gotta understand.
The doctors were telling me
that you would probably
never wake up,
and I just needed
somebody to talk to.
And that's what you were
doing in the country--talking?
(nurse) Mr. Delfino?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You can't just discharge
a patient without permission!
Oh, but you--I was just
trying to help him remember.
Tell her, Mike. We were--
we were making progress.
Take me back
to the hospital.
Oh, uh...
Mike!
Well, at the risk
of stating the obvious,
it's over. He's mine now.
No, no, no, no! No, no,
this--this is not how this ends.
No, evil does not triumph
over good.
That's how you see me?
Damn straight!
You lie, you cheat, you scheme!
You ruin
people's relationships!
I mean,
how do you sleep at night?
Soon with Mike
on top of me,
if you know what I mean.
See? Evil!
Evil!
has it ever occurred to you
that maybe Mike and I are
meant to end up together?
No!
You--you--Mike?
You don't even want him!
You're just doing this
to hurt me.
Wow. How self-absorbed
can you be?
I have had a thing for Mike
since the day he moved in here,
and I even backed off
when he fell for your
little Miss Adorable act.
But he's over that.
It's my turn now,
and I will be better for him
than you ever were.
and if you do get hurt,
Well... (chuckles)
that's just gravy.
All right, maybe that
was a little evil.
Finally.
Sorry it took so long.
That last digit
was barely legible.
I thought you'd like
to do the honors.
(Mike) You've reached
Mike Delfino plumbing.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
(beep)
Whoa, a D-minus. That blows.
- Yeah, it does,
especially since it's
not the one we did together.
You e-mailed me
the wrong paper.
You didn't even read it
before you turned it in?
I didn't think I had to!
The one you wrote
that night was great.
- Well, after you left,
I decided I really should
put it in your words.
Is this some weird chick thing
you did 'cause you're into me?
Oh, please.
No, no. No, it is.
You're, uh, pissed 'cause
I hooked up with your friend.
No, I'm pissed because
you told me some sob story
so I'd write your paper
for you.
Now you owe me 15 bucks.
You know what? Here.
Oh, and, uh,
I did learn something.
Iago betrayed Othello
because he was jealous.
Oh, Danielle, I thought you'd
be with Mr. Faladi tonight.
Oh, you'll be happy to know
he dumped me.
he dumped you?
- Said it was
getting too messy,
that I was gonna
complicate his divorce.
Don't pretend you're sorry.
I don't plan to.
Well, I hope this doesn't make
history class too awkward.
Oh, you don't have
to worry about that.
I went to the principal
and got his ass fired,
and then when he called to yell
at me for squealing on him,
I recorded the call and sent
a tape of it to his wife.
Thanks to me, he'll be getting
nothing in this divorce.
Well, I must say
that was rather underhanded.
Yes. I wonder
where she gets it.
(Kayla) Bye, Daddy.
Bye, my chipmunk. I'll see
you guys next Friday, okay?
Kayla said that
you're opening a pizza place.
Well, maybe. I mean,
it's not a done deal yet.
Ah...
Lynette put
the kibosh on it, huh?
What makes you say that?
(chuckles)
Well, you know...
Lynette.
Well, she's probably right.
I mean, there's a bunch
of dumb schmucks out there
trying to open a restaurant, so...
- You know, Tom, I've tasted your pizza,
and I have to be
perfectly honest with you.
It was like I died
and went to italy.
Really?
Oh, my God.
You are born to do this,
and I just hate to see you
give it up, because, well...
man,
this is none of my business,
but Lynette does...
bully you sometimes.
Well, she doesn't mean to.
Then don't let her!
You go to the mat on this one.
She will respect you
a lot more if you grow a pair.
I'm not
trying to insult you.
all I'm saying is that...
I know
what you're capable of,
and I believe in you.
I really needed to hear that.
(chuckles)
Thanks.
Sabotage--
everyone is capable of it,
but some go about it
more ruthlessly than others...
like the ones
who crave vengeance...
or the ones
who hunger for love...