Here's your check.
I didn't charge you for the
fries, 'cause I ate them.
[drone propellers whirring]
[gasps] Max, look out!
The diner water bugs
are getting really big.
Relax, it's the diner's
new surveillance drone.
God, you empty the
register five or ten times,
suddenly there's no trust.
So to be clear, we're out of
soap but we have a drone?
I hate that Han's just sitting
in back, watching us,
working his little joy stick.
Please, no one's getting any
joy out of Han's little stick.
This is so annoying.
It's following me.
Well, with a butt that flat,
it's the only black thing
that's ever going to follow you.
Ugh, there's another drone out here?
I just killed one in the
kitchen with a fly swatter.
Go.
I mean, if I wanted to be spied on,
I'd change my name to Achmed,
and buy a condo near the airport.
Whatever happened to buying a painting
of an old sea captain,
drilling out the eye holes,
and hiding behind it?
Not cool, Han.
And the worst part is, it's
moving around so much,
I can't find my good angle.
Not cool and not Han.
I stole this while he
was explaining to me
why a 77-year-old
man, on minimum wage,
doesn't need health care.
Earl, that is awesome.
Not really. I need that health care.
No, that you stole that.
We need to do something
that will make Han
never want to spy on us again.
Oleg, open your pants.
Earl, fly that camera in there.
But first, take off your underwear.
Underwear?
Come on. What am I, five?
Inches?
Oleg, aren't you at all worried
about Earl's cataracts?
Best case scenario, I get
a little manscaping.
Worst case, I've been
meaning to get circumcised.
[Han's screams]
My eyes!
[screaming]
(Peter Bjorn and John)
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
[cash register bell dings]
♪ Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh ♪
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
Max, I'm writing out
the check for our bank loan,
and I'm not quite sure
what our balance is
because here under "withdrawal"
you just wrote, "yeah".
Well, if you don't like that,
you're really not going to like
the picture I drew under "deposits."
I saw it.
Max, zeroes are not
balls, they're not boobs,
and they're not googly eyes.
They're just zeroes.
Says you.
I'll go check our balance at the ATM.
Even though the last guy who touched it
had a cold sore so big,
I charged him for a party of two.
Don't worry. You are not
going to get anything
from that machine.
Especially cash.
Hey, everybody.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody better make me some eggs
because I've been on a juice
cleanse for three hours,
and I'm dizzy.
Yeah. I mean, they call it a fast,
but it sure does go slow.
I was on a three weeks fast, once.
Then I realized my mother
wasn't coming home.
So I made a sandwich.
Oleg and my wedding is coming up
and we're trying to eat clean.
Yeah, baby, 'cause you
know we're eating dirty
on the honeymoon.
[screaming]
Oh, dear God, what?
Another used condom in the receipt slot?
- Worse.
- What?
Stuff that should be
in a condom but isn't?
We're below zero.
Oh, well, I better go, y'all.
A white woman screaming
anywhere in my vicinity
never turns out well.
This is a disaster.
I've been at zero,
but I've never had less than zero.
Oh, don't say that, Caroline.
I mean, you're forgetting
about your dating options.
We have less than zero money
and no way of paying off our bank loan.
Oh, my God. It happened.
I'm working class.
Hey. I've waited tables
with you for four years
and there's no way you could
call what you do working.
Cupcakes!
Buy cupcakes.
Buy cupcakes!
Stop.
You look more desperate
than Justin Bieber
in that Calvin Klein ad.
You don't understand the seriousness
of this bank situation.
You don't understand the
rules of World Of Warcraft.
The loan just keeps
escalating and escalating
until they close us down.
Cupcakes! Buy cupcakes!
Buy cupcakes! Buy cupcakes!
Oh, Pay-dirt. Look.
Here comes a big, fat frat house guy.
Hey, bitches.
Remember me?
Big Mary.
That's my name. Don't wear it out.
John, we haven't seen you
since pastry school.
Hey, for old times' sake,
want to buy a cupcake?
A dozen? The shop?
So I came because I may know of a way
for Max to make some extra money.
Whatever it is, she'll do it.
That was my yearbook quote.
I just got hired at a new restaurant
that's opening under the High Line Park
in Manhattan, and they are looking
for another day pastry chef.
I only have a year of pastry school
and I was stoned for,
like, a year of that.
I don't know if I have the skills.
[chuckles] Oh, girl, you don't.
But the manager, Joe,
wants only pretty people.
And what you lack in pastry,
you more than make up for in pretty.
She'll do it. You'll do it, Max.
And John will be there
to help back you up
with his pastry skills.
And 'cause I'm pretty.
I don't belong in a place like that.
It's called "The High."
Sounds right. Give me the deets.
Well, good night girls.
Sorry about your bank balance.
But I trust you'll both lapse
into denial fairly soon, as always.
Hello.
Who was she?
Hold me closer, tiny dancer.
Oh... Han's not gay.
You forgot the "yet."
Max, maybe button up a button or two.
It's a dessert bar. Not a strip bar.
Hey, I need this job,
and once this Joe guy takes
one look at these puff pastries,
he might cut me some slack when he sees
my other "not so puff" pastries.
And you're comfortable
with that?
Yup.
Like I guess you're comfortable
applying for a waitress job
on just the merits of
your waitress skills.
Should I keep going?
Why?
I'm here.
I'll take those applications.
Hurry, ladies.
If I was looking for pretty
and slow, I'd hire Nick Jonas.
Max, let's get out of here.
She reminds me of this nightmare
I'm going to have for
the rest of my life.
Relax, she's just his guard dog.
It's Joe guy we have to impress.
No thank you.
And how dare you?
Oh, I'm sorry, the restaurant
doesn't open until tomorrow.
Actually, no.
Hi. I'm here to apply for a waitress job.
At your age?
I'm 27!
And?
Max, I can't breathe.
And I'm here to apply for a pastry chef.
Also 27, but I've looked
this old since I was 6.
For a while, I thought I had
that Benjamin Button's disease.
I'll take the pastry chef first.
Why don't you sit over there and wait.
I won't be long, because frankly,
you don't have the time.
Thank you. I'll be over there.
Applying for Social Security.
So where did you go to pastry school,
and why aren't you working now?
Manhattan School Of
Pastry, and I am working.
I have my own cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
Oh, it's almost over.
This interview? Great.
No. Not the interview. Brooklyn.
Brooklyn's almost over.
Also, cupcakes.
Cool. I will tell them.
Wish I knew that before they all got
their belly buttons pierced
trying to stay cool.
Oh, great. A sense of humor.
Customers love that.
I don't, but they do.
So, um, where's this Joe guy
who's doing the hiring?
There is no "Joe guy". I'm Joe.
Spelled, J-O-E-D-T-H.
The D-T-H is silent.
As am I, because I want this job.
Well, I guess I can put these away then.
That was your plan?
To expose your breasts and
seduce your way into this job?
You say that like it's a bad thing.
Okay. Well, bye.
Sit, sit.
If you really can bake,
this position might be perfect for you.
Also, you have that edgy,
"I don't give a crap" attitude.
Customers love that.
I don't, but they do.
Actually, Joe, silent D-T-H, I can bake.
But how well?
My girlfriend and I are
obsessed with French pastry.
Oh. Girlfriend as in "girlfriend,"
or as in two ladies of a certain age
at a Cineplex splitting
one thing of popcorn?
Everything you just said offended me.
Yeah, that's my brand.
And the fact that you didn't cry
about splitting a popcorn makes me think
it's the first kind of girlfriend.
How are your macaroons?
Uh... oh. Mm.
My macaroons?
Great.
A little bit of French heaven.
What is your name?
Max.
M-a-x.
[clicks teeth]
Nothing is silent. Ever.
So I gather.
Okay. Why don't you go fill
out an application, Max.
And you can put those away again.
I'm really not into big-breasted women.
Girl, you got this.
First day. Are you nervous, girl?
Please. Nervous is telling
your elderly Mormon parents
that you're gay after
your three older siblings
already came out.
I have no idea what most
of these desserts are.
I haven't felt this lost
since the finale of Lost.
Max, can you see any of the
Barney's price tags on these?
Uh, I think there's one bunching up
inside the back of your pants.
No, that's the underwear
I'm also returning.
Here she comes.
Hi, ladies. This is Naomi,
the dessert bar hostess.
Go, Naomi, go.
Gorgeous, but as dumb as whoever
is the hot new idiot right now.
Let me take a look at you.
Good-bye.
Already?
Those pearls. They have to go.
Really? It's just, well,
I'm kind of emotionally
attached to them.
Well, honey, I love my
half-blind French bulldog,
but I don't wear her around my neck.
Max, let me take a look.
Love it.
Fabulous. Well done.
Hi, Joe. Big day. I'm so excited.
Why don't you be excited
in the back, doll?
I want Max up front now.
All my life, people have been
telling me not to come out.
Why should here be any different?
Ladies, I just got word that
the New York Times food critic
may make a surprise
visit this afternoon.
Everything has to be perfect...
the service, the desserts,
the precarious balance of my meds.
Nothing can go wrong.
Naomi.
Fetch.
"Welcome to The High".
"Hi. Welcome to The High".
Stop saying high. It reminds me I'm not.
Wait, Max, you're not high?
Like, not high at all?
No. I didn't want to screw today up.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You can't change who you are today.
The New York Times is coming.
How will you cope?
I mean, when's the last
time you weren't high?
My birth.
But I was really drunk.
I had just had a bottle of wine.
Well, my mother had.
I have to go wait on those customers.
Do what you can to get with the program.
I mean, get off the program.
You can't bake not baked.
Big Mary?
John?
Why not try my new name?
Quasimodo.
Do you have any weed?
Do I have any weed?
Let me check my hump.
Nope. No weed.
Thanks, Rico. I didn't want to ask
due to the city-wide ban
on racial profiling.
Wow. This dish room is cleaner
than Chris Christie's plate after lunch.
Max, I need two lavender macaroons.
- Where are they?
- I'm working on them.
Well, good. I'm so proud of you.
This is so Freaky Friday.
Here are the lavender macaroons.
See? Even just holding this, I'm better.
Now we just have to hope
nothing goes wrong.
(Sophie) Surprise!
We all came to support you.
(Caroline) Well, that's it.
The New York Times food critic
may be in the same room
as Han, Earl, Oleg, and Sophie.
We're dead. Time of death, 11:30.
I believe it's more like 4:20.
Oh, Caroline, I love your new place.
It's so fresh and pretty.
It kind of looks like
a douche commercial.
You're right, baby.
It looks exactly like
a douche commercial.
Okay. Can we stop saying "douche"
in the fancy pastry shop?
I agree. Not appropriate.
Caroline, darling, slip my phone number
to that fine Nubian princess.
And tell her not to be
fooled by my bad hip.
I can still gently rock her world.
Okay, guys, what are you doing here
and how quickly can you leave?
Real nice.
After we came all this way
to just order only desserts
that Max knows how to make
and to say nice things
about you as a waitress.
Oh, you'd do that for me?
Hell no, I can't pull that off.
If I could act, I'd sell the restaurant
and get cast in two-line
roles as the doctor
on any network television show.
Sophie's the actress.
And trust me, she's got
quite a repertoire.
In bed, I call her Meryl Sheets.
Do it, baby.
[Southern Belle accent]
Oh, what a lovely place.
That's the accent she uses when we play
"12 Years A Sex Slave."
Lovely, be right back.
Oh, and, welcome to The High.
(Joedth) What's going
on with that table?
Is there a European circus in town?
A circus? Well, I wouldn't know.
I really have no idea who they are.
That didn't require an answer.
It was just one of my
dead-on observations.
Just get rid of them.
Tell them we've run out of funnel cakes.
Well, I'm feeling like my old self.
Joe just told me to lose
Han, Earl, Oleg, and Sophie.
How am I supposed to
lose that many people?
I'm not air traffic control.
You are acting like they
don't know how to act
in a fancy place.
[Sophie, yelling] Girls, look!
Oleg's wearing his
napkin as a party hat.
[Sophie laughing]
Here's your dessert. Bon appetite.
Max, I can't believe you just made that.
Neither can I.
And what did you say to Oleg and Sophie?
It's been an hour, and I haven't seen
any over-the-table penetration.
I just told them to be
on their best behavior,
and they're fine with it.
Excuse me, Max.
Yes, hi.
May I go tinkle?
Or is that against the law here
at Guantanamo Dessert Bay?
I'm gonna go have sex
in the ladies room.
Unless you two prudes have
a problem with that, too.
Excuse me.
Can I get a latte and a red wine?
[clears throat]
'Cause I got a Vicodin
stuck in my throat.
Oh, my God.
Who could be that messed up
in the middle of the afternoon?
Uh, my new best friend.
I better get rid of her before Joe
or that Times critic walks in.
You keep doing good things by accident.
Hi, can I get a...
You sure can. Anywhere but here.
(woman) Oh, no. Spinning's
not good for me right now.
(Joedth) What is she doing here?
Leaving. You never saw her.
- Wait...
- Joe, I got this.
My bestie at school was totally hooked
on prescription pills for, like, a week.
Hey, hi, you.
Excuse me. Where is Max?
She's in the back for a sec.
So...
We meet again.
Sir, do you need something in the back?
Yes, Caroline said she'd
bring me a napkin,
but I could get Time Warner on
the phone faster than that.
Just ask Max.
She covers for Caroline
all the time at the diner.
Max?
Ooh. Drama at The High.
Han, that's my new boss.
Stop talking.
Also, stop collecting stickers.
You're a grown-up.
Okay, I threw that drug addict out.
That drug addict is my girlfriend.
More drama at The High.
And Caroline, we have a problem.
You called Allie a drug addict.
Oh, is that her name?
Allie? So cute.
Even lovelier.
And according to that very small man,
you're also a terrible waitress.
But I had no idea you two were together.
I would have thought a powerful...
Stop. Now.
Joe, look, we really need these jobs.
We made a bad decision
with our bakery business,
and we have a big bank
loan that we can't pay.
Honesty. Good.
People respond to honesty.
I don't, but they do.
Max, you have potential here.
Caroline, you're fired as a waitress.
Are you sure?
Stop!
There's nothing in there to save you.
Well, if she's fired, I'm fired, too.
Oh, relax, Norma Rae.
She's fired as a waitress,
but she's hired as a hostess.
I am? Why?
Because you're pretty,
you flashed a boob,
and you took more control
of Allie in five minutes
than anybody's been able to
do in her three rehab stints.
And that, lady, is a
New York City hostess.
Well, girls, I struck out.
Bill Cosby has ruined it
for all black men over 70
who are just trying
to buy a gal a drink.
Max, how do you like that?
I'm the hostess. I got a promotion!
I don't think a hostess is a promo...
It is, Max, 'cause with a
less-than-zero bank balance,
it has to be. It's all I have left.
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.