My siblings and I
are the first vampires
in all of history,
The Originals.
Unlike them, I am a hybrid...
half vampire, half werewolf.
300 years ago,
we helped build New Orleans.
Now we've returned, drawn back
by a coven of witches
who threaten the woman
carrying my child.
That baby will bring
death to us all.
Aah! Aah!
My brother
Elijah dealt with them.
No one hurts
my family and lives.
We thought
Hayley would be safe.
I'm Marcel.
I don't think
we've met.
Hayley is gone.
Where is she?
What?
Marcel was here.
We were wrong.
Ladies, gentlemen,
welcome to fight night...
And the first rule
of fight night is,
the vampire left standing
at the end of the night
is one step closer
to the inner circle
and one of these...
a daylight ring.
If you can impress me
with a little ultra-violence,
you too can enjoy the warmth
of the sun on your face.
All you got to do
is kick a little ass.
So here we go.
Our first two contenders...
Felicia and Otto.
Ha ha ha!
Whoo!
Damn, girl, not bad.
Good evening.
I'd like a word.
What do you think
you're doing?
It appears
that we've interrupted
a collection
of filthy amateurs.
We've come here
for the girl.
Give her to us,
or...We kill everyone here.
You two got
a lot of nerve
coming into my home
and making demands.
You're home,
is it?
The girl.
I will not ask again.
I assume you're
talking about Hayley...
yay high, dark hair,
bitchy attitude.
Who is she, anyway?
She's an old friend.
You know how sentimental
I am about old friends.
Well, I ain't
got her,
and before you
start whining,
I did pay her a little
visit last night.
I was feeling
nostalgic.
So I took a trip out
to the plantation
where I used to be
a slave,
and imagine my surprise
when I realized
that the Original
family of vampires
had taken up
residence.
Your girl Hayley
answered the door.
We exchanged hellos.
That was it.
You don't believe me,
look around.
Hell, I'll even
help you find her,
but the question
I'd ask is,
if Hayley
isn't here,
then where is she?
Uh!
Uh! Uh!
Seriously?
You don't want
to fight me, Hayley.
You know you can't
beat a hybrid.
Aah! Let me go,
you backstabbing,
half-breed piece of sh...
shut up!
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.Addic7ed.Com/
Not the most
attractive community,
are they?
You do realize
they can hear you.
I don't care.
You know, Elijah,
I liked you better in that box,
but, Klaus, my sire,
you I owe the world,
and I always show
respect to my elders.
If your special
lady friend is missing,
you can benefit
from the help of a witch,
and since I control
all the witches in this town,
I'll Grant you one
little locator spell.
Sabine is the best guide
in the quarter.
You need to find someone,
I guarantee
she's your girl.
Where are you
going?
I hate to cut this short,
but the sun is coming up soon.
My nightwalkers
need to get inside,
and I've got
a city to run.
I'll leave you to track down
your lost sheep.
Can you find her?
I can try.
What is this place?
The armpit
of Louisiana.
What are you gonna
do with that?
Depends on you.
Hey, you attacked
me, remember?
You ambushed me
in my own back yard.
It's not your back yard.
It's Klaus'.
You're shacked up in
a mansion with that psycho,
a long way from the girl
I met in the appalachians
helping
other werewolves.
Tyler, I'm sorry,
but a lot has happened
since the last time
I saw you.
You mean like
how you're pregnant?
A hybrid baby. Yeah.
I know all about it.
I've been roaming
around the bayou
asking questions.
Let me tell you
what I learned.
This crescent birthmark
means you come
from a big shot family,
some kind of royalty
to the werewolves
of this region,
and right here,
this is all
that's left of them.
Hey, help me.
They can't help you.
They're in
the woods hiding
because they've
been persecuted
for decades
by vampires.
Is that her?
Yeah, Dwayne.
Get her inside.
Tyler? Tyler?
She's in
the back country,
way out past houma,
deep in the bayou.
I don't suppose
you could be more precise.
What's the matter, Elijah,
are you worried a bit suppose
of splashing about in the bog
might ruin
your expensive shoes?
As a matter of fact,
after my recent confinement,
I could use a decent stroll
through the countryside.
There are stories of
exiled werewolves,
encampments.
If Hayley went out
that far,
chances are, she
went to find them.
Clearly, she hopes to make
the acquaintance
of more like herself.
I suppose our company
wasn't good enough for her.
You could always
join them, you know.
Uh, drinking games.
It's not really
my thing.
It kind of reminds me of
the jocks in my High School.
We had a pretty high quota
of what you'd call
douche nozzles.
Bullies, huh?
Yeah.
Wonder what'd happen if
you saw those guys now.
I bet you'd tear
them apart, right?
Ah, yeah, totally.
Ha! Probably go
all vamp ninja on them.
Ha ha ha! You're
a funny guy, Josh.
In fact, I thought
it was really
funny last night,
you know,
seeing you
at that plantation
where Klaus
is staying.
Ho ho! Ha ha ha!
You going
somewhere, Josh?
We should head south
towards the water.
You seem quite determined
to find the little wolf.
If I'm moving too fast
for you, Niklaus,
you're welcome
to wait in the car.
Do be certain to leave
the windows down.
Ah, so I've
touched a nerve.
You've begun
to admire this girl.
Perhaps that's why
you've been barking orders
since your return,
hoping to impress Hayley
by assuming the role
of family patriarch.
You want to insist
on treating her
like a walking
incubator,
then that's
your mistake.
Have you
found her scent?
No...
But I found
someone else's.
This vehicle reeks
of someone I thought
I was rid of...
Tyler Lockwood.
And why would your
little hybrid sidekick
from Mystic Falls have
any interest in Hayley?
He wants revenge because
I went after his girl.
Why do I suspect
this is the least
of your offenses?
Back when I had the means
to sire hybrids,
he was my first,
although I didn't give him
much choice in the matter.
He was loyal
in the beginning,
but he grew
insubordinate,
turned my other hybrids
against me.
I couldn't have that.
So I massacred
the lot of them.
Tyler ran
like a coward
before I could
finish him off.
Anything else that
you would like to share?
Well, there was
this business with his mum.
You killed his mother.
Wonderful.
He needed to be
taught a lesson.
And what lesson will
you be taught, Niklaus,
if he retaliates
by harming Hayley?
So you do care about her.
Well, go on, then.
Have at it, brother.
Save her.
Claim what spoils
you can.
I've sampled what
she has to offer,
and, let me tell you,
she is exquisite.
Niklaus,
so help me...
enough.
I'll kill
Tyler Lockwood myself.
Marcel,
something is happening.
There's a witch doing
magic in the quarter.
Oh, no worries.
That one is Marcel-approved.
Besides...
Oh!
Got something else
for you to handle.
Oh, no. You're
the super witch.
Say hi to Josh.
Why would you
bring him here?
Josh has a problem.
Klaus compelled him
to spy on me.
Agh!
I can't have that.
So I thought,
"I'll just kill Josh."
Marcel, please.
It's not my fault.
Then I thought,
"killing a vampire,
that would be breaking
my own rule."
Smart thing to do
is to flip Josh.
That way, he can tell Klaus
whatever I want.
He could even
spy for me.
All we got to do
is wipe away that compulsion.
So what do you think?
I can make him forget
what Klaus told him,
but the more
Klaus said,
the more it's
gonna hurt.
Hmm, probably gonna
hurt a lot.
Josh?
I'll do it,
anything, yes.
How much pain
are we talking?
R...
anything, yes.
Klaus destroyed everything
good in my life.
So I'm gonna take away
the thing he wants most.
No, please,
Tyler, please.
Aah!
Ggh...
Uh...
Oh!
I thought you were leaving town.
Couldn't stay away, huh?
I was half past Louisiana
when I found out
you invaded our home.
What have you done
with Hayley?
You're so hot
when you're angry.
Uh!
You used me.
I'm pretty sure
that was mutual.
Beguiled by your charms,
I slept with you like a fool,
led you to our home,
and then you took Hayley.
Whoa, I didn't
take anybody.
I already sorted this
out with your brothers,
but it begs
the question,
why'd you come back?
If Klaus learns
it's my fault
you found your way
to the plantation...
you really think
I'd rat you out?
Come on.
If you think that
I'd ever in 1,000 years
do anything to hurt you,
you got me confused
with Klaus.
All your charms
and flirtations
simply prove you're
every bit the liar
and manipulator
that Klaus is.
Is that what
you really think?
By all means,
prove me wrong.
Fine. Come on.
Something
you need to see.
Don't get all judgey.
Dwayne knew what
he was getting into.
He volunteered.
For you to kill him?
Dwayne is a werewolf who died
with your blood in his system,
same blood you share
with your hybrid baby.
You're trying
to turn him.
That's impossible.
Been running with wolf packs
all over the country.
One of them was tight
with a witch.
She had nightmare visions
about your baby
and how Klaus could
use its blood
to make an army
of hybrid slaves.
I am sick
of these witches
and the premonitions
about my baby.
It's just a baby.
Maybe. Maybe not.
That's where
Dwayne comes in.
You see, he was happy
to be the test case.
If you haven't noticed,
these people
don't have much
to live for.
They'd all welcome
the chance to become
the superior species.
Trouble is, all hybrids
are sired to Klaus.
They follow
his every move.
No way I'd
let that happen.
How can you be
so sure Klaus knows
what the baby's
blood will do?
What do you think?
Klaus Mikaelson...
killer of men,
women, and puppies...
all of a sudden
wants to be a daddy,
or he's got
an ulterior motive.
Hybrids can walk
in the sun.
Their bite is lethal
to vampires.
They'll take over New Orleans
by the end of the week,
and you know what's
gonna stop Klaus then?
Nothing.
You're gonna have
to feed on her.
What? No.
Aah...
do it.
No. No! Aah!
Aah!
Dwayne...
easy.
You're ok.
Look at me.
I'm better than ok.
Aagh!
I'm sorry, but it's
just gonna get worse.
Klaus' compulsion
runs deep.
You need to think
of something else,
take your mind
off it.
Do you like music?
What? What?
I can't think
about music right now.
Why? I don't know.
Maybe because you're
giving me a voodoo lobotomy.
Do you like jazz?
Oh...
So what, then?
Club stuff...
house, trance,
you know...
♪ nn ss
nn ss nn ss ♪
I'm a witch.
I'm not amish.
It's just I'm only 16.
I don't go to clubs.
When I was 16,
I'd been to 100 clubs.
God, it was only
4 years ago.
Feels like
another life.
All I wanted to do
was meet boys.
Things are so much
more complicated.
I mean, now all I want
to do is meet boys
and feed
on people's blood,
get one of those
daylight rings
so I don't burn
in the sunlight,
all perfectly
normal things.
I like the classics...
puccini, bach, Mozart.
I took piano,
not that it matters
while I'm stuck here.
Why not?
Marcel is worried
that someone could hear.
It's not his fault.
He just wants
to keep me safe.
Safe from what?
Basically, a coven
of psycho witches
want to sacrifice me
in a blood ritual.
Oh, wow. Ok.
Uh, I'm...Sorry.
Don't be. I'm gonna
destroy them all,
and once
the gone,
everything will
go back to normal.
I'll have
my old life back.
It worked, didn't it?
He's a hybrid.
If Klaus gets
a hold of you,
if he gets that kid,
he wins.
Then help me hide
the baby from him.
Help me run.
He'll find you.
He'll take
your kid away,
and he'll make
more hybrid monsters,
slaves who do
everything he says.
Tyler, whatever you're
thinking of doing,
there has to be
another way.
You're not
like this.
Uh!
Agh! D'ugh!
Agh! That was stupid.
Get away
from her.
What do you care?
I said, get away.
You got what you wanted.
Not get lost.
Dwayne, he's
gonna kill me.
He's gonna
kill you, too.
He said that hybrids
are too dangerous
to live.
You need
to stop him.
Shut up.
Uh!
Agh!
Huh!
Forgive me.
Thought you
were in danger.
It appears
I was mistaken.
You will not believe
the crap day that I'm having.
Let me
take you home.
Elijah...
There's something you need
to know about the baby.
Hayley,
don't make this harder
than it has to be.
Give up now...
I'll end it quick.
Quite an offer,
though not one I'll
be extending to you.
Klaus.
Hello, Tyler.
You look well.
I aim
to change that.
Threatening
a pregnant girl
in order to exact
revenge against me.
I never expected you
to sink so low.
I admit,
I'm impressed.
I used to hang out
with you.
I guess something
must have rubbed off.
What do you think
Caroline would say
if she saw what
you've become?
Perhaps I'll ask her
when I call her
to tell her
of your demise.
Whatever happens to me,
Caroline is never
gonna stop hating you.
Come on, mate.
Give it a bit more effort.
I want to enjoy myself.
What is this place?
This is the garden.
It's where I punish
vampires who break my rules,
but a long time ago,
used to be something else.
Go on.
Tell me what you see.
Two stories,
Greek columns,
wraparound porch,
high ceilings,
transom windows.
It's lovely.
So what?
So I designed it for you.
It was gonna be ours.
That...
this was supposed to be
our happily ever after?
Yours and mine,
except you flew the coop
with Klaus.
I already built
the foundation for the place.
I halted construction
after you took off.
Plan was to wait
for you to return.
You never did.
So now it's where I bury
the people who betray me.
You could've
come after me.
You were with Klaus.
I didn't know where.
I didn't know if you
still wanted to be with me.
All you had to do
was come home.
It was more
complicated than that.
Not long after
we left here,
he put a dagger
in my heart
and stuck me in
a box for 90 years.
He stole a century from
me like it were nothing.
That's what he does,
Rebekah.
Klaus will never
be happy.
He'll be damned if he
ever lets anyone
get something that
he can't have.
I know.
I've been dancing
to this song
for 1,000 years.
Starting right now,
you have a choice
between the brother who
takes away your happiness
whenever he feels like it
and the man who wants
to give you everything
you ever wanted.
He will kill you
in front of my eyes
out of spite.
Not if we get
rid of him first.
Klaus
must have known.
That's the only
explanation.
He could care less
about the baby.
He just wants her
to be born
so he can use her to
make more sired hybrids.
Although the way
that Dwayne was acting,
it was more like
he was sired to me.
I should
take you home.
Are you serious?
Home to what?
Look. Regardless
of my brother's intentions,
mine remain the same.
I said that I
would protect you,
even, if need be,
from Klaus himself.
I can take care
of myself.
I've done it
for a long time.
Is this your idea
of revenge, Tyler,
grueling game
of hide-and-seek?
D'aagh!
Rraagh!
Let's end this,
shall we?
Raagh!
How dare you?
I'm just
getting started.
Aagh!
You've grown
bloodthirsty.
Perhaps it's best
your mother didn't live
to see you like this.
Ha ha ha!
Yah!
It's sad, really.
I thought
I made you better.
Turns out, you're
quite the disappointment.
Yaah!
I guess I'm another one
of your failures,
like how you failed
at making hybrids,
how you failed
your family.
Now it looks like
you're even
gonna fail
your own kid.
And thus ends your
tedious, little life.
At least it was brief.
Yaagh! Ugh...
Do it.
You're never
gonna break me.
Only thing you
could do is kill me.
So go on. Go on.
Get it over with.
Ah...
You want me to end
your suffering, don't you?
Hmm? I did break you,
took everything from you,
and now you're begging me
to sweep away the shards
of your shattered,
little life.
Death offers more peace
than you deserve.
It's better
to let you live,
and each morning,
you will wake knowing
that your wretched
existence continues
only by my will.
Now go and live
the rest of your days
knowing you
are nothing to me.
Do you know how many
fools have tried
to vanquish
my brother?
If you stand against
him, he will kill you,
and it will be
awful and bloody,
and I will not stand
around and watch.
You forget I have
a secret weapon... Davina,
the most powerful witch
in the last couple centuries.
What if she can find
a way to kill him?
You don't know,
do you?
You can't
kill Klaus,
not without
dying yourself.
We learned it
from the deaths
of my brothers
Kol and Finn.
If an Original dies,
every vampire
ever made from their
line dies with him.
Even if you kill Klaus,
he'll still win.
It's been that way
for 1,000 years.
That's his trick.
He always wins.
There's
another way.
What would that be?
We bury him
down here forever.
Are you mad?
This little chamber
of horrors may work
for your riffraff,
but do you really think
it will hold
my brother?
Isn't it worth the risk?
You know I'm right.
Klaus will never stop
trying to control you.
And I'm supposed
to believe
that after a century,
suddenly you're willing
to risk death at
his hands to be with me?
I want to defend
my home.
I want to be free,
and if that means
I get to be with you,
all the more reason
to bury him.
Now you tell me,
what do you want?
There you are.
I see you found
our wandering stray.
Perhaps she could
shed some light
on the situation.
This...
Would appear to be
the body of a hybrid.
His name
was Dwayne.
Well, whoever he was,
I didn't sire him.
Any idea how
that's possible?
As if you
didn't know.
Ah...
Aren't you two
fast friends?
Well, come on, then.
What horrible accusation
have you conspired
to Levy against me?
Tyler Lockwood brought Hayley
here to test a theory,
that the blood of her child
could be used to sire hybrids.
He claims you knew that.
Furthermore,
you intended
to use this knowledge
to build an army.
And, of course, you
assume it's true.
I mean, why else
would I show
any interest in my
own flesh and blood?
A heartbroken,
little crybaby
points his finger at me,
and my own brother
falls in line,
eager to believe it.
How quickly you
assume the worst,
especially when
it comes from her.
Oh, spare me
you indignation.
When have you ever demonstrated
any kind of concern
towards Hayley
or her child
beyond your own
selfish pursuits,
and what was it
you once said to me?
"Every King
needs an heir."
My big brother,
so you doubt
my intentions.
Well, I can't say
I'm surprised.
Standing beside
the noble Elijah,
how can I be anything
but the lesser brother...
a liar, a manipulator,
a bastard?
That's all I am
to you, isn't it,
and to Rebekah,
and judging
by the way Hayley hangs
on your every word,
it's clear she feels
the same way.
No doubt, my child
will, as well.
Brother, if I...
we've said all that
needs to be said,
brother.
I'll play the role
I've been given.
Agh!
Klaus!
Oh...
You two enjoy each
other's company.
You'll have much
to bond over
once the hallucinations
and dementia set in.
Consider that bite
my parting gift
to you both.
Oh...
That's it.
You're free.
Uh...
You're right.
I can feel it.
Before, I was
always thinking
about what Klaus
would want me to do.
Now I'm like ,
"screw that guy."
Ha! Ha ha ha!
Klaus Mikaelson
can suck it. Ha!
What? What's
that look for?
Marcel wants me to make you
forget about me.
Oh, well, you don't
have to do that.
I owe you my life.
I'll keep
your secret.
Besides,
it's kind of nice
just talking to someone
normal again.
You think I'm normal?
I'm a 16-year-old witch
living in a church attic
like some kind
of freak.
I'm a gay club kid
who died
and came back
as a vampire.
Ha ha!
Yeah.
Normal is kind of
relative, you know?
Here.
Pinky swear on it.
You don't
have to help.
I can dig through the
werewolf antique show
on my own.
Besides, shouldn't
you put some kind
of ointment or
something on that?
The bite
won't kill me.
Like Niklaus himself,
it's more of a nuisance
than anything,
really.
Good, because
I'm eventually
gonna need
a ride home...
And thanks,
by the way,
for staying
out here.
You didn't have to.
I know,
but you said
the people
of this village
are all of the family
you have left.
I can relate.
You're thinking
about Klaus.
Perhaps I was too willing
to condemn him.
In the 1,000 years
that we have been together,
my brother has committed
numerous unspeakable acts,
but, then again,
so has Rebekah.
So have I.
So did I the last
time I was in Cabo.
We all do bad things.
It's just,
most people die
before the list
gets embarrassing,
but don't
for a second
compare yourself
to Klaus.
Heh.
It's like a freaking
hotbox in here.
I'm gonna
get some air.
Someone
left this here.
What is it?
A Bible with
a family tree
that goes back
generations.
What are these names?
Who is Andrea?
I think I am.
That's the day
that I was born.
I thought you
were leaving us.
We both know
this family
can barely function
without me.
Where are Elijah
and Hayley?
I left them
in the bayou.
Why?
Elijah and I had
a bit of a row.
Ha ha ha!
Hayley has conspired
to turn him against me,
and you know our brother
never was one
to resist
a pretty face.
So one thing led to
another, and I bit him,
left them both
stranded in the swamp.
Daggering, biting,
deserting.
Does your wickedness
ever end?
My wickedness
is self-preservation,
and I wouldn't have
to go to such lengths
were I not beset
on all sides
by incompetence
and treachery.
Now that Elijah
has abandoned me,
I'll be needing you
in my plot against Marcel.
Don't expect to be
leaving town any time soon.
Why should
I help you
after what you
did to Elijah?
You're my family.
Besides, who better
to spy on Marcel
than the girl he
so clearly loves?
You can tell me
all his secrets,
like how did he
find us here, huh?
Any idea about that,
little sister?
How should I know
why Marcel
does what he does?
You think I don't know
about your engineered run-ins
all over the quarter?
I know you've had
private chats with him.
So just tell me what secrets
he's confided to you.
Is he plotting
against me?
My poor brother,
so paranoid.
Marcel
knows nothing.
He is not plotting
against you.
He simply thinks
you're in a quarrel,
in need
of making up.
Perhaps we will.
After all, you know I'm
capable of forgiving
those who disappoint me
soon as they've seen
the errof their ways
and suffered for them.
You'd do well
to remember that.
You never
let me forget.
You want to make
a deal with me,
you got to offer me
something.
I already know about
Hayley the werewolf girl.
What else you got?
What if I told you
that werewolf girl
is carrying
Klaus' child...
And if that baby
is born,
it'll mean the end
of the vampire species?
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.Addic7ed.Com/