[Sizzling]
_
Lars: He's really... it's really messed up.
Hey, hello. Habla English?
Hey, are you the son? Ow!
Grandson.
_
She hit... hit him while driving.
- My leg. El smack-o.
- [Speaking spanish]
- Look. Look.
Just a crazy old biznatch
who ran over my brother.
Cal: It hurts so bad.
It hurts so bad. [Grunts]
It hurts so bad.
Look at that. Yeah, it's this one.
- My leg.
- She... she broke his leg.
And then she stood on the gas.
It's a hit-and-run.
She... she felonied me. That's a felony.
Got the whole thing...
Got the whole thing right here.
- Ay, dios mio.
- Okay, hold on. Hold on.
- L... let me talk to her.
- So, start talking.
- Yeah, good.
- [Crying]
_
Aah! Look.
He can't... he can't put
any pressure on it.
I need to lean on you, so...
I think it's... it's definitely broken.
Es muy mal for my leg-o.
Here. Lean up... lean up on the mantel.
No, man, it really hurts.
Just hang in there. Hang in there.
- "Muy mal"?
- Yeah, it's muy mal.
Dude.
- Dude.
- Yes, si, problema.
Shh, shh, shh!
- And now dos problemas. Aah!
- Dude!
Si, d-dos big problemas.
[Grunting]
I don't know what you're saying, man.
- Dude.
- Si.
We got a real problem here...  Si.
Yeah, si, problema. Shh.
Ay, dios mio. Ay, dios mio.
- [Speaking spanish]
- [Door closes]
Hey, amigo, what are you gonna
do about this leg situation?
I really need to see a doctor.
A doctor... doctors ain't cheap,
yo. It's gonna cost.
Either you or her... somebody's got to pay.
[Grunts] You want money.
Yes! Yeah, damn straight.
Hit-and-run? It's no joke.
We're... what are the cops gonna say?
- Cops?
- [Tv chatter in distance]
They coming?
- Y... yeah, yeah, maybe.
- That's up to you, man.
They... the cops...
They can be looking
at this tape anytime now.
It's all up to you.
[Inhales sharply] Aah!
Oh, that's really bad.
[Grunts] You c-called her "biznatch"?
- I didn't...
- Yeah, but whatever, man.
Please, hurry it up. I'm hurting here.
Show us the green,
or LA policia is gonna come,
and they're gonna be taking granny away!
She's gonna go to jail. Do you want that?
Yeah, that's right... play it smart.
Okay, good. So, let's talk dollar amounts.
For what you did to my... [grunts]
[Both groan]
No! No!
Biznatch.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.Com
[conversing in Spanish]
[Thudding]
[Conversing continues]
[Thudding continues]
[Door creaks]
Mijo?
Mijo...
_
Ah, si.
No, abuelita.
_
[chuckles]
Ay, mijo.
A-abuelita.
_
[gasps]
Oh. Bueno.
_
si. Si.
Si.
[Door closes]
[Beeping]
[Speed-dialing]
Hi. Get over here.
Uh, my abuelita's.
Bring No-doze and tell Nacho
to bring his van.
[Beep]
[Sighs]
[Spits]
[Knock on door]
[Sighs]
Jimmy: Open up! Officer of the court!
Open up in the name of the law!
Good afternoon. This...
[Breathing heavily]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. I'm showing hands.
I'm... I'm relaxed... okay?...
Um, non-threatening.
You move, and you're dead.
Got it.
Seems to be a misunderstanding.
Is there, by any chance,
a Betsy kettleman here?
See, I'm not sure if this is a situation
where I should or should not
look you in the eye.
[Sighs] Sit.
[Breathing heavily]
Who are you?
Are you with those redheaded scumbags?
My name's James McGill. I'm an attorney.
Uh, I got a call from some clients, uh,
said something about an accident.
I did not get any details.
When I saw some skateboards
in your front yard,
- I assumed they might...
- [Door opens]
Mijo...
_
si, si.
[tv chatter in distance]
[Door closes]
[Dog barking in distance]
Talk.
I'm gonna make an educated guess
what happened here.
My two clients,
frick and frack, the mopheads,
were in a simple traffic
accident, a minor Fender bender,
but maybe they were
on the wrong side of the street,
or they didn't look both ways.
It could happen to anyone. [Chuckles]
My clients, exhibiting
extremely poor judgment,
uh, followed your grandmother
to this delightful, well-tended home.
[Clears throat]
Now, at this juncture, I'm deducing
that they said or did something
that... Crossed a line,
and you, with some justification...
You put them in their place.
[Sighs]
Based on the salsa stain there,
could have gone a couple ways.
The bottom line... not to be morbid,
but if they're dead,
um, I'm guessing that I'm...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Yeah, I'm gonna go
with glass half full here
and say they're not.
Uh, my point is, if they're
still alive, why kill us? Why?
Because of a misunderstanding?
Our own stupidity?
Why mess up your lovely abuelita's place?
[Chuckles]
Why jump to the nuclear option?
See, I'm saying keep it simple.
I will collect my moronic clients, and...
Poof! We are gone.
Neither you nor your lovely abuelita
will ever lay eyes on us
ever again, guaranteed...
Signed, sealed, and delivered.
[Breathing heavily]
Assuming, you know,
that they're still breathing.
[Sniffs]
Wow.
You got a mouth on you.
Thank you.
Get up.
That way.
- That way.
- Y... Yeah, sure. Why not?
[Door creaks]
[Muffled grunting]
So, what... I should cut 'em loose?
[Grunting continues]
Oh! It was him! It was all his idea!
No, no, no!
Tuco: You shut up!
Say what?
He... he wanted to scam you.
He said we could clear 2 grand, easy.
[Muffled grunting]
You punking me?
[Gun cocks]
Are you punking my abuelita?
He hit his head.
He doesn't know what he's saying.
[Breathing heavily, grunting]
For what?
For what are you getting 2 grand?
It was for going after your grandma,
just for taking a header over
her car and then b-bracing her.
It was him, I swear! It was the lawyer!
[Grunting continues]
[Breathing heavily]
[Muffled grunting]
Who are you?! Why are you after me?!
I can explain. It's... you're gonna laugh.
It's so... I'm a lawyer.
I... check my I.D., okay?
But I was running a scam.
- On my abuelita?
-  No, no!
Not on your abuelita, not on you.
There's a woman named Betsy Kettleman.
I mentioned her.
She's married to Craig Kettleman.
He's the treasurer of Bernalillo County.
I wanted his business 'cause...
He stole a million and
a half bucks from the county.
He's gonna be indicted
for embezzlement any day now.
This is a good case for me...
A lot of publicity.
I'll get my name out, and...
Anyway, I thought if I had these two
run their little skateboard
hustle on Mrs. Kettleman,
I could, you know, rescue her.
Come in, throw some oil on troubled waters,
and, yeah, I'd get their business.
That was the plan.
But it turns out your lovely abuelita...
She drives a car... [chuckles]
That's a whole lot like the Kettle-mobile.
So, these two geniuses ran their
little stunt on the wrong one.
So, joke's on me. Ha ha!
I... simple as that.
[Muffled grunting]
[Breathing heavily]
Where's he going? W..
Talk to me, okay?
[Door creaks]
Who do you think I am? What is he getting?
[Metal clangs]
I was running a scam to get a client.
I made a mistake. That's all this is.
- Oh, geez.
- [Muffled grunting]
Y-you don't need...
That's not... I'll talk, okay?
Tell me what you want to know!
Who do... who do you think I am?
Hey, use your words, okay?
- What?
- [Sniffs]
You know what I smell?
I smell lies.
I smell pork.
No, that's not necessary.
Okay, we know you're with
the heat. The question is, who?
- Local? FBI?
- No, no, no.
D.E.A.?! No, I'm a lawyer.
Just reach in my pocket
right now... right there!
Truth.
[Gasps, groans]
[Grunts] That is the truth!
I'm a lawyer! Guys, I passed
the bar! Ask me anything!
Not contract law, okay? I'm down
at the courts every day!
People know me!
I'm a known quantity... I am!
Aah!
I'm... I'm special agent
Jeffrey Steele, FBI.
- FBI?
I'm undercover, okay? You got me.
I'm the tip of the spear,
and releasing me would be the smart move.
You hear that shit?
I told you the business was too good.
I knew it. I told you.
Can I?
Okay, uh, Special Agent, uh, Steele?
Jeffrey A. Steele.
Okay, Agent Steele,
what business are we in?
Business?
You're investigating us, right?
For what? What did we do?
- What do we sell?
- Drugs.
- What kind of drugs?
- Uh...It's title 21,
schedule II through schedule V,
including part "B."
That's what we call them
down at the bureau.
It's... the task force
is designated "Operation King Breaker."
"King Breaker"? So...
That makes me the king! Whoo-hoo!
Can I?
All right.
The next words out of your mouth
got to be the truth.
You understand?
Uh-huh.
Who are you?
I'm James Morgan McGill. I'm a lawyer.
I was trolling for business,
okay? That's the truth.
Now, you find a Bible, I'll swear on it.
Okay, what about, uh, operation,
uh, King Breaker, FBI?
I made it up, okay? I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't know you. I don't want to.
Uh, this was a mistake, oka...
It's my mistake, okay?
I take full and complete responsibility,
but I don't know any of your names,
and I got a bad case of face-blindness.
You let us go, we're gonna
forget this happened.
Guys, we're gonna forget, right?
- Nod your heads.
- [Muffled grunting]
Okay?
So, if you just let us go and just...
We want to just go... home.
[Metal clangs]
I say cut 'em loose.
He said he was FBI. He admitted it.
You had your wire cutters on him.
He would have said anything.
You really see the FBI
hiring those two flaquitos?
Maybe.
Croaking a lawyer
for no reason is bad business.
He goes away, someone's
gonna come look for him.
They walked into my house.
They disrespected my abuelita.
They call her "biznatch"!
[Muffled grunting]
And they just walk?! Unh-unh!
What about the lawyer?
[Sighs]
He's giving respect.
Okay.
"James M. McGill.
A lawyer you can trust."
I know how to find you, James McGill.
Understand what I'm saying?
Yeah.
[Muffled grunting]
Up.
[Breathing heavily]
Okay?
Take him back to his car.
Thank you.
Uh, uh, this is... this is good.
This... this is right. Thank you. Come on.
[Muffled screaming]
What... what... what about them?
- Gonzo: Come on.
- Yeah, right.
- Come on.
- Uh, yeah, right.
[Screaming continues]
- Whoa. Uh...
- Yo, where you going?
Uh, wait. Can I... can I say something?
- Where you going?
- Can you let them go?
- Just let them go.
- Are you stupid?
They don't deserve to die.
I put them up to it.
I don't deserve to die,
but they don't, either.
I'm gonna skin them, like javelinas!
Forget about them! They're insects!
They're... hey, think about their mother.
[Spits] I spit on their mama!
She is a sweet little lady.
She... she's a widow.
She works hard all day, every day,
just like her mother before her,
from dawn till dusk,
scrubbing the floors of rich people.
She needs a cane to walk, you know?
She's got arthritis.
And still, she works every day.
What... for herself? No. No.
For them... for these two,
her boys, her apples of her eye.
You say they don't deserve her?
Maybe so, but they're all she's got.
Now...You turn them inside out,
I want you to think
about what happens to her.
No, that's on them.
They should have thought about that.
When I was at your abuelita's place,
you were gonna let them go.
Way I see it, that's because
you're tough, but you're fair.
You're all about justice.
That's what I'm saying... justice.
These... these two shit-for-brains?
These big-mouths?
You... you already beat
the living hell out of them.
Do you think they're ever
gonna forget today?
Never... 10 years from now,
they're still gonna
be crapping their jockeys.
- It's not enough.
- Okay, okay.
Then let's talk proportionality.
They're guilty... oh, agreed.
[Muffled grunting]
Now you have to decide,
what's the right sentence?
Like a judge.
Ever hear of the code of Hammurabi...
Let the punishment
fit the crime, eye for an eye?
Eye for an eye.
You want me to blind them.
- [Muffled grunting]
- No, no.
All they did was trash-talk.
- So I cut their tongues out!
- [Muffled screaming]
Wait. See, I'm advising...
That you make the punishment fit the crime.
[Exhales sharply]
Punishment fit the crime.
Columbian neckties... I cut their throats,
and then I pull their
lying tongues through the slits!
- [Muffled screaming]
- "Biznatch"!
Or you... you could give them black eyes.
Black eyes? [Laughs] That ain't nothing.
No-doze: That one there, homes...
He already got a black eye, fool.
Stop helping.
Or you could sprain their ankles.
- Sprain?
- They're... they'reskateboarders, right?
That... that's how they run their scam.
[Scoffs] They can't skate.
You... you hit them where they live.
I ain't spraining nothing, bitch.
I'm gonna break their arms,
and I'm gonna break their legs.
Arms? When... when...
When did we get on to arms?
- Let's...
- I'm cutting their legs off.
But... we could go that way,
but...We were talking about breaking.
I think we're heading
in the wrong direction.
Okay.
Break their legs.
How many legs?
Two... they got two legs.
One leg... each.
One leg... each?
They're... [sighs]
One leg each, that's a total of two legs.
- Uh, hey, look.
- [Muffled shouting]
They can't skateboard for six months,
and they're scared of you forever.
You show everybody that you are the man,
but that you're fair, that you're just.
[Muffled screaming]
- One leg each.
- [Muffled screaming]
That's tough, but it's fair.
All right, lay 'em out!
I ain't got all day!
It's hotter than shit out here!
[Muffled screaming]
Quit moving...
You're only gonna make it worse!
We're sorry! We're sorry!
- [Bone cracks]
- [Screaming]
[Laughs] Lookit!
Hell, yeah! Hell, yeah!
He said he had a broke leg...
Now he's got one for real!
You... tell your mama you're sorry, bitch!
Other one.
Look... it's backwards. [Laughs]
[Screaming continues]
Check it out.
I'm gonna do this one real clean.
No! Oh, my God! No!
- [Bone cracks]
- [Laughs] Whoo!
[Laughs] Walk home now, bitch!
[Both crying]
Shut up! Shut up!
[Both groaning]
[Tires screech]
[Groaning]
[Horn honks]
[Gasping]
Here you go. Here you go. Easy, easy.
- You... you... you... aah! Aah!
- Save your breath.
You... you are... you are the worst lawyer,
the worst lawyer ever!
Hey, I just talked you down
from a death sentence...
- Oh, my God! Oh, my!
- ...to six months' probation.
I'm the best lawyer ever.
Dude, dude, dude, oh!
Oh, my God! Oh! No!
- [Scatting]
- ♪ cha-cha-cha ♪
♪ cha-cha-cha ♪
- [Latin music plays]
♪ Cha-cha-cha ♪
♪ cha-cha-cha ♪
♪ zu-zu-zu-zu ♪
♪ zu-zu-zu, zu-zu ♪
[Scatting]
- [Loud crack]
-♪ do-do-do, do-do ♪
♪ do-do-do, do-do ♪
- [Loud crack]
-♪ do-do-do-do, do-do-do-do ♪
♪ do-do-do, do-do-do ♪
♪ cha-cha-cha ♪
[Loud cracking]
[Cracking continues]
[Music distorts]
[Echoing cracks]
[Distant screaming]
Could you, uh...
Could you, um... I'll be right back.
[Door creaks]
[Vomits]
[Coughs, gulps]
[Gags]
[Humming]
[Gas hissing]
[Steam hisses]
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
Ground yourself?
[Sighs]
Jimmy, did you ground yourself?
[Sighs] Ohh.
I don't think you grounded yourself.
Jesus.
Jimmy, you didn't drive like this, did you?
[Snoring]
Oh, no.
No. I knew it.
[Grunts] Ohh.
Ah. Oh.
Aah.
[Chuckles]
[Breathing heavily]
[Clock ticking]
[Sighs]
[Lawn mower running in distance]
[Birds chirping]
[Sighs]
[Groaning]
Chuck.
Coffee?
Yeah, thanks.
You're gonna have to take it black.
We're out of milk?
Oh, sorry.
[Sighs]
Why are you in that space blanket?
You brought your cellphone
in here last night.
It was in your pants pocket.
Oh.
Sorry about that. [Sighs]
Where, uh... where is it?
Outside... I threw it out the door.
Yeah.
How did I get here?
Your car's not outside,
so I'm assuming taxi.
[Sighs] Right.
Uh, the bartender... wouldn't let me drive.
- [Buckle jingling]
- [Sighs]
[Sniffs, sighs]
[Sighs] Why are you in that space blanket?
I told you... you brought
your cellphone into my house.
Uh, Chuck, um, did you...
[Sighs]
Chuck, did you read this?
Read what?
Uh, this, um, this bill... did you read it?
Emergency-room bill...
Yeah, I may have glanced at it.
It fell out of your pocket.
Hey, Chuck, listen,
I... I know how this looks.
I'm down to my last dime, and, suddenly,
I'm paying for broken legs, but...
It's... it's not that.
I swear. [Chuckles]
This represents a good thing, ultimately.
Okay.
I... I'm not backsliding.
This isn't slippin' Jimmy.
Fine.
Take off the space blanket,
will you, please, Chuck?
It helps.
Take off the space blanket.
I didn't do anything wrong.
It has nothing to do with that.
It was your phone.
[Sighs]
Take off the space blanket.
Why?
Take off the space blanket, Chuck.
Come on. Take off the blanket.
[Grunts]
Thank you.
[Sighs]
Front yard?
Mm.
[Dog barking in distance]
Uh, do you have any idea where it landed?
No.
[Sighs]
[Zipper closes]
[Lawn mower running in distance]
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
[Telephone ringing]
Woman: No.
No.
No. No.
What do you want?
Not to starve to death.
What do you say?
Got something for me?
[urinating]
- [Urinal flushes]
- [Sniffs]
[Zipper closes]
[Sighs]
[Water runs]
It's showtime, folks.
[Coins drop]
[Beeping]
[Indistinct conversations]
- [Buzzer]
- Globis, lawyer.
I'm gonna kill him.
"Your honor, I'm very sorry.
I'll never do it again."
- Say what?!
- Just...
Your honor, I'm very sorry,
and I'll never do it again.
Okay, Mr. Pearson, up you go.
Up you go. All right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Whoa, whoa! Whoa, whoa!
- What's this?
- I told you a suit, remember?
Told you you want to look sharp.
That's a loaner, okay?
I need it back. Let's go.
- Petty with a prior.
- The kid took a slice of pizza.
- Look, the parents are a train wreck.
There's no food in the house!
He was hungry!
- Petty with a prior.
- Come on!
[Paper rustles]
[Brakes squeal]
- You're light on stickers.
- Jimmy: Come on.
- $5.
- You serious?
You got four. You need five.
There's four 90-minute stickers there.
You've been here 6 hours and 5 minutes.
It takes 10 minutes to walk down here!
$5, or you go get another sticker.
[Tires screech]
This makes you feel real important, huh?!
Not enough stickers! More stickers!
[Toilet flushes]
It's showtime, folks.
[Inhales sharply]
It's showtime.
[Indistinct conversations]
- Petty with a prior.
- [Urinal flushes]
Prior will stay on his sheet for life.
Petty with a prior.
[Sighs] You're overcharging him.
[Indistinct conversations]
That lady up there...
She shorts me every time, okay?
This is not a me problem...
This is a you problem.
[Sighs]
[Inhales sharply]
It's showtime.
[Keys jingling]
What? It's from a movie.
[Indistinct conversations]
Hey!
[Indistinct shouting]
- Petty with a prior.
- Misdemeanor shoplifting.
- Come on. Meet me halfway.
- Petty with a prior.
- [Sighs] I can't do it.
- Okay, or how about this?
I plead the kid to the sheet,
but you give me a continued sentence.
And in six months, if he's still clean,
you file for a dismissal.
Come on. Is this how
you want to spend your time?
You can have the rest of these.
[Buzzer]
Berger, lawyer.
Oh, Mr. Berger,
we've met before, haven't we?
Mr. Edison, like the inventor?
I'm James McGill.
I'll be your lawyer.
Doesn't matter. Judge has
got to see your mother.
Well, do you know anybody
who looks like her?
No, an Uncle won't do it.
Okay, so, a fire was started.
We all know that.
Freezing, shivering, as she is now.
In fact, wrote a book about it.
[Clicks tongue]
To make some cookies.
But because you...
...Given her this name...
You can see that this man...
Chose... A bonehead move.
[Brakes squeal]
[Gear clicks]
Like a troll under a bridge!
"You must have the stickers,
or you won't pass!"
Troll alert here... don't feed it!
[Indistinct conversations]
[Bell jingles]
Chao chi c'ung, ladies.
[All speaking Vietnamese]
Good evening, Mrs. Nguyen.
No mail.
Hey, Vicki, Maggie.
[Man singing in native language]
[Door opens, closes]
[Washing machine rumbling]
[Keys jingling]
[Lock turns]
[Door scraping]
[Sighs]
[Exhales deeply]
[Blows]
[Dial tone]
Female voice: You have...Zero messages.
[Button clicks]
[Sighs]
[Desk scraping]
[Sniffs]
- [Metal creaking]
- [Groans]
[Sighs]
[Indistinct conversations in distance]
[Door opens]
[Knock on door]
- [Door thuds]
- Customer.
- What?
- For you... a customer, waiting now.
Oh, uh, sure, sure. Uh, give me a minute.
[Humming]
[Desk scraping]
[Breathing heavily]
[Exhales sharply]
[Clears throat]
Welcome, welcome.
My office is being painted.
Excuse the temporary, uh...Quarters.
Wow. Cozy.
Just me. [Chuckles]
Tuco freaked you out, huh?
It's cool. He doesn't know I'm here.
So, uh... what can I do for you?
I've been thinking about what you said
out there in the desert.
Those people
that you were trying to scam...
How much did they steal?
Um, north of a million
and a half bucks... I think.
So, they have a million
and a half bucks somewhere.
In what, cash?
I don't... well...
Why are you asking me?
- I'm gonna rip them off.
- Oh.
I like ripping off thieves
'cause they can't go to the
cops... they have no recourse.
Mm.
You point me
at where they have their cash...
I'll pay you... a what do you call it?...
A finder's fee... call it 10%, 100 large.
Well, uh, why w... why would you
come to me for that?
You already tried ripping them off.
I'm gonna finish what you started.
I... I wasn't trying to rip them off.
I... I just wanted their business.
- Okay. [Chuckles]
- [Sighs]
I don't know where their money is.
Smart guy like you could figure it out.
If I know what I need to know,
nobody gets hurt.
We rip them off... easy money.
Hey, look, I'm a lawyer, not a criminal.
[Chuckles]
You are shitting me.
I crossed a line. I made a mistake.
I'm not doing that again, not ever.
I got between you and tuco.
Do you think you'd be here
now... I kept my mouth shut?
And I appreciate that. I owe you.
A-and if you're ever in trouble,
God forbid, legal trouble,
I will be there, 24-7, as a lawyer.
What's your angle?
No... no angle. [Chuckles]
And I'm not saying anything
about this to anybody.
As far as I'm concerned, you're a client.
This is a consultation,
and everything you just told me
is privileged.
You rat, you die.
And that, too, yes.
[Pen clicks]
For when you figure out you're in the game.
I'm not in the game.
- [Door opens]
- I... I promise.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Woman singing in native language]