Kites, ho!
ALL:
Excuse me.
You're misusing the word "ho."
It's an interjection used
to call attention
To a destination, not an object,
as in, uh, "Land, ho!"
Or, uh, "Westward, ho!"
ALL:
Kites, ho!
Hey, guys.
Whatcha doin'?
Going out to discover
electricity?
If you're referring to the work
of Benjamin Franklin,
He did not
"discover electricity,"
He merely used a kite
to determine
That lightning "consists"
of electricity.
Also invented
the Franklin stove,
Bifocals and the flexie
urinary catheter.
Kites, ho.
We're heading out
for some kite fighting.
"Kite ghting"?
Oh, yeah.
It's an extremely competitive,
cutthrt sport.
Well, actually, the risk of
throat cutting is very low.
On the other hand,
severe string burn is a real
And ever-Present danger.
You want to come watch?
, gee...
Sounds amazing.
But, um, I've got some
friends coming over.
Not a big thing--
We're just
Gonna watch the Nebraska game.
Oh. Football, sure.
(Sotto ve):
Good guess.
I would've invited you, but I
know you're not a footbl fan.
, no, I'm not, so... great.
You've got plans
Doing something you like,
I've got plans
Doing something I like,
so 's good.
Well, maybe we'll hang out
later--
You know,
after everybody's gone.
Yeah, great.
See ya.
Well, this sucks.
I'm sorry, I got bored
and drifted off.
Where exactly in the interaction
did the sucking lie?
Leonard just realized that
Penny's been hiding him
From her friends
because he's a tiny, little man
Who flies kites.
Oh, that certainly would suck.
* Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state *
*hen nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! *
* T Earth began to cool
* The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed too *
* We built the Wall
* We built the pyramids *
* Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery *
* Bang! *
Wolowitz is trying
to outflank us.
Let out some string,
add altitude
And I'll go under
and cut his line.
Why wouldn't Penny want
her friends to meet me?
Focus, Leonard, focus!
The heat of battle is upon us.
The dogs of war are unleashed.
Maybe Koothrappali's right.
Maybe I embarrass her.
You're embarrassing me
right now.
A grown man woying
about such nonsense
When in the middle
of flying kites.
Sorry.
Sorry won't bring
their kites down.
Ow!
String burn!
Oh, they thinkwe're flanking
They're playing
righ into our hands.
On the count of three,
we execute the flying scissor.
One, two...
Whoa!
Did you see that?
See what?
That chick--
She smiled at me.
No, she didn't.
Yes, she did.
Come on,
scissors, scissors!
Hold my line.
Wait.
What are you doing?
I can't scissors by myself!
Howard!
Come back!
SHELDON:
Victory!
Son of a bitch.
You're a sucky friend,
you know that?
A sucky, sucky friend.
What was supposed to do?
She gave me that
"come-Hither" look.
If she gave you
any look at l. It
was a "you suck" look.
I would've caught up to her
if I hadn't pulled a hammy.
Oh, please,
you weh 80 pounds.
You don't have a hammy.
So, Penny doesn't want
around her friends.
I embarrass her.
Whatlse could it be?
Well, her actions
Could be out of concernfor your feelings
Perhaps she's excluded you
from these gatherings
Because she's scouting
for a new mate
And don't want to do it
in front of you.
Oh... how kind of her.
Agreed.
Most primates don't show
that sort of discretion.
A female bonobo will
copulate with a new male
front of the old one
Without so much
as a "hodo you do?"
You always do this,
you know?
You ditch me for a woman
u don't have a shot with.
I totally had a shot.
With a woman
You were chasi
through a park--
That's not a shot,
that's a felony.
What's worse, it cost me
my prized Patang fighting kite.
Sheldon, I don't suppose
There's any chance you
could give me my kite back?
I'm sorry, Raj, but
the rules of aerial warfare
Dictate at the fallen
kite go to the victor.
And without rules,
the competition has no meaning.
And without meaning,
The following would
be an empty gesture.
(Tauing):
I have your kite.
(Knocking at door)
Hey.
Hi.
How was your football party?
It was prettgood.
We won.
Oh, wow.
That's excellent.
It's a weird figure of speech,
isn't it
"We won" when you weren't
actually playing.
When we watch Star Wars,
We don't say,
"We defeated the Empire."
I'm glad to hear it.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, on a related subject,
Are you embarrassed
to have me around your friends?
Oh, my god, no.
Why would you ask that?
Well, you know, I just noticed
Sure you have.N't really
met any of them.Well...
Yeah, no, I met
the huge ex-Boyfriend
And the smBy the way,till larger
were they here today?
Of course not.
Why would they be?
Whwould I ask?
Why am I rambling?
Why don't you stop me?
Leonard, look,
If you want to meet my friends,
that would be great.
I just, you know, I didn't
want you to be bored.
I wouldn't be bored.
Why would I be bored?
Well,
'Cause they're
not genius scientists.
Penny, I like all
sorts of people.
In fact, some ofmy best friends
aren't geniuses.
Like who?
Okay, some of my Facebook
friends aren't geniuses.
My point is, if we're
going to be a couple,
I should be friends
with your friends.
Okay, great.
Well, then why don't you
Come over next Saturday
and watch the game with us.
Another football game?
They have them every week.
Did not know that.
You wanted to meet my friends.
Sure.
Su, just I don't know
much about football.
Oh, that's okay--
A lot of the guys'
Girlfries don't know football.
They just kind of drink
and talk in the kitchen.
Great.
(Football game playing on TV)
Okay, a completepass.
First down, New England.
I think I'm starting
to get this.
Really?
The only thing I've learned
in the last two hours
Is that American men
love drinking beer,
Pee too often and have
trouble getting erections.
Focus on the game,
not the commercials, Raj.
I'm just saying,
maybe if you people
cut back on the beer,
You could get out of the
bathroom and satisfy your women
without pharmaceutical hp.
J, what are you
doing here?
You were supposed to help me
pimp outy Vespa.
I'm sorry, are you
under the impreson
that we're still friends?
(Groans):
Ohcome on.
Y're not still grinding
on the kite thing, are you?
It's not just the kite thing.
Every time we go some place,
you think you can just dump me
Whenever someone prettier
comes along,
Even though you don't have
a shot with them.
I had a shot with that jogger.
Fine. Paint green flames
on your little scooter with her.
It's not a little scooter.
It's the second biggest
Vespa they make!
(Door closes)
Are you watching football?
There's no fooling you.
Now, what is this sacks
statistic they put up there?
All I know about Saks is,
my mother shops there.
Sacks, sacks...
SHELDON:It's football nom
For when a quarterback
is taced
Behind the line of scrimmage.
Huh...
Scrimmage.
SHELDON:
The line of scrimmage
Is the imaginary transverse line
Separating the offense
from the defense.
Oh.
Sheln knows football?
Apparently.
I mean, Quidditch, sure.
But football?
Sheldon, how do you
know this stuff?
I grew up in Texas.
Football is ubiquitous in Texas:
Pro football,
college football,
High school football,
peewee football...
In fact, every form of football
except the original--
Europeanootball.
Which most Texans believe
to be a Commie plot.
Unbeliable.
If you're interested, Ilso
know all about frying meat
That isn't icken
as if it were chicken.
So you could teach me?
Football or chicken-Fried meats?
Football.
I'm going to Penny's on Saturday
to watch a game with her friends
And I don't want to look lik
an idiot. I want to blend in.
If you want to blend in
with Penny's friends,
I'd think looking ke an idiot
would be the perfect camouflage.
Come on, Sheldon, please teach
me about football. It'll be fun.
That's exactly
what my father said.
"Come to the games.
watch the games."
Week in and week out
from the time
I was five
until I went off to college.
Longesseven years of my life.
Please, I'm asking you
as a friend.
Are you making this a tier one
friendship request?
(Sighs):
Fine.
I really appreciate this.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, Poindexter,
sit wn, shut up and listen.
I'm sorry?
That's how my father
always began
Our football conversations.
And if you'd like,
After the game,
When are you going to stop
making Con toast?
When I have enough to destroy
all the human toast
On the battlestar
known asGalactica.
Is that what you're wearing
to watch football at Penny's?
What's wrong
with a football jersey?
Nothing. That, however, appears
to be a football cocktail dress.
I's the smallest size they had,
Except the one for dogs.
I can't believe
they had one for dogs.
Oh, yes.
Canine football fans
are a common sight in Texas.
Cats, however, refuse
to wear sporting apparel.
My sister found that out
the hard way.
Anyway, wish me luck.
Leonard, wait.
Am I correct in assuminghat
your attempt to be accepted
To ensure your continuing
mating privileges with her?
Well, I wouldn't put it
exactly that way
How would you put it?
Yeah, okay, like you said.
Huh. Seems like an awful
lot of trouble
To go through for intercourse.
Don't you have access to women
who will do it for money?
Another accepted usage
for the term "ho."
Good-Bye, Sheldon.
Hold on
I believe that
social convention
Dictate you not arrive
empty-Handed.
Would you like to bring
some Cylon toast?
Yeah, no, I'm trying to fit in,
not get laughed at.
(Door closes)
What's funny about Cylon toast?
It's open.
Hey, pal.
What do you want?
(TV clicks off)
I brought you
a little gift.
New kite.
The kite you made me lose
was an authentic Patang,
Indian fighting kite
That my brother sent to me
from New Delhi.
It took me a day to put together
and two days to paint.
This is Hello Kitty.
Yeah, but it comes
with a little coin purse.
Does a Patang?
Wow, you just don't
get it, do you?
Buying me something
pretty isn't going
To make our problem
just go away.
Look, I admit
I haven't always been
The best friend I could be.
Y've been a sucky friend,
a sucky, sucky friend.
Stipulated.
And you do it
all the time.
Last week in the mall at
Radio Shack, we were looking
For a phone with giant
numbers for your mother,
And I suddenly realize
you're not even there.
I know, I know...
Getting shot down by the girl
at Hot Dog on a Stick. Were you?
But in my defense,
she was gorgeous!
And working that squeezer
to make the lemonade,
Going  and down
and up and down.
It was like
a free pole dance
Right in the middle
of the food court.
You're impossible.
Hey, at least I can
talk to women
Without being drunk.
Excuse me,
I have selective mutism,
A recognized medical disorder.
You're just a douche.
No. You know what?
Maybe that's what
this whole thing's about.
You're not mad at me,
You're mad at yourself.
No, I'm mad at you.
I hate myself,
but I'm mad at you.
Fine. You're mad at me.
I get it.
How about we go
spend the day together?
Just the two of us.
We'll go anywhere you want.
I don't know.
Come on.
Let me take you someplace nice.
I-I do enjoy
the La Brea Tar Pits.
Really, now? With the traffic
and the parking?
Okay, fine.
The Tar Pits.
Let's go.
Oh, why can't I stay mad at you?
(Exclaims)
Go! Go! Go!
Go-Go-Go-Go! Yes!
Are you people watching this?
Is this amazing or what?
Sweetie, that's a highlight
From the '98
championship game.
Oh. Did not know that.
How much beer have you had?
None, why?
Oh. I was just kind of
hoping you were drunk.
Now we're back live.
Okay, yeah.
I can see the difference.
Oh, where's the flag?
That's intentional grounding.
Totally.
That completely was
A forward pass, which they
threw intentionally incomplete
To avoid loss of yardage
or to conserve time
I can't believe they're not
Being penalized
with the loss of a down
And by having to move the line
of scrimmage
Back to the spot of the foul.
Here, have some pizza, sweetie.
Penny, you know
I'm lactose intolerant.
I know. I just need you
stop talking.
(Knocking)
SHELDON:
Penny.
Penny. Penny.
Sheldon, come in.
Thank you.
I'd like to make a sandwich,
but I'm out of bread.
There's some
in the fridge.
You shouldn't keep your bread
in the refrigerator.
Staleness is caused
by crystallization
Of the starch molecules,
which occurs faster
At cool temperatures.
On Earth,
We say "thank you."
So Leonard,
how goes the mimesis?
"Mimesis"?
You know. Mimesis.
An action in which the mimic
takes on the properties
Of a specific object
or organism.
Mimesis.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm attempting
to communicate with you
Without my meaning becoming
apparent to those around you.
Let me try again.
Have the indigenous fauna
Accepted you as oneof their own?
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink.
Oh, I guess so.
Good. Oh, FYI.
After I eat my sandwich,
I'm taking Koothrappali's
Patang kite
out for a test run.
Would you like to get your
delta-Wing raptor and join me?
I don't want to fly kites,
Sheldon.
We're watching football here.
I can see that.
I was providing you
with an alternative.
A courtesy I was never offered
in similar circumstances.
(Whistle blows on TV)
Oh, look at that.
Indicating he's challenging
the ruling on the field.
I hope he's right, 'cause if
he'not, it'll cost him
One of his three time-Outs.
You know, Leonard, honey,
I wouldn't mind if you wanted
to go fly kites with Sheldon.
No, I'll watch the
end of the game.
Besides, there's only
three minutes left.
Until halftime.
This is just half?
We've been here for hours.
And you're gonna be here
for a couple more.
Oh, you're kidding me.
No.
Nice meeting all of you.
So, yeah, anyway,
that's my boyfriend.
I really like my
saber-Toothed cat.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Maybe after lunch,
we can go to Marie Callender's
And have some pie.
I'd like that.
(Takes deep breath)
This is turning out
to be a perfect Saturday.
Good. I'm glad.
Oh, man. Did you see
the way she smiled at me?
Fine. Go ahead.
No. This is our day.
If you want
to chase after her,
Chase after her.
Ah, who am I kidding?
I wouldn't have a shot
with a girl like that.
Don't put yourself down.
You're a very attractive man.
You think so?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
It wouldn't kill you
To take a Pilates clas
with me now and then,
But you have acertain
Yeah, well,
it doesn't matter
'Cause she wasn't
really smiling at me.
Actually, in this case,
I think she was.
Really?
Yeah.
Bye.
What a douche.
Captioning sponsed by CBS,
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
Done by mosito1001
www.addic7ed.com
www.dark-ville.com