Okay, Max.
How would you describe our apartment?
And I've already ruled out
worse than that girl-pit
in Silence of the Lambs.
Well, at least she had some
silence once in a while.
Look, no one's gonna pay
money to rent this dump.
We haven't in six months.
Everyone else in
Williamsburg is making money
renting their crappy places on Airbnb.
It's all how you describe it.
So let's start lying.
This is a fantastic idea
and I really want to do this.
First question: "Describe
your neighborhood."
Run-down with a bunch of rats.
Old-world charm.
Pet-friendly.
"What type of people live there?"
Junkies, whores, homeless.
Actors.
"Do you have a hot tub?"
Sometimes.
"Gym?"
Two. Gay Jim upstairs,
and straight Jim across the hall
who's only gay when he's drunk.
"When is your space available?
Always, sometimes, one time."
Oh, just like our sex lives.
Always for me, sometimes out of boredom,
and one time for you.
(Peter Bjorn and John)
d ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh d
[cash register bell dings]
d ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh d
Synced and corrected by backinblack
www.addic7ed.com
Earl, guess what Max and I did.
I know what you didn't do.
Clean this dessert carousel.
There's a Napoleon in
here since Napoleon.
We rented our apartment on Airbnb.
You rented to Arabs?
Well, good luck getting it back.
They tend to be a tad territorial.
Airbnb is an agency that
rents to out-of-towners
and I'm guessing local men
cheating on their wives.
Well, I did it.
I know.
When you were 18 with Prince Harry.
Or so you say.
We have three offers for our apartment.
How?
Let me rephrase that.
How!
I found the perfect sales pitch.
"Stay at the place where dreams die"?
"Have the authentic
Williamsburg experience""
Oh, you mean getting clumsily felt up
by a guy who looks like
he came from the gold rush?
Anyone can stay at a hotel.
But how often can you
say you went to New York
and stayed at a "Brooklyn
bohemian barn apartment
with a live-in horse"?
Girl, you are good.
So now we just have to
pick who gets our apartment.
A guy looking to get away from it all.
that's a suicide.
You're right. We lie, they lie.
Um, a married couple
looking to reconnect.
Murder-suicide.
And finally, a girls' getaway weekend
for some fashion model friends.
A couple of chubby
girls looking to murder
some pints of Ben and Jerry's.
With maybe a sui-side
of mac and cheese.
Hey, everybody.
Yeah, the temperature be droppin'
and the bitches be nippin'.
I need a hot chocolate.
I'm right here, Sophie.
And I'm right here, Earl.
I mean, I get it,
but bro code, man.
Well, big news.
I'm going on a trip.
Mushrooms or acid?
I'm going to vermont!
Oh, you're gonna be gone?
Would you mind letting us
stay upstairs at your place?
We're renting out our apartment.
You're renting out that dump?
Oh, are they filming
Survivor at your place?
[coughing]
So when are these losers arriving?
They're not losers.
They're just girls paying
us to have a fun weekend
In our apartment.
What losers!
[knock at door]
Now that is a hand that's
scooped some ice cream.
Hi, are you Caroline?
Oh, my God. They really are models.
Hi, I'm Lily.
Oh shoot, now I'm gay.
Lily? As in Lily Aldridge?
And I'm Martha.
Hunt? Martha Hunt and Lily Aldridge?
Max, do you know who they are?
Sure do.
This one is the girl
that I leave this one for.
No, Max, they're all
Victoria's Secret models.
Yeah, we all wanted
to hang out in New York
before we leave for London.
We're doing a fashion show there.
I worked at the Victoria's Secret
at the mall for one day.
Got fired for eating panda
express over the thongs.
This is Max. I'm Caroline.
I used to be rich.
I just felt like I needed to say that.
And these are our friends,
Petra, Gabriella, and Rina.
(all three) Hi.
What are the odds you're all
named after Columbus's ships.
Come in. Welcome to
"The Williamsburg Experience."
It's bigger than it looks in the photo.
Well, I shaved of a couple
of inches for the photo.
You know the drill.
So why the hell are you staying here?
Is this training for
when your looks run out?
Oh, look. The kitchen is so cute!
Question: How do you
walk the runway blind?
It's just that we stay
at the same Four Seasons all the time.
Well, you will experience
at least two seasons here,
'cause the thermostat's broken.
It's 40 outside and 100 in here.
So as advertised, this is our sauna.
And our bohemian barn's
right out that door.
Just follow the temperature drop.
Max, super models are
staying at our apartment.
It's so exciting, I want
to tell all my friends.
I guess I just did.
I see you met Chestnut.
That's his real mane, not extensions.
Also per our ad, a charming skylight.
In case you want to sit under the stars
and have a little peace and quiet.
Hey, girls!
Come up already.
I want to get to my college reunion.
can you believe it's been 10 years?
Wow, time sure does lie...
I mean, fly.
(Martha) You talk to your neighbors?
I talked to my neighbor once
and the next thing you know,
I have this long letter from Naomi Watts
saying, "leave my husband alone."
So we've known each other
like five minutes already.
Where's my free bra?
I mean, all that's left
of this one is the frames.
Trust me, it's like a
burlesque show under here.
Sophie's apartment is amazing.
It looks like an Easter bunny
banged a Golden Girl.
That was some showerhead.
I'd marry it, but it's
already attached...
to the wall.
Max?
Here!
Oh, this bed is like being in the womb
without all the second-hand smoke.
Martha and Lily were super-sweet.
So exciting to be back
hanging with celebrities.
Yeah, and maybe now you can
get a new celebrity story.
I was getting really tired
of hearing how someone thought
you were Gwyneth Paltrow from behind.
Still flattering.
[laughter]
Laughter?
Coming from our apartment?
What do you think they're laughing at?
Probably found our account
balance on an ATM slip.
I bet Martha said something funny.
She's hilarious.
You know, for someone who's so pretty,
she never had to develop a personality.
I'm gonna go see.
Max, give me a shove.
This is good practice
for the eventual cliff.
[indistinct chatter]
(Lily) Beers and wings.
(Martha) Beers and wings.
Now it's a party.
Max, you know how when
it gets hot down there,
we just sit, sweat, and
point the fan at our junk?
They do it a little differently.
They are dancing in their underwear,
drinking beers.
So? The guy on the corner
does that all the time.
[models toasting beers]
I can't take my eyes off those beers.
(lily) Hey! Hi, you guys.
(lily) you wanna come
down, and have some beers,
And cool off?
Be right down!
Now I wish I had those wings,
I could get down there faster.
Okay. So what is this big news?
Did the health inspector find out
that the imitation crab meat is cat?
Technically, it's imitation cat,
but that's not what we're announcing.
I'm here.
And make this snappy. I'm
in the middle of something.
Puberty?
No. I was on a call with
Ripley's Believe It or Not
to inform them that you still work here.
And they didn't believe it.
Okay. We have some friends
coming in for a meal
and we don't want you guys
to embarrass us and overreact.
Darlin', I don't overreact.
I'm 70-something years old
with a history of heart trouble.
I keep it in check.
Hey, Max!
And I keep my heart pills in my pocket.
Excuse me, much as I enjoy the view,
I really want that "100th
birthday" shout out
from Al Roker.
Yes, they're Victoria's Secret models
and our friends.
Last night we all stayed
up late trashing Kate Moss.
Models in my diner!
Oh, no. I wore the wrong sweater vest.
You also wore the wrong
face, body, and personality.
Max, let's go say hi.
How do I look?
Like a waitress.
Damn it, it's the
waitress uniform, isn't it?
What's up, homies?
What's up, homie?
I love my life again.
Well, it's been a
whole day since we met,
so where's that free bra?
Max!
What? This one's on it's last legs.
Last night I heard it coughing.
Could also use some new underwear.
Mine are running on fumes.
I just texted David.
He's coming.
This is going to be an amazing party.
- Party?
- Yeah.
We're having some friends over.
Cool.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And like Max said, "cool""
Jeez, pull it back.
You're acting needier than Sofia Vergara
on a red carpet.
Big fan.
Big, big fan.
Compliments of the chef.
My specialty, popsicles.
I find they taste best
when sucked slowly,
using plenty of tongue,
facing the kitchen.
I can't believe we're not invited
to the biggest party in our apartment
since those ants found your jelly beans.
Yoo-hoo!
Hi, so we're just up here hangin' out.
Doin' our thang.
(Lily) Oh, sorry, girl. Did we wake you?
Go back to sleep.
"Go back to sleep"?
Why does she think we're so lame?
Um, I don't know.
Maybe it's 'cause you're
throwing around words
like "yoo-hoo" and "thang,"
like a mom bringing cheetos
down to a slumber party.
This is your fault.
They were obsessed with
us until you started asking
for bras like some
bra-less homeless person.
We're never gonna sleep
with all that music.
Check the drawer, Sophie
must have ear plugs.
I mean, she lives upstairs from you.
I found plugs, but I don't
think they're for your ears.
It's fine, we'll just pop
downstairs and say hello.
Fashion's my scene.
Know what I'm seeing? That price tag.
Oh, tuck it back in,
I have to return it.
Okay. Remember our deal.
I got up and got dressed
so you're my slave for life.
Oh, hi, girls.
I thought you were the
man with the Greek food.
Wow, I have definitely got to
start waxing my upper lip more.
Sophie, why aren't you in Vermont?
Oh, I lied.
I didn't go to vermont.
I mean, it's far and I'm not a lesbian.
No, I stayed in town to spy on Oleg.
I mean, I know you girls
think that I'm perfect,
but I have trust issues.
Well then, whose apartment is that?
I'm staying at Jim's.
Straight Jim's or gay Jim's?
Sophie, you forgot your purse.
Oh, I think this is mine.
Just kidding, it's yours.
What's up, salt n' pepa?
(both) Gay Jim's.
Oh, girls, please don't
tell Oleg that I'm here.
You know, I've been following him around
to see what he would
do if I was not in town.
And so far, you know, he's been cool.
But you know the old saying:
"Cheat on me once, shame on you.
Cheat on me twice, your
balls are in a jar."
Oh, my God! There's a man
standing in our doorway.
I have a doorman again.
Weird to see a man
standing in our doorway
without a warrant, an eviction notice,
or a bible.
Excuse me, this is our apartment.
Yeah, we live here all the time.
No biggie.
No biggie, and no
electricity, no lease-y.
Hi, I'm Caroline. This is Max.
We live here.
Not according to the list.
Sir, look, we do live her. I have a key.
The key is to be on the
list, which you are not.
Okay, I can prove we live here.
Go over to the window,
kick the side of radiator,
a panel will open up.
You'll find a half-smoked joint
and another half-smoked joint.
Proving...
What? That you're a poor pot head?
This is crazy.
I can't believe I'm
begging to get into a place
I've been trying to get out of.
It's a very exclusive party.
It's a dump.
I should know. I live here.
(Caroline) This night
couldn't get any worse.
Turn that light off.
I'm watching the Vctoria's Secret
super model party
with my night vision goggles.
And updating.
Oleg, how did you get in here?
How do you think?
It's my girlfriend's apartment.
I broke in.
Yes, Oleg, it's your
girlfriend's apartment
where you're sitting in the dark,
watching models out the window
with night vision goggles.
Hey! My pants are on!
No, they are not!
Not my fault.
Five Victoria's Secret
super models downstairs?
They took themselves off.
So what are you saying?
You're the victim here?
What would Sophie say if she came home
and saw you sitting here?
She'd say, "stop
hogging the goggles."
Oleg, let me just say this:
Vermont is closer than you think.
I don't know where
this argument is going,
but I'm going to that
damn supermodel party.
Oleg, it's late, I'm gonna
lay this on the line for you.
You're no George Clooney.
You're not even George Costanza.
These sheets are amazing
and you are never gonna
do better than Sophie.
She is hot and clearly
has no sense of smell.
I love Sophie.
I'll go home.
On second thought, I don't trust myself
to walk by your apartment.
Better lock me in here.
(Lily) Caroline! Max!
Come down here! Hurry!
I knew it! See, Max?
They're begging us to come.
I'm back again.
Are you coming?
Oh, let me think.
Downstairs with an open bar or up here,
alone, with Oleg in his
tighty-not-that-whities?
Should we tie you up?
No, it'll just make me hornier.
I knew they wanted us
to come to the party!
How could they not?
Last night I taught
Petra how to eat bread
without tearing it into
little pieces first.
Don't try it. I was a navy seal.
You think you're tough?
I lived in a refrigerator
box for a month.
With no top.
Not the box. Me.
(Lily) Max, Caroline, get in here!
Hey! See we were invited.
'cause we're "A" list.
The toilet is clogged and I need
you to take care of it, please.
"A list" as in "a" janitor list.
I don't know what to do.
Can one of you call the concierge?
Sure. Caroline!
Wait, wait, wait...
you didn't just call us
down here 'cause the
toilet's clogged, did you?
No.
Okay, good.
The kitchen sink is backed up, too.
But, toilet, I got this.
I was almost born in one.
Excuse me, excuse me,
excuse me, excuse me.
All right, everyone just calm down.
No need to overreact.
And there's the pool
we mentioned in our ad.
Oh, boy.
Yup, we got some floaters.
Caroline, I'm gonna need the plunger
and a lobotomy.
This happens with vintage toilets.
Part of their old-world charm.
We got some charm stuck on your loofah.
Hey guys, remember last night
how we just bit into that bread
without chewing it? Good times.
I need that damn plunger, I
don't want to die this way.
Got it, but it's caught on something.
[grunts]
[screaming]
What kind of a dump is this?
Hey! You wanted
the Williamsburg Experience, this is it!
Good news, Martha. I have your flat iron
looking pretty much back to normal.
Oh, that's good. Keep it.
Again, sorry about your
cashmere sweaters in here.
But when we ran out of paper towels,
You did scream, "just use
anything, make it stop."
And of course, we'll pay to
have them all dry cleaned.
Oh, that's nice. Keep them.
Okay, we can leave.
I am off the phone with my therapist.
And it goes without saying,
we won't charge you guys
for this weekend.
No way. Here.
You are taking this check and
my therapist's phone number.
I do not know how you are
standing up without him.
What? Come on, this is nothing.
One month, the floor actually
opened up and swallowed us.
Yeah, we've been through worse.
Oh, it's really cool the way
you two support each other.
Yup, we're a pair of support hose.
And speaking of support...
Here, Max.
No way!
Look, Caroline, it's a bra-nanza!
And, Caroline, since you don't
really need to wear a bra...
Here. This apartment may be hell,
but you are a real angel.
Aw, my own wings?
Thank you, guys.
Hey, can I ask you something?
As long as it doesn't have
anything to do with rats.
How come you didn't
invite us to the party?
What? I thought Martha did.
I thought Lily did.
(both) Model moment!
Pick-up, Caroline!
Yup, I always knew you would die here.
Pick-up, Max!
Looking good, Max.
After you drop that, have
Caroline come back here
and lock me in the walk-in
till Sophie gets home.
Max, I just realized we're
kind of the supermodels
of waitressing.
And I just realized my boobs
aren't always supposed to hit
my side.
Synced and corrected by backinblack
www.addic7ed.com