This is what you missed
last week on Shameless.
My baby!
True love.
Hey, hot stuff.
What do you do?
Real estate. I live in Miami.
I kicked Lip out.
Where'd he go?
Is it all right if
I stay over tonight?
Was it weird seeing Jimmy?
Who's Jimmy?
Jimmy is Steve.
Holy shit. I'm gonna see
the little guy on Friday?
Yep. For, like, a second.
Christ almighty!
This cocksucker's killing me!
When they're good, they're good.
You're the only one
who truly understands me.
Is something wrong with her?
She hasn't gotten out of bed in days.
Monica's bipolar, Debs.
Time for you to
go back on your meds, huh?
- Holy fuck.
- What happened?
Mommy, Mommy...
Oh, God, there's been an accident.
She's bleeding badly. They're on their way.
You with me?
It's gonna be okay. We're good,
we're good. Stay with me.
How is she?
She's stable.
You should go home.
Lip just called.
He's coming?
Karen's having a baby upstairs.
Holy fuck!
It's coming, it's coming!
What's wrong with him?
He's has Downs Syndrome, Debs.
What the fuck, Karen?
I never said it was your baby.
I got the baby, I got the baby!
Come on, come on!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo!
I've got a baby!
♪ Think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ Know that it's not
for naught ♪
♪ You were beaming once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪ Round up the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that they're not
for naught ♪
♪ You were willing once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so... ♪
♪ Sure of? ♪
Monica!
Monica?
Monica Jean Gallagher!
Monica!
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Hey.
Oh, God...
Jesus.
Schutzstaffen.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
You stole my wife!
What?
You stole my wife,
and I want her back.
Okay, visiting hours
are 9:00 to 4:00.
You want to see her,
come back then.
Come out, Monica!
Hey!
Get out of here.
Monica, come home!
I love you!
I'll never leave you!
Never...
You're an angel.
A blessing.
My little Kung Pow blessing.
Hmm. Gotta figure out how to
get this security thing off.
What a big, beautiful,
panda-Pooh Bear boy you are.
Oh, look.
He's still got his
little dingy-ding skin.
Should we get him circumcised?
Hell, no.
Let that extra derma ride.
Oh, he needs a name.
What about Hiram,
for my father?
Are you a Hymmie?
Hmm. Think they can track
this thing, like a baby LoJack?
Are you a little Hymmie?
A Hymmie-wymie?
The name should be something Chinese.
Keep him connected to his people.
Hmm.
Chinese...
Chen, Chan,
Chang...
Wing? Wang?
Wu?
Hm... it's pretty tight.
I don't want to slip
and cut his leg off.
Well, you could
clip his ankle bracelet
and his foreskin
at the same time.
Hey, my friend Cindy
went back to work.
Has to pump.
For a five-spot,
I bet she'd hook us up
with some breast milk.
Oh...
They're going to
be looking for him.
We need to hide him.
How about the attic?
Like that movie about
the Hebrew girl.
No, it gets cold in the winter.
What about the basement?
No, it's the first place
they'll look, sweetie.
Dryer?
Just can't forget he's in there.
Right.
Oh...
I'll clear the table.
Debs, bedtime.
Fuck.
Oh, Jesus.
These poor kids.
Don't worry, they're already
pretty fucked up.
I mean...
Ah...
Okay, you can breathe.
Ah!
Keep breathing.
You gonna be all right?
Fiona, I...
♪ I should know ♪
♪ Who I am by now ♪
♪ I walk ♪
♪ The record stands somehow ♪
♪ Thinking of winter ♪
♪ Your name is the splinter
inside me ♪
♪ While I wait ♪
♪ And I remember the sound ♪
♪ Of your November downtown ♪
♪ And I remember the truth ♪
♪ A warm December with you ♪
♪ But I don't have to make
this mistake ♪
♪ And I don't have to stay
this way ♪
♪ If only I would wait ♪
♪ The walk has all been
cleared by now ♪
♪ Your voice is
all I hear somehow ♪
♪ Calling out, winter ♪
♪ Your voice is the splinter
inside me ♪
♪ While I wait ♪
Fiona?
♪ I remember the sound ♪
Yeah, come on in.
You awake?
Yeah.
♪ And I remember the truth ♪
♪ A warm December with you ♪
♪ But I don't have to make
this mistake ♪
♪ And I don't have to stay
this way ♪
♪ If only I would wait ♪
♪ I could have lost myself
in rough ♪
Shh. It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Shh.
♪ I remember the sound ♪
♪ Of your November downtown... ♪
Hey.
Hi.
Somebody stole the baby.
They think it was my mom.
Jesus.
You call the police?
She probably just
freaked out, like always.
I'm gonna get it back.
Well, maybe you should let
your mom keep him for awhile.
You know, at least
till you're sure
you're not gonna
change your mind.
I'm not gonna change my mind.
Yeah, but you don't know that.
I mean, you could really...
I don't want that fucking
thing anywhere near me, okay?
Go ask somebody when I can
get the hell out of here.
I want to hit Wendy's before
they stop serving breakfast.
Morning.
Kids still sleeping?
Uh, yeah.
Turkey and eggs?
With mashed potato pancakes
and cranberry jelly.
Hmm.
You back to being a legal
resident around here, Steve?
Jimmy. His name's
Jimmy now.
Steve was just an alias he used
to lie to me about
who he really was.
Ooh, not cool, Jimmy-Steve.
Eggs?
To go.
I changed my name 'cause I was
stealing cars.
Didn't want anyone to
be able to track me down
if things went south.
It didn't have anything
to do with you.
Yeah.
I want to meet your family.
Oh, no, you don't.
Yes, I do.
They're miserable people.
Nasty, egomaniacal
shit-heads.
All of them?
Yeah, Mom's okay
when she's knocked back
enough Chardonnay.
How many of you are there?
Uh, Mom, Dad--
shit-head superstar.
Older brother Chip--
shit-head
superstar-in-training.
Can't wait to meet them.
You're going to
be disappointed.
Wouldn't be the first time
someone's disappointed me.
Okay.
You look beautiful.
Liar.
So, you getting okay care here?
Good drugs?
You need anything?
Uh, cigarettes,
shampoo, hacksaw?
Clothes.
Mine are a mess.
I'll bring by some stuff.
I really screwed
up Thanksgiving.
No, it was no big deal.
The kids?
I must have scared
the shit out of them.
They're good.
We, uh, talked
it out last night,
and I tucked them in,
they're fine today.
You didn't tuck them in.
I read books to them,
the little ones, anyway.
You'll be out soon.
You'll see for yourself.
Not soon.
72 hours.
You already got
15 under your belt.
I signed myself in
for 60 more days.
Voluntary commitment.
Well, tell them
you changed your mind.
I can't.
That's part of the deal.
Frank, I got to
get myself normal.
I can't keep doing this to them.
You're just a little blue.
It happens to everyone
every now and again.
I can take care of you at home.
No, you can't.
I love you.
You belong with us.
I'm...
I'm where I need to be, okay?
I got to go.
I got group.
Can I borrow a cup of cocaine?
All out.
Coffee?
How are the little
ones this morning?
After seeing their mother
slit her wrists?
Traumatized.
Has to be support groups for
kids who've seen shit like that.
Yeah, in maximum
security prisons
after they've mowed down
half their classmates.
You let Steve spend the night?
You mean Jimmy?
Fuck that, I'm
calling him Steve.
I sent him out on a quest.
Mm! Making him re-win
the heart of the virgin?
Christ, V,
I can't let him
back into this madness.
Isn't that his choice?
Well, he thinks
he wants it now,
but just wait a year or two.
When I have one in the oven
and Frank throws up in our bed
in the middle of the
night or Monica tries
to hang herself in a closet
with an old shoelace.
He's a big boy, he can
make his own decisions.
Hey, Carl.
Sleep okay?
What do you think?
You hungry?
- Let me make you a sandwich.
- Okay.
Disability check
doesn't come
for another week, Frank.
I went to visit your mother
in the hospital this morning.
We have to get
her out of there.
Best place for her.
She's fragile.
She's broken.
They want to make her normal.
They want to help her.
By which they mean average,
boring, medicated,
a Stepford Monica.
She tried to kill herself
last night;
boring would be a blessing.
They perform lobotomies now.
No, they don't.
Shock treatment?
No.
Actually, I think they do.
Princess Leia did it.
100,000 volts of electricity
zapped into her skull!
Draws so much power,
it takes out entire city blocks.
When our lights dim,
some poor fucker's
getting his brains fried.
Don't listen to him, Carl.
Eat your breakfast.
What's a lobotomy?
They jam a screwdriver
into your head
and scramble your brains.
No, they don't. Jesus, Frank.
Yeah, they do!
They're gonna put Mom
back on her me.
They're gonna make her better.
She's not better on her meds.
She's a zombie. She gives up
everything she loves in life.
Yeah, like what?
Drugs, alcohol, you?
Us.
I'm gonna bust her out of there
before they steal what
makes Monica Monica.
Are you with me?
Leave her alone, Frank.
She needs a chance to get well.
Somebody can steal
what makes you you?
No.
Carl?
He's not helping you, either.
Can I bring my Mac-10 pistol?
Leave him out of this.
The pistol's going back
to the cops.
Where's your sister?
Shower.
Leave Debbie alone, Frank!
No.
Monica will be better when she
comes out of the hospital, Carl.
I passed.
The GED-- I passed.
Daddy!
Daddy, you're
supposed to knock!
Do you love your mother?
Cindy says they make this thing
for women who can't produce
their own milk.
You hang this doohickey
around your neck,
and then you tape these
right over
your nipples.
And the baby
can still breast-feed.
It's okay, honey,
I-I can do it.
No, it's important
for both of us to bond with him.
Okay.
There, sweet boy.
Whoa.
Wow.
That's... Whoa.
Whoa!
Now I know what
all the fuss is about.
Someone's here.
Oh.
Mom?
Mom.
Sweetie!
My goodness! Home already?
Did the hospital let you leave?
Where is it?
Thought they usually
like to keep you
for at least a day.
Where is it, Mom?
Where's what, honey?
It.
The baby that shoved
its ginormous head
out of my cooter for six
endless hours last night.
Oh, my. Did they lose it?
They showed me the video footage
of you taking it.
Oh, that baby.
They were gonna call
the police, but I said no.
Where is it?
Now, Mom!
In the dryer.
Take it out.
I think he's napping.
Take it out!
I don't want to touch it!
You're leaking.
Isn't he beautiful?
Take it back to the hospital.
Somebody will want it.
I want it.
Well, you can't have it.
He's such a sweet boy.
He never cries.
He's so handsome.
We want to name him Hiram
after your grandfather.
Or maybe Ming, to keep him
wired into his Chinese-ness.
Shut up, Jody.
It's going back.
Karen, please don't do this.
They'll give it to the retarded
freaks' home or whatever.
He's my grandson.
I won't let you throw him away
like used Kleenex.
You know, Karen, your
mom might be right.
Maybe she should keep
him for a while.
You know, who knows
what social services is
going to do with him?
Butt out, Lip!
What are you even doing here?
He's not even yours.
This is none of your
goddamn business.
At least call Tim Wong
or whoever the father is
and tell him about it.
Get out!
You dodged a fucking RPG
getting tossed over
by this one.
Don't I know it, man.
Take it back to the hospital.
What if they won't
take it back?
Then drop it in a basket
and leave it at
the fire station.
I don't give a shit.
No.
Yes!
He is staying with me.
Fine!
Then I'm calling the police.
Lip here?
Lip!
It's your sister.
So...
How'd you find me?
Jimmy.
How's Karen?
Girl's a fucking bitch.
My cousin, Eli, was born
with a foot coming out
of his knee.
Now he's a blacksmith.
Only one who can
pump the bellows
without using his hands.
I passed my GED.
Don't look so surprised.
No, I'm not.
That's, um...
that's great.
So... deal's a deal.
Ah, too late.
Spilt milk.
I passed.
You go back to school.
Water under the bridge.
Knock off the clichés.
Road not taken.
I want you home, Lip.
We all do.
Right.
It's cold water and
sleep deprivation.
Make you stand all day
with electrodes tied
to your genitals.
I think you're mistaking
Cook County for Abi Grabie.
Abu Gradie.
Abu Ghraib.
Did a tour with the
Guard-- Basra.
They don't do any
of that, Frank.
I was in there last year
after my accidental overdose.
Accidental? You set yourself
on fire freebasing.
It was mostly us
sitting in a circle
in a group talking
about how your family
- screwed you up.
- Oh, Monica talking about Frank?
That ought to take a while.
Frank, you got any cash?
Moolah? Green?
I got to spring her
out of there.
She's the yin to my yang.
She's the scotch in my soda.
We are Fred and Ginger.
John and Yoko.
Mickey and Minnie.
More like Siegfried and Roy.
Adolf and Eva.
Your boy still working nights
at the hospital, Tommy?
Support services
technician, yeah.
Support services technician?
I thought he was a janitor.
A job's a job.
At least Pat's got one.
What time's Patty go to work?
We're on for tonight.
What's tonight?
Dinner with my family.
You asked, you got it.
Are they coming here?
Uh... no.
Dad hasn't been south
of the Art Institute Gala
since Billy Joel
played Comiskey Park in '84.
Going to their house for dinner?
Nope.
Uh, Mom would have
to have you deloused first.
She's a germophobe.
You want an almond
out of the serving dish,
you have to wear
surgical gloves and use tongs.
I met your mom.
She's... she's cool.
You met his mom?
Candace.
A little heavy on the Botox
and Chanel No. 5,
but nice.
So where are we meeting?
Uh, Morton's, downtown.
Dad has a wine locker there.
Little brass plaque
with his name on
it and everything.
Everybody invited?
Yep. Dad's buying,
so order the most
expensive thing
on the menu.
Prime rib?
Sure.
Bone-in porterhouse steak?
Anything you want. What do
you say, Debs, free meal?
No can do, Jim. Busy.
Doing what?
Sleeping over at Holly Herkimier's.
Don't do anything she does.
Big-ass lobster?
You bet.
♪ Bad, bad heart ♪
♪ Bad, bad mind ♪
♪ Thinking bad thoughts ♪
♪ All the time ♪
♪ Waking up in the morning... ♪
Jesus Christ!
Don't you ever hose
these things out?
Smells worse than
a dead hooker's ass in there.
Keep your voice
down, all right?
Easy, cowboy.
That orange one's
for experts only.
Hey, you do get caught,
you never heard
of me, all right?
Doing good in there, pumpkin?
Mm-hmm.
A-okay, Daddy.
Cops!
Aah!
Come on, Mom. Hurry up.
Okay.
I'm hurrying. Okay!
Mom, come on!
Police are here, Mom.
Hello, Mrs. Jackson.
Hey.
Tony. How's your mom?
The diabetes still giving her fits?
Yes, ma'am.
Lost two toes over the summer,
but she's hanging tough.
Well, she'd
have to be--
all those years skating
with the Ice Capades.
Uh... we got a call
about a kidnapping.
Oh...
Mom and Jody
stole my baby from
the hospital.
You had your baby?
Congratulations.
Thanks. It was a fucking
horror show, but I...
finally had the damn thing.
They stole it, and I want
you to take it back.
You don't... want
to keep the baby?
It's retarded.
I want it to go back
so they can give it away
to the Down Syndrome
baby do-gooders
or the county or whatever.
Correct term for Downs kids
is "developmentally
delayed."
Well, my baby was
stolen by my mom
and her developmentally
delayed boyfriend.
He's not my boyfriend.
I'm not?
Uh, Mrs. Jackson,
did you take
your daughter's baby?
Baby? What baby?
Ma'am, is the baby
in the laundry basket?
Yes.
Give it to the cop, Mom.
Karen, honey, please
don't do this.
Ah, man.
Look how handsome you are.
Yes, you are.
Give it to the damn cop, Mom!
So this is your mother,
and she wants
to take care of the baby?
Yes, but I don't
want it here.
Oh.
And you want a total stranger
to take him or the
State of Illinois
to be responsible for him
on the taxpayers' dime?
You hungry?
I'm thinking Thai.
Yeah.
That's it?
You're just gonna leave?
Nice seeing you, Mrs. Jackson.
I'll tell Mom you asked after her.
Please.
It's either me
or that baby, Mom.
Your choice.
I think this must be the place.
Can I get out?
It's hot in here.
No.
Ow!
Monica?
I can be if you want me to be.
Jesus!
Monica?
Kermit?
Frank?
What'd you do to your head?
Oh, um, my therapy.
It calms my nerves.
You let 'em zap your head?
Helps with my seizures.
Jesus.
Try it before you knock it,
Frank. Very restful.
Have you seen Monica around?
Yeah, um...
across the hall on your left.
Monica?
Hey, Monica?
Frank.
I came to get you out.
I told you I don't want out.
Why'd you stop?
Did you come?
Um...
Frank,
this is Jill.
Jill this is my husband, Frank.
Oops.
Mom?
Fiona! Fiona, look!
Boys.
Carl...
Sorry. We don't let him out
of his cage very often.
Carl!
Get over here.
So, Jim, what have
you been up to?
Still finding new
and creative ways
to underachieve?
I was traveling around
South America till recently.
Are you still handling all the
hemorrhoidectomies for Dad?
Chip just joined Dad's practice
after his surgical residency,
following in
the great man's footsteps.
So you get to cut into people?
Awesome.
He take you skiing yet?
Uh, no.
My only talent involving snow
is knowing how
to shovel the walk without
disturbing my father sleeping on it.
And Carl's pretty good
at peeing in it as well.
What was the name
of that girl that he took
to St. Moritz
on New Year's? Chrissie?
Lizzie? Something. I remember it
had "ie" on the end of it.
I was 17.
You took a girlfriend to Europe
in high school?
Dad offered a ticket.
He drags her all
the way to the Alps,
then leaves her in
the hotel room sitting there
for some French girl
he met on the gondola.
Chip, leave your brother alone.
Two things you can count on:
Mom's naked favoritism
for her youngest...
That's not true.
My brother still thinks of me as
the runt that didn't punch back.
...and her youngest's quick
and stealthy exit
after he weasels her
out of another ten grand.
I was hoping to milk her for
another 20 this time.
With a name like Chip,
you'd think you'd want
to defy the stereotype.
Fiona, don't.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
Well, sorry to be late.
Whipple on
a stage-four patient.
So, you are
the mysterious Fiona.
And these are
Fiona's brothers, Carl...
and Ian...
Well, nice to meet you, Ian.
Have we ordered?
Excuse me.
Bathroom.
And your drink, sir.
Thank you.
Ah, you know,
I gotta wash my hands.
I'll have the iceberg lettuce
salad and the sea bass.
Double-cut,
48-ounce prime rib,
medium-rare,
and the two-pound
Maine lobster, please.
Hey.
Do they know you're gay?
I'm not gay.
Really?
What's this then?
Honestly?
Anything that walks, that's me.
Jesus, Moni, another lady?
You know,
I get lonely.
Do you love her?
I just met her.
What are you doing here?
We came to break you out.
I told you, I don't want out.
Oh, hell, I do.
No one's offering, Jill.
And why did you have to
drag Debbie into this?
I didn't think you'd come
if it was just me.
What is she in for?
Psych evaluation to see
if I'm competent
to stand trial.
What'd you do?
Shot my husband 26 times.
Jesus, what'd you use, an AK?
Pistol.
I reloaded... twice.
Moni, we want you with us.
The kids need you.
I need you.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm okay.
I'm sorry you had
to see that, honey.
I was just so low, you know?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
But I'm okay now.
Mm-hmm.
So...
What's this grand plan you have
for busting us out?
Got it.
Whoa. That's short.
That's a long way down.
Could tie sheets to the end.
What?!
Hey, it's only two stories down
to the roof...
outside the ladies' john.
You want me to go pick up Liam?
Uh, V will be okay keeping him
overnight.
Great restaurant,
Jimmy. Check out
this cool knife I stole.
That's going back.
Hey, they won't miss it.
They got tons of 'em.
Give me that.
Bed, now.
Hey, nobody touch
my leftover lobster.
I want to put it in my cinnamon
toaster waffle in the morning.
Hey, Fiona.
Hmm?
Jimmy's dad Lloyd,
he, uh..
Good night.
Night.
What?
I love you.
Are you gonna leave?
No.
Everybody always leaves.
I won't.
Patience...
Stop that!
Steve!
Estefania...
Jesus!
Hey, hey, hey, Estefania.
What is it?
Estefania, hey,
calm down, calm down.
What the hell happened?
Hey...
Marco...
Wait. Marco did this to you?
He hit you?
Did Marco hit you?
You my husband...
Help me, please?
Please help me!
Please?
What are you doing?
Uh, I couldn't sleep.
Needed a smoke.
You don't have
to do it out here.
With Dad home,
the whole house is an ashtray.
Christ, it's freezing.
Karen?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe. I-I don't know.
I don't get how you have a kid
and not give a shit
what happens to it.
Retarded, two heads,
no face, whatever--
it's still you.
No face?
Yeah, well, maybe it would
have to have a face.
You should go home.
Oh, you kicking me out?
Get your ass back in the house
and stop thinking so much.
You want to fuck again?
I'm only gonna be up
a couple more minutes.
Hey, pal.
Hey, buddy! Pal!
Got a light?
When are you gonna give those up?
They're gonna kill you.
I know.
I'm gonna try hypnosis next.
Uh, no, don't.
No, sorry.
Where's your I.D. badge?
Oh, left it in my locker.
Shift's not over.
Left my inhaler...
...in the car.
Tuberculosis and
asthma. Horrible.
Chuck, we got trouble on seven.
Psych unit.
Roger that.
Got to keep
your I.D. badge visible
at all times
on hospital grounds.
Debbie!
Get in the car.
Debbie, get in the car.
Debs, get in the car!
Get in the car!
I love you, Debbie!
Debbie, I love you!
She said we're better
off without her.
You will have two
hours for this exam.
This is multiple choice.
If you change an answer,
be sure to fully erase
your first answer and
clearly circle your second.
I am not...
I am not a mind reader.
If you do not know an answer,
move on and come back to...
Where you going?
Anywhere far the fuck
away from here.
Hey, I went back
to school today.
Took the AP Physics final.
You haven't even
been going to class.
I read the book a
couple years ago.
This is it, Mom.
Last chance.
I'm not kidding,
I'm gone.
It's me or the baby.
Decide.
Please don't do this.
Me or the baby.
The baby, sweetheart.
Karen!
You know, you're
going to regret this.
Ow, ow, ow! I thought you said
these things didn't hurt!
I lied.
Ow! Dude, knock it off.
Ow!
Carl's having an air soft war
with Jimmy in the living room.
They're gonna put a dent
in the TV screen again.
Outside! I told you both
twice already!
Turkey?
Get used to it.
That and Carl's
Morton leftovers
are going to tide us over
for the next two weeks.
Listen, I kind of need to talk
to you about something.
Don't worry about her.
She doesn't speak any English.
She living here now?
Good Lord, I hope not.
You know, Jimmy's dad Lloyd?
I, uh, think we kind of...
Oh, Jesus.
We're broke, Frank.
I haven't hidden money in
there since you cleaned us out
last May.
Where is it?
There is no money.
Whoa! No. Those are mine.
Come on, let him go, Ian.
No, put it back!
What, are you
fucking kidding me?
Hey! Hey! Watch it!
Get off of me!
Hey, stop that!
Are you kidding me?!
Hey! Hey!
Listen!
Fucking stop it!
Knock it off!
Don't you fuck with me!
You little...
♪ The evening sleeps away ♪
♪ Another day
has come and gone ♪
♪ The streetlights
soak the shade ♪
♪ Synthetic rays
replace the sun ♪
♪ Conscience soon dying ♪
♪ When you get what you want ♪
♪ Foresight goes and fades ♪
♪ In retrospect,
we'll figure out ♪
♪ The evening sleeps away ♪
♪ Realize the afterthought
of doubt ♪
♪ Well, these last couple days ♪
♪ Been why we're going there
and how ♪
Lip!
♪ For these three days on end ♪
♪ Got to be hopeful ♪
♪ These three days on end ♪
♪ Got to get up
and catch my second wind ♪
♪ Got to be up for it. ♪
I can't again.
I got to sleep.
Uh-huh.
Kids have school
in the morning.
I got to find a shoebox for...
Debbie's art project.
Carl hasn't done his spelling.
Uh-huh.
Carl's class is
having a bake sale.
I got to--
I'm gonna make cookies.
Cookies, right.
Mmm.
And Liam has to go
to the clinic for...
for his next set...
Screw it, get up here.
♪ We will know
what it's all about ♪
♪ And today is the day ♪
Lip?
I so cold.
You hot?
Okay.
Sure.
♪ And I want to say,
as I survey ♪
Oh.
♪ I'd like to take you
miles away ♪
♪ With me today ♪
♪ Sweet lover,
got nothing on me ♪
♪ You want it,
but you can't see ♪
♪ You want it, so just say so ♪
♪ One time, if you just let go ♪
♪ Baby, freedom's got
nothing on me ♪
♪ I'll give you
everything you need ♪
♪ Baby, give and take
is part of the game ♪
♪ Reacting like
it's one and the same ♪
♪ You thought you'd find
something on me ♪
♪ Slow down,
you got to slow down. ♪