I wanna take another look. Anyone object?
No, go ahead. Be my guest.
- I've never seen that much money.
- Mercy.
Look at that. That is awesome.
- How much do you think there is?
- I don't know. Thousands.
All right.
I still say we should take it to the police.
Hold on, all right. Just hear me out, okay?
One of us holds it.
We check in, say, I don't know, 30 days...
if nobody's reported it missing,
then we split it between us.
Yeah. All right. Okay.
So, who holds it?
- I wouldn't mind.
- No.
No, 'cause I don't know you,
and I don't know him.
How am I supposed to know
you won't disappear?
Yeah, he has got a point.
What about if our man here,
he looks after it?
But to prove he's not a thief,
I'm not saying that you are...
he goes to the bank. This is brilliant.
Take out... What you got?
I've got £6,000 in the building society.
You've got £6,000, okay. Takes out £6,000.
Gives us £3,000 each.
- But I keep the case?
- Obviously.
I ain't got a problem with that.
If you don't hear anything in a month,
we'll come back. Split the money.
- Okay.
- Yeah? Okay. Let's do it.
Man, we're gonna be so rich.
I can't believe it.
I came out this morning,
I had 20 quid in my pocket.
Now, I'm looking at
a third share in £25,000.
It's like it just came out of the sky
and we just found it there.
Brought from heaven, or something.
How's it going, Danny?
- What?
- The score.
How do you think it's going
on a scale of 1 to 10?
A nine maybe?
Nine-ish.
- No?
- Ask your question.
How do you know
how much is in the case?
We didn't count it yet?
Shit.
- What happened?
- He did. Come on.
First rule of cheating at cards:
Always cover the move.
Misdirection.
Big movement covers the small.
Simple stuff.
And, if you can, always sit by the door.
- Look, Mick.
- Forget it.
No, I don't want to forget it. All right?
Okay, I screwed up.
Yeah, what did you learn? In a sentence.
Do it by the book.
This way.
You screw up again, Danny,
I'll have it tattooed on your ass.
- So who's this Frank Gorley?
- Beelzebub.
I say we give him a taste
of his own medicine.
I know some people.
I can personally vouch for
how many places they can hurt you.
- That's not what we do.
- What are we gonna do, then?
Ash?
He runs a hotel and casino
in the West End.
The casino's bent.
He ships in girls from Eastern Europe
for the hotel.
Punters lose their money on the tables,
then curl up with Hilda from Hungary.
Not the sort of man
you take liberties with.
In fact, if we had a list of places
not to go...
he'd be right there at the top.
Find me an in.
The usual.
I was one card short of a great hand.
Maybe I should put you on a curfew.
I'd like to see you try.
- You're not 20 years old anymore, Albert.
- Yes, I am.
Up here, where it counts.
- You are setting a very bad example.
- Good.
I hear you're giving young Danny
a hard time.
He screwed up.
We all screw up.
- It's what you do next that counts.
- Maybe.
He's got grift sense. You can't teach that.
And I'm not gonna be around forever,
so you'll need him.
Let me worry about Danny.
You just get some rest.
We'll call back later.
Is there anything you want, Albie?
Three nurses and a deck of cards.
We'll meet Ash back at the hotel.
See what he's got.
Wait.
Call me.
- Peter?
- Yes?
Maureen Phillips, media services.
- Media?
- Sorry. Hello.
I'm already on it.
Please tell the Minister it's all in hand.
He has nothing to worry about.
I'm with Peter now.
Yeah.
I'll call you as soon as I'm on my way back.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
You know what politicians are like.
Yes.
The thing is, we've been tipped off...
that the press are conducting
an investigation into NHS Trust services.
- And this hospital's been earmarked.
- I see.
They select a patient and follow
his progress through the system...
debriefing him as and when he leaves.
Well, the thing is...
The patient they've selected
is an elderly man...
called Albert Stroller?
God, I can just see the headlines now.
Right, look, I'll get onto it...
Find him, Peter, treat him like a prince.
We're all in your hands, now.
Thank you.
If ever we needed Albert...
If there is an in, I can't find it.
Well, look, we know he plays cards.
We also know he can spot a cheat.
Women?
He's got two dozen hookers on tap, 24/7,
but doesn't go near them.
I spoke to one of the croupiers
at the casino. The guy's a loner.
He locks himself in his room every night.
- No friends?
- No, nothing.
- Stocks, shares?
- Doesn't trust them.
Dabbled once, lost heavily.
Vowed never again.
The man's a block of ice.
He calculates the odds.
He never goes out on a limb.
The only thing he's passionate about,
as far as I can see, is extreme violence.
There is one thing.
He carries a laptop wherever he goes.
If he has got a weakness,
that's where we'll find it.
Good, it'll give Danny a chance
to show us how much he's learned.
How we doing?
Depends how much we spend
on the set up.
Whatever it takes.
He put his hands on Albert.
But I thought the book says,
"Never let your heart rule your head."
Hello?
Your wife.
I don't think it works.
What?
Downloading from the hard disk
telepathically.
- I'm thinking.
- But they're on dessert.
Divide and conquer.
Excuse me, you dropped a fork there.
Having fun?
That's a natural laxative.
- What? Eye drops?
- Yeah, just watch.
- I thought you couldn't stand this place.
- I can't.
Then it must be important.
Did Stacie tell you I came to see you?
- Why wouldn't she?
- You didn't call.
I've been busy.
- You look well.
- I am.
- Thanks for the letters.
- I had nothing to say.
I want a divorce. Nothing else.
The forms just need a signature.
I even put a stamp on for you.
Simon and I want to get married.
Well?
I've gone from soul mate to obstacle
so fast, I think I'm gonna get a nosebleed.
You always loved this more than me.
Everything you ever dreamed of, is he?
Just sign the papers, Mick.
Two minutes.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Nearly there.
Come on!
Got it, Dan.
Well, now.
- It was there all the time.
- The usual.
I just didn't see it.
This guy is crazy about the movies.
The guy's a romantic,
so strictly black and white.
Then Stacie needs to be classier than Diaz.
Someone classic, like Hepburn.
Got it.
Mickey.
Listen, we talked about me moving up.
- Working the inside on the next big score.
- That was before you screwed up.
Yeah, exactly.
We need to get the lads down to Eddie's.
We're putting a team together for Albert.
You shouldn't take it out on Danny.
Pete will be great. What about Sam?
Is he free?
Give him a call for me, would you?
Any other names you can mention
who might be about?
Danny, knock yourself out.
Thanks, Andy.
Albert will really appreciate it.
- Sam.
- Miss Monroe.
- You might need to shave, Sam.
- For Albert? Sure.
- Hi, trinkle.
- Hello, Pete.
- How you doing?
- I'm here for Albert, all right?
Maritime Pictures? Hello, there.
I have a meeting with your financial
director there later this week.
I was wondering,
could you fax me directions?
Yeah, lovely. Thanks very much. Bye-bye.
Okay.
Right. We've booked you into a room
at Gorley's hotel...
and there are faxes waiting for you
from every major Hollywood studio.
We know he keeps tabs on all his guests...
and won't pass up the opportunity
to meet a big shot movie mogul like you.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
By the book, Danny.
I don't know any other way.
Look into his eyes, and think as he thinks.
For Albert.
Okay.
Good morning.
Could I interest you in a special discount?
Hello. Could I interest you
in a special discount?
I want a divorce.
- We're all set.
- Right.
Well, this is a whole new side of you
I haven't seen before.
- What?
- Suffering in silence.
What makes you think I'm suffering?
Mr. Happy left town days ago.
- Thanks for what you're doing for Danny.
- Why the sudden interest?
- Albie told me to look out for him.
- Albie.
Is there anything
Albert hasn't taken care of?
No.
Listen, if the strong silent thing
stops working for you...
- and you need somebody to talk to...
- Yeah.
It's Rachel.
- She wants a divorce.
- And?
- And that's it.
- So you agreed?
I told her I'd think about it.
- What? No lecture?
- You've got all this talent.
You can bend people to your will.
Make them do what you want them to.
If you set your mind to it...
you can convince her in a week
to take you back.
- So why don't you?
- You think I should con Rachel back?
That's what we do isn't it, Mickey?
Create a world the way we want it to be?
You convince her that you can be
the man she wants.
Problem is,
you gotta convince yourself first.
So, let's go get this bastard.
House & Garden, please.
Movie News.
Mr. Harris,
I'm from the hospital administration.
We need to talk about how you'd like
to settle your account.
I wish you lot would talk to each other.
You're a mess.
- I'm sorry?
- I've already settled my account. Cash.
The special discount.
- We've had some faxes for you, Mr. Elliott.
- Yeah?
These movie studios.
They never leave me alone.
Wanna do me a favor, sweetheart?
Send me up some mineral water
and some fresh fruit.
Of course, sir.
The car's outside.
I'll see to it,
and I hope you enjoy your stay.
Yeah, I'm sure I will. Thank you.
By the book, Danny.
Jason Elliott.
- So you're in the film business?
- So they tell me.
You like the movies, Frank?
Since I was a kid.
They don't make them like they used to.
So, what is it you do exactly?
I find the money
that makes the magic happen.
You ever thought of putting money
into films, Frank?
- I like my money where it is.
- And where is that?
Where I can see it.
- Would you excuse me?
- Sure.
Hey, Frank.
I'm wining and dining
a couple of investors later.
Might be nice to round the night off here,
if that's okay?
- No problem.
- Thanks, Frank, I appreciate that.
Danny thinks we need £20,000
for the convincer.
How much are we short?
If we can get £5,000 from Gorley up front,
we can scrape £16,000.
I'm telling you, Gorley's got trouble
written all over him.
I just don't want to get in there
and be half-cocked.
So the question is:
Where are we going to find a sucker
with £4,000 at this time of the night?
What? No.
Come on, Eddie. It's better than the banks.
A 50% Return in three days.
No.
- It's for Albert.
- No.
- Will you stop saying "no"?
Albert told me that if I ever thought
I was talking to a con man...
just keep saying no.
We're not trying to con you, Eddie,
we're asking for your help.
- Three days?
- Tops.
- For Albert?
- Absolutely.
If I don't get paid back, you're all barred.
Good seeing you.
- How you doing?
- Okay.
- What are we doing here?
- Come on, just relax.
Frank, this is Jeff Machin.
Jeff, this is Frank Gorley.
He owns this place.
Arrogant asshole.
- What's his problem?
- You tell me.
I made the guy $3 million last year...
he treats me like the hired help.
Excuse me, Frank.
- These bastards are cheating on me.
- Joe, just calm down, okay?
Let's get you a coffee.
I don't want a coffee, I want another drink.
You cheating bastards!
I'm sorry, Frank. It's okay.
- Your friend needs a lesson in manners.
- I know.
You got somebody who can maybe
run him home?
What?
Joe might not like to lose his money,
but he's got very powerful connections.
He's a personal friend of Sly Stallone.
And I promised that I'd keep
an eye on him.
He knows Sly Stallone?
Well, it's not so much Sly,
it's more his mother.
- I could buy this place.
- He's staying at the Grovesnor.
Close it down, turn it into a shithole.
I'm sorry, Frank. I gotta talk to Jeff.
You got anywhere quiet?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
He's a drunk.
I don't want to work with him.
Come on, Joe's okay.
If he's in this time, then count me out.
- I gave you my word.
- Then screw him and screw you.
The people you do business with
have got a really bad attitude problem.
You know that?
Do me a favor, pal?
Keep your nose out
of what doesn't concern you.
Okay, that's enough.
You want to watch your mouth, boy.
I'm sorry, Frank,
Jeff's just wound up about Joe.
Okay, look. All right. He's out.
I'll get somebody else to cover his end.
Now, this is Frank's office...
a bit of respect wouldn't go amiss.
- You found a buyer yet?
- It's all in place.
We buy in at £15,000, we get back £60,000.
That's film extras.
In all the casting agencies,
they try and strike up an exclusive...
with any movie with a decent budget.
It's small potatoes in
the grand scheme of things...
but, hey, every little counts, right?
Except we just lost Joe.
- I said, I'd take care of it.
- How?
This is a cash deal. We meet
the producer at breakfast...
before the banks open.
You know what?
Screw the deal, I'm glad Joe's out of it.
The guy's only interested
in the bottom line. He's got no soul.
You know what his favorite film is,
Frank? Rambo.
How are you gonna do business
with a guy like that?
- Bogart, Cagney, now they made movies.
- You like Cagney?
No one like him, before or since.
- Best film?
- White Heat.
- "Made it, Ma."
- "Top of the world."
Good film, but not his best.
Do you know he was a dancer?
- Came up through vaudeville?
- That's right.
Best song and dance man in the business.
When you two have finished,
can we get back to the job in hand?
Yeah.
So what is this deal exactly?
The deal is with the producer,
for the extras contract.
We meet him, pay him off,
then go to the set...
and collect from the guy from the agency.
- A film set?
- Yeah.
Trouble is, like Jeff says, we lost Joe
so we're £5,000 light.
Let me get this straight.
You take this producer £15,000...
then you drive over to the film set
and collect £60,000?
That's about the strength of it.
So what if I put up the £5,000 you're light?
So long as I pick up his share,
this guy Joe's share, in return.
- No way.
- I wasn't talking to you.
You gonna let this guy muscle in?
All he'd be doing is taking over
Joe's share. What difference does it make?
I don't even know this guy.
For God's sake, the lame brain's
gonna give us a check now.
- Jeff, come on, please. Just relax.
- All right.
It does have to be cash, Frank. I'm sorry.
You gonna be polite?
Frank helped us out with Joe.
Cutting him in is the least we can do.
Thanks, Frank.
Like I said, I like my money
where I can see it.
I'm coming with you.
All right.
I'll call.
Three sevens.
Flush.
Again.
- Pete.
- You took your time.
Nice to see you, too.
The money's in the one with the flap open,
so give that one to Danny first.
- How long?
- Any minute now.
Just be out of sight.
I've told you, Lucy,
either the line goes or I do.
Well, Jesus Christ! Go and tell them.
- Jenny baby.
- Jason.
How's it going?
The director's a moron.
Can't you fire him for me?
Baby, I could, but he'd sue my ass off.
This is a very good friend of mine.
This is Frank Gorley.
- Glad to meet you, Frank.
- How do you do?
Okay, come on, now. Back to work.
Time is money.
He's such a slave driver.
- That's Jenny Cole?
- You know her?
- I was reading about her this morning.
- She's gonna be huge.
They're calling her
the new Audrey Hepburn.
- Jason.
- How you doing?
Okay. We still on?
It's a done deal.
Great, I've got 200 wannabe starlets
waiting for the nod, here.
- You fellas wanna help me pick?
- No, we'll leave that, all right?
You gonna talk all day
or you gonna give me my money?
Split three ways, just like he said.
That's beautiful.
£20,000. Not a bad return for half an hour,
is it?
- Looks like Joe's loss is my gain.
- I guess so.
While we're here, any chance of walking
around the set, watching a bit of filming?
Frank, I gotta get back.
Square things up with Joe.
I thought Joe was out of the picture.
He is for this but not the big one.
- Big one?
- Shut your mouth, Jason.
- Did I say anything?
- Just get in the car.
Anybody asks for me,
tell them I left five minutes ago.
So where's my £4,000?
We just gave it away.
Hi, Eddie.
- Did you just give my money away?
- It's all right.
- It was bait.
- Bait?
So did we get the green light?
We tell him the tale tonight.
- Here he is. Frank. How are you doing?
- Okay.
- You remember Jenny?
- Of course.
She wrapped late today.
She wants a little bit of R and R.
Excuse me. Are you Jennifer Cole?
Have you got a pen?
Thank you.
Can you get someone to watch over Jen
while she plays the tables?
No problem.
See Miss Cole isn't bothered.
- Go have fun.
- Thank you, Frank.
- Can we get a drink?
- Yeah.
How did it go with Joe?
- The guy's a fruit loop.
- I told you that six months ago.
It's a shame, I kind of liked him,
you know?
- But this is business.
- Yeah.
So what about the big one?
- You mentioned it earlier.
- Jeff?
Okay, Frank, sit down.
Tell him.
We're gonna make a movie.
Kind of low budget. Say about £5,000,000.
Jenny thinks it's her big break
in the States...
but where we're really
gonna make our money is in Asia.
Asia?
- Can I be frank, Frank?
- Please.
While everyone else is looking at
the home market...
we sell the video rights to Asia up front.
We can virtually name our price.
I figure we're gonna get £10 million
without breaking a sweat.
- And she's agreed to do it?
- She signed the contract yesterday.
So is Joe in or out?
He still wants in, but you know what
these Mob guys are like.
They're a liability.
Bottom line is, Frank:
If you want a slice of the cake,
I can make it happen.
How much are we talking about?
It's gonna be the same as me and Jeff
are in for.
That's 200 big ones.
£200,000?
With a guarantee...
that you're gonna get
double your money back in three months.
No, I think I'll pass.
What?
I'm £15,000 up.
I think I'll quit while I'm ahead.
- What if we...
- We can find someone else.
It's not a problem, okay?
- How about that drink?
- Sure.
You've got to pick it up, Dan.
You're talking to this guy about money.
He's surrounded by money,
he's not fazed by it.
You're offering him something
he's already got.
You've gotta think about what brought us
this far.
What can you give him that he can't get
anywhere else?
Don't talk to his head, talk to his heart.
Emotion not reason.
Think.
- You like the movies, Frank?
- Since I was a kid.
- You like Cagney?
- Of course.
Best song and dance man in the business.
You like Cagney?
- What do you say, Frank?
- Count me in.
- Bankers draft.
- Thanks, Frank.
Now that's beautiful.
There's a receipt for £200,000
and a copy of the contract.
We're all going to make a lot of money.
We'd better.
- Top of the world.
- Top of the world, Frank.
You're not gonna join us, baby?
I'm trying to get my head around
this damn script.
Do you want me to
run some lines with you?
Would you mind?
I tell you what.
Why doesn't Frank help you?
Get him in the swing of things. Frank?
Me?
Come on. You just gotta read through
the script with Jen.
You're gonna be great. Come on.
Go ahead.
- I've never done this sort of thing before.
- Don't worry you'll be fine.
Thank you, Frank.
Thank you.
Check's cleared.
It's being transferred now.
Time to make sure he won't come after us.
Then we blow him out tonight.
You ready?
Yeah.
Do you think he's gonna be all right?
If he does as he's told, he'll be fine.
You have to be face-on to Mickey when
he shoots or the signal might not work.
If it doesn't work, when you go down
fall on your chest.
The force should split the bag, all right?
Danny, no theatrics, okay?
One shot and you go down
like a sack of potatoes.
- By the book.
We're done.
Okay, we start shooting next month.
Jason is talking to directors all week.
I hope he's getting someone better
than the last one.
Where is Jason?
He should be here by now.
Relax, Frank, he's just crossing the "T's"...
Hey, Jason.
- Jason?
- We're screwed.
- What?
- Joe's gone.
- He checked out of the hotel first thing.
- So what's the problem?
He wasn't in the picture anyway.
He was co-signature at the bank.
I didn't have time to change it.
He cleaned us out before he left.
Cleaned us out how? Of what?
Everything, all right. It's all gone!
Every penny!
- God, I had £200,000 in there!
- Well, we all did!
You mean, he took all the money?
He took my money, too.
I gave that money to you, you little shit.
Well, I'm telling you, it's all gone!
- Go get it back!
- I can't!
He figures we welched on him first
when we cut him out.
Let me know where he is
and I'll get it back.
You can't, none of us can.
He's connected.
- I want my money back.
- Don't be stupid, Jeff.
Come on, man. I'm telling you.
I'm telling you, man, he's taken all of it!
There's nothing left!
- Frank.
- You dirty rat!
- Get me out of here, Frank.
- Get her out!
Frank, please. The press.
- He lost my money!
- Please, Frank. Help me!
Get her out. It's okay.
I'll take care of it. Go.
Come on. Don't die on me.
Come on, Danny. You're gonna be all right.
How's he doing?
They're operating on him now.
What about Gorley?
He's laying low. He thinks he killed Danny,
so he'll stay that way.
Good.
- Police?
- I told them we found him like that.
He was there for a big game
and got robbed for his stash.
Did they buy it?
There were no other witnesses,
so they had no choice.
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
You were right. He wasn't ready.
Yes, he was. He did good.
He's gonna be okay.
£3,900. £4,000.
- What?
- Interest?
- I thought you'd forgotten me.
- No.
- How do you feel?
- Like I've been shot.
The doctor says you should be
up and about in no time.
We've got Albie's present,
you want to come?
Yeah, I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Your carriage awaits, sir.
- You know how I hate surprises.
- You'll like this one.
Just look at you two.
I should start taking out
medical insurance.
First, there's this.
Well, that's a lot of money.
And now, for the cherry on top.
Look, Albert...
there's no way I can apologize enough.
The truth is, I'm an idiot.
I'm not fit to lace your boots.
I'm the shit on your shoes...
and I don't deserve your forgiveness.
But I'm begging you.
Forgive me.
Thank you, Frank. So sweet of you
to run those lines with me.
Now that's show biz.
English