Previously on "The Originals"...
This town was my home once.
I want it back.
The city grew accustomed
to having a King.
You wanted this throne.
If you won't do anything, I will.
Kieran's the only family I have left.
I'm tired of being alone.
You're supposed to be a harvest girl,
but maybe you don't belong here.
A battle is brewing, T.
While everyone's busy choosing sides,
I'm gonna find a way
to take back our city.
Daylight rings shield
vampires from the sun,
so why not a moonlight ring to
protect werewolves from the curse?
You made a deal with Klaus Mikaelson?
We could finally control what we are.
The humans who hunt us,
the witches who curse us,
the vampires who hate us,
we wouldn't just be their equals.
We'd be their superiors.
You're up early.
After the night we had,
I expected you to sleep in.
Yes, well, morning sun
offers the best light.
Hold still.
I'm almost finished.
In my last life, I was far too
modest if I was in the nude.
Well, then consider
yourself much improved.
Modesty is for the weak.
Well, are you gonna show me?
The painting is a gift.
A token to honor our pact.
Our pact?
We had such a lovely night
and now I see it was
all a means to an end.
A rather delicious means to
a mutually beneficial end.
Tell me.
Beyond the pleasures of last night
and the promise of what I'm
sure is an exquisite painting,
what exactly would
a french quarter witch gain
from aligning with you?
Well, the treaty my
dear brother negotiated
between the warring
factions of this city,
the one that you yourself signed.
No doubt everyone means well,
but this is after all...
Still the french quarter?
A borough rife with natural enemies.
What you and your witches need is
the protection only I can provide.
No one... not vampires,
not werewolves,
not even my brother will dare trifle
with you if I am on your side.
And in exchange...
I am to offer you what, exactly?
All I ask is for
the promise of your allegiance.
One never knows when a powerful
witch might come in handy.
Well, then.
[Women chanting in french]
Aah!
Sine la quatrieme puella leve,
comme Genevieve ceciderit.
Sine la quatrieme puella
leve, comme Genevieve ceciderit.
Monique, are you ok? Monique, you
sounded like you were possessed.
I wasn't possessed.
I was channeling the ancestors.
They say it's time to
complete the reaping.
To do that, the fourth harvest
girl must be resurrected,
which means... it's time
for Genevieve to die.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/
[Drill whirring]
Enough with all the racket!
Is there a problem, brother?
Gentlemen, please.
I agreed to a general sprucing
up, not a bloody 3-ring circus.
Marcel and his minions abused our home
for the better part of a century.
Now, you might be content
to live in squalor. I'm not.
I agree with your brother.
It's a new era in the french quarter.
This place could use a makeover.
Careful, Elijah.
When this one agrees with you, it's
a sure sign she wants something.
Actually... I do
have a request.
I'm told our coven hasn't been
able to celebrate feast days
in the open since Marcel
restricted the use of magic.
Now with the new peace,
I'd like that to change.
Am I to assume that you have
a certain feast day in mind?
The fete des benedictions.
Feast of the blessings.
In the past,
members of the community
offered witches gifts
in exchange for blessings.
We'd like to use it as a forum
for introducing our young
harvest girls to society.
So your coven attempted
to destroy my family
and you yourself held my
siblings in unspeakable torment.
And you would like
a party for the witches.
[Klaus chuckles]
I made my amends with your brother.
Why don't you think it over?
Oh, don't be such a stiff, Elijah.
The tourists love a good festival.
Besides, what better way
to cement the solidarity
than a show of faith
toward a onetime enemy?
A onetime enemy with whom you've
grown rather nauseatingly intimate.
Who said maintaining
alliances can't be fun?
One would think you'd
be a little more interested
in attending to the needs of
the mother of your child.
So she's the reason behind this
oh-so-thoughtful renovation.
Elijah, the truth is the mother
of my child is werewolf royalty.
She's far safer in
the bayou with her pack
than she would ever be here with us.
Don't worry. I'll bring her
home before the birth.
No child of mine
will be born in a swamp.
Hayley: You've gotta be kidding me.
Seriously, what is going on?
Who are all these people?
Why are they standing out
here all weird and lurky?
They've come from all over.
All the packs.
Why? To see a baby
that isn't even born yet?
Forget the baby. These freaks,
they come here to see you.
Oliver: You know, given
the place your parents
held in pack hierarchy,
maybe they think
you're gonna be the long-lost
werewolf messiah or something.
Great. No pressure or anything.
[Telephone ringing]
Hello?
Oliver. I trust you have an update
on the matter we discussed.
Yeah, um...
About that.
We got wolves coming in
by the truckload right now,
so it's gonna be a little
tricky to find us one guy.
I mean, all you gave me
was a first name.
Yes. His name is Cary.
He's got blond hair and blue eyes.
He's one of my clan...
A distant relative
from the northeast Atlantic pack.
His presence is required if
we are to continue with our plan.
You find him and you bring him to me.
All right, fine.
I'm on it.
Another thing... my brother
will soon invite you
to a feast honoring the witches.
You and your friends will
graciously accept the invitation.
Why the hell would I do that?
Because if Elijah believes
his treaty is working,
he'll be less inclined
to get in my way.
[Music playing]
What do you want?
I formed an alliance with someone
who may be able to help your uncle.
Let me guess.
Tall, redhead, axe to grind?
Those resurrected witches
are the ones who
hexed Kieran in the first place.
Why would she want to help?
Because it's my decree that she does.
I believe the words you're
looking for are "thank you."
By all means, say no if
you have an alternative.
No.
Wait.
Do whatever you have to do.
Just help him.
Thierry: You wanted me to
keep an eye on Klaus. I did.
If you ask me, this is a good thing.
Him fawning all over a girl
you've got wrapped around
your finger helps us.
I don't want Cami getting hurt.
She's already got witches spying on her.
Do you have any idea
what Klaus is gonna do
when he finds out that we hooked up?
Not my problem.
The thing we need to worry about
is what his hybrid ass is up to.
He's got something going
on with the witches,
and he's doing it
behind Elijah's back.
Whatever he's up to,
if I can find proof...
Oh, you'll what? You're gonna rat
him out to his older brother?
You're gonna turn them
against each other?
You're exiled from the quarter.
Elijah even smells you
coming and you're dead.
You don't know them like I do.
They're half turned
against each other already.
1,000 years of family
drama, pride, guilt, envy,
all built up like a powder keg.
All you have to do is light a match.
Then where do we buy matches?
Look around, Marcel.
We have nothing.
I started with nothing.
Hell, things didn't get
rolling until I turned you.
You and your music and the
whole city for the taking.
Those were the days, T.
Let's go get them back.
And who put you in charge?
I communed with the ancestors.
They said it's time for
you to sacrifice yourself.
Of course. It will be an honor
to fulfill my duty to our coven.
But it's not quite my time yet.
The ancestors were very clear.
We need for you to die so
our community can have
the full power of the harvest.
Careful, Monique.
Not so long ago,
I was one of those ancestors.
A spirit forced to watch
as little by little,
witches surrendered
everything to vampires.
We may no longer live
under Marcel's thumb,
but I for one don't particularly
enjoy answering to Elijah, either.
Before I take my leave,
I'd like to ensure
that you have the power
to control your own fate.
The Mikaelsons' mother
Esther was a powerful witch.
Her spellbook contains enchantments
that we can use to our own ends.
I can steal it for our coven
and we'll never be held
in subjugation again.
You'll have your sacrifice...
But I have things to do before I die.
You want us to go to a witch event
on bended knee and give them a gift?
I'm sorry, but I just remembered.
We're busy doing just about
anything else that night.
Diego, this isn't a request.
Your name is on that treaty.
Now, if you have
any difficulty whatsoever
with your newfound position, I'd be
more than willing to remove you.
I never thought I'd see the day.
Vampires bowing down to witches.
I see it as a demonstration
of strength...
Acknowledging a lesser faction.
But you're not asking, are you?
I see it's true what
they say about you, Elijah.
You make even
strong-arming seem noble.
Well...
The tourists do eat this stuff up.
Can you imagine what they'd think if
they suddenly found
out it was all real?
I take it you want me
at the public show
and the private party afterward?
That is correct.
I'd be happy to attend.
And in return, you will
owe the humans a favor.
Your people are uniquely poised
to set an example for
the rest of the french quarter.
Elijah: Which is why it's important
for the wolves to attend.
Thanks but no thanks?
Let's hear the man out.
The witches are the ones
that cursed your pack.
And they've been
nothing but crap to me
since I first came to town. No.
We're not going.
It's a new day in the quarter, Hayley.
I agree with Oliver.
If we're gonna coexist,
we have to play ball.
We'll send a representative
with a gift.
That was too easy.
Don't trust him.
Don't trust any of them.
Oliver: You don't stop squirming,
I don't care who you know, I'm
gonna kneecap you right here.
When I asked you to bring Cary
to me, it was as my guest.
Might I recommend you release him
before I opt to release you
from your mortal coil.
I found him like you
asked and he jumped me.
Now, his pack's been going at mine
since the beginning of time
I don't owe him a thing.
You see, it's that shortsighted attitude
that led to the demise
of the werewolves.
I'm pretty sure Marcel
and the witches did that.
The packs should have been united.
Marcel saw that weakness
and he exploited it.
If you seek to rebuild
with only the crescents,
you may as well stay
in your hovels in the bog.
I don't believe we've had
the pleasure of an introduction.
Legele says you're
descended from our line.
The legends are true.
Come here. I understand that
this ring was passed down
through generations of our family.
I need to know what stone it housed.
I never saw it with a stone.
Could you ask around
for me, mate? Hmm?
See what you can find out.
Diego: You can't just start
a revolution all on your own
from exile across the river.
I mean, like it or not, Elijah's
plan is the new reality.
Elijah's got you
bowing down to witches.
How long until you're
kowtowing to werewolves?
Right. And who's gonna lead
this rebellion, huh? You?
I got a few ideas.
I remember the last time I stood
with you against an original.
Didn't go so well.
All we gotta do is show
that we won't bow down.
Make enough noise, they'll leave.
I figure we can be a lot louder
if we're in it together.
Look, Elijah Mikaelson's
a dick, no doubt.
Thing is, with him at
least I know where I stand.
Marcel: Do you?
We've been watching Klaus.
Making deals with witches, holding
secret meetings with werewolves.
You can't trust these people.
You're the one who
picked up Klaus' coin.
You, Marcel.
Maybe T's got a short you're
the one who memory, but I don't.
You're a coward.
Thierry: Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa!
When I picked up that coin,
I was saving your ass.
Klaus was gonna kill all of you.
A good leader knows when he's
gotta fight another day.
Now that day's here.
I'm ready. You gonna fight with me?
With what? Huh?
Look around.
All you got is Thierry
and a whole bunch of talk.
You guys don't seem to get it.
You lost, all right?
I picked the winning side, so
if you want to start a war...
You're fighting against me.
Time we got more persuasive.
[Door creaks]
What is this?
High School?
Why don't you take the hint
and mind your own business?
This is my pack.
That makes it my business.
Jackson: No need to get all riled up.
It's not good for you, Hayley.
I have tried no need to get
to play nice.
The last month of pregnancy is
all hormones and mood swings,
so unless you want me to
snap your arm like a twig,
I suggest that you
tell me what is going on.
Oliver: You can go to hell.
Jackson: Knock it off.
There's no reason to keep it from her.
I can think of a reason.
Tall and immortal and wears
a pocket scarf. Uhh!
Hayley, you're one of us.
You deserve to know.
Go on.
We made an alliance... That's gonna
change everything for the wolves.
An alliance with who?
Klaus.
Tell me everything.
You came all this way to
beg for some human's life?
Father Kieran's time is running out
and he has been an ally to me.
Your ally, and Cami's uncle.
Sorry. As I've already said,
there's no way to undo that hex.
Oh, come on. You and I both
know there's always a loophole.
Not for this.
At least not among my people.
Although I do wonder.
Your mother was powerful.
She would have had access
to all manner of spells.
Perhaps I could take a look
through her grimoire.
You want to use
father Kieran's ailment
as an excuse to look through
my mother's spellbook.
Very devious.
Come on.
The grimoire is worthless to you.
But with its power, I could
solidify my place in the coven.
No, I'm sorry, love.
It's bad enough my mother's power was
consecrated with your ancestors.
The last thing I need is for you to
get a look at an entire book
of her dirty, little tricks.
That's unfortunate.
Particularly for poor father Kieran.
I guess you'll be
the one to tell Cami.
You think you have leverage over me?
I will not be manipulated.
[Whispering indistinctly]
[Groaning]
And I won't be threatened.
So, between the two of us,
we each know where we stand.
As long as we can retain
that mutual respect,
I don't see a need for any
further demonstrations of power.
Don't call me again.
[Music playing] [Crowd cheering]
It's time.
Klaus will be at the event, which
means the compound will be empty.
You know what to do.
Now, in accordance with
the fete des benedictions,
the witches of New
Orleans bless you all.
[Crowd cheering]
Klaus: A little too easy, isn't it?
I've been expecting you.
You're late.
[Music playing]
Davina.
Elijah.
It's lovely to see you.
And under far better circumstances.
Is it?
My friend Tim is still dead and
your brother's still breathing.
Davina, that's enough.
Elijah has been a patron
to us this evening.
We will show him respect.
Thank you for all of this.
This isn't for you.
You know as well as I that your
people would never accept a truce
unless we showed them some respect.
So be it.
Enjoy your party.
Strange. I thought you'd be in the
company of your colorful friends.
Oh. You asked for a representative
for the werewolves,
so... take me or leave me.
Is something wrong?
These people came to praise witches.
What has she done
to prove herself worthy?
She's a harvest girl.
Like you.
Our power is a gift
from the ancestors.
I've had to make sacrifices
to honor that gift.
I lost my mother.
My aunt.
Davina has done nothing
but stand against us.
She just needs a little lesson.
If there's one thing I'm good at,
it's putting people in their place.
[Clinking]
Welcome. As is our
time-honored tradition,
you are all welcome to
deliver your offerings.
It is our custom that no one
should be turned away,
no blessing be denied.
Cami: Do you get any gifts?
What are you doing here?
Technically, I'm crashing,
but it's you I came to see.
Don't worry, I just want to say
my piece and then I'll leave.
Here.
And what is this?
An offering, from me.
I know we have no reason
to like each other,
but I want to honor
what Elijah has built.
What my uncle worked for.
Oh. So this is about your uncle.
Like I said, I know you have no
reason to help me, but Klaus said
a long time ago,
you were cheated out of life, and
if I can't help him, if you can't
help him, neither will he.
And so I'm asking you... please.
Klaus said you were from this era.
And I thought with your red hair...
I had one just like this.
Perhaps I can help you.
[Music playing]
Josh. What are you doing here?
What, are you kidding?
No way I'd miss out on your big day.
Besides, music, wind, fire...
The club kid in me
is, like, in heaven.
You don't look like you're
having much fun, though.
Hey. Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Joshua.
What a fortunate coincidence
finding you here.
We have unfinished business.
You need to leave here.
Right now.
Now, to be fair, you're not
quite as powerful as
you once were, are you?
You're in no position to give orders.
Come along, lad.
Hey, can we talk about this?
Davina: Josh!
Klaus: Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention, please.
We are gathered here today to pay
homage to our beloved witches,
but one very special witch
has been utterly ignored.
Klaus: That seems
a little unfair to me.
No.
I don't want your gift.
I understand why you would
reject me, given our past
in truth, many of us here today
have been wronged in the conflict
which my brother's treaty ended.
Your friend Josh was involved
in a plot to kill me.
It would be well within my right
to execute him here and now.
But. In the spirit of solidarity,
and for your favor, Davina,
I hereby pardon him.
Josh... from this day forward, you
have nothing to fear from me.
Please.
[Music playing]
So are you gonna open it?
What? What is it?
It's the spell that
makes daylight rings.
I hear you made quite an
impression with the wolves.
My arrangement with them was
supposed to be a secret,
and yet you forced it out of them.
It's very bold.
As was your decision to represent
them here today, on your own.
I trust you'll do nothing
to harm our cause.
Are you really gonna go
behind Elijah's back?
What difference does it make to you
as long as your people benefit?
If I find out that you are playing
some game, trying to manipulate us
for one of your schemes...
You know, you've come a long way,
little wolf.
I knew you were tough,
I knew you were cunning,
but I never knew you were a queen.
[Playing]
Happy fete des benedictions.
We have a message for all
of you from Marcel Gerard.
[Crowd murmuring]
Control yourselves.
This is a vulgar trick.
We do not violate our agreement.
[Shouting]
Hey!
- Elijah?
- Elijah: Hayley.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Thierry: Blood on the walls.
Pile of bodies.
All in all, I'd say message received.
Did you get Davina out first?
As planned, Josh took care of Davina.
I made sure the other harvest
girls got out in the clear.
That was just the warning shot.
Now we double down.
Man: Marcel!
Aah!
I.
And yet still you return
to the french quarter.
You gonna kill me, Elijah? Go ahead.
But then you won't know
what Klaus has got going
with that witch in his pocket.
Oh, whatever shall I do?
I suppose I could just ask him.
Yeah. Make sure he tells you all about
the secret meetings
with the werewolves.
That is, if he's still speaking to you
once he knows that you killed me.
Do you not know me?
[Groaning]
For your violation.
No. No, no.
You live... or you die
according to my will.
Try to remember that.
[Crying]
You left without my offering.
Your vampires ruined my party.
Oh, they're not
my vampires anymore, love.
Although Marcel certainly took a page
out of my book of dramatic effect.
Look, I owed Davina some consolation
because I killed her first love.
I do try to make up
for my wrongdoings.
As with our little quarrel earlier.
So. Here.
I picked it out earlier tonight.
A friend of yours gave me a hand.
And what friend was that?
Well, open it.
See for yourself.
Did you really think I would leave
my mother's grimoire unprotected?
A century ago, I dreamed of what
it would be like to know you.
Now I'm glad I didn't.
I might have been naive enough
to fall for you, or fear you,
but I learned a lot in death,
and trust me, Klaus Mikaelson:
It's you who should be afraid of me.
Pity. I will miss the sex.
Your friend Cami showed up tonight.
Her offering was quite sweet.
So I gave her hope that I
would lift Kieran's hex,
but there is no hope.
Or if there was, there isn't now.
If the priest dies, then believe me,
you will follow swiftly after him.
[Chuckles] It would be foolish of
you to kill me, a potential ally,
in defense of some powerless
human who is, by the way,
sleeping with your enemy... Marcel.
Hayley: I've learned my lesson.
At first I was against your plan.
I thought that we should just
live with Elijah's treaty,
but after that party,
those innocent people.
There will never be a peace.
The weak will always be at the mercy
of whoever is calling the shots.
It's survival of the fittest.
We need to protect ourselves.
And we... we need
to protect each other.
We need to use Klaus' help while
he's still willing to give it.
But Jackson... From now on, you
have to tell me everything.
And no matter what...
We do not trust Klaus.
Well, I see that you've already
avenged the little wolf.
But judging by your look,
you're still out for blood.
If the definition of insanity is doing
the same thing repeatedly and
expecting different results,
then surely my quest
for your salvation
ranks me as one of the maddest of men.
Come on, then. What horrible deed
has the bastard done this time?
Do you know, in the past,
I actually appreciated
the methods to your manipulations.
However, now here we are, poised
on the brink of a new era
which will benefit not only
your home but your child,
and you go behind my back
to conspire with wolves.
Conspire is hardly the word I
would use for a family council.
Lest you forget, Elijah,
they are my family
as much as any Mikaelson...
A name, in truth,
I cannot even call my own.
How casually you disavow 1,000
years of allegiance towards you.
And now that I've found the remnants
of my other family,
am I to ignore their plight?
I would've thought you'd
support my desire to help them,
when in doing so,
I help Hayley, and the child.
Do not question my allegiance
towards that child.
Oh, and I suppose
your affection for Hayley
has nothing to do with
your tireless dedication.
Yes, you see, I saw how
you cared for her tonight.
Called her name in the dark.
The zeal with which you destroy
those who would harm her.
I have denied every single impulse
I have ever had for that woman.
Out of some misbegotten respect
for intentions that
you don't even have.
Klaus: I'm warning you...
Elijah: I'm warning you.
I've forgiven you.
I have stood by you.
I've forsaken every single
one of my desires
in the name of your
ridiculous redemption.
No more.
If I want something...
I'll take it.
And nothing... nothing...
Will stand in my way.
Cami: Klaus, what are you...
I came here to apologize.
I've made a terrible mistake.
Whatever it is, you
should sleep it off.
I'm sure it can wait till morning.
You went to Genevieve.
She was moved by your plea.
She may even have cured Kieran.
But I insulted her.
And as a means of revenge,
she is refusing him aid.
Kieran will die because of me,
and it will be a horrible death.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I believe that
secrets are a poison.
They need to be spat out.
Like your secret...
About your time with Marcel.
Isn't that what you wanted?
You compelled me
to go out with Marcel.
You made me your spy.
And maybe it's your fault
we got together,
and you're just mad because
you didn't get to control it.
You tell Marcel if I see him again,
I'll kill him.
[Music playing]
[Indistinct chatter, laughter]
You don't need to keep coming out.
I'd tell you if something was wrong.
But she's doing ok.
The girl has a natural
gift for leading.
She surprised everyone.
Not everyone.
[Music playing]
Do you want to join us?
What I want...
Is for that girl to be happy.
Don't tell her I was here.
Marcel: This is Thierry Vanchure.
Mean-ass horn player,
lover of feisty women,
witch, vampire, and human alike.
[Music playing]
[Sigh]
I rebuilt this city with him
and he always had my back.
Even when I screwed up
and forgot to have his.
And now...
All I can do is promise you this, t.
I won't let you die in vain.
I will take back our city.
[Thud]
Going up against The Originals?
For real, no backing down?
No backing down.
Monique: You failed us.
Genevieve: I told you.
It will take time.
Do you think the ancestors
care about your excuses?
The vampires attacked us.
We can't retaliate
until we possess our full strength.
Your sacrifice is the final step.
[Groaning]
[Gasping]
Nous concedumus sa vie a Genevieve.
Si elle hecatage a filia de Mikaelson.
[Gasping]
What are they saying?
They told me to let you live.
But in exchange, they
want another offering.
One of their choosing.
Tell me. Whatever it is they want,
I will make sure they get it.
I swear it.
It's the child.
They want us to kill Klaus' child.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/