Come on, Albert!
Mickey Bricks, if you've
ever been brilliant,
please be brilliant now.
Gentlemen! I know what
you're thinking...but, er...
I guess...
most of you must
have thought that...
one day it would end like this...
sync and corrections by Bellows
www.addic7ed.com
- Oh, you did not just say that!
- It is a well known fact.
- Well known by who?
- Everyone. - Not me.
- That's because you're a bird.
- Mickey?
Leave me out of this.
How can you say women are
more argumentative than men?
- Because it's a well-known fact.
- No it is not. - See?
- See what? - I mentioned that women
are more argumentative than men,
and you've done nothing
but argue since.
- I was discussing.
- What's the difference?
One is arguing and the other one....
isn't.
Way to go, sis.
You baffled him with logic...
He knows what I mean. Eddie,
do you think I'm argumentative?
- You are a bit, yeah.
- No, I'm not. I wasn't arguing.
No, she was discussing, you see.
- Yeah, they do a lot of that, birds.
- Yeah, they do...mmm. Mmm.
Oh, all right.
You can be so annoying,
really...all of you.
Well, looks like you were right,
he arrived last evening.
Who did?
Our new mark.
Madani Wasem.
Came to London in the '80s to
re-trace his father's footsteps
and accept a place
at Oxford University.
He graduated with a degree in
economics before returning
to Bahrain to take his place on the
board of his father's company,
The Gulf Partnership.
Wasem was with friends when he heard
of his father's death five weeks ago.
Yes! It's party time!
So they didn't get on then?
He'd lived his entire life
in his father's shadow.
He was heard telling
an aide at the funeral
that he'd spent his adult
life waiting for him to die.
Oh, what a charmer.
How much did he get?
North of 850 million.
He got the family money
and his father's shares,
but he has no real power.
His father was respected,
but he isn't.
The board of Gulf Partnership
quickly closed ranks
to stop him taking control.
Which left Wasem with a bit
of a chip on his shoulder.
Oh, poor love
They see him for what
he is... Little more than a thug.
He doesn't earn respect,
he buys it.
Using his wealth to surround
himself with people
who will do whatever he asks.
Including an enforcer, someone who
will kill or torture on demand.
The man who led the move
to stop Wasem taking control
of his father's company was
found with his throat cut
in his own bathroom by his 10-year-old
daughter, yesterday afternoon.
Wasem has been linked
to two similar killings
since his father's death, and
a long list of business associates
being beaten and having
their families threatened.
- Question.
- Go on.
We usually spend our time staying
away from people like this.
Why are we going after him?
I think he's too good to pass up.
He's been making his way around
Europe playing the markets.
For anyone that openly opposes
him, he uses violence,
but he knows that to take control
of his father's company, he has
to prove to the shareholders he has
his father's flair for making money.
So far he's played the markets
in Greece, Turkey, Spain,
and Portugal, making a
hefty profit in each.
Now he's in London, and he'll
be looking for a broker.
Why travel?
You can buy shares anywhere.
That's one of the lessons he
actually learnt from his father...
local knowledge is the key
to making a good return.
So he flies in, talks
to whoever he can,
tries to find an inside track, and
then buys through a local broker.
What kind of money
are we talking about?
In Spain he invested
six million euros.
He is very definitely high risk,
but with that comes high rewards.
Well...I'm in.
Ash?
Well, you know me.
Where you go, I go.
Albert?
Yeah, all right.
It would be rude not to.
Good.
Then let's go get him.
It is done.
How?
His throat cut from ear
to ear while he sat...
in the restroom.
Very appropriate.
You know the last
thing he said to me
was that my only chance
of regaining my father's company...
had gone down the toilet.
There was a problem.
His wife ran to a neighbour,
the police shut off the streets,
- our enforcer was trapped.
- Was he arrested?
No.
They shot him.
He is dead.
Replace him.
So what's going on?
Truth?
Always.
I'm tired, Albert.
Take a break.
I don't think a fortnight in Vegas
is gonna cure it this time.
Well, so take a year...two.
It's not that easy.
What about you?
Ash?
Sean and Emma?
We're all big enough
to take care of ourselves.
No, we're a crew, a family.
We don't walk out on each other.
So this guy isn't just another mark?
He's your retirement fund?
Marks like this one don't
come along very often.
No they don't.
So maybe everything we've done
has been leading us to this point.
One big mark, our
very own lottery win.
Then we can all walk away on
top, money in our pockets.
He could kill you.
Well, then we make that
a risk worth taking.
Oh, Emma, shopping list.
Oo, my kind of job.
Anything new there Em?
Yeah. His favourite buys are gas
and oil, but he hates new media,
pharmaceuticals,
retail companies.
What he loves best
is an edge, something
that sets him ahead
from everybody else.
Then that's exactly
what we'll give him.
Sean, let's see how long we've
got, he's got a private plane,
but check with the service see
when he's due to leave.
- Yeah, gotcha.
- How are things going?
It's going live now,
bank account's set up,
- I'm still working on the hardware
but I think I can crack it. - Great.
We're in.
Yeah. No, no, no.
Sure...
No, listen, we wait. We wait until
New York opens in the morning,
because if the Dow Jones rallies
we'll get more action here.
Yeah. My clients have very specific
targets with zero risk attached.
Yes, I said zero.
No, but listen, we wait...we wait
until the very last moment,
and then we buy fast before anyone
else gets wind of what we're buying.
No-one else in London
will get close.
All right, call you later.
Bye.
- It's too much.
- Would you relax!
This is still peanuts. We could
move up to ten million
before anyone else
starts asking questions.
Well, I'm not so sure.
I think it's all happening too fast.
What if they realise why
we buy what we do?
They won't.
How could they?
Relax. Breathe! Have some wine,
try the T-bone, it's to die for.
- Gentlemen, forgive me.
- Yes?
My employer, Madani Wasem,
was on the next table
and couldn't help overhear you
talking about your business.
You trade on the London
stock markets, no?
I'm sorry... Why are we having
this conversation?
Mr Wasem is in London
for a short time,
and he would like to invite you
to visit him at his hotel.
He believes you may find such
a visit to be mutually beneficial.
He said what!?
That he did not do home visits
and should you wish to talk to him
then to do so during office hours.
Did you tell this "William Cole"
who I was?
- Yes, sir.
- And?
He said that he had
heard of your father.
There's a fine line between
piquing someone's interest
- and being so rude they never want
to set eyes on you again. - True.
- But do you think he'll call?
- He's a bully.
It upsets him when people don't do
what he wants them to do.
Evening, all.
- What's that?
- What's what?
- The cable.
- What cable?
Oh this! Oh! Well, it depends
on how you look at it.
To the untrained eye, this is just a
length of fibre-optic cable.
But in the right hands and
with a bit of razzle dazzle,
this is the beating heart
of the British economy.
He called yet?
Playing hard to get never
worked for me either.
We've found a London broker who
can oversee all our purchases.
OK, I think we might
need a boost.
Bloody marvellous, the
man's a miracle worker.
Invested 40k, got a 60%
return inside of three days.
- That's incredible. - Someone
must be giving him an edge.
- What's his name again?
- Cole. William Cole.
- Don't they call him "Golden Balls"
or such like? - That's the chappie.
Can you get me in to see him?
Well, I'll try, old son,
but he's quite exclusive.
Mind you, not hard to see why.
You won't make it ring
by looking at it.
Maybe I called it wrong.
No, you're just wound up.
I mean, most of the time,
when a mark's just a mark,
you get a set-back, you don't panic,
you take it in your stride.
It's only cos this one's
more important.
Sorry, I don't get you.
How long have I known you, Mick?
- 20 years? - And in all that time,
you've played the odds.
Avoided marks like this Wasem
bloke like the plague.
So I figure if that's
no longer the case,
then either you've got a
death wish, in which case
I'm not sure why you have
to take me with you.
Or...he's a special kind of mark.
The kind of mark who'll give you enough
money to get out of the game forever.
Am I that easy to read?
Yeah, a doddle, always have been.
I should have known.
You can't kid a kidder.
No, that's bollocks.
You can kid anyone...
Except a mate.
Whatever you do is all right
with me. Do you mean that?
I wouldn't have said it otherwise.
Just don't start getting all
soppy on me, all right?
Anyway, I'm not getting any younger
and I'm fed up of carrying you.
Well, yes. Yeah.
Although none of this makes a blind
bit of difference if he doesn't call.
Time for plan B?
William Cole.
Mr Cole, this is Madani Wasem.
Let me check my diary.
No, sorry, I can't do noon.
Yeah, yeah, I can do 12.30.
OK, yeah, see you then.
Yeah, it's me.
We're in.
Thank you, Emma.
I swear that girl could scam a space
shuttle if she set her mind to it.
You know, long before "con"
became a dirty word,
all it stood for was "confidence".
And what's so bad about that?
Now, I'm not saying that all my
peers are angels, far from it!
But whatever industry you work in,
be it an office, or a hospital,
or a road gang I guarantee you'll
have your share of rogues too.
We're criminals because
we work outside the law.
Fine. But what we do, we
can't do without greed.
Take Madani Wasem for instance.
Now, he could buy his stocks
and his shares just
like everyone else.
Pay the same price,
take the same risk. If he did,
there's no way we could touch him.
Honestly, do you think
we could do what we do
if he wasn't looking for an edge?
If he wasn't looking
for something that gave
him an unfair advantage
over everyone else?
No. It's his greed that
makes him fair game.
All we do, is feed that greed.
And the greedier he is,
the more we can take him for.
All we need to do now is plan
things and cover all the angles
so there are no surprises.
- So how we doing?
- Yeah, good to go. Sean's out front,
he'll give us a heads
up when they're here.
- We doing a convincer?
- I thought I'd freeze him out.
Do you think that's a good idea?
The more we drive him mad,
the more he'll want to break us.
I get the logic, but this is a mark
who has people killed, mate
and your strategy
is pissing him off.
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah?
He's here.
And he's got some bird with him.
What bird?
"Fit" doesn't help, Sean.
Any clue what she does?
No, no, it's OK, send 'em up.
If you'd just like to take the
elevator up to the sixth floor,
somebody will meet you there.
Thank you.
Mr Wasem?
Perfect, right this way, please.
Don't worry.
Don't worry, ok?
Take this one. When you get
back, all right, just call me,
- we'll talk about it. Ok?
- Ok. Ok. - Good, good.
Mr Wasem.
Very pleased to meet you.
This is my broker whilst I'm
in London, Yvonne Hammond.
Ms Hammond.
A pleasure.
So. Well, look, we can, er...
Oh, Henry, for God's sake, leave it.
- Get out! - I'm sorry
- Get out! Out! Come on!
How quickly can
you leave an office?
Terribly sorry about that,
must be hire a cretin week.
You stay.
- I've been hearing a lot of good
things about you, Mr Cole. - Oh?
People are very impressed with
the returns you've achieved
and in such a short space of time.
Well, that's the beauty
of the markets isn't it?
I mean, if you're well informed
and you're, you're quick enough,
all things are possible.
They talk to you like you're
the lowest form of life.
Want to know where you are
every minute of the day,
run here, go there, do this, move that,
then they treat you like a muppet.
I know everything he does.
I know how he makes his money
and why everyone thinks
he's golden bollocks.
What do I get for it?
Nothing. Just abuse.
I don't suppose your bloke's
got any jobs going, has he?
I do IT.
Information exchange systems.
- I don't think so. - Yeah, well, if you
hear of anything, let us know, eh?
I'd love to be able to tell him
where to stick his job.
Mr Wasem is in London for three
days and whilst he's here,
he's very keen to make
some investments.
And?
He would be very interested to hear
if you have any advice to give him.
After discussing your fee, of course.
- We do some business, yes?
- Ah.
Ah?
Mmm, awkward.
I have a waiting list.
- You have a waiting list?
- Yes.
Do you know who I am?
Yes, yes, but even so.
We understand that you must
have a very long list of people
eager to do business
with you, Mr Cole,
but we're equally sure
that you could find a way to
make an exception for Mr Wasem.
He asked me to wait in line!
- I could go back in there and
speak to him. - No, screw him.
You.
Screw you.
I will crush you.
Get the car.
I don't think he's very happy.
I do not know what you said
to him but he was not pleased.
What have I missed?
- Does anyone know she
was in London? - No.
I mean, we didn't know she was in
the game but did she know we were?
She can't have known.
Sorry, I've missed something here,
- like a meeting or something.
- We need to talk to her.
- Do we know where to find her?
- No. But she knows where to find us.
Eh! You'll never guess what.
Stacie's here.
- How does he, how does he do that?
- Mickey! Your face was a picture.
Never thought I'd see
you speechless.
- Well, it was a bit of a shock.
- I'm sorry.
- Ash.
- Hello darlin'. Long time.
- Albie. - You look magnificent
and you feel even better.
- Stacie, this is Emma
and Sean Kennedy. - Hi. - Hello.
- You all right?
- Ash has told me all about you.
He called occasionally.
Yeah, well, I'm not
good with small talk.
- Yes, so I noticed.
- Where's Danny?
Oh, he fell in love with a
cocktail waitress in Santa Monica.
They were planning a summer wedding,
choosing names for their children.
Then her husband found out.
Last I heard, they were
heading for Vegas.
- Apparently, Danny had a plan.
- Yeah, I bet he did.
How long you been back? Why
didn't you tell us you were coming
and how long you staying?
A girl can't answer that many
questions without a drink.
I'll kill him.
I'll wipe every trace
of him off the Earth.
Now, you.
You, go and shoot him.
It's the UK, sir,
we can't carry guns.
- Where's my enforcer?
- I have found someone.
A Ukrainian, Alex Klukas, he was
recommended to me by one of our men.
He has the details.
But there may also be another way.
- So what you playing?
- Nothing fancy.
Just thought I'd siphon
off the top of whatever
he invested, get 10 or 20
grand and disappear.
- That's when you ran into us.
- Exactly.
Have you any idea how
angry you made him?
Yeah, I think so.
I don't know how far
along you are, Mickey,
but I'd think seriously about
walking away from this one.
Why?
There's just something about him.
He's not a very nice man.
Everyone's frightened of him.
- I've never met a nice mark yet.
- No, it's more than that.
We know he uses a hit man, he knocked
some bloke off two days ago.
Exactly.
We know what he's capable of.
It's a calculated risk.
- So are you going back?
- I don't know.
It ain't going to hurt,
having you on the inside, Stace.
That's true.
As far as I can see all you've
done so far is wind him up
- and make him furious.
- Look, he's a bully.
So we take away his control,
you know, take away his power,
- make him feel small. - And, then,
when he's ready to burst...
- We find a way to give him
that control back. - How?
Just like that.
Ah-ho-ho-ho.
Hello?
We don't have to do this, you know,
we could bring him in another way.
- Yes, Mum.
- I mean it. - I'll be OK.
Tell him what he wants to know
quickly, don't string it out.
This is our convincer, if he
doesn't have to work for it,
he won't believe it.
I know but you can make sure...
Will you just stop? I've been to
the toilet, I've washed me hands
- and I've got a clean hankie,
all right? - All right.
Don't wait up.
Hello, how are you?
Good, thanks.
- Barir said something about a job?
- Yeah, of course.
Think of this as a job interview.
Right.
OK.
Now Barir tells me that you know
how Mr Cole selects his investments.
Er, yeah, well, kind of. But I'm
not sure I should talk about that.
Oh?
Well, it's not part of
my job, not really,
I do IT, you see.
I've, um, brought my CV.
There you go.
Let me ask you the question
in a different way.
You know how he selects
his investments.
I know what he does,
I heard him talking to the
yank but I don't know how.
Look, I swear, I don't know.
I know what his edge is, I know
why he never loses any money,
but how the whole thing works,
the mechanics, only he knows that.
You will tell me everything
you know about William Cole
and how he selects his investments.
Everything.
Every detail.
You leave nothing out.
Do you understand?
Oh, Jesus!
I think he's convinced.
I'm not going to meet you.
Sorry, sir, you don't
have an appointment!
I don't need one.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Sit down and shut up.
- I'm so sorry! He won't listen to me.
- Call security.
Call whoever you want,
you piece of shit.
Because the second after you throw
me out, I'm going to tell the police
about how you're intercepting data
from the London Stock Exchange.
Which would put you out of business
and into prison.
Sir?
Erm, yeah, it's, er, it's OK,
Alice, take the rest of the day off.
Close the door behind you.
Now he wants a meeting.
Now he wants to talk.
Well, maybe I don't want
to do business.
Maybe I got a waiting list.
Look, I didn't mean to offend you.
No? Well, I'm about to
offend you. Talk to him.
Mr Wasem is a very reasonable
man and he has no wish
for things to be anything
other than cordial.
It's very lucky for you I'm a
reasonable man, you horse's ass.
But he insists that you show him
how the data is intercepted
and how you use this data to
choose which investments you make.
Before I do anything at all,
I want to know how you
came by this information.
That is none of your business.
You just show me how it works.
I can't do that because there
are other people involved.
Let me explain something
to you, Mr Golden Balls.
It would give me great pleasure
to just tell the police
everything I know and I can go home.
Or I can forget about the police
and just shoot you and
everyone you love in the head.
The only thing that's
stopping me from doing that
is the thought that I can
make some money here.
So you, you got
a very simple choice.
You can either show me
how the interception works
or you can go to prison
or you be dead.
All right, I'll need some time.
Of course.
You have a minute.
- Have you gone insane?
- I had no choice, they know.
How? That doesn't matter.
All that's important is that
you show me what I came to see.
I'm sorry, there's no other way.
This is it?
This cable carries a live feed into the
stock exchange building next door.
There was a fault in the system
and George was sent over
from the company in Houston
who supplied the software.
His team had to dig up the cable
so that they could fit a new
digital transcoder unit.
When we did, I realised with an
exposed cable and the right software,
we could manipulate the data
that passes through it.
This is a hard drive.
It records all of the data coming in
and holds it up for
nine tenths of a second
before playing it on down the line.
- To the stock exchange?
- Exactly.
It holds it up long enough
for us to analyse it
and identify any major shifts,
trends or movements,
before playing it on to the
stock exchange boards.
It's also hooked up to
our trading account,
so it can make purchases
based on those calculations.
Wait. You're saying you
can analyse the data
and actually purchase stocks
before the stock exchange
gets the same information?
- That's exactly what I'm saying.
- But that's, that's genius.
- Can this be done? - Well, if,
if what they're saying is true.
- It's absolutely true.
- And there's no risk. Ever.
We only ever buy stock
we know is going to rise.
And presumably you can off-load before
anyone else if it starts to go down?
We don't hold on to it that long, we
just make our profits and get out.
OK, I'm in.
- You're in?
- In for what?
You will make investments for me.
Look, I'm sorry,
it's not that simple.
I heard you in the restaurant.
You said you have a
capacity for ten million.
Well, yes, I mean, that's the top
end of our buying power but...
But what?
Well, even if we had
that kind of money,
which, by the way, we don't,
we'd never go over a million,
we don't want to draw
attention to ourselves.
That's because you're a horse's ass.
You will invest the full ten million.
- Ten million?
- Hedge fund managers invest hundreds
of millions in a day, why
would anyone notice ten?
Because we're private brokers
trading for private investors.
Then you buy the stock in my name,
no-one will question that level
of investment if it's from me.
You take my ten million,
you double it.
Look, well I'd need all
the money in the account.
- And the returns?
- They'd go to the same account.
Miss Hammond will put
everything in place.
Look, I don't know, we'd have to
programme in a new trading account,
- and re-set the buying criteria.
- Then do it.
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
what do we get out of this, huh?
Yeah, I mean we still
get our commission, right?
Er, 22%. Cash.
Five per cent.
What?
Perhaps the experience will
teach you some manners.
You call me when it's ready.
OK, once the money is
in the trading account,
- I want two men watching
Cole around the clock. - Yes, sir.
I want you to learn how
they programme the machine.
Me? Why?
Because once you can use it,
I'll have no further use for Cole
and the old man.
Wait.
I don't mind bending the
rules to make money,
the City's corrupt anyway.
But I won't be a party to murder.
Would you rather
I asked someone else?
Cos then, I wouldn't need you either.
No.
Then just do it.
Call my enforcer,
get him on a plane.
OK, time to bail out.
You what?
He wants me to learn how
to programme the machine.
So that he can have you killed.
Well, that's kind of
what we expected.
He told Barir to call the
enforcer and whatever you do,
- he's not going to let you
out of his sight. - I know.
From tomorrow morning he'll have
two of his guards on you full time.
Even if you pull this off,
you'll never get away clean.
This is wicked.
Without a doubt, this is one of the
coolest things I've ever tried on.
I actually look like I could
swim faster than a shark!
- All right, Stace?
- Hi.
Just for the record,
this isn't an accurate
representation of my underwear.
Pleased to hear it.
He's got issues, from
when he was a baby.
I do not have issues.
Mickey, I don't like it.
- It feels wrong.
- What about the money?
He's having it transferred first thing
tomorrow before the markets open.
He's also bringing 500,000
in cash which is your commission
- if you double him up.
- OK.
I tell you someone's planning to have
you killed and all you say is OK?
You're taking ten million
from this man, Mickey,
he's not going to just put it down
to experience and walk away.
I know Wasem won't just walk away.
Which is why it's a good reason
for us all to lay low for a bit.
So, I was thinking,
when this job is done,
we should take a break.
Go our separate ways for a while.
- How long's a while?
- Who knows?
I thought it best
not to make plans.
I was going to talk to you about
this when the job was done but...
seems now is as good a time as any.
So, that's why we're taking this
job? It's walking away money?
If you want to call it that.
That's it, then? One last job
and we're finished, huh?
I've always thought it was a good
idea to quit while you're ahead.
I think ten million
qualifies as being ahead.
This is the question.
If you didn't take this break,
would you still do the job?
If I'm honest.
No, I wouldn't.
And I wouldn't blame any one of you
that wanted to walk away right now.
But, come on!
The money comes in tomorrow.
Our play is that the
City of London police
has had us under surveillance.
Ash has lined up a dozen
grifters and all the vehicles.
We get ourselves arrested
but we let Wasem get away.
He'll go straight to the airport,
desperate to leave the country,
thinking the money's been impounded,
there's nothing to keep him here,
where as we, on the other hand,
will cash in and be long gone
by the time the dust settles.
It will work.
Trust me.
Hello.
We have a job.
Stay in your room,
I will send over a package.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
So, it must be nice
to see Stacie again.
- Yeah, yeah, it is.
- Yeah, Ash told me that you two, um,
- you were quite close for a while.
- Yeah, we were.
- Yeah, you go back a long way.
- Yeah, that's right.
So, this, er, whole break thing.
You know the whole, um,
going our own way thing.
Only it's a bit sudden
and it's a bit like,
Stacie turning up the way she has
and I just, I...I was wondering
if the two things were
related in any way.
It's just curiosity, really,
It's a good job I'm not a cat.
- No, the thing, the thing is...
- No, it's not. - It's not what?
- Related.
- OK.
It's just... I want to live
a normal life for a while.
Get to know people
for who they are.
Not constantly look at them and see
if they'd make a great mark or not.
So, it's more like a holiday, really?
Yeah, I guess so. Yeah, so we could
still, you know, like, meet up
and spend time together
and...and chill.
I'd like that.
Me too. Then the work thing wouldn't
be there any more, would it?
No, it wouldn't.
And if everything goes right
tomorrow, then you know,
we'll be stinking rich.
Yes, we will.
So, at some point,
we could be talking
you and me, and a desert island and,
like, a couple of million
in the bank or something.
That doesn't sound
too shabby, does it?
No, it doesn't.
OK, good.
Great, well, then I'll just
leave you to your thinking.
I just thought I'd ask.
I'm really glad you did.
OK, so you go when Albert calls
Nick to give him the thumbs up.
Hard and fast, OK?
Lots of noise.
We need them scared enough
to run straight to the airport.
Everyone in cuffs and
dragged out to the vans.
So, we're going to be outside
the London Stock Exchange,
in broad daylight, so it won't be
long before the real old bill notice.
So, don't hang about, get them
in the vans and on your way.
The mark is last up.
He'll be with his
bodyguard and Stacie.
Stacie will offer to
bribe Nick at that point
- and that's when you let them go.
Is that all clear? - Yeah.
Right, get yourselves in position.
Good luck.
All right?
Nice one.
Take care, Albert.
So, Stacie called.
The money's in the trading account
but when we get there, Wasem
needs to put his pin number in,
- before we can move it.
- OK.
We'll clear out of the penthouse and
meet at the hotel when it's done.
We'll split the money by
direct transfer, and then...
all go our separate ways.
Everyone know what they're doing?
Right.
What about me?
Eh?
Everyone's talking about
the biggest job ever,
you know, history in
the making and all that
and everyone's got
something to do except me.
Even the bloody dogs
have got a part.
Yeah, yeah, well, er, there's a reason
we haven't given you anything yet, Ed.
- Yeah? - Because we've
saved the best till last.
Ah, see, I thought it'd be
something like that.
So, what? Do I get like
a uniform, an' all that?
No, you won't need one,
you see, the most important
part of your job...
is to have the drinks ready and on
the table for when we get back.
Good luck, Ed.
Sir, we need your pin.
Thank you.
OK.
Three minutes.
- That it?
- Yeah. Like we were never here.
What's happening with my money?
It's all right.
It's buying.
Are we ready to do the transfer?
So, now, we transferring
his ten million
from the trading account,
into our account.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- We have a reservation,
under the name of Jones. - OK.
This is the most fun I've ever had.
You know what?
I think we come back tomorrow,
we do it all over again.
Stay where you are!
Get on the floor! Down now!
Armed Police! Nobody move! You are
under arrest on suspicion of fraud.
Come on.
- This has nothing to do with us.
- All right, darlin', tell it to the judge.
No, no, no, I mean it.
They did it,
they have this machine,
they wanted us to invest.
That's what happened,
she's telling the truth!
- We didn't even give them the money.
- Hold up.
Bring 'em back.
Take the rest of them away.
It was...it was just
a demonstration,
we only met them yesterday.
They were trying to convince
us to invest but we didn't.
Open the bag, you can
see for yourself.
- So, this is your money?
- Yes.
B-But it doesn't have to be.
It could be yours.
So, if it just disappeared.
There is half a million pounds
in cash in that bag, so...
If you let us go we won't
even look back, I swear.
I've got a jet fuelled
and ready to leave,
I can be out of the
country in an hour.
You've got the machine,
the people who built it.
Why do you need us?
Our friend's on his
way to the airport.
Stacie's going to lose him and
meet you back at the hotel.
You son of a bitch, you did it.
Hold tight.
You did well.
Just get on the plane before
they change their mind.
We're back.
Ah. Hey.
Ha-ha-ha.
Current balance, ten million pounds.
Yes! And he gave us half a
mill commission in cash
- for taking it off him.
- Yeah-hey.
Thank you, my dear.
- To us. To us!
- Yeah, yeah! Woo hoo!
They've just gone into the hotel.
No. No police.
- Ah, taste of victory.
- Scary. Scary.
Guys, get out.
Go. Go, go, move.
Come on, Albert.
Mickey Bricks,
if you've ever been brilliant,
please be brilliant now.
Gentlemen. I know what
you're thinking but, er...
That's my money. That's my money.
Come on, come on.
I guess most of you
must have thought that,
one day, it would end like this.
Which, without an extraordinary
amount of planning,
it very well might have done.
Come on, then. Off your arses.
Wakey wakey.
Honestly, eh?
What would you lot
do without me coming
to bale you out of
trouble all the time?
I mean it's all right Mickey
doing all that,
"Look at me, I'm a clever bastard"
stuff, but when it comes down to it.
You just can't do it
without me, can you?
- Are you sure you couldn't find
anyone else? - I'm sorry.
- Hello. Who's this? Very pretty.
- Hello, sweetheart.
I'm Danny. Danny Blue.
Probably heard a lot about me.
Call my enforcer,
get him on a plane.
- Alex Klukas?
- I'm here.
Hello, Mickey.
Try this on.
Just for the record, this isn't
an accurate representation
of my underwear.
I want you to learn how
they programme the machine.
How does the machine work?
Well, basically, it's a box
with a bunch of lights in it.
I thought it might be.
Gentlemen.
I know what you're thinking.
Come on then, off your arses.
- Did you, er, did you throw it all
over? - Nah, fifty grand or so.
Er, now might be a good
time to slip away.
I think that's a fabulous idea.
How about, me and you, we
just slip away together?
Danny, behave.
Easy pal, that's my sister.
Whoa, everybody's a bit
touchy, ain't they?
I didn't have to use blanks,
you know, I did think about it.
- How you doing, Albie?
- Pretty good, Danny, pretty good.
- I'm sorry I had to shoot you.
- Don't worry about it.
I blame Mickey.
He's very theatrical.
- Someone shut him up.
- It was OTT, that's all I'm saying.
- We were still being watched.
- Exactly.
Always playing to the audience.
Listen, listen, mate, when you've
taken someone for ten million,
the only way you can
be sure they're not
coming after you is if
they think you're dead.
Ten million? Is this a good time
to talk about my cut?
I think we'd better be going.
Time we should make a move, come on.
Wahey. Yeah.
- I've just had an amazing and
original idea. - God, help us.
Bear with me, right, one, two,
three, there's seven of us, right?
We should hook up. We'll start
a new gang, maybe I'll lead it,
we'll call it....
The Magnificent Seven.
- What d'you think, Albert?
- I think that's a hell of an idea.
- What about The Great Eight?
- To The Great Eight.
So, that's it.
I'm out of here.
I hope you've picked up
a few things along the way.
If something seems too good to
be true, it almost certainly is.
Always look a gift horse in the mouth.
Unless you don't much care
whether it has teeth or not.
And, remember, you can't
cheat an honest man.
So, if you bend the rules
to make some easy money,
you deserve what you get.
Oh, and, er, don't believe
everything people tell you.
Whoever they are.
Think things through for yourself.
Is it for real?
Is someone telling you
that story for a reason?
Or...are they
having you right at it?
But most important of all...
Whether it's business...
- Buying.
- Selling.
- Whether it's someone you know.
- Or someone you don't.
Even if it's love.
Never be a mark.
Sync and corrections by bellows
www.addic7ed.com