Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
- Previously on Why Women Kill...
- (sniffing)
- (truck horn blares)
- Fuck!
I-I know that it looks bad.
You're going to rehab
first thing in the morning.
You are cut off.
I-I-I don't think
it's the best time
for me right now.
You don't really
have a choice here.
I just sold a script
for $1.2 million.
- You know, I think I got a lot of fucking choices.
- Come on, Jade.
I think maybe
the best way to help him
- is to stay here.
- Fuck you both.
(door opens)
KARL:
Uh, I have an appointment.
SIMONE:
And would this appointment
involve your new boyfriend
Hector?
He may tag along, yes.
I, uh, leave for Paris
two days after graduation.
Care to join me?
- You should go.
- You'll be okay?
I'll be delightful.
(laughs)
You've got get over
this obsession
with another woman's husband.
I'm pregnant.
How do you think he'll react?
- He will be thrilled.
- Come clean.
Tell him you know about
the affair and the baby.
What if...
he doesn't choose me?
Aren't you done
with all the lies?
- We definitely need to have a talk.
- You're starting to scare me.
I'm scared, too.
Once I tell you,
everything is going
to be different.
Are you sick?
I'm sick.
Baby, what's wrong?
I have cancer.
(sobbing):
Oh, my... oh, my God.
("L-O-V-E" by Michael Feinstein
playing)
♪ "L" is for the way you look ♪
♪ At me ♪
♪ "O" is for the only one ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ "V" is very, very ♪
♪ Extraordinary ♪
♪ "E" is even more ♪
♪ Than anyone
that you adore can ♪
♪ Love is all ♪
♪ That I can give to you ♪
♪ Love is more ♪
♪ Than just a game for two ♪
♪ Two in love can make it ♪
♪ Take my heart
and please don't break it ♪
♪ Love was made ♪
♪ For me and you... ♪
♪ ♪
I'm going to die.
I'm not sure when.
I just know
one day I won't be here.
I'm afraid to meet God.
I'll have to account
for my sins.
I have sinned a lot.
I had an affair
with a married man.
I slept with another guy's wife.
I had sex with a married couple
and pretty much everyone else
I ever met.
Now I'm pregnant and unmarried.
My mom has no idea
I've fallen in love.
Taylor doesn't know
I gave Eli drugs.
I'm not going to tell Rob.
I'm gonna propose to Simone.
I'll probably deny everything.
When I do meet God,
I'll just beg his forgiveness.
I'll thank him for sending me
the perfect woman.
I'll say I did what I had to
to survive.
(laughs)
Sheila.
SHEILA:
Oh, my God.
I've been on pins and needles.
Did you talk to Rob last night?
I did.
So? I'm dying here.
How did he react
when you told him
you knew that he was
cheating on you?
Well,
the conversation went
in a surprising direction.
(speaking indistinctly)
You said what?
What? How could
you say that?
How could you say
that, Beth Ann?
What are you thinking?
I can't even believe
you just said that!
Get back here
so I can give it to you!
It's your mother's fault.
Clearly, she forgot to teach
you some of the basics.
Things like, when you grow up,
don't pretend to have cancer.
Women lie to
their husbands every day.
Some lie about
how much they spend.
My lie's that I'm dying.
Just because
you act classy
doesn't mean you're
not fucking crazy.
There is a method
to my madness.
Rob will never leave me
while I'm sick.
But what if April decides
to tell him that
she's having his kid?
That is where her good friend
Sheila comes in.
I'm going to convince her
to leave town.
Start a new life,
sever the tie for good.
And then, once she's out
of the picture
and I have Rob
all to myself,
my cancer will be
miraculously cured.
I used to find
that little grin charming.
Now it just scares
the shit out of me.
NURSE:
Ladies.
The doctor will see you now.
SHEILA:
Enzo.
Aunt Sheila.
Look at you in the white coat.
This is my neighbor,
Beth Ann Stanton.
Beth Ann, my nephew, Enzo.
The doctor.
Nice to meet you,
Mrs. Stanton.
Likewise.
So, Sheila says
you studied oncology.
For a little while,
- and then I switched to hematology.
- Oh, still,
I bet you remember lots
of useful tidbits.
I suppose so.
How can I help you?
Well, I was wondering
if there was a cancer
you could recommend.
- Recommend?
- Something rare.
That no one's ever heard of.
It should be serious.
Oh, but occasionally curable.
I'm sorry...
- And symptoms. She's gonna need symptoms.
- (gasps)
Oh, some symptoms
would be lovely.
Just wait a...
What exactly
are we talking about here?
SHEILA:
Enzo.
I say this to you as your aunt
and a Sicilian:
The less you know, the better.
Okay.
Um, rare cancers.
What about...
Epithelioid
hemangioendothelioma.
Say that again.
I'd rather not.
That's the cancer you have?
It affects soft tissue.
I'd give you the details,
but they're disgusting
and we're having fondue.
(sighs)
God, I wish you'd let me go
to the doctor's with you.
You always get
so emotional.
No. I prefer to go
with Sheila.
Now, I'm going to set the table.
Wait. Wait.
At least tell me your prognosis.
I will, but I don't want
to ruin our meal.
Beth Ann!
Please, just tell me!
Fine.
But I need you to be strong.
Can you do that for me, Robert?
Can you be my brave boy?
Yeah.
Well,
it seems I only have
six months to live.
Six months!
But that doesn't mean
I can't recover.
- Miracles happen every day.
- (crying)
But the doctor feels
we should prepare for the worst.
It sounds like
he's giving up already.
We should get a second opinion.
No. I mean, what is
another doctor going to say?
I don't have cancer?
No, this is the situation,
and we all must accept it.
Okay?
Okay.
Now, obviously, if I'm going
to fight this thing,
I need you by my side.
Constantly.
I'm not going anywhere.
You're my wife.
I meant it when I said,
"Till death do us part."
Oh, my darling.
I'm going to hold you to that.
This is hard.
I've never packed
for a three-month trip before.
Oh, packing for three months
is easy.
I do it every time
I go away for the weekend.
These look sturdy.
Should I try them on?
Knock yourself out.
Hey, I know we agreed that you'd
fly to Paris a week after me,
but wouldn't three days
be enough?
Or even two?
You can't wait one week?
We need as much time
for sex as possible.
Remember, you said you'd
make love to me in
every city in Europe.
What am I supposed
to do on my own
for a whole week?
Beat it.
That's cold.
Oh, not you.
What do you think?
Do you like them?
Oh, what are all
the pockets for?
Carrying stuff.
They'll be great
for hiking over the Alps.
- Hiking over the Alps?
- Yeah.
Good Lord, are we taking a
vacation or fleeing the Nazis?
I'm starting to think that we're
imagining very different trips.
Well, I want our vacation
to be elegant, romantic.
(gasps) Nights at
la Comédie-Française,
dinner at Maxim's.
Yeah, well, I can't
afford those things.
Oh, well,
if that's the problem...
No, I know you can
afford those things,
but I-I don't want to
feel like your gigolo.
- I have an idea.
- What?
Return my brooch
and get your money back.
What you spent on it can buy
a whole lot of escargot.
I bought you this to show you
what you mean to me.
Well, find another way
to show me.
Like what?
You're an artist.
Use your imagination.
Okay.
I'll see what I can
come up with.
Taylor.
What are you doing here?
Can we talk for a sec?
My mom got sick when I was ten.
From that point on, it was
just us, so I had to step up.
But it was good, because
I learned to take charge.
I found out I could
figure out the solution
to any problem
that came my way.
Until last night.
I sat in that hotel room
until dawn
trying to figure out
how to fix this thing with Eli.
And I just can't.
I'm so sorry.
You know, when Eli
O.D.'d last time,
I knew exactly what to do.
I got him into rehab,
I paid off his debts.
But I think that a part of him
always resented me
for managing the situation
in a way that he couldn't.
And now he's just
so angry at me.
And I don't think
he'll let me help him.
And I'm so scared of what
will happen if I can't.
Eli is not going to die.
He will
if he doesn't stop using.
But the good news is
he still listens to you.
So I am begging you. Please.
You are my last hope.
Of course, yes. Totally.
I'm totally with you.
I promise.
Thank God. You have no idea
how much that means to me.
(sighs) Okay.
We have to move fast, before the
money comes in for Eli's script.
You're worried he's gonna
spend it all on drugs?
Not just drugs.
When Eli's using,
he gets stupid generous.
- Stupid generous?
- Oh, yeah.
The last time,
he bought gifts for everyone.
Rolex watches, designer shoes.
When he's high, he just wants
everyone to be as happy
as he is.
So, I've been thinking of ways
that we can handle this
covertly.
And I have one idea, but it...
it's kind of crazy.
I like crazy.
The next time
Eli's in the shower,
I need you to go into his phone
and find all of his passwords.
What?
The code to his phone
is 0-4-2-9.
Just here, look,
I wrote it down for you.
If we can get access
to his his business accounts
and his credit cards,
we can cut off
his cash flow.
Oh.
And I'm gonna call his dad.
How will that help?
Eli is terrified of his dad.
Jake will force him to admit
who got him using again.
(laughs softly)
Why does that matter?
He was clean
for two years,
and then suddenly he's not?
No, I need to know
what happened.
Of course.
And I want to help,
but is this really
- the best plan?
- What do you mean?
Look, you remember how you felt
when you thought
that Eli and I were
ganging up on you.
How is he gonna feel
if it... if it seems
like we're ganging up on him?
So what do you propose we do?
Give me a few days
and I'll reason with him.
You really think
you can talk him into this?
Trust me.
I'll get through to him,
he'll come home,
and we'll all be a family again.
Look who's here!
- Karl, it's the Sitwells!
- You're back from Scotland, I see.
And we're meeting Rex
and Julie for dinner.
They should be
here any second.
Oh, I love her.
She thinks I'm pretty.
We all think you're pretty.
But she says it out loud.
(Hank and Denise chuckling)
Tell you what...
when they get here,
why don't you bring them over
to our table?
We'll dine together.
Wonderful. Then you can
tell us about your plans
for Amy's
lavish wedding.
We're so excited.
We can't wait.
- Mm.
- I can't wait, either.
(laughs)
For it to be over.
Yes, I was thinking
the same thing.
Oof, are we terrible people?
No. Weddings
are exhausting.
Besides, we need to conserve
our energy for our male lovers.
At least yours isn't younger
than the groom.
Yeah, I think the, uh,
stepfather of the bride
should have at least
an age-appropriate boyfriend.
- (chuckles)
- Call me old fashioned, but I just do.
Oh, Karl.
What's that on your face?
What?
Oh, my God, are you
wearing makeup?
Less than you.
You really are
spreading your wings.
I think I'm leaving
the country in the nick of time.
- I'm off to the ladies' room
- I'll order you a gimlet.
♪ ♪
Simone?
Hi.
(toilet flushes,
stall door opens)
Uh, you are Dr. Bennett's
wife, right?
Maureen. I also work
in his practice as a nurse.
Well, isn't that nice?
I don't know
quite how to say this.
But... do you know
your husband's a homosexual?
Yes, I know.
And you said it just fine.
I realize it's none
of my business.
I'm just trying to
be a good person.
And like all good people, you
just couldn't wait to tell me.
I'm going now.
Feel free to adjust your halo.
Has Karl told you
he's sick?
What?
I can see he hasn't.
Karl isn't sick.
He saw my husband
three days ago.
He has that new disease
that all the gay men
are spreading.
That's a lie.
He's the third man
my husband's seen who's had it.
The first two
are dead.
I'm so sorry.
I just thought you should know.
(laughter)
KARL:
I know, I know, I know,
I know, I know
it sounds unbelievable
and faintly ridiculous,
but bear with me on this...
Oh, hello, darling.
It's perfect timing.
I was just telling everyone
the story of our trip to Venice,
when you accidentally knocked
that gondolier into the water.
HANK: Now,
did that really happen?
Or is Karl just
embellishing?
No, that-that's not the kind
of thing Karl would lie about.
So, there he was,
dripping wet,
hacking up great lungfuls
of the Grand Canal,
and I realized
it's very difficult
to maintain
one's dignity...
(voice fading)
♪ ♪
(door opens)
Hey.
- Hey. Where have you been all morning?
- Ah... out.
Doing stuff.
Doing great stuff, in fact.
Come with me outside.
I've got something to show you.
- Come on.
- You never came to bed last night.
Did you get
any sleep at all?
No. No, it turns out
one of the side effects
of near-constant cocaine use
is a wee bit of insomnia.
Come on.
- Oh! Wow!
- Right?
You like it?
- It... uh... you bought this?
- I did.
Well, uh, technically
American Express bought it.
But that bill's gonna get paid
the second my first script
payment comes through.
You like it?
Look, I know you've been
working really hard,
and I get that you'd want
to treat yourself...
Me? No. Whoa.
(chuckles)
No, I didn't...
This isn't for me.
Y-You bought me a car?
I did.
- Shut. Up.
- I won't.
This is me saying thank you.
- For what?
- My God, for everything.
For all the help
you gave me with the script.
For standing by me when Taylor
lost her mind...
Oh, God... Taylor's
not gonna like this.
Well, you know what?
Taylor doesn't get a vote, okay?
It looks expensive.
Are you sure?
Well, I made you
a promise, right?
I said when this money
came through,
I would take care of you.
People have made me
a lot of promises in my life.
Nobody's ever kept one before.
Well, this is me keeping mine.
And this is
just the beginning.
So... do you like it?
It's perfect.
Just keep
going straight.
So I've been doing
some research,
finding jobs a
pregnant woman can do.
I already have a job.
You shouldn't be on your feet
all day when you're expecting,
but don't worry.
There are plenty of ways
a girl in your condition
can make a living.
Are there?
Sure. You could be
a pin setter in
a bowling alley.
All you'd have to do
is punch buttons.
- I found an opening at an alley in Anaheim.
- Now take a left.
BETH ANN: Or... there's a place
hiring switchboard operators.
For that, you'd have
to move to Barstow.
It sounds like you're
trying to get rid of me.
Don't be silly.
I just thought it might
be easier for you
to make a fresh start
in a new city.
- Well, I'm not moving.
- Okay.
Just know I'm here for you.
For anything you need.
Thank you.
Oh... uh, pull over,
this is it.
This must be
a mistake.
A doctor wouldn't have
his office in here.
No, this is it.
Are you sure you have
the address right?
Sheila, I lied. I'm not
here to see a doctor.
(shudders)
I don't understand.
I'm sorry. I just
can't have this baby.
What are you
talking about?
Please do not make me
say this out loud.
What you're going
to do, it's illegal.
(exhales)
I know.
God, how did you even
hear about this place?
A girl at the
diner referred me.
You...
Excuse me.
You can't do this,
it's not right.
Sheila, please do not make this
harder than it already is.
I'm Sally Jones.
We spoke on the phone.
Who's she?
My friend.
She'll drive me home afterwards.
- You got the money?
- I do.
Come on in.
Sheila. Please.
I really need a friend
right now, more than ever.
- Here you go, son.
- Thank you, sir.
I'll have your car here
in just a second.
- Terrific night.
- Lovely seeing you all.
Let's do it again
very soon.
Good night, Simone.
See you at the wedding.
All right, we're alone.
You can tell me now.
Tell you what?
How I've upset you.
And don't say you're fine.
You've barely said two words
to me the entire evening.
Wait till
we're in the car.
Can I at least have
a headline?
I ran into your doctor's wife
in the ladies' room.
Don't think I've ever met her.
She also works as a nurse.
(quietly):
In his office.
What did she say?
You're sick.
Well, two things:
first of all...
I'm not sick.
Secondly, what a gossipy bitch.
- Are you saying she lied?
- I'm not... symptomatic.
- I feel fine.
- So what's the makeup hiding?
A spot.
- Don't you mean a lesion?
- Oh, come on,
it's miniscule.
Do you have any idea
how scared I am?
- You don't have it.
- What?
Look, the fact is, it can only
be transmitted through blood
or bodily fluids,
and we rarely had sex,
and never without a condom.
Is that what you think?
- That I'm scared for myself?
- Darling, darling, darling,
I, I, I...
I should have told you,
my love, I just...
I did... I just didn't want
to spoil your trip.
Oh, God, the trip.
Look, I'm so sorry.
I-I-I-I promise
I... I-I will call once
a week while you're away,
with, with full
medical updates.
You think I'm still going?
That I'd leave you
at a time like this?
And what would staying achieve?
Other than letting me know
that you think I won't make it
past Labor Day?
You need care, Karl.
Specialists. And at least
one doctor whose wife
is not the goddamn town crier!
I know how much
Tommy means to you.
I'm staying with you,
and that is the end
of this discussion.
(quietly):
Thank you.
- Do you want some whiskey?
- Whiskey?
It's good to get a little
drunk before you start.
Helps with the pain.
- No, thank you.
- Suit yourself.
Just give me a couple
of minutes.
I got to get some plastic
over the table.
She's doing this
in the kitchen?
Apparently.
But it's an
invasive procedure.
It requires a clean environment.
Sterilized instruments.
Well, this is all
I can afford.
I'm out of options, Sheila.
Please understand.
(sighs)
There's something
you don't know.
I need to tell you.
What's that?
I had a child once,
but she died.
I left the gate
to the backyard open.
She wandered out
into the street
and she was hit
by a car.
It's been years, but I think
about her every day.
Sometimes,
late at night,
I wonder what kind
of young woman
she'd have
turned into.
How could you tell me
something like that right now?
Are you... are you trying
to make me feel guilty?
- No, you don't understand.
- No, I think you don't understand, Sheila.
- I have to do this.
- Honey, I'm trying to say...
I think my daughter would have
grown up to be a lot like you.
That is one of the reasons
I love you.
But right now
I'm afraid for you
because women die
in places like this.
I can't
let that happen.
Sheila, I'm single
and I'm broke.
I can't raise a baby.
We'll figure it out.
We just need time to think.
- Let me help you.
- How?
Well, I'll...
I'll get some... I'll get
my hands on some money.
We can go somewhere else,
somewhere safe, but please,
let's get out of here.
Okay. Okay.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Yeah, this is she.
No, I haven't lost my Amex. Why?
Suspicious activity?
Um, how much was spent?
TAYLOR:
Nice car.
Taylor.
- Were you in the house?
- I came to talk to Eli
so he could explain to me
why my credit card is maxed out,
and then I saw you pull up
in this brand-new car.
Well, I-I don't know
when he'll be home.
He has a meeting
at Paramount and...
He bought it for you, didn't he?
I told him
it was too much.
- When?
- The moment he gave it to me.
No. I'm asking
when did he give it to you?
Before I saw you in the park
this morning or after?
After.
So why didn't you insist
he take it back?
I was so surprised,
I didn't know what to say.
Surprised? Jade, I had just
told you that when Eli is high,
- he's stupid with money.
- Well, I don't think it's stupid.
I spend every day
cooking and cleaning,
running errands
and looking after you both.
I think it's nice
that someone actually
wanted to say
thank you.
You want a thank you?
Okay, fine, Jade.
Thank you.
Now give me
the keys.
- Why?
- 'Cause I'm gonna return the car, obviously.
No.
- What do you mean no?
- You can't return the car.
It's not yours.
Eli bought it for me.
Yeah, but he's coked
out of his mind.
To accept a gift from a man
in that condition
is not a good look.
My God. Why are you
acting like this?
I haven't done
anything wrong.
You are taking advantage
of this situation.
You're using Eli.
Just give me the keys.
Stop it.
If anyone is a user,
Taylor, it's you. You have been
using me for months.
I saved you.
I brought you into my home.
You did that for yourself,
not for me.
Your marriage was falling apart
and you needed a distraction.
Eli wasn't writing
or making money,
and you were
so angry
you could barely
even look at him.
By the way, I'm the one
who got him writing again.
I did that for you.
You're welcome.
I keep wondering why
Eli started using again.
Are you the reason?
(sighs) Oh, my God.
We shouldn't be doing this.
Fighting and throwing blame
at each other.
We're supposed
to be a family.
Stop it. Stop it, Jade!
Eli and I
are a family.
You are a houseguest.
That's all.
You know what, Jade?
Go upstairs,
get your stuff.
I want you out of my house now!
That's not gonna happen.
You can leave again
if you want,
but I'm not going anywhere,
and I'm keeping the car.
I'm not gonna let you
take it away from me.
Tommy, come in.
Hi. I have great news.
I returned your brooch
and I got your replacement gift.
Well, it's not
a traditional gift
so much as a tribute to you.
I sure hope you like it
because, uh,
I can't really return it.
(chuckles)
Hey. You look sad. What's wrong?
We need to talk.
Hey. Hey, great news.
Paramount wants to talk to me
about adapting a novel.
I got a meeting on Friday.
I'm telling you,
this comeback shit
is really starting to get real.
I'm really,
really happy for you.
What's wrong?
Taylor stopped by.
(sighs) I'm guessing that
didn't go so well, huh?
(crying):
Oh, Eli.
I hate this.
I hate that she's putting me
in this position.
What position?
What are you talking about?
She wants me to get
the passwords to your accounts,
so she can take away
all your money.
Cancel the trip?
I can't leave
when Karl is sick.
Yeah, but-but he's not
even in the hospital.
Not yet, but this disease
is unpredictable.
I need to be here.
No, that's not fair.
This was supposed to be
the best summer of my life.
And this could be
the last summer of Karl's life,
so please stop sulking.
- What are you doing?
- I need a drink.
You're barely 18.
Yeah, well, dating
you has aged me.
Give me that.
(sighs)
One week, that's all I ask.
Nothing can happen
in-in a-a week.
What would be the point?
I wouldn't enjoy myself.
In Paris? With me?
My husband is dying.
Can you not understand
what that means?
So what's gonna happen to us?
I don't think
there can be an "us."
Look...
I know that I can act
like a kid sometimes,
but if you give me another
chance, I can be more mature.
No.
You stay young.
I'm the one
who needs to grow up.
(phone ringing)
That might be
Karl's doctor.
I, I'm gonna take it
in the other room.
- Simone...
- No.
Tommy.
(engine starts)
(tires screech)
All right, great,
and you can transfer
those funds today, right?
(sighs) All right, thank you.
Yeah, I'll talk to you.
Bye.
All right. All right,
so my business manager's on it.
He's gonna reset the passwords
to all my accounts.
And I spoke to Lamar. I forbid
him to speak to Taylor,
so she can't use him to try
to get to my script payments.
(sighs)
That's a relief.
Do you think
it'll be enough?
What do you mean?
Taylor was here, in the house,
while we were out.
Maybe we should think
about changing the locks.
Whoa. Uh, I mean,
she's my wife and she loves me.
In her way she's just
trying to protect me.
She's trying
to control you.
There's a difference.
I don't know.
I mean, maybe I should
just call her.
No!
I mean,
I know you want
to believe that
she's gonna come around,
but you have to know, deep down,
there's no way she's ever
gonna get on board
with the idea of you using.
And she's threatening
to call your dad.
My dad?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Why?
She knows that I don't speak
to him. Goddamn it.
She can't just fucking do that.
She's trying to make
you feel small.
I hate that she's
treating you this way.
The last thing I want is
to see you lose everything
you've been working
so hard to get.
Who are you calling?
Our handyman. You're right.
We're gonna change
those fucking locks.
Rob's got an awful lot
of old sports equipment.
BETH ANN:
And he never uses any of it.
So I'm taking it
to the pawnshop
and giving the cash to April.
Well, that'll be
a nice chunk of change.
It will be easier for her
to make a rational decision
about the baby if she's
not so worried about money.
I still can't believe
you talked her out of it.
That horrible place?
I couldn't let her stay.
Here, put this
in the big pile, please.
I got to admit
I'm a bit surprised.
Surprised?
She's pregnant
with your husband's kid.
Most wives in that situation
wouldn't care how rusty
the knives were.
Couldn't let anything happen
to April or her baby.
Honey, y-you know that she could
still decide to get rid of it.
I know. That's why
I have to work hard
over the next few days
to change her mind.
Well, talk to her
about adoption.
You know, there's-there's plenty
of nice people out there
who can't have kids.
I'll mention that.
There's also
another possibility.
What's that?
Rob and I could raise the baby.
What?
I've got it all figured out.
I'll support April
until the baby arrives,
then I'll offer to raise it.
As far as Rob's concerned,
I could arrange some scenario,
finding it in a bassinet
in a park, abandoned.
No one would ever have
to know the truth.
Rob would have his child,
April could have her career,
everyone would be happy.
What's wrong?
At first I thought it was funny,
you becoming friends
with your husband's slut.
- Sheila, that word.
- And then, when you kept getting
closer to her, I thought
you were a little nutty.
But no. You're sick.
I'm not sick.
Your kid is dead.
And you're trying to replace her
with April's baby.
That is not what I'm doing.
That is what you're doing
from where I'm standing.
You're not allowed to judge me.
Not until
you pick out
Benny's casket
and dress him in his Sunday best
and put him in the ground.
Until you do that, I don't
want to hear another word
from you.
(door closes)
SIMONE (over phone):
Hello?
Simone, thank God you answered.
Naomi. What's going on?
I ran out without my purse,
and I don't have
my insurance card or my ID,
and the housekeeper
isn't answering,
and I don't have
anyone else to call.
Slow down. What's going on?
Where are you?
I'm at the hospital.
I need my purse.
Can you please bring it?
Well, of course.
What's happened?
Tommy's been in a car accident.
I-I'll be right there.
Yes. Can I help you?
I'm here to speak
to Rob Stanton.
- Do you have an appointment?
- No.
But I'm not leaving
until I speak to him.
I beg your pardon?
Tell him it's April.
Oh.
So you know who I am.
I do.
I'm sorry, but he won't see you.
I really think
that you should go.
Miss!
Please stop.
I'm sorry, Mr. Stanton.
I told her you were busy.
It's all right.
What do you want?
One lousy minute
of your time.
You owe me that,
don't you think?
Claire, go ahead
and shut the door.
I'm sorry I didn't return
your phone calls.
I thought a clean break
was just better for...
I'm pregnant.
Don't worry.
I don't need anything from you.
I'm not keeping it.
The way you
treated me,
I wasn't even
going to tell you.
But I'm not a bad person.
You have a right to know.
Anyway, that's all
I came here to say, so...
goodbye.
Have a nice life.
Wait.
Simone, thank you so much.
- Where's Tommy?
- They're doing some scans of his head.
He has a possible concussion.
They need to be sure
there's no swelling.
But he'll be all right?
He's pretty banged up.
He has a bad cut on his leg,
but he'll recover.
- Oh, thank God.
- He was driving while drunk.
I couldn't believe it
when the nurse told me.
Tommy would never...
God. What's happened to my boy?
I feel so awful.
You're so sweet to be here.
Even now, when you're going
through your own hell.
What do you mean?
I know about Karl,
how he's sick
with that gay disease.
(scoffs) I don't know
what you've heard, but...
Ida Coy told me.
She was in one of the stalls
when you were talking
to Dr. Bennett's wife.
Oh, God. Well, please
don't tell anyone else.
Karl would be so upset.
I don't care about Karl.
You're the one
I'm concerned for.
Are you okay?
Well, I don't have it,
if that's what you're asking.
Well, I hope not.
No one seems to know how
those people are spreading it.
NURSE: We brought
your son to a room
- if you want to see him.
- Yes, please, let's go.
Oh, but we can only allow
family back there.
Oh, Simone is
practically family.
Sorry, it's policy.
It's fine.
Just-just
- call me later.
- I will.
And I will be there for you
when you need me.
TAYLOR: Truth is,
I fell in love with Jade
without really knowing
who she was.
And what's worse is
I brought her into my home.
Now she's sleeping in my bed
and I'm living in a hotel.
I need her out of my house.
But she's enabling
my drug addict husband
and I don't think
he'll just let her go.
Not to mention the fact that you
and I both know how intensely
she can react
when she feels threatened.
If I'm gonna get her out of
the house, I need to be smart.
I need leverage.
And I thought you might be just
the person to help me with that.
Why would I help you?
I'm thinking, you scratch
my back, I scratch yours.
All you got to do is
tell me where it itches.
They set my bail at $10,000.
They seem to think
I'm dangerous.
Well, as luck would have it,
I brought my checkbook.
Well, in that case,
how can I help?
Tell me everything
you know about Jade.
Well, for starters,
that's not her real name.
(exhales):
Oh, shit.
Hold on, darling.
You ain't heard nothing yet.
Oh. Oh, my poor baby.
How is his leg?
Well, he needed
some stitches,
but he will be good
as new in no time.
What in the world?
NURSE:
Who's Simone?
That his girlfriend?
Bit young
for a tattoo.
One day he's gonna
regret that.
So will she.
Hey there.
How you feeling?
Better,
now that you're here.
Aw. Need help with anything?
Oh, I'm just peeling potatoes.
I think I can handle it.
I'm gonna change clothes.
When I'm done, I'll come down
and set the table for you.
You're sweet.
(knocking on door)
Leo.
What are you doing here?
Where's Rob?
He just went upstairs.
Is something wrong?
Yeah, you need
to come to our house.
You got a phone call
from you-know-who.
She said
it's important.
Oh.
And Sheila wanted me to tell you
this is the last time
she's doing this for you.
She's still angry with me?
Yeah, something like that.
Do you think I'm
a horrible person?
Nah, I think
you're a nice lady
who's gotten herself
in a real fucking mess.
We're here.
Is she serious?
Oh, yeah.
Hello?
Sheila. What took you so long?
Long story.
I-Is everything okay?
Better than okay.
Everything is wonderful.
- Tell me.
- Well,
I went to Rob's office to let
him know that I'm pregnant.
You did what?
I figured the S.O.B.
had a right to know.
Anyway, I stormed into
his office and I blurted it out,
and do you know
what that big galoot did?
No.
(laughs):
He got down on one knee
and asked me
if I would marry him.
But no, but he's still married.
That's what I said.
But he told me
that his marriage is ending.
He said he just needs
six months.
Six months.
And then
he'll be totally free.
Oh.
Anyway, I just wanted
to call to tell you first.
Now I have to call
and tell my mother.
(laughs):
Oh, Sheila.
I am so happy.
(phone clicks)
Uh, I would ask if
everything's okay, but, uh,
I don't think I'm allowed
to talk to you anymore.
So...
♪ ♪
(phone chimes)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org