Oh,
sorry Holmes.
No, no,
you couldn't have come at a better time.
I was afraid you were engaged.
I am,
very much so.
Dr. Watson shares my love
of all that is bizarre,
but outside the routine
of everyday existence.
It is at present and impossible to say...
...that this case is an
instance of crime or no.
But suffice it to say that I know as little...
...about Mr. Jay Beards Wilson
as you do yourself,
beyond the obvious facts.
That he has done manual
labor at sometime.
But it takes staff that he has been to China.
And that he has done...
...a considerable amount of writing lately.
How in the name of good fortune...
...did you know all that Mr. Holmes?
As true as gospel I once did manual labor.
I started off as a ship's carpenter.
Your hands my good servant.
The muscles of your right hand...
...are more developed than the left.
And the writing?
What else could be indicated.
By the right cuffs are
very shiny for five inches.
And the left sleeve with
smooth pattern over the elbow...
...where you lean it on
the desk... but China?
The fish tattooed immediately
above his right wrist.
I have made a small study of tattoo marks.
Mr. Wilson, and have even contributed...
...to the literature of the subject.
That trick of staining the fish scales,
a delicate pink is quite peculiar to China.
Wherein addition I see
a Chinese coin hanging...
...from his watch chain.
The matter becomes even more simple.
Well I never...
I thought at first it was something clever,
but now I see there's nothing in it after all.
You know I begin to think
that my reputation...
...such as it is will suffer
shipwreck if I'm so candid...
...pro magnifico.
Everything becomes
commonplace by explanation.
Watson that is a very loose translation.
Oh, please show the doctor
that advertisement.
Oh, there, you can read it for yourself sir.
To the Red Headed League.
On account of the request...
...of the late Iscar Hopkins of Lebanon.
Pennsylvania USA there
is a vacancy open...
...which entitles a member
of the league to a salary...
...of four pounds a week
for purely nominal services.
All red headed men sound
in body and mind...
...and above the age of 21 are eligible.
Apply in person on Monday
at 11:00 to Mr. Duncan Ross...
...at the offices of the League,
7 Copes Court Fleet Street.
Is this serious?
It is a little off the beaten track, hey Watson.
Oh, would you make a note
of the paper and the date?
Evening standard of Saturday
the 27th of April,
two months ago.
Do try this sitting.
Now, Mr. Wilson,
off you go...
...at scratch and tell us all about yourself.
Oh, well gentlemen I have a small...
...pawn broking business
in Sax Coburg Street,
near the city.
It's not a very large affair.
It just gives me a living.
I used to keep two assistants
but now I just keep the one.
And to tell you the truth
I'd have a job to make you pay...
...but the deeds willing
to come at half wages...
...so as to learn the business.
About two months ago...
What is the name of the obliging youth?
Vincent,
Vincent Spalding.
Oh, but he's not such a youth
either Mr. Holmes.
It's difficult to say his age...
...but I couldn't wish for a smarter assistant.
You seem most remarkably fortunate.
In having an employee who
comes under the market price.
I don't know that your assistant...
...is not as remarkable
as your advertisement.
Oh, but he does have his faults.
However, he was such a
fellow for photography.
Always snapping away with his camera...
...when he should be improving
his mind and then diving down...
...into the cellar to develop
the wretched things.
Still on the whole he's a good worker.
No vice in him.
It was he who first showed
me the advertisement.
I wish to the lord I was
a red headed man Mr. Wilson.
Why is that?
Well there's another vacancy...
...in the League of Red Headed Men.
I've never heard of it.
Well, I'd wonder at that
you being so eligible yourself.
Nice money too.
A couple hundred a year
and the work's light...
Oh, there'll be thousands
of red headed men apply.
Oh, well I doubt that sir.
Well nobody with such a fine fiery color...
...as you're blessed with Mr. Wilson.
But then I suppose
it's only worth your while...
...to put yourself out of the way...
...for sake of a few hundred pounds.
Yes, sir.
Well I'm very much of a
stay at home sort of person.
Sometimes weeks on end before
I put my foot over the doormat...
...but this it looked interesting.
I was intrigued and young Vincent...
...said he'd come with me.
So, on Monday morning
we shut up the shop...
...and off we went.
Now, Vincent let's go back.
I can't get by the crowd.
Courage Mr. Wilson.
We're so near and so much at stake.
Now you put your coat on...
...and come along with me.
Ohy, Ohy, Ohy,
a little less noise...
...please gentlemen.
Here, here what's your game?
Hey get out of here.
Hey, hey...
Off you go,
you next, get in.
Hey, where are you going?
Straight this way,
Come on.
This is Mr. Wilson.
Right in you go Mr. Wilson.
Admirably suited.
Every requirement.
Very quiet.
Congratulations Mr. Wilson.
It would be injustice to hesitate.
You will I'm sure excuse me
if I take an obvious precaution.
Tears in your eyes.
I perceive all is as it should be.
We have to be careful.
Twice deceived by wigs,
once by paint.
I could tell you tales of cobblers wags...
...that would disgust
you with human nature.
My name is Duncan Ross.
I am myself a pension upon a fund left by...
...a noble benefactor.
I see you're about to question
me about Mr. Ethic Guya Hopkins.
He was himself red headed.
In his youth he left London
for America where he made...
...many millions of dollars.
On his death it was found
that he had instructed...
...a trustee in his will
to make life a little easier...
...for the red headed men
in the town of his birth.
Wonderful color.
Now what's your full name Mr. Wilson?
Jay Beards Wilson.
Jay Beards Wilson
and are you a married man.
Mr. Wilson?
Do you have a family?
No,
I'm a widower.
No, I never had any family.
Oh dear,
sad to hear you say that.
The fund of course is for the propagation...
...and spread of red headed men...
...as well as with their maintenance.
In another case the objection might be fatal.
However, I've think we've
got to stretch a point...
...in favor of a man with
such a head of hair as yours.
The vacancy has been filled.
The vacancy is filled.
Now,
off you go.
Sorry about that.
Off you go.
Now, when would you be free
to start upon your new duties?
Oh, well it is rather awkward
as I do have a business already.
What would be the hours?
10:00 to 2:00.
Well the mornings are quiet.
I do have an assistant.
Yes, that would suit me very well.
And the money mentioned,
four pounds a week.
Correct.
And the work?
Purely nominal.
Yes, but what do you call purely nominal?
Well, you have to stay in the office...
...or at least in the building the whole time.
If you leave you forfeit
your whole position forever.
The will is quite clear on that point.
Oh, I shouldn't dream of leaving.
No, excuse will avail.
Not a sickness,
business, anything else.
Here you will remain
or else lose your ability.
Oh, I am quite clear on that point.
But what exactly is the work?
It is to copy out
the encyclopedia Britannica.
There is the first volume.
You will supply the ink,
paper and pen.
We will supply this desk and chair.
Now would you be free to start
next Monday morning?
Oh, yes,
certainly.
Then once again my congratulations.
Mr. Jay Beards Wilson
on the most important position...
...you've been fortunate enough to gain.
Wonderful head of hair.
Good bye Mr. Wilson.
Well done Mr. Wilson.
Well done indeed.
This is the quickest way out sir.
Oh.
This way.
When I got home the whole thing seemed...
...on reflection to be quite ridiculous.
Why?
Who would make such
an extraordinary will?
Not a very generous
millionaire to make you...
...buy your own pen,
ink, and paper.
Exactly Mr. Holmes.
I soon persuaded myself
it was some great hoax or fraud.
And then when Monday morning
came along it seemed stupid...
...to turn down a good job...
...so, off I went and bought
a penny bottle of ink...
...and a pen and seven sheets
of fools kept paper.
And I set off for Popes Core.
Good morning,
Mr. Wilson and welcome.
Good morning.
Well to my surprise and delight...
...everything was as right as possible.
The table was set up ready for me...
...and Mr. Duncan Ross was there
to see I got fairly to work.
My employment had truly begun.
The schedule never varied.
My work started at 10:00
and ended at 2:00...
...with a small break for my lunch
at half past 12:00.
Every Saturday at 2:00
Mr. Ross would come in...
...and give me my money.
Compliment me upon
the amount that I'd written...
...and then we'd both leave.
Mr. Ross locking the door afterwards.
The artichokes I found
were positively fascinating.
They have a kind of a bloom on them but...
I thought that was very interesting...
Good Morning.
Oh, the work was very interesting.
Abacus,
abbey,
architecture,
acts of the Apostles,
adulteration,
anatomy,
apes,
aquaducts.
After eight weeks I'd fairly dealt with...
...the letter 'A' and was
hoping the diligence...
...to get onto 'B' when suddenly
this morning...
...the whole business came to end.
I went to my work as usual
but the door was shut...
...and locked with a little
square of cardboard...
...hammered onto the middle panel.
Oh, excuse me.
Have you seen Mr. Duncan Ross
this morning?
Ross, Ross?
Never heard of a gentleman
with that name, sir...
...and my memory is good.
It's very good,
it's infallible to me.
No, the gentleman in number seven.
Ah, the gentleman who is red headed?
Yes, yes.
Uh, yes, yes, yes,
gone.
Gone?
Mr. William Morris,
solicitor using my room as...
...a temporary convenience
until his new premises were ready.
Moved out yesterday, paid in full,
doesn't owe a penny.
Mr. Morris,
where can I find him?
At his new offices.
William Morris...
...17 King Edwards Street,
near St. Paul's.
Oh, thank you.
I don't see that there's anything
very funny about it.
If all you can do is laugh at me
well I can go elsewhere.
No, Mr. Wilson please,
please sit down.
I wouldn't miss this case for the world.
It is most refreshingly unusual.
I was so incensed with
the forgery of deceit...
...that I came straight to you sir.
Having heard of your great reputation...
...for helping poor people in distress.
Mr. Wilson.
You know Mr. Wilson
I really don't think that you've got...
...any great grievance against
this extraordinary league.
On the contrary you've been
very well paid to say nothing...
...of the detailed knowledge
which you've acquired...
...on every subject under the letter A.
Yes, but what's the object of them
playing this prank on me?
That is what I want to know.
This assistant of yours,
how long has he been with you?
Well about three months.
How did he come?
With the answer to an advertisement.
Was he the only applicant?
No, I had 12 others.
Why did you pick him?
Well he was handy and would come cheap.
At half wages in fact.
Yes.
What's he like,
this Vincent Spalding?
Oh, well he's tall,
slightly built...
...and he's very quick in his ways.
He's got no hair on his face.
He's got a white splash of acid
on his forehead.
Uh, have you ever
observed whether his ears...
...have been pierced for earrings?
Yes, yes,
he told me a gypsy...
...had done it for him when he was a lad.
He is still with you?
Yes,
I just left him.
Mr. Wilson,
You will be at your shop...
...if I should need you?
Well I had thought of shutting up shop...
...at dinner time today
because Vincent had suggested.
I spend the rest of the weekend...
...with my sister in Barking.
This whole business
has upset my nerves very much.
Well you enjoy
a restful weekend in Barking.
Today's Saturday.
By Monday we should have
a conclusion for you.
In the matter of your fee...
Don't worry about that.
I believe it will be paid for by another.
Good day to you Mr. Wilson.
What do you make of it all Watson?
I make nothing of it.
Most mysterious business.
Yet there are graver issues...
...hanging from this affair
then that first had appeared.
What are you going to do?
To smoke.
It is quite a three pipe problem...
...and I beg that you won't
speak to me for 50 minutes.
The business of the Red Headed League...
...is concluded sir.
Satisfactorily I trust.
Most satisfactorily professor
I am pleased to report.
Good.
Come Watson.
Huh?
Excuse me.
Can you tell me the way
to the Strand from here?
Uh, third right,
fourth left sir.
Thank you.
Holmes?
Holmes,
I could have told you that.
No doubt, Watson.
What is it?
And why did you beat
the pavement with your stick?
Watson we are spies in
an enemy's territory.
It's a hobby of mine...
...to have an exact knowledge of London.
Now there's Mortimore's,
the tobacconist.
The little newspaper shop.
Coburg Branch,
the City and Suburban Bank.
McFarland's Carriage Building Depot...
...and the vegetarian
restaurant around the corner.
Watson commit to memory,
it's just possible...
...that we're being observed.
A considerable crime's in contemplation.
Today being Saturday
somewhat complicates matters.
But now doctor...
our work is done.
It is time we had some play.
Sarasate's playing at
Sir James Hall this afternoon.
A sandwich and a cup of coffee?
And then off to violin land with all...
...its sweetness, delicacy and harmony.
And no red headed clients
to vex us with their conundrums.
All the afternoon he sat in the stalls...
...wrapped in the most perfect happiness...
...while his gently smiling face,
and his languid dreamy eyes...
...were as unlike those
of Holmes the sleuth hound...
...as it was possible to conceive.
When I saw him so enwrapped in music.
I felt that an evil time
might be coming upon those...
...he had set himself to hunt down.
Excellent Watson.
You have a future as a cartographer.
That will be Athelney Jones.
I thought it was well enough
to have someone...
...from Scotland Yard with us.
He's an absolute imbecile
at his profession...
...but he does the tenacity
of a lobster when he gets...
...his claws into someone.
Good evening Jones.
So we're working in couples again.
Mr. Holmes.
Our friend is a wonderful man
for starting a chase.
All he needs is an old dog
to help him do the running down.
Mr. Merryweather, my friend
and college Dr. Watson.
How do you do sir?
I only hope a wild goose may not prove...
...to be the end of our chase.
I'm not personally in favor...
...of amateur criminal investigation.
You might place considerable
confidence in Mr. Holmes.
Oh, if you say so Mr. Jones.
He has his own little methods,
which if he won't...
...mind me saying so a little theoretical...
...and fantastic,
but he has the makings...
...of a detective in him.
But I do say as I've said before...
...the Colburg Branch of the Bank
is as well secured...
...as any building in London.
There isn't a possibility
that it could be broken into.
Even insurance assessors
agree on that point.
And you sir should know...
...being not only the resident
manager but also the director.
I should know and I do know.
And what is more,
this is the first time...
...for seven and twenty years
that I've missed my.
Saturday night of whiskey at my club.
And I find myself
extremely inconvenienced.
I think that you will find the game tonight...
...much more exciting
and the stake will be...
...for many,
many thousands of pounds.
And what will be my reward be Mr. Homes?
A young man,
called Clay.
John Clay?
Oh, how I'd like to get
my hands on that devil.
You shall.
This young fellow's
a gentleman as Mr. Holmes says...
...but he's turned against his class.
He's as cunning as the devil.
Slippery as an eel
and he's turned crib cracking...
...and forgery into a fine art.
His grandfather was a royal duke...
...and he himself was educated
at Eaton and Oxford.
So Watson,
bring the gun.
Come gentlemen our cab is below.
There are only two keys to the vault.
I have one,
the chairman holds the other...
...in his personal safe.
Well you are certainly not
vulnerable from above.
Nor from below.
Just a minute.
I'm going to ask you to be
a little more quiet please.
Might I get you to sit
on one of those boxes...
...and not to interfere?
There is no way in which a thief...
...could break into this bank.
Is there a special reason why a thief...
...should want to break into this bank?
Nothing particularly...
Something in the past few months?
Something that you
had concealed from us?
The information I have is confidential...
...known only to the directors of the bank.
It is not to be divulged
to members of the public,
not even amateur detectives.
Private consulting detective,
Mr. Merryweather.
Unique in the annuls of crime I believe,
isn't that so inspector?
Yes, doctor.
I advise you to cooperate with Mr. Holmes.
Especially as at this moment
I am trying to save your skin...
...and that of your fellow directors.
So what is it?
Our French gold.
We had occasion some months ago
to strengthen our resources...
...and borrowed for that purpose
60,000 Napoleons...
...from the bank of France.
Therefore our reserve of bullion
is much larger than is usual...
...in such a branch of the bank.
Where is this gold?
The crates upon which Dr. Watson sits...
...contain 30,000 Napoleons...
...wrapped between layers of lead foil.
May we see it?
This is much bolder
and larger in conception...
...than I had first thought,
wouldn't you say Jones?
I would indeed.
This Clay's more of an
amateur adventurer...
...or spur of the moment criminal.
Long planning is not Clay's type
at all sir, not at all.
Unless he's a pawn in a much larger game.
Mr. Merryweather someone
has had access to...
...information of the most confidential sort.
Careful plans have been made.
A mastermind has been at work.
Are you suggesting that...
I am suggesting that it
bears the hallmarks...
...of Professor Moriarity's work.
Moriarity?
And who is this Moriarity?
We don't really know sir.
That is neither the police nor I think.
Mr. Sherlock Holmes
here has ever set eyes on him.
His name echoes and re-echoes
throughout the underworld.
It appears that he's a man of good birth,
an excellent education
but he has hereditary...
...tendencies of the most diabolical kind.
A criminal strain runs in his blood...
...which has increased and rendered
infinitely more dangerous...
...by his extraordinary mental powers.
He's the organizer of half that
is evil and nearly all that...
...is undetected in this great city.
He is never caught.
His agent is caught but the central power...
...is never caught certainly even suspected.
We shall not see the professor tonight.
The only way for tonight's
enemy to escape is through...
...the pawn brokers.
There's already an inspector at the doors.
Exactly.
We have only a few moments...
positions...
Would you be so kind as
to put out this lamp.
And sit in the dark?
I'm afraid so.
We cannot risk the presence of light.
When I shine the light, act swiftly...
If they fire have no compassion...
...about shooting them down.
Shhh.
Great Scott.
Jump at it,
jump.
It's no good John Clay.
You have no chance at all.
So I see...
...though I fancy my pal's all right.
At this moment he is running into...
...the welcoming arms of the police.
You seem to have done
the thing very completely.
I must compliment you.
And I you.
I'm Sherlock Holmes,
a private investigator.
I didn't for a moment suspect your being...
...a policeman Mr. Holmes.
Come on, hold that one off for the Darby's.
I beg you to take your filthy hands off me.
You may not be aware
that I have royal blood...
...in my veins and be so kind
as to say 'sir' and 'please'
when you address me.
All right.
Would you please sir,
mind marching upstairs...
...while we get a cab to
transport your highness...
...to the police station?
That's better.
Gentlemen.
Oh, one question Mr. Clay.
Am I right in thinking
that professor Moriarity...
...was somewhere behind the idea
of the Red Headed League?
I suggest you keep that name
off your lips Mr. Holmes...
...if you value your future well-being.
Really gentlemen,
I don't know what to say.
Please forgive me
Mr. Holmes for ever doubting...
...your outstanding,
your brilliant qualities.
There is no doubt
you've detected and defeated...
...in the most complete manner
one of the boldest attempts...
...at bank robbery that has ever
come within my experience.
Mr. Merryweather I have then some
small expense over this matter.
I shall expect the bank to refund.
Of course,
of course.
It won't do you know...
...it won't do.
No Professor.
I'm sorry we failed you.
Sherlock Holmes...
Holmes is a mere amateur
in the field of detection.
Still he seems a clever man or a lucky one...
...and he has a positive talent
for getting in my way.
Should he be removed?
It may be necessary.
It would be disappointing.
I find him interesting.
I believe this is the third time...
...he has incommoded me.
If this continues then certainly something...
...will have to be done
to encourage Mr. Holmes...
...either to withdraw or stand clear.
Thank you.
Morning Constable.
Beg your pardon Dr. Watson...
...but this has all been too much for me.
My clients respect me
as a man of confidence...
...but where's the confidence left here.
I'm utterly ruined...
Oh, cheer up Mr. Wilson.
You'll feel better when you've
cleared up the mess.
Well that's all very well...
And Mr. Holmes asked me to give you this,
50 sovereigns with the compliments...
...of the City and Suburban Bank.
Well that's fair enough.
Oh, Dr. Watson, this
is more than acceptable,
and my compliments
to Mr. Sherlock Holmes.
And he sends the same to you Mr. Wilson...
...and a word of advice...
Next time you engage an assistant...
...pay him the proper wage.
Good day to you.
Oh, Holmes,
I trust I am not more dense...
...than my neighbors and
yet here I have seen...
...what you have seen,
heard what you have heard...
...and yet you have seen clearly
not only what had happened,
but what was about to happen
while to me the whole business...
...was still confused and grotesque.
Dr. Watson recollect,
when I heard that the assistant
had come for half wages,
it was obvious that he had some motive...
...for securing the situation.
Yes, but how did
you know what his motive was?
Had there been a woman in
the house I would have...
...suspected immediately if
some vulgar intrigue,
but when I heard from Mr. Wilson...
...about the acid stain and the pierced ears.
I knew that Vincent
Spalding and John Clay...
...were the same person.
But why was Clay there?
The photography gave you the clue.
Exactly.
The cellar, he was working
on something in the cellar.
Something which took many hours a day...
...for two months on end. He was
tunneling but where to?
When I tapped my stick on the pavement...
...in the street that day I was ascertaining...
...whether the tunnel stretched
in front or behind the building.
It was in front,
towards the back.
Could you tell me the way
to the strand from here?
I recognized Clay
immediately and delayed him...
...to have time to examine his knees.
There he spoke clearly
of many hours or tunneling.
No doubt linking up with
a maze of sewers...
...beneath Saxe Coburg Square.
When they closed
the Red Headed League offices,
it was a sign they no longer cared about.
Jay Beards Wilson's presence.
In other words the tunnel was complete.
And that they would make
the attempt on a Saturday...
...was just a guess?
Watson,
you disappoint me.
I never guess.
Saturday's an excellent
night for stealing bullion.
It gives you a full day to escape.
Thank you then.
Thank you.
Oh, you've reasoned it out
beautifully Holmes.
It's so long a chain
and yet every link rings true.
It saved me from irony.
You know sometimes I think
my whole life is spent...
...in one long effort to escape from...
...the common places of existence.
No, no.
You are a benefactor of the race Holmes.
Well maybe it is of some little use after all.
as Gusta Flabare wrote to George Sand.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs. org.