What are you doing?
I heard you could
punch a hole in these
and make them double-sided.
Then it would have more storage?
Yes, but I didn't pay
for a double-sided floppy disk.
So?
So it's an ethical dilemma.
We have to take a shower
in the locker room next period,
and that's what
you're worried about?
Actually, I have
a bathing suit under my pants.
Whoa.
That girl just took
a book on geostatistics.
Yeah, so?
That's not required reading
for any science course.
Maybe she wants
to squash a spider with it.
No, look, she's reading it.
Who is this mystery woman?
Should we invite her
to have lunch with us?
I don't know. So far,
it's just been you and me,
and we know that works.
Do we really want
to mess with success?
We could think of it
as an experiment.
Oh, you do know
how to push my buttons.
All right, go ask her.
Why me?
Your lack of testosterone makes
you adorable to women.
I can't argue with that.
Hello.
My name is Sheldon.
Yeah, you're Sheldon Cooper.
You know who I am?
Well, there's only one
nine-year-old in high school,
and you still have
your baby teeth.
She knows who I am.
It's going well.
What do you want?
Would you like to have lunch
with me and my friend?
Why?
Why else?
So we can have
a spirited conversation
about geostatistics.
You really are
as smart as everybody says.
My teeth are small, but my
prefrontal cortex is enormous.
♪ Nobody else
is stronger than I am ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man. ♪
The addition of Libby brought
a level of sophistication
to our lunchtime discussion.
Her mom also packed
extra string cheese,
which is a well-known
social lubricant.
You're gonna be a geologist.
That's fascinating.
Why'd you choose that?
When I was a little girl,
my grandparents took me
to Carlsbad Caverns,
and I was hooked.
Exploring caves,
that is super cool.
Disagree. Dark,
enclosed spaces are terrifying.
I get scared putting on
a sweatshirt.
Hmm.
I've seen it.
Pretty entertaining.
Do you know what you're going
to major in in college?
I'm leaning towards quantum
chromodynamics, but who knows?
A few years ago, I would've
said choo-choo trains.
What about you?
Oh, geology for sure.
Hmm.
Really?
When did you decide that?
A long time ago.
Eat your apple slices.
So we eat in the
library every day.
You're welcome to join us.
It's much better
than the cafeteria.
It's quiet, and a lot less food
gets thrown at us.
Yeah. Maybe
I'll see y'all tomorrow.
Right.
Maybe y'all will.
Bye, Libby.
"Y'all"?
I'm assimilating.
Shut up.
So how was school today?
Sheldon's got a girlfriend.
- What?
- That's not true.
Oh, yes, it is. I seen him
talking to her at school.
Sheldon Lee Cooper, you dog.
Is she cute?
Compared to what?
What grade is she in?
Eleventh.
An older woman.
Nice.
Most everybody's older than me.
Why is that nice?
So what do you think, George?
Is it time to have
"the talk" with him?
What talk?
No talk. Nobody's talking.
If "the talk" is in regards
to human reproduction,
I already understand
how that works.
How do you know that?
I told him.
Oh, Lord.
And so,
our little social circle
grew from two to three.
An early example of how people
are just drawn to me.
Are you saying
that without geology,
there'd be
no theory of evolution?
Charles Lyell taught
Charles Darwin
the Earth was much, much older
than anyone thought,
which gave Darwin the courage
to figure out
all species evolved
over billions of years.
That's good.
I can use that
to humiliate my pastor
at Sunday school.
I don't know
what's more beautiful,
your mind or your eyes.
Tam, please.
We're eating.
You know spying
on kids is creepy.
I wasn't spying on kids,
I was s-spying on your brother.
Why won't you just go inside?
Well, then, it wouldn't
be spying, now would it?
Oh.
Oh, what?
You didn't mention
she was black.
Was I supposed to?
No, 'course not.
Then why bring it up?
It just wasn't
what I was expecting.
What were you expecting?
It's a big school.
Why are you right here?
They've got some books in there
about Martin Luther King.
Maybe you should go read one.
Morning.
So why did it take
people so long
to believe in continental drift,
when it's obvious
that Africa and South America
- fit together like a puzzle?
- No, they don't.
People didn't understand
continental drift
because they didn't understand
seafloor spreading.
What?
I'm both threatened
and delighted by your brain.
I'm just delighted by it.
They do fit.
That's nuts.
"Geologists lead
a sedimentary lifestyle."
Libby, that is a good one.
Can you believe
what's going on with him?
I know.
He's been on the phone with
that girl for almost an hour.
Sheldon's got
a girlfriend.
What are the odds?
She's not a girlfriend,
it's more of a mental rapport.
That's where it starts.
I did win you over
with my superior intellect.
It was your motorcycle
and you know it.
Good thing it wasn't
your masculine physique,
because that is long gone.
Why do you think
I kept the motorcycle?
How come he gets to tie up
the phone and I can't?
Because what is happening
in there is called a miracle,
and God-fearing people do not
get in the way of those.
Hey, Georgie,
if you ever find a girlfriend,
maybe you can go on
a double date with your brother.
She's not his girlfriend.
And I can find one...
I'm just not looking.
Yes, that was a geology joke.
We gotta get that Sports
Illustrated swimsuit issue
away from him before he's
ruined forever.
Oh, Libby, Libby, Libby.
What is happening?
What was happening was,
like many men before me,
I was being seduced
by the exotic world of geology.
♪ I want to rock ♪
♪ Rock ♪
♪ I want to rock
♪ Turn it down... ♪
We searched for tektites
in a nearby ravine.
Tektites are natural glass
formed
during meteorite impacts.
They also bear
a close resemblance
to raccoon feces,
so I wisely adopted
a "no touching tektites"
policy.
♪ No ♪
♪ So if you ask me... ♪
It's called perfect cleavage
when gypsum separates
this cleanly.
I was so proud of Tam
for not making
an immature cleavage joke.
Look at me,
I'm touching cleavage.
Until he made one.
And, like
Mother Nature's piñata,
geodes contained
a secret surprise inside.
But you didn't have to suffer
through a birthday party
to enjoy it.
How's it going?
Well, I think I figured out
the problem.
What is it?
I'm a terrible mechanic.
- What's up?
- Well,
Sheldon's been spending
quite a bit of time
with this Libby girl, lately.
Yeah, so?
So isn't he a little young
to be hanging with teenagers?
Oh, he's only young
on the outside.
Inside, he's an old man.
I'm being serious.
So am I.
And with that bowtie,
he's old on the outside, too.
Sorry I bothered.
Hang on.
What did you think
was gonna happen
when we sent him to high school?
I don't know,
that he'd learn stuff,
and then, come back home
and be my baby forever.
Mare, it's good for him.
He may start college in a couple
years, what happens then?
Off the top of my head,
he and I share a dorm room.
You know I'd laugh at that
if I didn't kind of believe you.
What are you doing?
I need to use the bathroom,
but it can get uncivilized in there.
Anyone in there now?
I don't know.
I was afraid to find out.
Anybody in here?
Go ahead.
I'll stand guard.
Where have you been all my life?
I don't think so.
I gotta pee.
That's your problem.
Keep moving.
Thank you.
Happy to help.
Is there any chance
you'd be available
to stand guard at 1:45?
You have a bathroom schedule?
You don't?
See you later.
Whoever said the
quickest way to a man's heart
is through his stomach
did not consider
his tiny bladder.
I think the best space shuttle
name so far is Discovery.
What about Challenger?
- Too in-your-face.
- Atlantis?
A fictional island
that couldn't stay afloat?
I don't think so.
There's the Enterprise.
There is,
and it's on Star Trek,
where it belongs.
You know they're playing
a space shuttle movie
at the Museum of
Natural Science.
- It's in IMAX.
- I heard about that.
- The screen is supposed to be huge.
- They also have
a great geology exhibit.
Well, it's in Houston...
How are we gonna get there?
I'll drive.
Oh, I would love to
see a movie with you.
Don't you need to ask
your parents first?
No, Sheldon, I don't.
But won't they worry where you are?
They'll be fine.
Count me in.
Glad you're not my son.
And now he wants to see a
movie in Houston with them.
Why Houston?
I don't know,
it's in MixMax or something.
So you're saying I got
to drive to Houston?
No. This girl Libby's
gonna drive.
Great.
It's not great, George.
I don't want my little boy
in some car
with a teenager
behind the wheel.
All high school kids drive.
Yeah? Well, I
don't like it.
Would you let me
get in a car
with a stranger
when I was young?
Well, nobody ever asked you out,
so it didn't really matter.
Hey. I want to talk to you.
Hold on. Let me bring
this into the station
so as not to disappoint
my commuters.
They'd like to get home
to their families.
I gave it a lot of thought,
and I'm afraid I can't allow you
to drive to Houston
with your friends.
Why?
Well, honey, you're
still a little boy.
I don't think it's right.
I'm not a little boy.
I'm a high school student.
I'm sorry, I made up my mind.
If you'd really like
to see this movie,
I'm willing to drive you.
Maybe we could meet
your friends there.
I don't want my
mommy to take me.
Well, then, you're not going.
Anger is an ugly emotion.
Unbridled rage even more so.
And when it bubbled up
inside me,
I channeled it
the only way I knew how.
♪ We're not gonna take it... ♪
I cleaned the house
like a man possessed.
♪ We're not gonna take it ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
♪♪
♪ We've got the right
to choose it ♪
♪ There ain't no way
we'll lose it ♪
♪ This is our life ♪
♪ This is our song ♪
I can't hear Oprah!
I don't care!
♪ Don't pick our destiny... ♪
Sheldon, I need to get in there.
Poop at Meemaw's!
♪
♪ Oh, we're not gonna take it ♪
♪♪
♪ We're not gonna take it ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
You missed a spot, weirdo.
I see it.
♪ Your gall is never-ending ♪
♪ We don't want nothin' ♪
♪ Not a thing from you ♪
♪ Your life... ♪
What am I supposed
to do with this?
Send him over to my house
before he runs out of gas.
All right, I'll make
a deal with you.
I'm listening.
You can go to Houston
with your friends,
but I want to meet
this girl first.
That's very reasonable.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now, can you please reach
the dryer sheets?
I get vertigo on the step stool.
I've often been accused
of being stubborn and willful,
but sometimes
it works like gangbusters.
Please come in.
Have a seat.
You have a
beautiful home.
- Thank you.
I hope you'll forgive me,
I just wanted to meet
the person driving
my nine-year-old son to Houston.
- I understand.
- Me, too.
I wasn't talking to you, Tam.
And I just wanted
to make certain
that you've had
no traffic tickets
or, heaven forbid, accidents.
No, ma'am.
I'm a very safe driver.
- You've got nothing to worry about.
- Good.
Good. Have you made
this trip before?
- A few times, yes.
- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
You smoke marijuana?
Mom!
No, ma'am.
Just say no.
Well...
I find this very reassuring.
I have to admit,
I had some trepidation, but...
having met you,
I'm feeling a lot better.
Good. You've got nothing
to worry about, Mrs. Cooper.
I've been babysitting kids
for years.
Babysitting... babysitting...
Babysitting.
Babysitting... babysitting... I've
been babysitting kids for years.
Excuse me.
I don't feel well.
They'll have to go without me.
♪♪
Shelly,
you okay?
No.
You want to talk about it?
You want me to leave you alone?
No.
I thought Libby and I
were equals,
but she thinks of me as a child.
I'm sorry, baby.
Calling me that
isn't helping right now.
Right. Sorry.
She is almost twice your age.
There are people
five times my age
that are stupider than me.
This is not about being smart.
- What else is there?
- Well...
there's other kinds of maturity.
What's up?
None of your business.
Why is he crying?
Again, it's none
of your business.
Please go.
Fine. Celeste and I know
when we aren't wanted.
Where were we?
Different kinds of maturity.
That's right.
There's emotional maturity,
physical maturity,
all things that have nothing
to do with being smart.
Are you suggesting
I'm not emotionally mature?
I was hinting at it.
Regardless, I'm not interested
in making any more friends.
Oh, I don't think
that's how you really feel.
It is.
From now on,
it's a hermit's life for me.
I bet, when you grow up,
you will be surrounded
by lots of smart,
wonderful friends.
I can't see that happening.
Well,
the Lord works
in mysterious ways.
And here we go
with the God talk.
Hey.
How was the IMAX movie?
Well...
Okay, status. Find them?
Go.
Guidance...
What are you doing?
What do
you think I'm doing?
Move your arm
before I rip it off.
It got a little uncomfortable.
Why is that?
Libby's got feelings for me,
but I think it's better
we just stay friends.
I've been giving
geology some more thought.
Yeah, and?
I've decided
it's not really a science.
- It's not?
- No, it's more like a hobby.
Rock collecting.
Childish, really.
I can see that.
As you can see,
sometimes a person can be
both incredibly intelligent
and full of baloney.
♪♪