Previously,
on "The Originals"...
This town
was my home once,
and in my absence,
Marcel has got
everything
I ever wanted.
I want it back.
Marcel: I hereby pledge
my allegiance to you.
- Celeste.
- Celeste?
Whoever she was,
she was smoking hot.
I believe that when
you love someone,
you're uniquely
vulnerable.
She died because of me.
Klaus: Davina,
she's a powerful weapon.
Yaah!
I knew that I was supposed
to be killed
so the harvest
could be completed.
Marcel: She is dead!
Do you hear me?
Rebekah: 4 were supposed
to rise, and none did.
Where did
all that power go?
- Tunde: Someone called us forth.
- Who?
Celeste: I did.
I'd appreciate if you
call me by my real name...
Celeste.
Oh...
I remember
this cemetery.
Hmm. Hasn't
changed a bit.
I've been coming here
over a century
wearing one face
or another.
[Drums playing]
Clara Summerlin,
will you come on?
We're gonna miss
everything.
[People cheering and whistling]
Genevieve:
Told you.
Every witch in
the quarter is here,
come to see the
great Papa Tunde.
[Drums stop]
Witches of the french quarter,
thank you for your welcome.
It is good to be
among people of the faith.
I, too, practice
ancestral magic,
honoring those who walked
the path before us.
From them we draw strength...
And you will need strength,
for a great darkness is coming.
The city your forefathers
left you is now overrun
by pirates, beasts,
and vampires.
[Wind whistling]
Tunde: I practice
other magic, as well...
Sacrificial magic.
Channeling power
from the lives of my offerings,
I use this strength
to vanquish my enemies,
and I will punish your enemies
for their greed.
In return, you will accept
my family into your coven...
And me as your leader.
Gentlemen,
make yourselves at home.
Mayor O'Connell appears
to be running late,
but there's much to discuss,
so I shall begin.
Klaus: One moment,
please, brother.
You know
how much I enjoy
these illicit,
little gatherings.
Do not be troubled.
Despite my brother's
reputation, I can assure you,
we've invited you here
to broker in peace.
You have my word.
And, lucky for you,
my brother always
keeps his word.
You two are from
the guerrera crime family,
a brutish pack
of thieves and killers,
and that's nothing compared
to what you become
on a full moon,
is it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Of course,
a bite from your kind
is not lethal
to an original.
Conflict between us
would not
end well
for you at all.
Let's state
our proposal here.
My brother and I control
the ports of the city,
but with prohibition
soon to be the law
of the land, there'll be
a certain uptick
in the kind of federal
presence we prefer to avoid.
Therefore, I'd like
to suggest a system
whereby... under our
supervision, of course...
The guerrera family
can traffic alcohol
into the city of
New Orleans for a profit.
We would still be
in charge,
but our rule would
remain a secret.
[Clap clap clap]
Tunde: This all
sounds very good,
but, tell me,
how will it benefit
the witches?
I am sorry.
This is a private meeting.
Yes, for kings
of the city,
but I, too,
am a King,
and I
have rules.
I'm impressed.
You're either quite ambitious
or quite mad.
What's your name, mate?
I am Alphonz
Bellatunde Delgallo,
Papa Tunde
to my followers,
and I come to ask
that the witches
be granted
fair tribute
for allowing your
existence in our city.
Are you suggesting
that you speak
for the french
quarter witches?
I do now, and I expect
our future negotiations
to go very smoothly.
As a guarantee,
I brought a gift.
I await our
next gathering.
Well, I suppose
we'll need a new mayor.
Hey, Marcel, maybe you
know what's going on.
Klaus ordered us
to meet here,
and now he's
a no-show.
What do you
want from me?
It's a new regime.
Get used to it.
Klaus: Dearest brethren,
your attention, please.
No doubt, you're all surprised
to see Thierry Vanchure,
who's supposed to be rotting
in the garden
for the crime of killing
one of our own,
and I personally decided
to issue him with a pardon.
I hope you'll all
welcome home Thierry.
Welcome home, mate.
[Applause]
[Laughter]
You're in a good mood.
You should visit
Mystic Falls more often.
Well, as much
as I might like to,
I have pressing
responsibilities here.
Now, as you all know,
the witch Davina
is no longer with us.
Without Davina, we can
no longer monitor
the activity
of our witch neighbors.
However, since
their harvest failed,
their magic will soon
be gone forever.
Until then, I say we
keep them on their toes.
Diego, I wonder
if you might lead
a rousting
in the cauldron.
Marcel, I'd hoped
you would join Diego.
Nah.
I'm gonna take
a personal day.
Elijah: Now,
you may doubt him.
Today I saw Niklaus
demonstrate mercy
towards an enemy.
Tell me
that's not progress.
Please, Elijah.
Who do you think convinced
Klaus to let Thierry out?
Why would you do
such a thing?
Because, despite
Klaus' reprieve,
Thierry despises him.
I like that
about Thierry.
I also like that he
used to date a witch,
so he knows about
french quarter covens.
Maybe he can lead me
to whoever
stole off with
the harvest magic.
Rebekah, we are
all devastated
by the outcome
of this ritual.
That's just it.
There was no outcome.
We both know that power
like that doesn't just vanish.
I say someone
stole it.
I'd like to know who,
and then I'd like to make
an ally out of them.
To what end,
exactly?
I'm tired of
being threatened
and controlled by
our tyrant brother.
If you want
to stop a bully,
you need the power
to stand up to them.
I expect such behavior
from Niklaus.
It's so very disappointing
when it comes
from you, Rebekah.
Do you not see
that, in his way,
he's making
an effort here?
He's invited us back
into our family home.
He yearns for our family
to be reunited.
Yes. He's in a
brilliant mood now,
but for how long?
It's his trick, Elijah.
He lulls you
into a false sense
of camaraderie
and kinship,
and then he turns
on you like a snake.
I fall for it
every time
and wind up with
a dagger in my chest
for my trouble.
No more.
I believe that he
is approaching
some semblance
of peace here.
Leadership may, in fact,
be a good thing for him.
Now, sister, please,
I ask you,
if you cannot
support him,
then at least do nothing
to provoke him.
Klaus: Ugh, is this
what's it's come to?
I bear the full weight
of our kingdom
while you pout
like a child.
You wanted to be King.
Besides, you look
like you guy it covered.
If the men see you
shirk your duties,
they're likely
to do the same.
I told you, I am not in
the mood for vampire Hijinx.
No. You'd rather sit
wallowing in sorrow
for your lost
little friend.
Don't push me
right now.
I am sorry Davina
is gone, ok?
I'm sorry, but this
mournful attitude
is unworthy of you,
and it's boring to me.
Diego: Hey, guys,
we got a problem.
We came to mess
with the witches,
just like you said,
and these two,
they went missing,
found them
like this...
Not even staked,
just dead.
Where are you going?
Someone has to account
for this.
You want revenge,
get it yourself.
That mark is tied
to some bad mojo.
Any of y'all got any brains,
you'll head back
to the compound and stay
the hell out of this.
[Thunder]
Klaus: We're gonna find
whoever did this,
and I will show them
what suffering is.
Thierry: Used to run things
down here for Marcel.
Thought you'd like
to see what I found
before Klaus did.
Not a day
out of the garden,
and you're already
proving yourself useful.
We made a deal,
and if it screws things
or your brother,
I'm all for it,
though, to be honest,
this stuff
makes my skin crawl.
I've never seen
anything like this.
I have,
a long time ago.
Somebody is copycatting
a very dangerous witch.
They draw their power
from sacrifice.
I just don't understand
why someone
would leave it here
for us to find...
Unless they wanted it
to be found.
Tunde:
Mademoiselle Mikaelson.
That's not possible.
Sure, it is, chérie. It's magic.
Symbole du masque
et de l'ombre, embrase-toi.
Embrase-toi.
Symbole du masque
et de l'ombre, embrase-toi.
Embrase-toi.
Symbole du masque
et de l'ombre, embrase-toi.
Embrase-toi.
Symbole du masque
et de l'ombre, embrase-toi.
Ah!
Klaus: Someone will die for this.
Remarkably,
I don't disagree.
However, I would
like to know
where they learned
such dark magic.
I had hoped never to see
that symbol again.
I recall it is
the signature of a fool
who once stood
against us.
Clearly, some upstart witch
is salvaging old tricks.
I'll do for him
as I did the other.
Diego.
When night falls,
I want you to gather
every vampire
in the quarter.
Get me the head
of whoever did this
and put it
on a stick.
Yeah. That's gonna
be a problem.
Everyone is
freaked out, man.
We haven't had witches
killing vampires
in a long time.
Marcel made sure
of that.
Marcel has run off
like a scared child.
You lot are left
with me.
Now, who of you
will fight
to defend our home?
Not a single one of you
will stand with me,
so afraid are you
of this new threat?
You should know better.
I'll handle this myself.
Cami: Sophie, the restaurant
is an epic disaster... again.
Do you think maybe
you could come in today and...
Voice: User's mailbox is full.
Good-bye.
Marcel: Looks like
I should've been
here last night.
Before you try anything,
I'm on vervain.
Yeah. Klaus mentioned
you broke free
of his compulsion.
Good for you.
Sophie around?
No. Why?
Got a witch problem.
Thought she might have answers.
Mind if I wait?
It's a little early
for day drinking.
Let me guess,
Klaus problems.
I thought you'd be
on top of the world
now that you have
Davina back.
Davina is gone.
Was it Klaus?
I told him,
if he hurt her...
It wasn't like that.
The power that she
had was too much.
We tried to fix her with
this crazy-ass ritual,
and something
went wrong.
Now she's...
I don't know...
Floating in limbo
or waiting
on her ancestors.
[Crash]
Marcel...
I'm sorry.
Yeah. Me, too.
There you are.
Here I am.
Davina's drawings.
Yeah. Morbid, I know.
I was just thinking,
we never figured out
why she drew those
pictures of Celeste.
Anyway, I'm just
killing time
now that I'm on
vampire lockdown.
Whoever did this,
we will deal with them.
It won't be long.
I'm not worried.
Just think
it's kind of funny
that it took some big,
supernatural threat
for you to even come
into the same room as me.
I do apologize
if you feel neglected.
I have been occupied.
My siblings
are in some quarrel.
Niklaus remains
agitated.
You'll recall that even
our slightest interactions
seem to...
Infuriate him.
So Klaus is a dick,
and you want to be
a good big brother.
So we can't
hang out.
That sum it up?
I get it, Elijah.
It just seems like a
really crappy deal.
[Cell phone vibrating]
El presidente?
He likes to keep track
of his people.
Why are you loyal
to him, exactly?
For someone who says
she can't stand the guy,
you sure ask a lot
of questions about him.
My interest
is purely academic.
I know what
you're doing.
You're mad he used you,
and you want
to get back at him.
Maybe you're hoping
I'll let slip
some chink
in his armor.
Friendly advice...
Don't do that.
It won't end well.
Let me tell you
a story about someone
who went up
against Klaus.
[Music playing]
Marcel, voice-over:
This was right after I returned
from world War I.
I'd been trying to get away
from New Orleans for a while.
Something kept drawing me back.
Why don't you get me
some Martinis?
Thank you.
Aren't you gonna
welcome me home?
I wouldn't
want you to think
that I was happy
to see you.
How long
you gonna hate me?
You left me in a box
for 52 years.
Twice that seems
like a good start.
Come on, boys.
Klaus: There he is...
Our war hero
triumphantly returned.
Oh, good to have you
back, Marcellus.
Welcome home.
Mm. Ha ha!
The prodigal son has finally
learned to hold his liquor.
The army'll
do that to you.
Well, it's good
to have you back.
Niklaus was beside himself
in your absence.
Now that you are here,
perhaps you could help
settle an argument.
You see, you've traded
a war abroad
for one here
in the quarter.
Some rogue witch wants a piece
of the city we built,
and Elijah, for reasons
beyond my comprehension,
insists that negotiation
is our best recourse.
Yes. On the topic of
your failed comprehension,
you forget,
as a soldier,
Marcel has seen
not only
how small
the world has become
and how fast
news can travel,
but also the very
horrors of war itself.
Surely, Marcel
would agree with me.
The best way for us
to defend our home
is by exercising
discretion.
So who's the witch
you want to kill?
His name is Papa Tunde.
I think
he's a charlatan.
Elijah: Well, Marcel
shall be able
to decide that
for himself.
You invited him
here.
Of course.
We're not savages, are we?
Thank you for accepting
our invitation, and welcome.
I hope you'll allow me
to play the role of host.
If there's
anything you need...
Anything at all...
Pleasure before
business, then.
Ha ha ha!
Marcel, voice-over:
I didn't get it at first.
Klaus was the one
who wanted to go to war.
So why was he inviting
his enemy into his home?
Why be so generous to someone
who he's gonna have to kill?
But, you see, that's the thing.
It was all part of Klaus' plan.
He was sussing
the guy out,
learning his weaknesses,
his strengths,
getting him to let
his guard down.
That's how Klaus
does it.
Then he goes in
for the kill.
Because he's
a two-faced sociopath.
There's nothing enviable
about what Klaus does.
He's a monster.
We're all
monsters, Cami.
If you're powerful
like Klaus is,
you just don't have
to bother hiding it.
Davina was powerful.
She wasn't a monster.
It is done.
The power of the original
sister flows through me.
And will that be enough
to make Klaus suffer?
I will hurt Klaus Mikaelson
as he hurt me.
When I am done,
he will wish
that he could die.
You gonna open
this place today?
And risk you eating
the clientele?
Oh, and here
I thought
you were starting
to like me again.
[Cell phone vibrating]
[Beep]
Ah, you've deigned
to break your despair
long enough to
pick up the phone.
I figured you'd
just keep calling.
Klaus: I'm in
the cauldron now.
You could meet me here.
We could start burning
passersby at the stake.
Sorry. I'm gonna
chase down my own lead.
And where
might that be,
the bottom of
a bottle of scotch?
I'm at
Sophie Deveraux's place.
I figured I'll sit here
and drink till she shows.
Or you could snap
out of this funk
and come and
help me end this.
[Beep]
Sophie: Big, bad
Klaus Mikaelson.
Sophie.
Just the witch I was
looking to brutalize.
Perhaps you could explain
the attacks on my men.
[Beep]
Rebekah is not
answering her calls.
You worried about whoever
killed those daywalkers
still being out there?
Frankly, I'm
worried that she
had something
to do with this.
She's very displeased
with Niklaus,
perhaps even
conspiring
with others.
Thierry, is it?
That's right.
My sister
is rather fond of you.
Strange, she's not typically
drawn to unremarkable men.
Would you care to explain
your sudden magnetism?
I don't know
what you're...
You can either
tell me what you know
or I can distribute tiny pieces
of you throughout the quarter.
She asked me to keep an
eye out on witch stuff.
I found something,
and when I showed her,
we were jumped
by some guy.
He desiccated her
with his touch.
Like a coward,
you left her.
What was I
supposed to do,
fight some warlock that
took out an original?
Where was this,
exactly?
The docks,
warehouse 57.
I was just doing
what she asked.
You cannot tell
Klaus about this.
I shall take that
into consideration.
I'm coming with you.
No. Stay here.
Compound is safe.
Rebekah is in trouble.
I'm going.
Do not leave my sight.
Understand?
Me calling things
off with you
wasn't lack
of interest.
I was hoping to save you
from all this.
Well, thanks, Romeo,
but I'm in it.
So when are you gonna
get to the good part
with Klaus
and that Papa guy?
Papa Tunde said he wanted
to empower the witches.
Mostly, he wanted
money and territory.
Klaus and Elijah weren't
about to give him either.
He didn't like that,
so he went on a rampage.
No one was safe...
[Panting]
Marcel, voice-over:
Not the humans in the faction...
Not the guerrero werewolves.
He even went after the witches
who opposed him.
Elijah offered a truce...
He gave his word, in fact...
But Klaus, being Klaus,
he had another idea.
You're late, Elijah.
It's not like
the noble brother
to keep me waiting.
I'm sorry, mate.
Elijah is
the brother you meet
when negotiations
are to be had.
I'm the one you get when
negotiations are closed.
You do not scare me.
You have no idea
the power I possess.
Oh, in fact, I made
it a point to learn
all about
your power.
I noticed how you're
almost always near
those twin sons
of yours,
how they bear your
distinctive mark.
Got me to thinking.
You channel their
power, don't you,
which, of course,
begs the question,
what would happen
were that power
to be taken away,
if those sons
whose lives
you depend on
were suddenly
struck down?
What of that power
then?
I will kill you
for this.
I cannot be killed.
You, however...
Aagh!
That's horrible.
Oh, to Klaus,
it's just business.
And don't you think
there's something
fundamentally wrong
with that?
Don't you worry
you'll end up
one of his victims or,
worse, just like him?
Tunde: Poor Marcellus.
You remain always in
the shadow of your father.
Climb out from
beneath it, will you,
so you can die
like a man?
Cami, you need
to run now.
Don't look back.
Just go.
I think
she should stay.
I prefer an audience,
and I'm about
to put on
quite the show.
[Rattle]
[Crack]
Cami: Marcel?
I said,
get out of here.
You cannot defeat me.
I channel the power
of an original vampire.
Soon, I will have all 3,
but first, I will take you.
[Glass shatters]
Sophie:
It's a complex spell,
old-school stuff rooted
in sacrificial magic.
Whoever did this
to your guys, my guess is,
they were an offering
to gain more power.
More guys they kill,
more power they get.
[Cell phone vibrates]
[Beep]
I didn't expect
a call from you so soon.
You need to get to
Rousseau's now.
Some lunatic witch doctor
is killing Marcel.
Get as far away
from there as you can.
[Beep]
Elijah: Rebekah.
[Whoosh]
Oh...
What's happening?
Some kind
of boundary spell.
Someone is
channeling her.
Typically, it's
a lethal process,
but, because she's
an original, she cannot die.
Instead, she's an endless
source of power.
So what are we
supposed to do?
You have to get her
out of there.
As I recall, you're
one of the few people
Niklaus Mikaelson
ever gave a damn about.
You know what he did
to my family.
Aah!
The sins of the father
are paid for by the son.
I will take pleasure
in telling Klaus how you died.
I remember killing you.
I rather relished it.
What a joy it is to
relive fond memories.
Tunde:
You're here. Good.
I can crush you before
the eyes of your son,
then I will
consume you both.
This time,
I'm stronger.
You're not listening.
We cannot enter the circle.
There's some kind
of confinement spell or...
If I can't remove her,
we can't break the link.
Sophie, on phone:
It's a convoluted spell.
It's like
a witch's recipe.
You can spoil
the balance by adding
a more potent
ingredient,
a mystical binding
agent... I don't know...
Volcanic ash, rock salt,
anything up to and
including eye of newt.
What about the blood
of a witch?
Do you have the
blood of a witch?
[Beep]
I need a favor.
The baby.
She's a quarter
witch.
Uh!
[Whoosh]
- Is he dead?
- Get out of here.
Is Marcel dead?
Did that guy kill him?
He didn't finish him off.
Marcel needs blood to heal.
Go. Find me someone
off the street.
- I'll do it.
- No.
Not you.
I don't want you
involved in this.
You don't control me
anymore, remember?
It's ok, Marcel.
It's ok.
[Chomp]
[Slurping]
Ah!
I should rip out
your coward heart.
What, Rebekah?
We made a deal
to take out your brother,
but at he end of the day,
it's every man for himself.
I am so sick
of self-serving narcissists.
Are men simply incapable
of committing to an alliance?
[Crack]
Oh...
I asked you to cease
these petty moves
against our family,
and yet you conspire
with this fool.
Is this
what its come to,
making moves against
your own blood?
Don't you try
and shame me.
Nik grows more powerful
by the day,
and you do nothing
but encourage him.
I offer him my counsel
because it's clear to me
that he needs to make
the city our home.
Now, perhaps leading
these... derelicts
will curb some
of these impulses,
Grant him some
degree of happiness.
You always talk
of Nik's happiness.
Over 1,000 years,
he has robbed me
of any chance
at my own.
What about me, Elijah?
Am I not a concern
for you?
We all make sacrifices
in the name
of this family, Rebekah,
but know this.
I will never stand
against you or Niklaus.
What about Hayley?
Nothing I conspire to do,
none of my treachery
will harm this family as much
as your feelings for her.
You're a hypocrite,
Elijah.
You would choose love
over family
and then condemn me
for doing the same.
Fancy meeting
you here.
That symbol is already
up and down the cauldron,
more of them
popping up everywhere.
I suppose Papa Tunde
is marking his territory.
I'm told you
saw him, as well.
Yeah.
Brought up a lot
of memories.
Memories that are
best left buried.
[Music playing]
You're sauced.
Celebrating Klaus' defeat
of the mad Papa Tunde?
Not celebrating,
drowning sorrows.
I'm the one who
brought Tunde to town.
What?
I made some inquiries
while I was abroad,
wanted the most dangerous
witch anyone could find.
Why on earth
would you do that?
For you.
I figured if someone
as bad as Tunde comes in,
maybe Klaus
gets chased off.
Very least, he's occupied
enough that he can't stop me
for trying
to get you back.
You mean to tell me
that you would tear down
everything
my family built,
you helped us build,
risk your own life
on the off chance
that I would show you
the slightest bit
of affection?
I would.
I did.
I'd do it again.
Klaus has killed
a thousand tundes.
All his life,
there's only ever been
one man he has
truly feared...
My father Mikael.
The vampire
who hunts vampires.
If he came here,
Klaus would flee
and never turn back.
All we need
is a witch
who can help us
find him.
[People talking]
Not long ago,
you all united against me.
You failed.
Since then, in my benevolence,
I have wiped the slate clean,
yet it seems clear you think
that I am the one
who needs to earn your respect,
your loyalty.
You're mistaken.
It is you who must
prove yourselves to me.
Our community is under attack.
I require soldiers.
I need warriors, not cowards.
Each of you has
a decision to make.
You either fight alongside me
or you leave... now.
[Murmuring]
We don't owe you anything.
If staying in the quarter means
living under your rule,
I'd just as soon
get the hell out.
Marcel: I got to admit,
I thought you'd lose
a lot more guys than that.
Well, good riddance
to them, I say.
We've no room for
slackers of cowards
in our kingdom.
Now that you've
regained your composure,
let's move on
to the next item
of business,
shall we,
with a little help from
our dear friend Sophie.
I got no reason
to help you,
and I sure as hell don't have
a reason to help him.
Klaus: Now, now,
don't be difficult, luv.
You'll only live as long
as you're of use to me,
and right now,
your best use is to explain
why a witch I killed
100 years ago
has come back
for revenge.
Sophie: Come on.
Resurrected witches
with vast power?
It's the harvest.
4 girls were meant
to die and be reborn.
I don't know how,
but someone
jacked that power,
and they used it
to bring back 4 witches,
just not
the right ones.
So there's still
a chance.
If we can get that power back,
we can save Davina.
Let's concentrate
on the immediate
problem, shall we?
Papa Tunde
wants revenge.
He'll continue
to attack us,
channeling power from
the vampires he sacrifices.
He kills, he grows
more dangerous.
So how do I end him?
He needs sacrifices
to gain power.
Hmm.
You keep him from killing
any more nightwalkers,
that's a start.
Unless... he finds
the one place
with a load of vampires
ready to be sacrificed.
[Music playing]
Is it done?
This blade now contains
all the power
I harvested
from the vampires.
It will do things
worse than death,
even to an original.
And are you ready
for the final offering?
In the name of the witches
of the french quarter,
it is my honor.
Thank you, Papa Tunde.