Hey, will you steam
my uniform next?
Yeah, w...
Interesting.
Do you recall this conversation?
"Leonard, want to go halfsies
on a steamer?"
"No, Sheldon,
we don't need a steamer."
Looks like that rumpled
chicken's come home to roost.
Hi.
Here are the make-up sponges
you asked for.
Oh, thanks,
I thought I had more.
Damn, you've got
more makeup than I do.
You've got better makeup
than I do.
Yeah, I'm borrowing this.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
This is my Comic-Con makeup.
I love you,
but there are some things
a man doesn't share
with his girlfriend.
That's a wise policy.
I once borrowed
my sister's makeup
for a costume contest.
Got a terrible case of pinkeye.
Yeah, but luckily,
I was going as a zombie.
I won second place.
I feel like you guys
just went to Comic-Con.
That was San Diego Comic-Con.
This is Bakersfield Comic-Con.
Is that better?
Well, it's a lot smaller.
It's more about
the comic books.
The way these
conventions used to be
before they went
all Hollywood.
So to answer your question,
no, it's not better.
Well, then why are you going?
It's a comic book convention.
You know, it's like pizza
or particle accelerators,
even the stinky one's
still pretty good.
All right.
Well, you guys have fun.
I guess I'll see you
Sunday night.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, hang on a second.
Hold this.
What was that for?
To show people
when they don't believe me.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x13 ♪
The Bakersfield Expedition
Original Air Date on January 10, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Oh, this is the best.
You have booze
with breakfast on a Tuesday,
you got a problem.
You do it on the weekend,
you got brunch.
Sheldon doesn't believe
in brunch.
He can't stand being at a table
where one person's
having an omelet
and another person's
having a sandwich.
He's not exhausting at all.
(phone chirps)
Oh.
It's Leonard.
he says they're on the road
and headed for Bakersfield
at "warp speed."
(chuckles)
Maybe it's the mimosa,
but I'm gonna give
the kid an LOL.
It's cute how excited they are.
You should have seen Howard
sewing his costume all week
for the convention.
When did Howard learn
to sew?
When he was a little boy,
every couple months,
he would have to let
his mom's pants out.
I don't even understand why
they go to these conventions.
I know. The four of them work
at a major university.
They're all super smart.
How can they still be
into something
made for 12-year-olds?
I don't mind it.
I think Howie's just in touch
with his inner child.
Although when he comes to bed
in his Batman pajamas,
sometimes it feels like
I'm touching his inner child.
It's probably because
they were bullied growing up.
In a world
where you can't fight back,
superheroes provide
meaningful wish-fulfillment.
(groans)
Now I feel bad for picking
on all those kids.
Although, in my defense,
if Danny Biffle didn't want
to eat a mouthful of dirt,
he shouldn't have shown up
to school wearing a bow tie.
I've never even read
a comic book. You guys?
Uh-uh.
No.
I mean, it's such an important
part of their lives.
Maybe we should try
reading some.
Seriously?
The comic book store
isn't far from here.
That is an amazing idea.
Okay, how many of these
have I had?
I think you should turn
on the GPS.
It is on.
But the turn-by-turn
voice option isn't on.
I know I'd feel more safe
if you turn on the turn-by-turn
voice option.
I love the turn-by-turn
(quietly): Has it really only
been ten miles?
I'm turning it on,
but just to shut you up.
SHELDON'S VOICE (on GPS):
Leonard, bear left and continue
on Interstate 210.
Ooh, sounds like that fellow
knows what he's talking about.
I'd put on my listening ears
if I were you.
What did you do?
I found a hack online.
I was able to upload
MP3 recordings
of my voice to your GPS.
That is so cool.
Counterpoint,
no, it's not.
SHELDON'S VOICE:
Continue on Interstate 210
for five miles.
Here's an interesting fact
about interstates.
Really?
Shh,
he said it's interesting.
Interstates are numbered
as follows.
Even-numbered routes
run east and west,
odd-numbered routes
run north and south.
Three-digit route numbers
indicate bypasses
or spurs.
(Sheldon mouthing with audio)
Look, Leonard,
there's a bridge.
Drive off it.
You know, we're not that far
from Vazquez Rocks.
Oh, they shot a lot
of Star Trek episodes out there.
We've got our costumes
in the trunk.
We could go there
and have a little photo shoot.
Great idea.
I haven't had a carbohydrate
in two weeks.
These cheekbones need
to be in front of a camera
before I eat a pretzel
and they're gone.
Yeah, that sounds fun.
Oh, smashing.
Now, Leonard,
do you know how to get there?
No.
Yeah, well luckily,
someone in the car does.
SHELDON'S VOICE:
Recalculating.
While we're waiting,
do you know
which president signed
the Intestate Highway System Act
into law?
The answer,
coming up in 14 miles.
None of you will get it.
It's Eisenhower.
Why are they staring?
Who cares?
Just soak it in.
Hello, boys.
Oh, hey.
Could you please stop staring?
They're just girls.
It's nothing you haven't seen
in movies or in drawings.
Hey, Stuart.
Wh-What brings you guys here?
We were looking
for a recommendation
about comic books.
Oh, well, I recommend
you don't open a store
and sell them.
No, we were just wondering
why the guys like
this stuff so much,
so we thought we'd
give it a try.
Oh, okay. What do you think
you might be into?
Superhero, fantasy,
graphic novels, manga--
I swear
I will turn a hose on you.
What kind of comics
do the guys like?
Um, a litt bit of everything.
Mostly superhero stuff.
All right, well,
who's the best superhero?
Shh!
You can't ask a question
like that in here.
Are you trying
to start a rumble?
Well, what do you recommend?
Well, uh, let's see.
You've got your basic
clean-cut good guys--
Superman, Spider-Man,
Captain America.
Then you have
your darker anti-heroes--
your Batman, your Wolverine,
Punisher.
Ooh, I do love a bad boy.
As evidenced by your boyfriend
and his fear of hamsters.
If I were you,
I'd go for Fables number one.
The artwork
is sophisticated,
it's intelligently written,
and it doesn't objectify
or stereotype women.
Ooh, Thor!
He's hot.
Yeah, he kind of is.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
And we're blending,
and we're blending,
and we're done.
I know Mr. Data
isn't supposed to smile,
but here it comes.
WOLOWITZ:
Come on, guys.
Let's do this.
Yeah, I'm sweating
my bald cap off.
So what's our first
pose going to be?
I say we begin with a classic
Star Trek fight scene.
I'll set the timer.
Sheldon,
how is that a fight pose?
Mr. Data's weapon is his mind.
I'm wielding it.
(shutter clicks)
Phasers on the Borg!
Charlie's Angels.
(shutter clicks)
Okay, what's next?
Now let's do
some sexy glamour shots.
I'll set the mood.
(beat-boxing):
Oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz...
oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz,
oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz...
oontz, oontz, oontz,
oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz.
Yeah, nice one.
Oontz, oontz, oontz.
That's right.
(car door slams)
(engine revving)
Oh, my God.
Leonard,
someone's stealing your car!
What? Hey, hey!
Come back here!
Stop!
Stealing is against the law!
I don't believe this.
Son of a bitch.
I'll call 911.
Wha...
Oh, no, my phone is
in my other pants.
Oh, so is mine.
Mine, too.
Anybody got any ideas?
Nope.
The only thing left to
do now is assign blame.
Nice going.
What kind of a person steals
another person's car
in broad daylight?
What kind of person
leaves his keys in the car?
I thought we agreed this was
all Koothrappali's fault.
You're right.
Nice going.
Car.
(car approaches)
What is wrong with people?
Why don't they stop?
Maybe we're better off.
What if we were to get in a car
with a crazy person?
Look at us, Sheldon.
We're the crazy people.
Well, perhaps we should
hold up a sign
that assures passing motorists
of our mental competence.
Good idea.
Why don't you
get started on that?
Come on,
let's just start walking.
There's got to be a gas station
or something nearby.
What, you think just
because you're wearing
a captain's uniform,
you're in charge?
Yes.
All right.
Hmm, okay, I'm done.
How did you guys
finish so fast?
I don't know,
there were a lot of pictures,
and one page only had
the word "brakkadoom!"
Yeah, well,
I have street smarts.
So, what'd you guys think?
Well, there was a lot of action,
Mmm.
and the story moved along
at a brisk pace.
It was, overall...
what's the word I'm looking for?
Stupid?
So stupid.
I don't know how
Leonard can get
so caught up in this.
It's crazy; they spend hours
arguing about things
that don't even exist.
What a waste of time.
I know.
A hammer so heavy that no
one else can pick it up?
(chuckles)
I don't think it's heavy.
It's some sort of magic,
so only Thor can lift it.
That makes even less
sense, I mean...
No, no, no, it doesn't.
Thor is a god.
The hammer is his;
only he can use it.
It's like Sheldon
and his toothbrush.
Or his thin, beckoning lips.
Okay, hang on, what if
Thor's hand is on the hammer?
I mean, if he's touching it
with his god magic,
does that mean I could lift it?
No.
Yes.
Well, which is it?
Maybe we missed something.
Let's read it again.
Okay.
Yeah.
(sighs)
You want some tea?
Good idea.
I'll help you.
Wait, I thought we were reading.
We are.
We're just, uh,
giving you a head start.
I wish my mom was here.
We could all hang out
in her shadow.
Wool pants in the desert.
I feel like I've got
poached testicles.
Oh, you poor thing;
you're sweating.
That's so much worse than
having your car stolen.
Insurance is gonna buy you
a new car.
It's not gonna
de-funk my junk.
Gentlemen,
a little less bellyaching.
We're Starfleet officers
and a member
of the Borg Collective.
Please, Sheldon,
I am so not in the mood.
Leonard,
all our lives we have dreamed
of finding ourselves
inside one of
the fantasy worlds we love.
And look at us.
At this moment, we are, in fact,
a Star Trek landing party
stranded in an alien
and unforgiving environment,
relying only on our wits,
our fortitude
(car approaches)
and our moxie.
As long as we have
those things,
nothing can stop...
MAN: Nerds!
I hate this planet.
It says right here
on the hammer,
"Whoever holds this hammer,
if he be worthy,
shall possess
the power of Thor."
Hold on,
who decides who's worthy?
Does the hammer decide?
Yes!
No!
It can't decide.
It's a hammer.
You said it's a magic hammer.
Yeah, it can't make decisions.
If Harry Potter's wand
can make decisions,
why can't Thor's hammer?
Okay, if you're going to start
comparing wands and hammers,
I can't even take you seriously.
Hello.
Uh, four glasses
of water, please.
Anything for you guys?
Can I use your phone?
Our car got stolen.
Why don't you ask Scotty
to beam you up?
(laughter)
Scotty was on the
original series,
and we're Next Generation.
So... joke's on you.
We're not with him.
You can't pick something up
in outer space.
In space, there is no up.
Oh, yeah? Then how does
the sun come "up" every day?
Hard to argue with those kind
of street smarts.
Leonard and Sheldon have boxes
of comics across the hall.
Why don't we go look at those?
Oh, great! Yes!
And then you will see.
I am not wrong, because
if we were in outer space,
then anyone
could pick up the hammer
because it would be
floating around
in a weightless environment.
Yeah, that's right, the
slow reader used science.
Suck on that.
Was there anything
valuable in the car?
Our clothes,
our wallets, phones.
And about $300 worth of makeup,
so this thief could look like
anyone right now.
Makeup?
Sure.
Uh, we're going to the Comic-Con
in Bakersfield.
They have a big costume contest.
It's cooler than it sounds.
I don't know,
sounds pretty cool.
I-It is.
It's not just comic books.
They've got
action figures, toys,
a Tron-themed dance party...
Okay, he gets how cool it is.
I think I have all I need here.
You guys need me
to call someone?
I'm guessing your moms?
Thanks,
but we've got it covered.
Okay,
I just talked to my mom.
She arranged for us
to get a rental car.
Great.
We can still make it
to Comic-Con.
Are you kidding me?
After all we've been through,
I just want to go home.
Don't be like that.
Come on, Howard,
talk to him.
I'm with Leonard.
I'm done.
Fine, then I guess
it's two against two.
How do we decide?
Actually,
it's three against one.
What?!
What about the mission?
You said we were
a real-life landing party.
Yeah, well, we're not.
We're an imaginary landing party
who had real-life garbage
thrown at us
by real-life strangers
who think we're idiots.
And to tell you the truth,
I'm starting to feel like one.
I want to go home now.
Okay.
Did we at least rent the car
from Enterprise?
Get it? Enterprise?
Screw you. That's funny.
Well, what if the
Hulk picked up Thor
while Thor is
holding the hammer?
Yeah?
Then by the transitive property
of picking things up,
Hulk picked up the hammer.
No.
Hulk picked up Thor,
Thor picked up the hammer.
Okay, hang on.
If I go to a bar
and pick up a guy,
and he picks up a girl,
and then we all leave together,
did I pick up the girl?
Did that ever happen?
Hey, are we talking about me
or are we talking about Thor?
Well, I say that's the last time
we ever go outside.
AMY:
Look, right here.
Red Hulk is picking
up Thor's hammer
'cause Thor's touching it.
PENNY: No, it's because
they're in space.
BERNADETTE: He's really
just touching the strap.
AMY: The strap is part
of the hammer!
PENNY:
No, it's not!
Are they actually arguing
about comic books?
No, that can't be right.
Maybe "Thor's Hammer"
is a new color of nail polish.
BERNADETTE:
Then Red Hulk must be worthy.
PENNY: How could
Red Hulk be worthy?
BERNADETTE:
You don't know his life!
There's only one
logical explanation.
Somewhere in the desert
we crossed
into an alternate dimension...
where the women in our lives
can finally appreciate
great literature.
If it's an
alternate dimension...
sounds like a job
for a landing party.
Captain,
what are your orders?
I say we investigate.
Wait.
They might be hostile.
Fine, but set them to stun.
If we vaporize Penny,
I'll never find a girlfriend
that pretty again.
SHELDON'S VOICE:
Fun fact:
President Eisenhower signed
the Federal Aid Highway Act
from his hospital room.
Wow, that is interesting.
You learn something new
every day.
SHELDON'S VOICE: Say, can you
name the four state capitols
that are not served
by the interstate system?
Ooh, another quiz.
Yes!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==