Previously on "The Originals"...
This town
was my home once.
Our community is under attack.
They're declaring war on us.
I die, all because
of your vow,
always and forever.
If you have come here
seeking revenge, don't...
Oh, I'll have
my revenge.
I'm Jackson.
You're the wolf
who's been watching me.
Jackson: Marcel had us
cursed by a witch.
You and I are gonna
have a little chat.
You're my family.
Rebekah: My brother
expects my loyalty
as he has
for 1,000 years.
Marcel: Klaus will never
stop trying to control you.
All his life,
there's only ever been
one man he has
truly feared...
My father Mikael.
All we need
is a witch
who can help us
find him.
That's how I'm going
to have my revenge,
by showing you
her betrayal.
It was my idea
to summon Mikael.
Uhhaah!
Both of you, run as far
and as fast as you can.
[Music]
Well, this is a first...
Werewolves, vampires,
witches, and dirty cops,
all happy as clams
and drunk as stoats.
You got to love
this city.
To a new era
of collaboration
in the face
of prohibition.
To your docks,
their booze,
and our theaters
to hide it under.
You're welcome, boys.
Now I shall have
to think of a way
to thank you
personally
in a manner befitting
a werewolf queen.
Catch you
on the dance floor.
Who would have
thought it possible...
The unification
of New Orleans?
We did it, brother.
Oh, certainly, we worked
together, Niklaus,
but this vision...
This was all you.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/
Camille...
Please.
Why did you call me?
Have you found a way
to help my uncle?
I can try, but first,
I need your help.
I don't have time
for games, Elijah.
The hex on him is getting worse
by the day.
My brother has
a mystical torture device
buried in his chest,
and the mother of his child
is inexplicably missing.
So, I can assure you,
I have no time
to play any games,
either.
What do you
need me to do?
Cami: The dagger the witch
gave me is inside of him?
And every second
it remains
causes Niklaus
untold suffering.
Who stabbed him?
I did,
and now I intend
to remove it.
You might want
to take a step back.
Why am I here?
Because of all the people
that could be here,
you're probably the only one he
wouldn't immediately slaughter.
Mm...
Also, he speaks of you
with what is
a rare degree...
For him, at least...
Of respect.
I can see you challenge him
to see himself and others
in a new light...
Ugh...
Ahh...
A wonderful skill that I shall
be counting on very shortly.
You see, Niklaus
will be weak as he recovers.
So watch over him and
feed him if you would
but slowly, please,
and from your wrist.
Don't you guys have bags
of blood in storage?
We do, but your blood
is laced with vervain.
So it will burn him.
He'll ingest it slower.
Perhaps you could use
the time constructively,
persuade him not to
murder his baby sister.
Niklaus...
It was not my desire
to bring you pain,
but I will not
see you hurt Rebekah.
Now, I fear Sabine
may be making
a final move against us.
I intend to find her
and to end this.
Elijah...
You will pay
for this.
Sabine: So what's
this, payback?
Look. I'm sorry
I tricked you.
I wasn't after you.
Eve: What, and we were
just collateral damage?
You almost burned her
and Jackson alive
in that plantation fire.
[Gunshot]
Careful, Sabine,
or Celeste or whatever
you like to call yourself.
Sudden moves make me
jumpy and homicidal.
What, you're gonna
kill me, honey?
No. I know better.
See, I know
all about you.
I know that you like
to off yourself
and then jump into
other people's bodies.
Well, that's not
gonna happen here.
I know I can't kill you,
but try hexing me,
and my friend Eve here
will kneecap you.
Go for her, and then, well,
I'll really make it hurt.
So what do you want?
Back in the nineties,
you inhabited
a witch named
Brynne Deveraux,
remember?
Marcel had her, you,
put a curse on a lot
of werewolves
so they'd only turn
human on a full moon.
I see.
Yes. That was me.
Let me guess.
You want revenge.
I want you
to undo the curse.
Wow, things I never
thought I'd be doing...
Feeding a vampire.
My 16-year-old self
would think
I'm really cool
right now.
Mm.
Ah! Slow down.
Ok. Doesn't
the vervain burn?
Ah... ah...
As you may have yet
to realize, Cami,
the line between
what brings us pain
and what sustains us
is far thinner
than one imagines.
You talking about
my blood or your need
to hunt down the people
you love most?
I'm too weak for one
of your talks right now.
She's your sister.
How can you hate her?
Because she has done
what no one else
has managed to do to
me for 1,000 years...
Rip my heart out.
[Music]
Look at these two
pretending to be apart
while so clearly
a pair.
Niklaus, not now.
Why must you cause...
[Clinking]
[Music stops]
I'd like to take
this opportunity
to draw attention
to two people
who have been sneaking around
behind my back together.
As we move into a new era,
we require more
progressive attitudes to match.
So... to my loving sister
and my right-hand man
and best friend Marcel,
may they find joy
in each other.
Enough talk. Music.
[Music]
Over the years,
I've thwarted your loves
simply to protect you.
I knew if we had
to run again,
your heart
would be broken,
but we don't have
to run anymore.
We've found a home.
[Kiss]
Be happy, my sister.
I'd let
my guard down
and given in
to happiness,
more fool, I.
Klaus, voice-over: Turns out,
they'd already betrayed me...
And brought to town
the one thing
I'd been running from
for centuries...
My father.
Oh.
Yes. Oh.
So you're consumed by revenge
you'll never achieve.
Elijah implied
Rebekah and Marcel
could be anywhere
in the world by now.
Oh, I'm not so sure
about that.
Rebekah: Can you believe
we're sitting out here
in the open
bold as brass?
No. Ah, it feels
like heaven.
You know, it's been
over 6 months
since Genevieve summoned
my father, and nothing.
Her spell
must have failed.
Hey, if so,
we dodged a bullet.
Right.
I am off to speak
at the women's temperance
society meeting
to make sure the wives
of this city
urge their husbands
not to drink.
Aren't you all in
the booze biz now?
Yes, but the more
one tells you
you can't have something,
the more you crave it
at all costs.
Ha ha ha!
He'll chase us
to the ends of the earth,
and he'll find us.
No one can hide
forever,
especially not from
an angry Mikaelson.
Then we go through
with the plan.
There's only one way
that we'll truly be able
to hide from Klaus
forever.
They'll need
a cloaking spell,
and for that,
they'll need a witch.
Davina
is our one shot.
If we go back
and get her...
It's a suicide
mission.
It's our only hope.
We resurrect her,
take her with us,
and get out of town.
Then she can hide us
from Klaus
so he'll never
find us.
We don't even know the right witch
to kill to bring her back.
Then we'll
kill them all.
Just kill the 3 witches
that brought
the mighty Klaus Mikaelson
to his knees, no big deal.
Look. Unless you want
to spend eternity
looking over
your shoulder,
there's only one thing
that we can do.
There's only one
place they can go...
Home.
[Chanting in foreign language]
[Footsteps]
When order is restored,
your kind won't
be allowed in here.
Well, fortunately, that
day has not yet come.
I need to find
Sabine.
I believe she's
taken someone
very important
to me.
And you thought
I'd help you?
Sabine is one of us,
committed to the rise
of the witches.
The only thing Sabine
is committed to
is the destruction
of my family.
And that would be
a bad thing why?
Like your mother,
my mother
was also a witch,
a very
powerful witch.
In fact, because
of my family,
her power now flows
through your veins.
Now, once Sabine
manipulates
those around her,
she will do
what she has
always done.
She will jump
into another body
and disappear,
leaving your witches
powerless.
No. She has
the faith.
She will see
our power restored.
There's a way of
guaranteeing this.
I'll also secure
the safety
of yourself
and your kind.
Here. This is from
my mother's grimoire.
Celeste used
a similar spell
to body jump.
If what Sabine says
is true,
when she sacrifices
herself,
all of her power
will flow
back into the earth.
However,
if she has lied
and tries to take
another body,
this spell
will deliver her
to a very different
destination.
Now please
locate Sabine.
Rebekah:
Papa Tunde is dead.
That leaves Sabine,
Bastianna,
and Genevieve.
We want to kill
them all,
and as soon
as Davina rises,
we take her with us.
Look. We have
one shot at this,
and I know our
chances of success
are sweet bugger all,
but we've got to do it.
So please, one stray
dog to another,
help us.
Not many go up against
those odds
and live to tell
the story.
Have you?
I'm still standing
here, aren't I?
I've gone up against
the worst of them all.
You're a lucky man.
Men search the world over
for a woman like her.
Well, she's taken,
friend.
Oh, I can see that.
It's just that she
reminds me so much
of my departed wife
as a girl.
See, I've been traveling
for such a long time
that it's a blessing
to see a familiar soul
so far from home.
I'm sorry
for your loss.
Here's to old faces
in new places.
I've been in New Orleans
for a day,
and I find it to be
quite surprising.
Had I known of its charm
and fascinating denizens,
I would have come
ages ago.
Don't supposed
I have to thank you
for extending
this invitation.
Who are
oh, you're
a smart man.
I think you know.
I'm an intelligent
man myself,
so have a seat.
Let me tell you
what I learned
about you this afternoon,
Marcel Gerard.
You chafe under the control
of my son Niklaus
and would do just about
anything to get rid if him,
even call the one man
on this earth
who hates him
more than you do,
but I couldn't understand
what you hoped to gain...
Rule of this city?
Well, as I said,
New Orleans has its charms,
but to call me...
The one they call
the destroyer,
the one who's
burnt cities
far more charming
to the ground
in pursuit
of his children...
But now I see.
You did it for love,
the love of my daughter.
Don't you dare
touch her.
Mm, so I'm going
to make you a promise.
I won't hurt Rebekah...
Truth be told, she was
always my favorite...
And this city,
you can have it,
but first,
you must tell me
where to find my son.
Uh...
You're
still weak.
I'm still hungry.
There's a fresh
blood supply
in the kitchen.
You won't make it
that far.
So be a good little boy
and get back into bed.
If I had a quid
for every time
a woman has tried
that line on me...
You'd have, like,
no money.
I beg to differ.
Some women
actually find me
quite charming.
Uh! Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Sleeping with
the enemy, I see.
I'm the ally now,
darling.
Well, indeed.
Klaus: Oh, and as a
gesture of goodwill
from our old enemy,
tickets to
tonight's opera...
"Les huguenots."
They have a soprano
to die for.
I'll introduce you
if you promise not to eat her.
Oh, Lana,
a good soprano
is never dinner.
Tell Rebekah
to bring Marcel.
Feel free
to tell her now,
big brother.
I have some business
I need to discuss
with our new ally.
Why am I not surprised
you like opera?
I always had a
particular soft spot
for "les huguenots."
I like the story.
It was a tale
of forbidden love,
a "Romeo and Juliet"
of sorts.
On the day
they are to marry,
family and
long-festering hatred
intervene.
Thousands are massacred.
A father even kills
his own child
in the final act.
I can almost
appreciate the irony.
Here.
It's herbs
ground into paste.
It'll act as a conduit
for the spell.
On the next
full moon,
your people
become human.
Feed it to them, the
curse will be broken.
Great way to poison us
all at once.
Look. I know you
have no reason
to trust me,
but, Hayley,
I actually like you.
I was you,
caring for Elijah
when he cared more
for his brother,
and I ended up dead.
So did a lot
of others.
This, call it a chance
for me to give you
what I was too in love
to give myself.
It's a chance
to free yourself
from The Originals.
You believe her?
[Growls]
Elijah: Whatever she's
promised you, it's a lie.
Elijah, it's ok.
I'm ok.
She cannot
be trusted.
She's the only one
that can help my pack.
Do you have any idea
what she has done
to our family?
I know you want revenge,
and come the next full moon,
when I'm sure her cure
works, she's all yours.
Are you suggesting
that we hold her,
her, captive
for an entire month?
It would take
an army.
And I've got one.
[Howls]
[Distant howling]
So help me
or get out of my way.
You tricked her.
It's no trick.
You're holding the cure for
Hayley's clan in your hand.
If her wolves take that elixir,
the curse is no more.
They're free.
You condemned her people
to decades of agony,
and now you just
break the curse
without so much
as a whimper.
Why?
Because it's the best thing
I could do for her
and it's the worst
possible thing
I could do to you.
What are you saying?
That, no matter
what happens now,
you've lost her.
You destroy that jar,
you kill me,
Hayley will hate you
for snatching
her family from her.
Now, if you
give her the jar,
we both know that
she'll leave you
in the end to be
with them,
and I know that as long
as she's alive
and happy and
fulfilled in ways
that you can't
even imagine,
then I get
my revenge.
So you decide...
Give her everything
she ever wanted
and lose her
or deny it, see
what happens then.
Where's the third one...
Sabine?
I asked to meet
with all 3 of you.
Our meeting you at all
is a courtesy
for your being a friend
to witches in the past,
but courtesy
has its limits.
Now, you said you
had information
of interest to us.
Rebekah and Marcel
are back.
They came for Davina,
and they think
that they can get her if
they kill all 3 of you.
Now look.
I can lead you
straight to them,
but there's something
I want in return.
And what's that?
Your life.
[Chanting]
Follow me, and I'll turn
you both into ash.
Forget her.
We'll get her later.
Marcel, all we have is
the element of surprise,
and we have lost it.
If we don't
leave now,
there will be
no one to save us.
I already
failed Davina once.
I'm not leaving
her behind.
Not sure that helps.
Not sure it doesn't.
You want to self-medicate
your self-pity, fine.
Better scotch than my blood,
no matter what Elijah says.
Don't speak to me
of Elijah.
He loves you.
Yes.
He does,
and he proves it
time and again,
even when my father
enlisted him
to kill me.
"Uguenots".
Saw it in venice,
marvelous production.
You.
It's all right, son.
I just want to talk.
You mercilessly
hunt us for centuries.
You laid waste
to half of Europe.
Now you simply
wish to talk?
It was your bastard
brother I hunted,
not you, never you.
You're my blood,
one that I'd be
proud to call son.
So I came here
to give you a chance
to help me put down
that whelp for good.
Waah! Aah!
Do you really
not know me?
Do you think
I could or would
believe in anything
that you say?
If you honestly believe
that I would betray
my own brother
for you,
you're a fool
without equal.
I'll forgive you your
sentimental affections
for the thing
you call brother,
but you need to realize,
as I did when I learned
his mother had lain
with a beast to beget him,
Niklaus
is an abomination.
You do not talk
to abominations.
You do not reason with them.
Do not try to change them.
You erase them.
So, yes, I am asking you
to help me kill
your brother.
You keep saying kill,
but you're immortal.
You can't be killed.
Oh, but we can, luv,
and my father
was the only one
with the means
to do it...
A white oak stake
fashioned by my father
to take from us
the very thing
he forced
upon us all...
Our immortality.
Stand with me
or fall with him.
Choose, son.
I will always...
Choose him.
Fine.
Klaus, voice-over: Elijah
has always carried guilt
for that night for not
stopping our father.
I told him not
to blame himself.
When your father
wants to kill you,
he wants
to kill you,
nothing you can do
about it.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Oh, I hate to be
a know-it-all.
My sister
and her lover
have been spotted
in town.
So story time endeth
here, I'm afraid.
What is that?
A white oak stake,
my own special version,
and, unlike my father's,
this one
cannot be destroyed.
What are you doing?
Well, if you
have to ask,
you obviously haven't
been paying attention.
I'm going to kill
my sister,
but first, I needed
some sustenance
with a little less
vervain in it,
no offense.
When Davina showed me
all you did to me,
all you took from me,
I wanted to kill you.
I even thought about
burying that blade in you
like the witches
asked me to, but I didn't.
I stopped. I thought.
I weighed the good
I see in you
versus the horrible things
I know you've done,
and I realized
if I hurt you,
I'd be filled
with a terrible regret.
You will, too,
if you hurt your sister,
your sister, Klaus.
As a person who has
lost a sibling,
who has felt that pain,
you won't survive
if you're the one
who kills her.
I'll tell you
what I almost
didn't survive,
luv...
My sister bringing
the most vile creature
ever to have
walked the earth
down upon me.
Yes, your father,
but by hunting Rebekah
and Marcel down
to the ends of the earth,
by terrorizing them the way
you yourself were terrorized...
Don't become
your father.
I've been called
every shade of monster,
but that's new.
My father?
Mikael
was the monster
monsters
were afraid of.
Come.
Let me show you.
You came back.
I'll always
come back.
Take it.
It will work.
Eve and I will round up as many
of our people as we can.
Come full moon, I can
finally free my family.
Hayley...
I wonder if they
have any idea
how lucky they are
to have you.
Mm.
That was touching,
such a chaste,
little kiss.
The Elijah I knew
was never so meek.
Well, the Celeste I knew
was never so cruel.
What is it that you want?
What's your endgame?
Oh, this game
never ends, Elijah.
We're both immortal,
you know.
Then what's the point
if you can't possibly win?
But I have.
You just
lost the girl,
the girl you never
made a move on
because you were
so desperate
to save your family,
and now your family
lies in ruins.
My family, despite
all that you have done,
will heal in time.
If you had
the time, maybe,
but you really think
Rebekah ran far
and fast from here?
I bet she didn't.
She's long gone.
Is she?
She's with Marcel.
Now, Marcel
loves Davina.
Davina is dead, but
she could come back
under the right
circumstances.
You wouldn't dare.
If you hadn't been
so worried about Hayley,
you might have
figured it out sooner,
but you know who did
have the time
to think about it?
Your brother.
I wonder
what he'll do.
Heh. Do it.
You know
your city's history,
that night in 1919
when the opera house
burned down
on this very spot?
That was my father
at his worst.
Klaus: Well, this is
off to a bad start.
Your first big date
together in public
after I gave you
my blessing,
and he stood you up.
Something must
have delayed him.
Or, now that
your elicit affair
is out in the open,
he finds
the whole relationship
a tad lackluster
and has run off to
havana with a showgirl.
Don't be such a toerag.
I'm going to check the lobby.
See if you can't
find our brother
while you're there.
The curtain
is about to go up.
I would advise against
trying to flee, boy.
I can drive this
into your heart
before you
can even think
of getting
to your feet,
and I don't want you
to die... yet.
Father...
"Father"? Ha ha!
Still clinging
to that word
after all
these years,
a bastard desperate
for a daddy?
I wonder if your
real father would be
as embarrassed
as I was of you
before I discovered
you were not mine.
Most likely.
Oh, oh. Uh-uh.
Easy now, boy.
Don't worry.
Death will come,
but we need to have
a little chat
before you
shuffle off
your immortal coil.
Any words we have
for each other
have been spoken
long ago,
but know this.
I am no longer
the animal
begging for scraps
of your affection.
I will die knowing
my hatred for you was just.
I will fall proud of all
I have achieved here.
So... Mikael...
If you're going
to kill me,
then get on with it.
Au contraire,
Niklaus.
Some things
remain unsaid.
For instance,
you were right
to be proud of your
achievement here.
As I walked the streets,
your name was spoken of
in reverent tones
by the city's finest.
So after I kill you,
I will remain here
in New Orleans
until every last person
who remembers you
is dead.
The deeds
of the mighty Klaus
will be remembered
by no one...
And you, boy,
will simply
never have existed.
[Orchestra tuning]
Ah. The grand show.
Oh, I made
some alterations
in your honor.
You'll love it.
[Baton taps]
Klaus, voice-over:
And what a show it was.
Mikael compelled the audience
to watch it all,
applaud as if it were
the drollest of comedies
and then to leave
celebrating
a terrific night
at the opera.
I tried to save
Marcel.
[Spike clatters]
My father
had other ideas.
Rebekah attempted
to intervene.
Yaah!
[Applause]
All these years,
I actually believed
she was trying
to save me...
Klaus: Agh!
[Laughter and applause]
But then big brother
swooped in...
There's no
helping Marcel.
Just when we thought
all was lost.
We must run.
Klaus, voice-over:
And so I ran,
beaten like the dog
my father
believed me to be...
Agh!
Klaus, voice-over:
And as we fled for our lives,
he burnt it all to the ground
and with it, he assumed, Marcel.
I lived, but all
that we had built died,
as did the last shred
of me that felt human.
That is what my father
took from me that night.
I assure you,
Camille,
I will not terrorize
my sister and her lover
for centuries.
Nor will I humiliate and
torment or dehumanize them.
No, none of that.
I will simply
and quickly end them.
Klaus, wait.
Now, you didn't have
to bite me to get me here.
I wanted front-row seats
to this show.
And what show
would that be?
The one where you see
your "always
and forever" pact
come crashing down
around you.
It's a myth, Elijah,
a myth I died for.
And yet here
you stand alive...
For now.
Is that a threat?
Oh, there's always
another pretty,
young body
for me to jump into.
From now on,
every time you feel
a connection to a woman,
you'll be forced
to wonder
if it's me.
You'll trust no one
and spend the rest
of eternity alone.
Ha ha ha!
I'm afraid
you're trapped.
Boundary spell.
The Originals can enter,
but they can't leave.
You wouldn't.
I would, and I did.
I got you, D.
I got you.
It's a trap.
Run. Get Davina
out of here.
I'm not leaving
you behind.
You must.
I will not
leave you behind.
I swear I will
join you.
Go. Get Davina
someplace safe.
Sabine: Don't worry.
It's a lunar spell.
You'll be free by
the next moonrise.
My guess is,
your sister won't
last that long.
Ah, while
this body has been
a hell of a lot of fun,
I do think it's time
I find someone else
to play in, don't you?
[Coughing]
[Coughing stops]
You were right.
[Speaking
foreign language]
[Gasps]
Hello, Celeste.
How is this
possible?
Monique Deveraux and I
had a little wager
regarding your ability
to keep a promise.
It appears I won.
You were so consumed
with my downfall,
that you lost the trust
of one of your own.
Non.
Mon cheri, non.
Tout est possible.
Ce n'est pas fini.
Aah!
Desole.
[Moaning]
Davina, you're ok.
You're safe now.
You hear me? You're safe.
I won't let anyone
hurt you, ok?
Rebekah!
Cherish the breath
in your lungs!
It'll be your last.
The final act of
le grand guignol is upon us!
Where are my players?
Enough running, children!
Step out of the shadows
so we can finish
this tale of sorrows.
He's coming.
All right.
Come on, sister.
Marcel.
He's gone,
sister.
No. No.
Elijah: Both of you
must flee the city.
I'll hold him off,
Niklaus.
No.
We fight him
together.
Elijah:
We cannot fight him.
All we can do is do
what we've done.
We deceive him.
We lead him astray.
Now, I can do that
as well as anyone.
You take her
far away from here.
I'll follow you.
No, Elijah. You can't.
You can't, Elijah.
This is just...
This is my fault.
No. This is my fault,
Rebekah.
I am so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Marcel...
[Alarm bell ringing]
I thought we'd found
a home here.
Niklaus, please.
Sister, come.
You must leave. Go.
Leave!
Elijah?
What are you
doing here?
Rebekah,
you should be
on the other side
of the world by now.
You and I both know that
wouldn't have been far enough.
Get away from her!
She's mine.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.Addic7ed.Com/