In any ecosystem,
you'll find a delicate balance
between predator and prey.
Some wellknown predators
include Panthera leo,
Ursus arctos,
and star of the 1987 film Predator,
Predator.
Now, examples of prey
include Oryctolagus cuniculus,
Gallus gallus domesticus,
and weighing in at
58 pounds soaking wet,
Diminutive homo novus...
Curiously, a close relative
of Gallus gallus domesticus.
Cooper.
Your stop.
Would you mind dropping
me off closer to my house?
You know I'm not allowed to do that.
What if I did your taxes?
Sorry, kiddo.
I could've gotten you a nice refund.
The perilous journey
from the bus stop to my front door
was 97.5 meters.
FYI, insisting on
using the metric system
in East Texas is another reason
I was hunted by predators.
Homo novus needs a Yoohoo.
Jiujitsu?
I've decided to learn selfdefense.
- Why?
- I'm quite small,
and will be for several years,
maybe even more if I'm a late bloomer.
Your dad's big, maybe
you'll take after him.
We both like my mom.
I think that's where
the similarities end.
You know, one of the books mentioned
a Vietnamese martial art.
Vovinam. I'm a blue belt.
- Wow.
- Don't be impressed.
It's what you get when
your mom buys the uniform.
Do you remember any of it?
I don't even know where the belt is.
The book says jiujitsu
is based on using your attacker's
momentum against them.
It's just physics. Come at me.
Like, run at you?
Well, I'm new to this, so
maybe just walk quickly.
And what happens when I get to you?
I'll use your inertia to take you down.
Okay.
And when does inertia take me down?
Any second.
I don't understand.
I'm using physics.
This leg lock is called
an Outside Ashi Garami.
What happens next?
That depends, is this your foot or mine?
Cooper. Your stop.
I bowled a new high score last night.
Nice.
- I got two turkeys.
- What's a turkey?
It's three strikes in a row.
Why do they call it a turkey?
Well, when they first invented bowling,
they used to just throw
frozen turkeys at the pins.
Eventually, they switched to balls
to cut down on the smell.
Why you lying to her?
I find it keeps my mind sharp.
Sheldon, breakfast!
Be right there!
Sheldon!
Coming!
Hello.
Shelly, you all right?
Yes. I must be a little sore
from doing jiujitsu with Tam yesterday.
Why were you doing jiujitsu?
We're boys. Roughhousing is what we do.
- What was that?
- What was what?
That sound.
What sound?
What's all this?
An extra layer of protection.
Protection from what?
Sweetie, is someone bothering you?
- Yes.
- Who is it?
I'd rather not talk about it.
No, I want a name right now.
Mary.
Have you been hurting him?
Only with my words.
Tell me who it is, Shelly.
Mary, slow down.
Don't tell me to slow down.
- Someone is bullying him.
- Okay.
Okay.
Sheldon, you can't go to
school wearing all that.
Go to your room and take it off.
Yes, sir.
You go with him.
But my cereal's gonna get soggy.
Go.
I'd like one nice morning.
Why aren't you more upset about this?
I am. I just think we
should proceed with caution.
- Someone is hurting our son.
- I understand.
But handling bullies is tricky. It...
It's easy to make things worse.
And what makes you the expert?
Honey, I was a bully.
He's right.
You get involved in
this in the wrong way,
and they'll take it out on Sheldon.
Well, I'm sorry, but
I can't just stand by.
Georgie, I need to talk
to you, and wake up,
you're gonna be late.
Got it covered. I slept in my clothes.
Lord. Look, somebody has
been picking on your brother.
You know anything about it?
No.
You better not be covering for anybody.
I'm not. Most kids at school ignore him,
and the girls all think he's cute.
It's kind of annoying.
Well, I need you to look after him.
Why?
Because I'm your mother,
and I'm asking you nicely.
What if I don't want to?
I don't care, you're doing it.
How was that nice?
So there I was flying above the city,
but when I woke up, I couldn't fly.
That's like the dream you had
where you were dating Madonna,
but when you woke up, you weren't.
Exactly.
You ever have the ones where
your teeth are falling out?
Better my teeth than my hair, but...
- Sheldon?
- Over here.
- What are you doing?
- Hiding.
From who?
Is Billy the one giving you trouble?
No.
His dad?
No...
No.
She's a demon.
The little Sparks girl?
You're kidding. She seems so sweet.
He says she slaps him
around, takes his lunch money.
She even put a tadpole down his shirt.
Poor kid, he tucks in those shirts.
- She looks harmless.
- She's cute.
So she probably gets away with stuff.
I'm like that.
I wonder if stray cats
poop in that sandbox.
George.
You need to talk to her parents.
Me? Why me?
Because you're more
intimidating than me.
That's rich.
Hey, Billy.
Hello, Missy's dad.
- Is your father home?
- Yes.
Could you get him for me?
Happy to.
Dad, it's Missy's dad!
He's also Sheldon's dad!
Well, howdy, neighbor.
Hey, Herschel.
What brings you by? Chickens too loud?
- Nah, they been fine.
- Good, good.
Fried up the noisy one last week.
That shut him up.
Anyway, how can I help?
Well...
It's come to my attention that...
Sheldon's run into a bit of
trouble with your daughter.
What kind of trouble?
He says she been beating on him.
- My Bobbi?
- Yeah.
This one? The sixyearold?
Bobbi, get over here!
You realize I've taken
dumps bigger than this kid.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hey, babydoll,
Mr. Cooper says that you've
been picking on Sheldon.
- Now, is that true?
- No, Daddy.
Are you sure?
Okay, go wash up for dinner.
I don't know what to tell you, George.
I mean, is it, is it possible
your son has a little crush on her?
I don't think he's wired that way.
Are you saying that he's a...
No, no, I'm saying he's a bookworm.
Unless she's math or a
dictionary, he ain't interested.
Yeah.
Thanks for hearin' me out.
Your wife sent you
over here, didn't she?
I don't want to talk about it.
I bet she did!
Not talkin' about it!
Tell her I said hi!
How'd it go?
Good. Yeah.
I handled it.
Thank the Lord.
Yeah. Me and the Lord.
Team effort.
Hello, Bobbi.
You told on me.
Well, actually, my brother
figured it out, so, technically,
I would argue that I didn't.
Doesn't matter.
I should let you know,
I've read a book on jiujitsu.
And I'm prepared to throw it at you.
Shelly, it's just Bactine.
Aah!
I didn't even put it on you yet.
You want to tell me what happened?
Bobbi Sparks came into the garage...
And she attacked you?
Not exactly. I tried
to use jiujitsu on her,
but I tripped and fell.
Aw, baby. I'm so sorry you're
havin' to deal with this.
It's okay.
German philosopher
Friedrich Nietzsche said,
"That which does not kill
us makes us stronger."
And do you feel stronger?
No.
How are the knees?
Better, thank you.
Good.
And regarding this jiujitsu
stuff, you should know
that a man's not supposed
to raise his hand to a woman.
I won't. I don't
want to hurt myself again.
Did you ever have a bully
when you were growing up?
Have you met your grandma?
I thought you said you
handled it next door.
I did say that.
Where you goin'?
To handle it.
Should've been you in the first place.
What?
Good luck!
Way to go, Scooby! That's my newshound!
Missy, I could really use your help.
With what?
I'm being bullied by Bobbi Sparks.
Hilarious. Go on.
Madame Doo!
That's me!
Mom says a man should never
raise his hand to a woman.
But I believe I've found a loophole.
You're a woman, so
you're allowed to hit her
as much as you want.
Why would I do that?
Because I'm willing to pay you.
How much?
My life savings, four dollars.
That's a good start.
Now, let's talk TV privileges.
What do you want?
Complete control every
afternoon for two months.
That's when Professor Proton is on.
I know. Sucks for you.
I'm on fire!
Hello, Brenda.
Hey, Mary.
How many lanes you need?
Actually, I'm here to talk to you.
Seems that our kids are
havin' a little problem.
Yeah. Herschel told me.
Good, good.
So, I was wondering what
you're plannin' to do about it,
'cause the situation doesn't
seem to be gettin' any better.
Well, if you haven't noticed,
I'm at work right now.
I see that.
But you understand
that your daughter's
being abusive to my son.
Well, maybe your son
needs to grow a pair.
And in due time, he will.
But right now, I expect you
to teach your children how to behave.
Connie Tucker to the front desk, please.
Connie Tucker.
Why are you calling her?
You say my daughter's
harassing your son.
Well, her daughter's harassing me.
Hey, Mary.
- What are you doin' here?
- Well,
I was hopin' to have a rational
conversation about Shelly,
but there's only one
person being rational.
And it ain't you.
Could you excuse us for just a minute?
Do you understand that
you are in the place
where I socialize three
to four days a week?
So you care more about
bowling than your grandson?
Of course not. I'm just saying
maybe there's a better
way to go about it.
Now, I'm warnin' you,
Brenda is one mean...
I know you don't like bad language,
but we are in a bowling
alley... One mean bitch.
Well, I can be mean, too.
Okay, you listen to me. You get your kid
in line or I...
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
This is my place of business.
And now I see where
your daughter gets it.
You know what?
I have been nothin' but nice
to you and your family
since the day y'all moved in,
and I'm over it.
Watching you walk around all holier
than thou, like you're better
than everyone else.
Well, guess what,
you're not.
I'm gonna pray for you.
She says that to me all the time.
I'm not even sure she does it.
How'd it go?
I don't want to talk about it.
Is that pine?
We're not talkin' about it.
And you get that!
Herschel.
Hey, George.
It has come to my attention
that your wife went
to speak with my wife
at her place of work,
- and...
- She send you over here?
Thethe important thing
is that I'm here to tell you
that, Mary's behavior
was inappropriate.
You know, it's interesting.
When I came to your
house, you were laughin',
and...
now you're all serious.
Why is that?
What do you say we go talk about this
somewhere a little more comfortable?
Who's at the door?
Make yourself at home.
Boy.
You hang out in here?
Sure.
Once you get used to the smell,
it's not so bad.
I coach a high school football team.
This smells like petunias.
I like to...
take a break from the family and...
come out here and watch the games.
Ooh!
Your wife don't mind?
She don't know.
She's scared to death of chickens.
- Is that right?
- Once I found out,
buildin' this coop was a nobrainer.
You were gone so long.
How did it go?
Well...
One lump or two?
Two, please.
Billy?
Why would I want lumpy tea?
Isn't he pretty?
Very pretty.
I feel pretty.
I handled it.
Thank you so much.
We're family. It's what we do.
Listen, I'm sorry my wife
went down to the bowling alley.
Please, I'm sorry Brenda
made me come to your door.
I'm not.
This is the most fun I've had all week.
II feel bad about the
whole thing with the kids.
Hey, it happens.
I know, but Bobbi shouldn't be
beatin' on Sheldon like that.
- It's not okay.
- What's not okay
is Sheldon gettin' beat
up by a little girl.
Well...
Yeah.
Look, I'll talk to Bobbi.
I don't know if it'll
help, but I'll try.
Hey, you're a good man.
Yeah, II should be headin' back.
All right, well, look,
come on by anytime.
Yeah.
You know, we should obably
get our stories straight
before we talk to our respective...
- mates.
- Sure.
What do you want to say?
How 'bout this?
We had words,
it almost got ugly,
but we came to an understanding.
- I like that.
- Yeah.
You want to take a swing at me?
Make it look real?
I have a freakishly
high tolerance for pain.
No, no. But you're sweet for offering.
- You have a good night.
- You, too, pal.
Herschel!
Where the hell are you?!
Shh.
I built a hideyhole under here,
but there's only room for one of us.
Where is that fat dumb-ass?
Believe it or not, that means
I'm gettin' lucky tonight.
Y'all have an odd relationship.
Love is a mysterious thing.
Herschel!
Existing in a world of
predators isn't easy,
but we prey have developed
several natural defenses
to help us survive.
There's playing dead,
warning calls, camouflage...
and, last but certainly not least,
good oldfashioned running away.
A little screaming never hurts either.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
www.Addic7ed.com...