Previously on AMC's
"Better Call Saul"...
I want a new front.
My father is a simple man.
You will teach him.
[Coughs]
Tonight, I celebrate
with the world's best attorney.
Have you given any thought
to what you're gonna
do for the next year?
I'm out 4,000 bucks.
So you're gonna keep
paying for half a law office
even though you're not practicing law?
I'll hold up my end, you hold up yours.
I'm selling advertising...
why not advertise?
What commercial did you run?
I made a new one.
_
[Footsteps approach]
[Birds chirping]
[Slurps]
[Footsteps approach]
[Vehicle door opens, closes]
[Man clears throat]
[Vehicle approaching]
[Brakes squeal]
[Sniffles] Name?
Um. [Clears throat]
James McGill. [Sniffles]
Bring your card?
Yeah.
[Sighs]
[Clears throat]
Sign there.
[Horn honks in distance]
Can I read it first?
It's just a waiver.
We're not responsible
if you hurt yourself.
[Train whistle blows in distance]
[Sighs]
[Engine rumbling]
[Gearshift clicks, door creaks]
[Engine shuts off]
[Wind whistling]
[Vehicles passing]
[Scoffs]
[Cellphone vibrating]
Good morning. Saul Goodman Productions.
T-that's right.
We, uh... we do it all...
we write it, shoot it,
get ya on the air for
one low, low price.
May I ask what business you have?
Computer repair?
That is a perfect business
to advertise on television
because, you know,
computers are our future.
[Chuckles]
Uh...
yes, well, our rates are...
- [Trucks engines rumbling]
- Ah!
Sorry. That was, uh, one of our trucks.
We're, uh, location shooting today.
It's a big production, actually.
Our usual rate is one
commercial, one airing...
$850, but you're in luck...
today, we have a one-time special.
Our Elite package.
Seven commercials, seven airings
for forty...
forty-six hundred dollars.
Yeah. Forty-six hundred dollars.
And we can a... Hello?
Hello?
[Cellphone beeps]
[Engines rumbling]
No, I didn't, because you
keep putting me on hold.
[Vehicle passing]
Okay, my situ... Hello?
My sit... yes, my situation is this.
I... two months ago,
I paid for a full year,
uh, but, due to
unforeseen circumstances,
I'm not gonna be a lawyer
for the next 12 months.
- [Vehicle passing]
- [Sighs]
Uh-huh. Yes, suspended.
So I'm not practicing,
so I don't need malpractice insurance,
and I'd like to speak to
someone about a refund.
But y... well, then, may
I please speak to someone
who can make a decision?
No, no, no. Don't put
me on hold again, please.
He... Hello? He...
[Vehicle passing]
[Horn honks]
[Whistle blowing]
[Vehicle passing]
Wait a minute. This says 30 minutes.
Yep.
We were out here for four hours.
You were on your phone.
You knew the rules when you signed up.
But I collected more garbage
than anybody out here.
I have to be able to conduct business
to earn a living.
No. [Scoffs]
What do you mean "no"?
Think of community
service as your jail time.
No phones allowed in jail.
W-w-well, hold on there, buddy.
I mean, who do you think you are, huh?
Y-y-you think you can
treat us like this? Yeah?
We're out here for the good
of the great city of
Albuquerque... not for you.
You're not our lord and master.
You don't get to sit back and decide
who's worthy and who isn't.
Am I right?
Dude, are you gonna
get in the van or what?
C'mon. 30 minutes?
That stuff's not right.
You can do better than that.
[Sighs] We could make it zero.
[Sighing]
[Paper rustles]
[Sighs]
[Horn blares]
♪ ♪
www.addic7ed.com
[Vehicle approaching]
[Brakes squeal]
[Door opens]
♪ ♪
[Engine shuts off]
[Trunk creaks]
♪ ♪
[Engine starts]
[Keys jingling]
[Engine sputtering]
Come on. Come on!
- [Sputtering continues]
- Come on, baby!
Ohh!
[Sighs]
[Engine starts]
- Yes!
- [Gearshift clicks]
[Engine revs, exhaust pops]
♪ ♪
So come on down to Duke City Recliners
and put your feet up!
Mention this ad and get
10% off your first purchase.
And... cut.
Great! How was that?
- Good for camera.
- Sound was good. Yep.
- Thank you. That was great.
- Hold up. Hold up.
I wanna do one more.
Was that okay?
[Clicks tongue] It was great,
uh, but I just... I want...
I want you to connect
more with the audience.
Like you're talking to a friend.
Look into that lens and see a friend.
Can you do that?
I mean, think of a specific friend.
- Do you see him?
- Yes.
Okay. Who is he?
- My friend Ron.
- Great.
Look into that lens and see Ron.
And just two guys, just
chattin' about chairs.
- [Sighs, sniffles]
- D-don't think about it.
Just throw it away.
Last looks. Roll sound.
Sound speed.
- Camera?
- Cam... camera set.
And...
havin' a conversation
with your good friend Ron.
Just a couple of guys talkin'.
And you got some very exciting news
about the recliners
that you've been dyin'
to share with him.
And... action.
So come on down to Duke City Recliners
and put your feet up!
Mention this ad and get
10% off your first purchase.
And... cut!
Great! That's the one!
Check the gate! How did that feel?!
Good, I guess. What...
what did you think?
Good! So good!
Just very, very...
- just great!
- It was very nice.
Listen, you are on a roll, my friend.
I say we strike while the iron is hot.
Remember that other offer we discussed?
More commercials at the discounted rate?
Got my whole crew here.
We could bang out seven more
and give you a run that'll
make you a household name.
- Waddya say?
- But, Mr. Goodman, I...
love the idea of more commercials,
but I just can't swing it.
- My wife didn't want me to do this one.
- You know what?
They say you gotta spend
money to make money.
And, uh...
[Chuckles]
and I tell ya what...
you got a chance here
to potentially spike
your sales by hundreds...
hell, thousands... of new customers
who'd never even heard
of Duke City Recliners.
- What do ya say?
- Sure, s-sure.
B-but... but like I said... [Sighs]
I only have enough to pay for the one.
[Sighs]
Well, you know what?
I like you, and I wanna help.
So I know we discussed a discounted rate
of $545 per commercial,
but if you sign up right
now for our Elite package...
now, that's seven commercials...
I think we can do the whole thing for...
$500 per commercial.
Now, that is $3,500, all in.
That is the bargain of a lifetime.
[Sighs]
I don't know.
Any chance you could do it on credit?
[Inhales sharply] On credit?
No. No.
I can't.
- I'm sorry.
- Uh, maybe another time.
Uh, let me get your money for this one.
Uh, can we make this easier
and just split it four ways?
"Split it four"... I'll
split you four ways.
Don't they teach you capitalism
in that school of yours?
I'm just sayin', we got expenses, man.
You... expen... you don't have expenses!
I've got expenses! You see this?
This is money I've already spent
on airtime for that commercial.
445 bucks.
You know what that leaves me with?
- $100.
- $104.95!
For writing, directing,
producing, client outreach,
- sales, transpo... all of it!
- I get it.
Yeah. So let's get you in the
editing room and finish this thing,
and I don't want to hear
another word about expenses.
Kim: Okay. Electric.
- Jimmy: [Sighs]
- I paid this month.
Anything else?
I bought a couple reams
of paper for the printer.
Hmm. Paper.
One hundred... sixty-two.
Okay, so...
Mm...
Looks like puts me ahead this month...
$3,172.
All right. And what's it to even me up?
Uh... divided by 2.
[Calculator buttons clicking]
$1,586.
Okay.
[Inhales sharply] One thousand...
five hundred...
[Chuckles] Wow.
Mr. Moneybags, huh?
So this... commercial
thing. It's turning a profit?
It's TV.
How could there not be a profit?
You didn't...
drain your bank account, did you?
[Chuckling] What? No...
- I didn't...
- [Knock on door]
Uh, oh, that's, uh, Chinese food.
I ordered it for us.
- You're workin' late, right?
- Yeah. Right. Thanks.
Oh, uh... wait, here.
No, I got this.
- Hey, hi.
- $24.
[Clears throat]
Here. Keep the change.
A dollar?
Yeah.
We can make it zero.
[Freez's "I.O.U." plays]
♪ A-E-A-E-I-O-U-U ♪
[Insects chirping]
[Clattering]
[Door creaks]
[Locks clicking]
[Alarm beeping]
[Beeping continues]
[Keypad beeping]
[Beeping stops]
Ahh!
Geez! What the hell?!
I mean, what the hell?
How'd you get in here?
Relax.
I just want to talk.
Talk? [Chuckles]
You mean, like, apologize?
'Cause that's really the
only talk I want to hear.
I want to do some business. Like before.
[Chuckles] Business?
Is that, like, code for
stealing my baseball cards?
I'm not here for your baseball cards.
I'm here...
for this.
Can you get more of these?
You want me to steal this?
Get a prescription
and go to a pharmacist.
- It'll be cheap.
- I need those capsules empty...
before they're sealed.
With those exact markings.
Well... the place I
work doesn't make these.
But...
But what?
I could probably get
some samples diverted
on an R&D request.
So do it.
Why? I mean, what's the point?
I need them.
[Scoffs lightly] O-kay.
And if I don't get them?
Then what?
Are you gonna threaten me?
Break my legs?
You get me those pills,
and I'm gonna pay you $20,000.
Get them.
[Insects chirping]
[Door creaks]
[Sighs]
[Creaking]
[Thud]
[Children shouting in distance]
Woman: Let her have the ball.
[Chatter]
Man: Hold on, okay?
Stacey: Hey, Pop.
You doing okay?
Uh, yeah. It's coming along.
Have a couple of volunteers
here who want to help.
Well, thanks, but I think I'm good.
Please, we can't let you
do it all by yourself.
Certainly not after you
bought all the supplies.
At least let the church reimburse you.
- It's a donation.
- Woman: C'mon.
You've got unskilled but eager laborers.
Let us do something.
Just point and tell us what to do.
Oh.
All right, uh...
how about you dump one of those packs
into the wheelbarrow?
And you... you fill that bucket
up to the brim with water.
And then you dump it
in, little by little,
while he stirs it with a hoe.
- You got it.
- Okay.
I'm ready. What can I do?
- I think we're covered.
- [Chuckles]
You're kidding, right?
It's not that big a job.
[Water splashing]
- Am I doing this right?
- Uh...
why don't you try using this instead?
Excuse me?
It's for the walkway.
Look.
It puts down a texture
so the kids don't slip when it gets wet.
[Chatter in distance]
Like this?
You got it.
Nice and gentle.
- You're Kaylee's Pop-Pop, right?
- [Laughter]
I am.
I am the very proud grandfather.
- I'm Anita.
- Mike.
- Nice to meet you, Mike.
- And you.
And thanks for helping.
Well, thank you for not trying
to do this all by yourself.
[Chatter continues]
[Car door creaks]
[Insects chirping]
[Vehicle passing in distance]
Hey. Carl?
Yeah.
Hold the fort for a
few minutes, wouldja?
You got it, Mike. [Sighs]
[Video game plays "Trojan
Warrior Theme"]
Oh, hey.
You're here.
This your idea of stealth?
I never claimed to be good
at this. Any of it.
- [Siren wails in distance]
- On that, we can agree.
Yeah, I know. That's why I'm here.
I wanna hire you again.
Do what now?
Hire you. As my back-up man.
Same terms as before.
I don't wanna make the
same mistake as last time.
You don't wanna make the same mistake,
then don't get involved
with whatever it is you're
getting involved with.
But... I'm involved already.
I'm not.
Well...
it's Nacho Varga.
[Sighs]
What about him?
He broke into my house.
He was inside, waiting for me.
Somehow, he got past my security system.
I have no idea how!
All he had to do was
unplug your phone lines.
Oh. That's it?
Huh.
What'd he want?
Pills. Well... not exactly.
Empty Lydristel capsules.
- Lydristel?
- Yeah. They're like nitroglycerin.
And he offered me
money... lots of money.
Way more than they're even worth.
But...
I'm afraid if I don't do it,
or even if I do do it...
I don't know...
Tell him you can't get what he needs.
I already ordered them.
I mean, the shipment gets
here in two days. He knows.
Then make up an excuse.
[Sighs] Fine. $3,000.
- I'll give you $3,000.
- I'm not interested.
And you find a way out of it.
[Scoffs] But...
Not interested!
[Gearshift clicks]
[Seatbelt clicks]
[Engine shuts off]
[Engine starts in distance]
[Cellphone beeping]
_
[Sighs]
- [Alarm beeping]
- [Gasps]
- Paige: Look... full disclosure.
- [Beeping stops]
When you told us about
the disciplinary hearing,
- I admit it... I had concerns.
- [Elevator bell dings]
So, just so you know, I
had to do my due diligence.
I read the transcripts.
All of them.
It was amazing.
What you did to Charles...
you and James set him up perfectly.
[Chuckling] You destroyed him.
Oh, my God.
I couldn't believe some of it.
"I'm not crazy. It's 1216,
- "one after Magna Carta."
- [Elevator bell dings]
- [Laughing] The Magna Carta?
- [Chuckles]
It was perfect.
[Chuckling] "You think
this chicanery is bad?"
Who talks like that? [Chuckles]
On page 5 is a breakdown
of loan-to-deposit ratios
by county, and you can see,
if Mesa Verde is going to
comply with Section 109,
you will have to raise
your loan numbers.
Mm. That can't be right.
We were fine in Arizona.
Yes, but the FDIC requirements
in Utah are different.
96%?
Is it really that high?
I thought Arizona was only 79%.
Again, it was,
but Utah has a higher
loan-to-deposit ratio.
[Sighs]
I think we're gonna need to check that.
That number seems way off.
The numbers are right.
But you can review the
guidelines if you want.
Right here.
[Papers thud]
You gonna check 'em or can we move on?
Uh...
no...
of course, if it's 96%, it's 96%.
We'll increase our loan numbers.
Absolutely.
[Sighs]
Can we review these
fixed mortgage rates?
'Cause that's... [Sighs]
definitely an area we're
gonna need to focus...
- Paige, I'm s... that was...
- ... our attention...
unprofessional.
I didn't mean to speak to you that way.
Kim. Don't worry.
It's not a problem. At all.
No, I'm sorry. There's no excuse
for talking to you like that.
[Sighs]
I know how hard you've
been working on this.
Please, I've forgotten about it already.
You should, too.
Okay?
As far as I'm concerned, all we did...
all we did was tear down a sick man.
Fixed mortgage rates.
I think it's page 3.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
There's an acquisition
comparison at the top,
and you want to go by total...
[Vehicle approaching]
[Brakes squeal]
[Gearshift clicks]
♪ ♪
[Wheelchair squeaking]
[Tires screeching]
[Engine revs]
- Get in!
- Yeah.
Go! Chop-chop!
C'mon, c'mon!
[Grunts]
Oh.
Get in!
- Let's go.
- Trying.
[Sighs]
[Engine sputtering]
That doesn't sound good.
C'mon, c'mon.
- I think you're flooding it.
- I'm not flooding it!
You're over-cranking it.
Oh, you don't know what
you're talking about!
We're still getting paid
whether we get there or not.
- Maybe we should catch the bus.
- Sh... come on!
Just... it's gonna start, okay?
- [Sputtering continues]
- Yeah, you definitely flooded it.
He drained the battery.
You drained the battery.
Can you not talk about something
you know absolutely nothing about?
- There's a bus we could get in.
- Shh! Shh!
I just need to think for one minute!
[Sighs]
Look, we're taking the bus.
Yeah.
[Grunts]
[Trunk creaks]
[Panting]
Film crew!
Hold up the bus!
You see that?
Fender Stratocaster,
signed by Ritchie Blackmore.
- You know who that is, right?
- Someone no one's ever heard of?
That's real good.
I hope your parents enjoy supporting you
for the rest of their lives.
C'mon, Ritchie Blackmore.
Deep Purple.
Ohh. "Another Brick in the Wall."
Oh, I weep for the future.
[Sighs]
Mr. McGill, we have a problem.
Them.
Hey, fellas. Uh, you ready?
We got the first shot all lined up.
- Can I walk you through it?
- Uh...
We hate to do this to you, but...
- We're having second thoughts.
- Yeah.
I get it. That's just
nerves. Just stage fright.
Uh, tell you what... we got cue cards,
and with the magic of editing,
we're gonna make you guys look like...
James Garner and Mariette Hartley.
It's not that.
It's just that it...
it seems like too much money...
For not a whole lot of return.
And that, my friends... that
is where you're mistaken,
because this is about brand awareness.
From now on, when people think guitars,
they're gonna think "ABQ In Tune."
When they think pianos... "ABQ In Tune."
Drums, xylophones...
for less than the price
of that Ritchie Blackmore
beauty you got on that rack,
you're gonna have the whole
town thinking, "ABQ In Tune."
Yeah, but... but what
about the time slot?
I mean, "Murder, She Wrote" repeats?
- Come on.
Hey, grandmas love
buying the gift of music
for little Johnny and
Sally and Skip, hmm?
And it's school-recital season, so...
where are the kids gonna
get those recorders?
Uh, we don't sell recorders.
Synthesizers, then. But the point is,
those Social Security checks...
they got to be spent somewhere.
Mnh.
Hey, uh... [Clears throat]
as it happens, uh, today only,
I can, uh, offer the
same package, but...
50% off.
Look...
I'm sorry, but we can't.
Not today, guys.
Don't do that. Guys. Now, come on.
Look, I know you want
this. I know you do.
50% off!
Yeah, we get it, but we're just not...
Convinced.
[Sighs]
Free.
[Clears throat] I'll
shoot the spot for free.
For free?
You will shoot this spot for free?
I'll film your ad, and
I'll put it on the air.
But when you see more
traffic coming through here...
and you will...
then we do the other spots
for the original rate.
Okay? Now, how can you say no?
[Sighs]
- I mean, when he puts it like that...
- I guess we can't.
Good.
That's the best decision
you're gonna make.
The... the best!
[Vehicles passing]
[Wind whistling]
[Sighs]
Uh...
you gonna catch the bus, Mr. McGill?
No, I... um...
You guys... get to the editing room.
I just need t...
to sit.
Mr. McGill?
Oh, no. I-I can't.
It's okay.
No, that's yours.
You earned it.
But you're losing money.
We'll see.
It... it'll be fine.
Okay.
So, I finally got my act together.
I pulled a bunch of Alan's
boxes out of the closet.
[Inhales sharply]
Only took me eight years.
I gave all of Alan's clothes a last wash
before driving them over to Goodwill.
I cried.
I cried when I washed them.
I cried when I folded them.
I cried when I dropped 'em off.
But once it was done...
it felt good...
to let them go.
[Man coughs softly]
I kept his uniform, though. [Chuckles]
Can't let that go.
Lord, he'd never forgive me if
I let that go. [Laughs]
But I figure it's okay
to keep one thing, right?
I mean...
people can use the other clothes, but...
not sure what use they'd
have for an old uniform.
[Vehicles passing in distance]
I just don't remember this much homework
when I was Kaylee's age.
It doesn't seem to
bother her, but still...
Most of it's just busywork.
A couple of us actually
spoke to the school board,
and they agreed...
Done. All yours.
Fair warning, the coffee's not all that.
[Chuckles] Mm.
I guess they feel if you can face this,
- you can face anything.
- Could be.
- I must be stronger than I think.
- Mm.
You mind if I ask...
and I really don't mean to pry, but...
Let me guess.
You have another construction
job you need my help on.
Uh, no.
But if I do, you'll be
the first person I call.
[Chuckles] Okay, ask away.
You said you kept
your husband's uniform.
Was he on the job?
On the job?
Oh, you mean the police.
[Chuckling] No.
Alan was a Navy man.
He was well out of the
service when I lost him.
I'm sorry.
The group has heard
my story over and over.
Well, that's what we're here for.
Well...
Alan loved to hike.
We even opened a camping-supply store.
I helped him with the
mail-order side of it.
And then, uh...
this was eight years ago...
he went hiking in Gila National
and never came back.
They found our car,
but they never found him.
And I don't know if...
he slipped and fell
or had a heart attack
or met someone who didn't
like the way he looked...
I don't know.
And even after all these years,
not knowing how he
passed or where he is...
I wish it didn't matter.
But it does.
[Insects chirping]
[Vehicles passing in distance]
[Cellphone dialing]
Pryce: Hello?
It's me.
You make the deal?
Uhhh, no.
Not yet.
Why?
I'm in.
[Insects chirping]
[Vehicles passing in distance]
[Leaves rustling]
[Door closes]
[Groans, sighs]
[Sighs]
[Vehicles passing in distance]
[Chuckles]
Hey, let's get outta here.
[Scoffs] What?
Get out where?
I am up to my neck in
Mesa Verde. I can't.
- C'mon, we're going. Up.
- No, I can't.
- Na-ah! Nope. Nothing...
- Jimmy... [Laughs]
nothing you can do to stop this.
[Inhales sharply] Uh, one thing...
you have to drive.
[Kruder & Dorfmeister's
"Black Baby" plays]
Oh, oh, oh.
Lookit this guy.
Ohh.
It's Alfred Hitchcock
in a rented toupee.
[Laughs] C'mon.
Why would you rent a toupee?
Y'know, from the Toupee Store.
- So you don't have to maintain it.
- [Chuckles]
- All right. Seven and Seven.
- Yeah.
And an Old Fashioned.
Keep 'em coming, good sir.
Uh, oh. [Clears throat]
Can you, uh, start charging this card
- instead of that other one?
- Yeah, yeah. You got it.
- Thank you. [Sniffles]
- No problem.
You're not maxing out
your cards, are you?
Of course not.
I'm, um, spreading the points around.
- I got a system.
- Oh.
[Inhales sharply, sighs]
- That moron takes the bet.
- [Clears throat]
He took 3 points. He's a fool.
Look, is it wrong...
Whoa. Hey, hey, this guy over here.
[Inhales sharply]
Yeah, he wants everyone to
know what a big spender he is.
I got every dollar the guy owns.
We're here to meet a celebrity
who's donating to my charity.
Kevin Costner.
I-I will go stand in that corner.
You point me out...
you're meeting Kevin Costner.
What? You don't look like Kevin Costner.
Uh... I look exactly like Kevin Costner.
People are always coming up to me,
saying they loved me in "Bull Durham."
Never. Never happened.
- Always.
- No, not once.
- [Snapping fingers] Hey! Hey, you!
- Waiter: Yes, sir?
- What is this?
- Uh, dirty Martini?
No, this is a $14 glass of puke.
Why don't you get that
idiot look off your face
and get me another one?
- That guy.
- Who said anything about gin?
- How do we get him?
- Well, I want vodka.
- [Inhales sharply]
- W-what am I just gonna hold it here?
- What do you think?
- You go and get me another one.
The... the trick with the
coin you told me about?
I know your boss. I'm an investor here.
- Or the counterfeit bill?
- No.
I know your boss, and
I know your boss' boss.
That guy's a real asshole.
... Act together and
get me a real drink.
He needs to go down. Hard.
What kind of menial job is this?
♪ ♪
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna sell him
a worthless credit card
for 5,000 bucks.
[Chuckling] Here's what you do.
Make eye contact with him.
That's all it'll take for him
to think you're interested.
I'll act good and drunk,
and he'll think I'm a loser
and try to steal you away.
He will persist.
Mm.
Tell him you can't
leave me. Not... not yet.
Let him know you're trying
to roll me. [Inhales sharply]
He'll want in.
He'll help you ply me with booze.
Then you take my wallet.
You lift the card.
Following this?
We're not actually doing this, right?
We're just talking?
♪ ♪
Yeah.
[Chuckling] Just talkin'.
[Sighs]
♪ ♪
What?
Nothing.
It's not nothing. What?
I keep thinking...
was there another way?
[Chuckling] Another way?
W... Chuck? Is that what
you're talking about?
Kim... he had us in a corner, okay?
- We did what we had to do.
- But Rebecca...
Everything that happened
was his own fault.
Everything.
And put him in the rear-view mirror.
He is not worth thinkin' about.
Done.
♪ ♪
Woman: Why, thank you.
Have a good evening.
[Sighs]
[Indistinct conversations,
glasses clinking]
[Planet E's "Klub Kola" plays]
How about that one?
♪ ♪
I bet we could get him to...
invest in some of Giselle St.
Claire's land in South Africa.
Oh, yeah. Definitely.
[Sighs]
The mining rights would be all his.
♪ ♪
[Insects chirping]
[Gearshift clicks]
- [Engine shuts off]
- [Keys jingle]
[Wind whistling]
[Sighs]
Really?
He called me. For obvious reasons.
Look, I'm not here to rip him off.
He has the stuff, right?
I need to know what you're planning.
What's it matter to you?
I know they're for Salamanca.
Nitro pills.
Your boss has heart problems.
You already got it all
figured out, why're you asking?
How you gonna make the switch?
[Sighs]
Hector keeps the pills
in his coat pocket.
When he hangs up his
coat, I'll make the switch.
Mm. He goes down. Then what?
His heart goes out. That's it.
A lot of eyes on Salamanca.
You do this, how are you gonna stop them
from finding out it was you?
Are you tryin' to
tell me not to do this?
I'm not tellin' you anything.
Just want to make sure you
know what you're getting into.
I'm not getting into
anything. I'm in it.
I've got no choice.
[Sighs]
Hector wants to use my dad's business.
My dad is a straight arrow.
He won't stand for it,
which means he goes to the police,
which means he's a dead man.
And that's not happening.
You get caught, it could get worse.
You don't think I know
who I'm dealing with?
No.
I don't.
[Gas cap rattling]
What are you doing?
[Gas-cap door closes]
There are more people
than the Salamancas
to worry about here.
Now, if you manage to pull this off
without a bullet in your
head and switch those pills,
then switch 'em back.
Switch them back?
Why?
Anyone gets an itch about
the medicine not working,
they're gonna look at those pills.
You do this...
switch 'em back.
So... you gonna let us make this deal?
You got the money?
Good.
[Sniffles]
Now, before we do this...
I'm gonna need one more thing from you.
- [Indistinct conversations]
- _
[Intercom beeps]
Yes?
Okay.
Miss Valco will see you now.
- Oh.
- Second door.
[Breathes sharply]
Hi there. Come on in.
Yeah. Hi. I've...
called quite a few times
about an issue I'm trying to address.
Do you have your policy number?
No.
[Sighs]
Can you just look up my name? McGill?
Charles McGill of
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill?
No, that's my brother.
Um... [Clears throat]
I'm Jimmy. James McGill.
Solo practitioner.
Oh. There you are.
Looks like you're all
paid up through the year.
That's sort of the issue.
Long story short, through a
series of unfortunate events,
my license has been suspended.
Yes, I see that here.
Right. Well...
I was hoping I could get a refund
for the time that I won't be a lawyer.
Now, that's only fair, right?
I'm sorry, Mr. McGill.
It doesn't work like that.
We don't refund for unused
malpractice insurance.
[Sighs] But it's a...
it's a lot of money for nothing.
I understand it seems that way,
but if one of your clients decides
they want to bring a suit against you,
this continues your coverage.
[Snaps fingers] That's the thing.
My clients?
They love me.
And they would never
bring a suit against me.
I'm [Chuckling] extremely lovable.
I can see that.
But it's company policy.
[Snaps fingers]
What about we put the insurance on hold?
And then, if someone
were to try to sue me...
which they won't...
then we just, uh, [Clicks tongue]
kick that ol' policy back into gear?
I understand your situation. I do.
But there are rules preventing us
from stopping and starting coverage.
And I regret to inform you that...
when your license is
reinstated next year,
because of the suspension,
your premiums are going to... go up.
Considerably.
How considerably?
Um... [Drawer opens]
Looks like roughly... 150%.
[Breathing sharply]
[Chuckling] God.
[Sniffling]
[Drawer closes]
Mr. McGill?
[Sighs]
[Sniffles]
Oh.
I...
Mr. McGill, I'm sorry.
I wish we could help
you, but we just can't.
[Sniffles]
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
Very, very hard.
[Sniffles]
I'm just having a rough time.
I just need a break.
[Voice breaking] Just one break.
And I know you... I know
you can't do anything, but...
[Crying]
I'm getting run out on this
community service and...
getting ripped off
left and right, and...
my car won't start.
[Chuckles]
My gal is disappointed in me, and...
my brother...
[Sniffles]
[Crying]
My brother is sick!
And he's alone.
I spent years caring for him, and...
now he hates me.
He's the only family I got left,
and he hates me.
He hates my guts.
Is this your brother, Charles?
- Oh.
- [Sniffles]
And I pretend not to
care, but he's my brother.
How can I not?
He's mentally ill.
He's... he's holed up in
a house with no electricity.
He's working by the
light of gas lanterns.
Wha...
He's making mistakes
with his clients. He's...
mixin' up numbers on
important documents.
He... he...
He had a complete mental breakdown
at the bar hearing.
Your brother... he had
a breakdown in court?
It's in the transcripts.
[Sobbing]
God. And I'm worried, I'm just...
if he screws up with
one more big client...
it's just gonna destroy him!
[Sniffles]
Oh, don't... don't write...
What are you writing? No, don't write.
I-I didn't mean to say that.
I don't want him to get
in trouble with you guys
- 'cause of me. I...
- Right.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go.
You're not gonna do anything, are you?
I-I wouldn't worry about it, Mr. McGill.
Uh, please feel better.
I'm sorry.
Just for... uh, forget.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Telephone ringing]
www.addic7ed.com