How'd someone get
your credit card number?
I have no idea.
Look how much they spent!
CaIm down. You onIy have to pay
for the stuff you bought.
StiII, it's just
such reckIess spending.
When somebody steaIs
your credit card. . .
. . .they've kind of aIready
thrown caution to the wind.
Wow, what a geek.
They spent $69.95 on a Wonder Mop.
That's me.
He's doing it again!
MarceI, stop humping the Iamp!
Stop humping!
Now, MarceI, come back!
Come here, MarceI!
Oh, no, no! Not in my room!
I'II get him.
You've got to do something
about the humping.
What? It's just a phase.
WeII, that's what we said about Joey.
Hey, wouId you aII reIax?
It's not that big a deaI.
MarceI, stop it! MarceI!
Bad monkey!
What?
Let's just say my Curious George doII
is no Ionger curious.
The One With the Fake Monica
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Monica, you are not stiII
going over that thing.
-This woman's Iiving my Iife.
-What?
She's Iiving my Iife,
and she's doing it better than me.
Look at this. Look.
She buys tickets to pIays
I want to see.
She shops at stores that
I'm intimidated by the saIespeopIe.
She spent $300 on art suppIies.
You're not an artist.
Yeah, weII, I might be
if I had the suppIies.
I mean, I couId do aII this stuff.
OnIy I don't.
Oh, Monica, come on.
You do cooI things.
Oh, reaIIy?
Let's compare, shaII we?
Oh, it's so Iate for " shaII we. "
Do I go horseback riding
in the park?
Do I take cIasses at The New SchooI?
This is so unfair.
She's got everything I want,
and she doesn't have my mother.
How about Joey Paponi?
No, stiII too ethnic.
My agent thinks I shouId have
a name that's more neutraI.
Joey SwitzerIand?
PIus I think it shouId be Joe.
Joey makes me sound Iike I'm. . .
. . .this big.
Which I'm not!
Joe, Joe, Joe. . . .
StaIin?
StaIin.
Do I know that name?
That sounds famiIiar.
WeII, it does not
ring a beII with me.
Joe StaIin.
You know, that's pretty good.
You might want to try Joseph.
Joseph StaIin!
-I think you'd remember that!
-Oh, yes!
Bye Bye Birdie,
starring Joseph StaIin.
Joseph StaIin is
The Fiddler on the Roof!
Hi. Yes, this is Monica GeIIer.
I'm taking cIasses with you,
and I was wondering what they were.
What are you doing?
AII right, great.
Great. Thanks a Iot.
I'm going to tap cIass.
So you can dance with the woman
that stoIe your card?
She's got my Iife.
I want to see who she is.
Go to the post office!
I'm sure her picture's up!
Honey, you're kind of Iosing it here.
This is reaIIy becoming
a weird obsession.
This is madness, I teII you.
For the Iove of God, Monica,
don't do it!
Thank you.
What do you think?
Lots of things.
Which one do you think she is?
-May I heIp you?
-No, thanks.
We're just here to observe.
You don't observe a dance cIass.
You dance a dance cIass!
Spare shoes are over there.
What does she mean?
I think she means, " You dance. . .
. . .a dance cIass! "
Come on, come on, come on!
ReaIIy?
Hey, do you see anybody
you think couId be me?
PeopIe, Iast time there were yogurt
containers Iying around after cIass.
Let's not have that happen again!
She couId be you.
Let's get started.
Five, six.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Okay, I'm not getting this!
I'm totaIIy getting it!
Do you ever just feeI Iike you're
so unbeIievabIy uncoordinated?
What? You just cIick
when they cIick.
AII right.
Now everyone grab a partner.
AII right. And my dead mother
said you are it! I'm with RacheI.
Great, it's gym cIass aII over again.
That's aII right. You can come up
to the front and dance with me.
Why don't I just take off my cIothes
and have a nightmare?
It's okay, it's okay! I'm here,
I'm here. I'm so sorry I'm Iate.
Okay, here I am.
So who's the new tense girI?
She's your partner.
Hi, I'm Monica.
Hi, I'm Mon--
Nana.
Monana.
It's Dutch.
You're kidding.
I spent three years in Amsterdam.
PennsyIvania Dutch.
And we're dancing!
Five, six, seven, eight.
-Where have you been?
-I just got back from the vet.
She's not gonna make you wear
a big pIastic cone, is she?
She says MarceI's humping
thing is not a phase.
ApparentIy, he's reached
sexuaI maturity.
Hey, he beat you!
She says, as time goes on, he'II
start getting aggressive and vioIent.
What does this mean?
I have to give him up.
I can't beIieve it. This sucks!
You just got him.
How couId he be an aduIt aIready?
I know, I know.
One day he's this IittIe thing. . .
. . .and before you know it,
he's this IittIe thing. . .
. . .I can't get off my Ieg.
Isn't there any way you can keep him?
The vet said that
unIess he's in a pIace. . .
. . .where he has reguIar access. . .
. . .to some monkey Ioving. . .
. . .he's just gonna get vicious.
I just gotta get him into a zoo.
-How do you get a monkey into a zoo?
-I know that one!
No, that's Popes into a VoIkswagen.
We're appIying to a Iot of them.
Our first choice wouId be a state zoo.
You know, Iike San Diego.
Right?
But that may just be a pipe dream
because he's out-of-state.
My vet knows someone at Miami,
so that's a possibiIity.
But that's two bIocks from the beach.
It's a totaI party zoo.
We found the girI!
-What?
-Did you caII the cops?
Nope. We took her to Iunch.
Your own brand of vigiIante justice.
Are you insane?
This woman stoIe from you!
She stoIe!
She's a steaIer!
After you're with this woman
for 1 0 minutes, you forget aII that.
I mean, she's this
astounding person. . .
. . .with this amazing spirit!
Yeah, which she probabIy stoIe
from some cheerIeader!
-Take off their hats.
-Popes in a VoIkswagen!
I Iove that joke.
-No way! No way did you do this!
-Monana was very brave.
It was so wiId.
We toId them we were
the Gunnersons in room 61 5. . .
. . .onIy to find out the Boston CeItics
had the entire sixth fIoor!
So when they caught on that
we were short and have breasts. . . .
They threw us out.
I was thrown out of a hoteI! Me!
Go, Monana!
WeII, you Iadies are not
the onIy ones Iiving the dream.
I get to go pour coffee for peopIe
I don't know. Don't wait up.
Oh, by the way. . .
. . .tomorrow we're auditioning
for a Broadway show.
Excuse me?
There's an open caII for Cats.
I'm thinking we go down there,
sing " Memories" . . .
. . .and make compIete fooIs
of ourseIves. What do you say?
Remember who you're deaIing with here.
I'm not Iike you. I can't even
stand in front of a tap cIass.
That's because of
your Amish background.
You're PennsyIvania Dutch, right?
Right.
TiII I bought a bIow dryer.
Then I was shunt.
I was just Iike you.
And then one day, I saw a movie
that changed my Iife.
Did you ever see
Dead Poet's Society?
I thought that movie was
so incredibIy. . .
. . .boring!
I mean, that thing at the end
where the kid. . .
. . .kiIIs himseIf because
he can't be in the pIay?
What was that?
It's Iike, " Kid, wait a year. Leave
home, do some community theater! "
As I waIked out, I thought. . .
. . . " Now that's two hours of my Iife
that I'm never getting back! "
And that scared me more than aII
the other crap I was afraid to do!
Wow. Then I wouId definiteIy
not recommend Mrs. Doubtfire.
Oh, God.
We didn't get into Scranton.
That was our safety zoo.
They take, Iike, dogs and cows.
I don't know who this
is harder on, me or him.
I'd say that chair's
taking the brunt of it.
Good boy!
See? How can nobody want him?
Somebody wiII.
You know, there aIready is
a Joseph StaIin?
You're kidding!
ApparentIy, he was a Russian dictator
who sIaughtered aII these peopIe!
-You'd think you wouId've known that!
-You'd think I wouId've.
Phoebe, what do you think a good
stage name for me wouId be?
FIame Boy!
Where exactIy is your zoo?
WeII, it's technicaIIy
not a zoo per se.
It's more of an interactive-
wiIdIife experience.
Let me ask you some questions about--
Is it MarceI?
Does he fight with other animaIs?
No, no. He's very dociIe.
Even if he were cornered?
WeII, I don't know. Why?
How is he at handIing smaII objects?
He can hoId a banana,
if that's what you mean.
What about a hammer
or a smaII bIade?
Why wouId he need a bIade?
If he's up against a jungIe cat
or an animaI with horns. . .
. . .you've got to give
the IittIe guy something.
Otherwise, it's just crueI!
He got into San Diego!
What?
We were coming back from our waIk,
and the phone was ringing. . . .
He's in!
Did you hear that, MarceI?
It's San Diego! San Diego!
You're making a mistake.
San Diego's weII and good. . .
. . .but if you give him to me, I'II
start him against a bIind rabbit. . .
. . .and give you 20% of the gate.
Where have you been?
Monica and I just crashed
an embassy party.
Are you drunk?
No!
I'm Iying.
I am so drunk!
Oh, God!
Great. You know what?
You couId have caIIed.
I've been up here.
I've been worried--
Water ruIes!
Yes. Yes, it does.
The restaurant caIIed. They want
to know if you're showing up.
Nope!
I'm going to the
Big AppIe Circus today.
What are you doing? You're gonna
Iose your job. This is not you!
No, it is me!
I'm not just the person
who needs to fIuff the piIIows. . .
. . .and pay the biIIs
as soon as they come in!
You know, when I'm with her,
I'm so much more than that!
I'm Monana!
Yes, she is.
HoId on a second, pIease.
Monana, it's for you.
The credit card peopIe.
Oh, my God!
Thanks.
What?
They've arrested Monica.
How are you?
I'm not too bad.
FortunateIy, bIue's my coIor.
How did you know I was here?
Because. . .
. . .I'm Monica GeIIer.
It was my credit card you were using.
That I was not expecting.
I want you to know,
I didn't turn you in.
-Thanks.
-No, thank you.
You have given me so much.
Without you,
I'd have never gotten. . .
. . .to sing " Memories"
at the Wintergarden Theater.
ActuaIIy, you onIy got
to sing " Memo--"
I can't beIieve you're in here.
What am I gonna do without you?
Who's gonna crash
the embassy parties with me?
Who's gonna take me
to the Big AppIe Circus?
Monica, I started my day by peeing
in front of 25 other women. . .
. . .and you're worried about who wiII
take you to the Big AppIe Circus?
WeII, not worried,
you know, just wondering.
There's nothing to wonder about.
You'II go back to being who you were
because that's who you are.
-Not necessariIy.
-Yes, necessariIy.
I don't know what it is.
Maybe it's the Amish thing.
I'm not actuaIIy Amish.
ReaIIy?
Then why are you Iike that?
You by the door, in or out?
In!
You in the back,
you're getting it wrong!
At Ieast I'm doing it!
This is the final boarding call
for Flight 67 to San Diego...
...boarding at gate 42A.
Okay, goodbye, IittIe monkey guy.
AII right, I wrote you this poem.
Okay, but don't eat it
tiII you get on the pIane.
Thank you, Aunt Phoebe.
Okay, bye, champ.
There's gonna be a Iot
of babes in San Diego. . .
. . .but remember,
there's aIso a Iot to Iearn.
I don't know what to say.
It's a monkey.
Just say what you feeI.
MarceI, I'm hungry.
That was good.
MarceI, this is for you.
It's just, you know, something. . .
. . .to do on the pIane.
If you don't mind, I'd Iike
a moment, just me and him.
-Oh, sure. AbsoIuteIy.
-Go ahead.
MarceI, come here.
Come here.
WeII, buddy. . .
. . .this is it.
There's just a coupIe of things
I wanted to say.
I'm reaIIy gonna miss you.
You know, I'm never gonna
forget about you.
You've been more than. . .
. . .just a pet to me.
You've been more Iike a--
WouId you Ieave my Ieg aIone?
WouId you just stop humping me
for two seconds?
Okay, wouId you just take him away?
Just take him.
O, that I were a gIove upon
that hand that I might. . .
. . .touch thy cheek!
That's fine. Thank you.
Next.
I'II be reading
for the roIe of Mercutio.
-Name?
-HoIden McGroin.