Previously on Desperate Housewives:
I have another child, Lynette.
You didn't wanna give me permission, remember?
Not to sleep with the woman who's carrying our child!
For some, love will wither.
Do I know you?
- Orson Hodge, Susan's dentist friend.
While others will wait for love,
for others,
new love will bloom...
that may never arrive.
Desperate Housewives 3x01
"Listen to the Rain on the Roof"
(Mary Alice)
Something awful happened
on Lake View Drive
last year.
To understand why,
you need to know
that when Alma Hodge
awoke that morning,
she had no idea
this would be the day
she'd leave her husband.
Certainly,
it began normally enough.
She put away the groceries
per his instructions.
She hung his dry cleaning
exactly as he had requested.
She folded the towels
just as he had taught her.
It was just before noon...
Mama loves her baby.
Does the baby love mama?
Mama!
Something inside Alma broke,
and she decided it was time...
to fly away
of course, she knew better than
to say this to her husband.
He thought Alma was happy,
and Orson Hodge did not
like to be contradicted.
So she waited
till he left for work,
and then...
Oh!
(squawks)
Baby, you gotta come down now.
Mama's in a hurry.
Hurry! Hurry!
If you don't get back
in your cage right now,
I'm gonna have to
leave you behind. Please!
(gasps)
(squawks)
The next day,
Carolyn Bigsby stopped by,
and like most nosy neighbors,
she knew you learned more
if you didn't knock.
Alma? Are you home?
Carolyn?
I'm just looking for Alma.
We had a coffee date
this morning. She never showed.
Uh, Alma left yesterday.
Left?
We had a bit of a row.
Oh. Harvey and I thought
we heard some raised voices.
So where'd she go?
don't know,
but I wouldn't worry about it.
I'm sure she's fine.
(parrot) Orson, no!
Orson, no!
(parrot squawking)
So if I hear from Alma,
I'll let her know
that you dropped by.
Yes, Orson Hodge was a man
who did not like to be
contradicted...
by anyone.
It doesn't rain very often
in the town of Fairview,
but when it does,
it pours.
It was on just such a day
that Bree Van De Kamp
went on her first date with
her new friend Orson Hodge-
a date that ended
with a kiss in the rain.
This occurred just as
Gabrielle Solis was conferring
with her new divorce lawyer
and describing in vivid detail
her husband's affair
with their maid,
who also happened to be
their surrogate.
Meanwhile...
Lynette Scavo was busy meeting
her husband's
illegitimate daughter...
Here, you can have this.
while resisting the urge
to strangle the girl's mother.
This happened just after
Susan Mayer learned
Mike Delfino
had been badly injured
in a hit-and-run accident
and was now in a coma
at Fairview memorial hospital.
At that same moment,
Edie Britt was putting up
a "for sale" sign
on the lawn of the house
where I once lived.
Edie had also planned
to spruce up the property
by washing down the driveway.
but she was pleased to see
the rain had already
taken care of that.
This is what rainy days
are good for.
They make everything clean
again,
which is necessary on a street
like Wisteria Lane...
where everything
can get so messy.
(thunder crashes)
Welcome, welcome. Oh.
Don't worry about the water
the floors are laminated.
Here's a flyer.
(Mrs. McCluskey)
And then the police
found her severed fingers
in the garage.
- (woman) Oh, no!
And they never found
Felicia's body.
I wouldn't be surprised
if someday you opened a cabinet,
and... hello!
Karen, dear. Have you seen
the marble backsplash?
Oh, I just must show it to you.
Excuse us.
What are you trying to do to me,
you backstabbing cow?
They asked why the owner
was selling.
I told them that Paul young
was in jail. They asked why.
Conversation has a flow.
Well, knock it off.
I've been trying to unload
this house of horrors
for months now,
and you are not helping.
Ah-ah-ah! Those are
for potential buyers,
you withered old mooch.
Good luck trying to find
one of those.
Maybe you'll have an easier
time with the Applewhite house
and that rec room
in the basement.
Get out. Get out.
Get out, get out, get out!
(man) Edie, uh,
do you have a moment?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
(boy) Yeah! Yeah!
(boy) Come on!
Is Kayla ready yet?
(Nora) Just a sec.
(lower voice)
Honey, thank you for this.
I know it's a little weird,
I mean, to send out
a family Christmas photo
with your husband's love child,
but it means a lot to her to feel included.
no problem, she's a great little girl.
Okay? All right,
let's do this.
I am just going to, um,
check the focus.
Nora.
Lynette.
(chuckles nervously)
What are you doing there?
Well, it's a family photo,
right?
Tom, could I - could I -
could I check your tie again?
She sat down so quickly,
I didn't know what to say.
How about, "you're in the frame,
bitch. Move"?
No, I am sorry.
How much of her crap
do I have to put up with?
First,
it's the little drop-bys.
Then she's inviting herself
to dinner three times a week.
Now she wants to be
in our Christmas photo?
I'm sorry.
No, that's not happening. Hey, guys.
Don't fight.
It's the holidays.
Nora... this is just
for our family.
I would prefer
if you weren't in it.
Okay.
Kayla, honey, we gotta go.
They're kicking us out.
We didn't say that Kayla
couldn't be in the photo.
Yeah, well, you know what?
If I'm not your family,
then she's not your family.
It's okay. I don't have
to be in the picture.
Fine!
Fine. No, absolutely fine.
(lowers voice)
Put crazy at the end,
and we can crop
her out later.
Fair enough. Fair enough.
Hey, everything's okay.
It's okay. Come on, guys.
Come on back.
(Nora) Thank you, Lynette.
Back to the Christmas spirit
that I was looking for.
Ten seconds!
(camera beeping)
(sighs)
I think this is a little stiff.
I have a really fun idea.
(giggles)
(gasps)
(boys) Ugh!
(camera shutter clicks)
Where are my crackers?
We're out,
but I got you a pickle.
Pickles and soup?
Who eats that?
You know,
that's all I got.
Ever heard of a store?
You did not just do that.
I hate pickles.
Pick it up.
Doctor say
I only get out of bed to pee.
Better for baby, remember?
Don't go.
I need you to rub my feet.
They're sore, and doctor say -
Oh, cut it out, Xiao-mei.
The doctor didn't say anything.
About rubbing
your chubby stumps.
Rub 'em yourself.
You treat me like dirt.
Would you rather go live
with Mr. Solis
in a dingy
one-bedroom apartment
with no air conditioning
and no cable, huh?
No, I didn't think so.
You are meanest person
I know.
I am the meanest person.
You've been in this country
a year.
Modify your nouns, damn it!
What... a... bitch.
I can't wait for you
to pop out that baby,
because when you do,
I am putting you on the first
plane back to shanghai,
and you're gonna be on all fours
in a rice paddy
before the epidural
wears off!
But you promised to get me
apartment in Chinatown,
so I can work for my friend
in restaurant, start a new life.
Tell it to my Chinese friend-
sue me!
You know, we do have people
here in the hospital
who could do that. But I like doing it.
I think Mike would want me to.
Oops. Oh.
So have you got the results
of his latest M.R.I. yet?
I'm afraid
there was no change.
Oh. Well, how long until
you can do another one?
I don't want to tell you
not to be optimistic, but-
look, I know it's been
six months,
but he could still
come out of it, right?
I saw in the news there was
this woman in Peru.
She woke up after ten years.
- There's a reason that made the news.
you might think I'm naive,
but I know
he's coming back to me.
Susan-
don't say it.
You just keep doing your job,
and I'll keep doing mine.
Oops.
(thunder rumbling)
That risotto was perfect.
Just like you.
Listen, I hope
you saved room for dessert.
I got us something special
from a wonderful little bakery
downtown.
Oh!
That is so adorable,
but I don't think
I can eat another bite.
Well, here,
let me take half.
What do you say, Bree?
Will you marry me?
(exhales deeply) This is
a little sudden, isn't it?
We've only known each other
six months,
but I've loved you
every minute of it.
But if you don't share
my feelings -
No, no. Um...
I do.
It's just that, um,
I can't help being cautious.
Since Rex, I haven't been
exactly lucky in love.
I used to feel
the same way.
When Alma left me,
I was shattered,
but I realize now it was
the luckiest day of my life
because it meant I was free
when I met you.
Luck can change, Bree.
Let me change yours.
Yes.
Yes?
Ian Hainsworth
had been miserable
ever since a tragic
horseback riding accident
had left his wife Jane
in a coma.
For the next three years,
he shied away
from all social contact
because he wanted to be alone
with his grief.
Then one day,
he met Susan Mayer,
who,
because of her own tragedy,
was just as miserable
as he was.
And a friendship
slowly blossomed,
because as everyone knows,
misery loves company,
And Ian was loving
this company...
more and more every day.
Two...
three - oh, itch, itch, itch,
itch, itch. Ooh!
Itch, itch, itch.
Do the nurses know
you do this?
Oh, hey! Um, you weren't
supposed to see that.
Well, clearly.
Now, you can buy my silence
if you'll have coffee
with me.
Oh, I would love to,
but I think I'm in a rush here.
I'm supposed to meet
my girlfriends for lunch
at 1:00. Is it 1:00 yet?
Well, you tell me.
I notice you're always rushing
into the hall to check the time,
so I, um...
Well, I bought you this.
Oh! Wow.
(chuckles nervously) Um...
I - I - I can't accept this.
This is too extravagant.
Oh, no, it's nothing.
There was
a guy on the sidewalk -
had a bunch of them
laid out on a blanket.
If you look closely,
it says "Folex."
(chuckles) Still, I -
Well, in that case, thank you
for my cheap knockoff.
(laughs)
Oh, my god. I'm late.
Hi! Hi, hi, hi.
Hi!
I'm so sorry I'm late.
No, that's fine.
Wow, white gloves.
What, are we having luncheon
in the 1880s?
Well,
it's a very elegant club.
You know, Orson’s been a member
here for years.
It'll be even nicer when
they finish the construction.
So you were very mysterious
on the phone.
Why did you wanna have lunch?
Well, I wanted to invite you
to a dinner
that Orson and I are having
this Saturday.
So you asked us to a meal
to announce another meal?
That's so... Bree of you.
(chuckles)
What's the occasion?
Oh, um, no occasion.
Just a little get-together.
What are you being
so coy about?
I'm not being coy.
She said coyly.
If you don't tell us,
we're not coming.
Oh, all right.
I wanted to wait and make
a proper announcement, but...
Orson and I are engaged.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, let me see!
(Lynette) Wow!
You move fast.
I know it's quick,
but it just feels so right.
Orson is just the most warm,
wonderful, generous man.
Oh, generous. That means
he's good in the sack.
Actually, uh, no.
We haven't had sex yet.
We're waiting
until we get married.
(laughing loudly)
Oh, my god.
You're serious?
(Gabrielle) No sex at all?
Not even...
Whatever you're alluding to,
no.
But - but you're gonna
get married.
You wouldn't buy a car
without at least taking it
for a little test drive.
It's not like
you've never slept with a guy
you weren't married to.
True. Uh, I have in the past
given myself away too freely.
How charming of you
to bring that up
while I'm announcing
my engagement.
But I like to think that
I have learned from my mistakes.
So the dinner is at 8:00,
and when we make
the announcement,
please, everybody, look surprised. Okay.
No, don't worry. I'm just
gonna replay the look I had
when I found out you hadn't
banged him yet. (gasps)
(helium inflating loudly)
(high-pitched voice)
Hey, sexy mama.
(laughs) That's cute.
(normal voice)
So you invited Kayla
to Parker's birthday party,
right?
Of course.
And?
- And?
What did you tell Nora?
I told her that we were
picking up Kayla
for a quiet afternoon
at home.
You lied?
Yeah, you're damn straight
I lied.
I will not have that lunatic
ruining one more family gathering.
But Kayla’s gonna, you know,
tell Nora that we had a party,
and I'm just afraid that
Nora’s gonna blow a gasket.
What?
So what are you saying,
you're more afraid of Nora
than you are of me?
Is - is that what you think
I meant because that is
so not what I meant.
You scare the hell
out of me, baby.
Thank you.
The coffee machine
was broken,
so I got us
a couple of smoothies.
They had strawberry
and strawberry.
Well, I hate strawberry,
so give me the strawberry.
(chuckles)
Hi, Jane.
- (Ian) Nothing-nothing against smoothies,
but I wouldn't mind having
some real food sometime.
May-maybe we could go
to a restaurant.
You mean,
like, outside the hospital?
Yeah, you know,
l-like a date.
A date? (gasps)
Oh, um...
There's a lovely little bistro
down the street.
(whispers) I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
(normal voice) Uh, well,
that sounds, uh, just-
that sounds great!
I mean, I hope that's okay.
Yeah! Uh...
So, I was, um,
I was thinking about
how that sounded just now-
the, uh, the-the date thing.
I really sprang it on you
out of nowhere.
Yes, you did.
Jane looked cold.
Oh. Thanks.
Look, we're, um, we're both
in difficult situations.
I've been in mine
a lot longer than you have,
so, uh, if you're not ready,
I understand.
If you ever should be,
uh, let-let me know.
All right. (sighs)
Wow, I am really hungry.
Well, then let's, um,
let's go to the blood bank
and swipe some-some sugar cookies.
Oh, uh, you might want
to give Jane a sponge bath
'cause she had a little...
accident.
Are you having a party?
Shh! Shh! (whispers loudly)
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet!
Shh! Yeah, no, no,
of course not. In fact,
we're just having
a quiet afternoon at home.
Um, the kids are so bored.
Tom and I were thinking of
taking 'em out for ice cream.
Well, would you tell Kayla
that mommy called
to check on her?
Oh, I will, I will,
and I'll see you tonight.
Okay. Bye.
You think she bought it?
No. I think she'll be
over here in ten minutes.
Okay, let's move! Let's move!
I've got 10 bucks here
for the kid who can
carry the most stuff, okay?
Hey, Gaby, it's Lynette.
Got a little emergency here.
Is it okay
if we use your backyard?
Great. Great.
And we take
complete responsibility
for whatever the pony does.
Hope you get
this message soon.
Oh!
My only concern would be
the neighborhood.
We really need a quiet place
for our retirement.
Oh, are you kidding?
There's no place in Fairview
that's more peaceful.
(Lynette) Stay off the pony!
Okay, guys,
come on, come on, come on!
(children
screaming and laughing)
Let me show you
the media room.
Okay, go on in.
Got the balloons?
Good. Good. All right.
Okay, all right, that's it.
Everybody's in.
Where's the cake?
Oh, crap!
(Nora) Yoo-hoo!
Anybody home?
Hello?
Hey, Nora.
Wow. We weren't expecting you
until 7:00.
So where's Kayla?
I thought I told you. Tom took
the kids to the movies.
Unh-unh. You said ice cream.
Uh-huh. After the movies.
Movies, then ice cream--
an American tradition.
So, is something wrong?
To be honest, I thought
that you were lying
and having a party.
I guess I was wrong.
Oh, apology accepted. Want me
to walk you to your car?
(toilet flushes)
Where did everybody go?
Nora, look,
I am sorry I lied,
but you know,
you gave me no choice, and--
Lynette,
I want my daughter.
Where's the damn party?
No, I'm not telling.
Where's the party?
(sighs)
No! No, no!
If you want in, you're gonna
have to go through me.
I want my kid, Lynette.
Kayla!
Kayla, come out here now!
What is going on?
Well, first you have a party,
and you don't invite me,
and then you lie about it,
so now we're leavin'.
Well, wait a minute.
Hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on, Kayla.
I'm sorry.
We're--we're sorry.
We--we shouldn't have
done that.
But look, Kayla is having
such a good time.
Why don't we all just
come on in and have some cake,
and we can just--
Lynette, Lynette.
We can just have fun.
Could you excuse me
for one second?
Lynette.
Okay, okay, I know,
but what else could I do?
I'm just thinking
of Kayla.
I know you are, Tom,
and I know you love her.
Why else do you think
I'm willing to put up
with all this for six months?
Why do you think I'm willing
to say to my college roommates,
"Yes, that's my husband's
love child and her mother
in our Christmas picture"?
Because I am your wife!
You always come first
with me.
Do I still come first
with you?
I guess I'll see you later,
Nora.
Well... I'm taking Kayla.
Well, that's a shame.
I've gotta go hoist
a piñata.
Mommy, they have a piñata.
Fine!
I'll be back at 7:00.
But there had better be
a corner piece of cake
waiting for me.
Come on, Kayla.
Go--go have some fun.
Go have some...
Thank you for that.
Sure.
I'll be back in 20 minutes.
Gonna go buy a piñata?
I sure am.
Xiao-mei?
Come on out!
I have your lunch.
Xiao-mei,
your favorite soap is on.
There's a doctor
fondling a patient
on the operating table.
You're missing it! Xiao-mei?
(man on TV)
Oh, I'll have to examine you.
(woman) Oh, again?
Xiao-mei?
Hey, quick question.
Have you, by any chance,
seen Xiao-mei?
I can't believe
you lost our baby.
I did not lose our baby.
Stop saying that.
I know exactly where it is--
inside some crazy Chinese woman
who also stole
half a chicken from my fridge.
(all speaking loudly
in Chinese)
Hi! Hi.
Liang, right?
Remember me?
Xiao-mei lives with me.
You came over. We had lunch.
You got some nerve showing
your face here. Get out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey!
Uh, what happened to that
famous Chinese hospitality?
Xiao-mei called me.
She said you threatened
to send her back to china
to work as a slave
in a rice paddy.
I... I may have mentioned
deportation,
but I didn't think
she'd take it personally.
Are you crazy?
It was banter.
I mean, has this country
come to the point where you
can't joke with the help?
You treat Xiao-mei
like dirt.
She's just
a poor, innocent girl
trying to live
the American dream,
just like your ancestors.
Oh, don't give me
that "we are the world" crap.
That woman's uterus is
harboring a stolen baby.
So if you know where she is,
you better start talking,
or else I'm gonna get
the health department down here
and take a closer look at what
you're serving as Mu shu pork.
Boy, those people just don't
have a sense of humor, do they?
I'm telling you,
at this number,
it's not gonna last long.
Well, we like the neighborhood,
but we've heard
that some odd things
have gone on with this house.
Complete fabrication.
Malicious lies spread
by jealous competitors.
Now you've gotta check out
this storage.
You're not gonna believe
what you can fit in here.
And now the media room.
Wow, you certainly devoured
that ice cream.
Can I get you anything else?
You tell me.
Hmm.
Orson...
Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm.
I thought we...
Orson.
Mm? Oh, I just assumed
now that we're engaged...
Well, does that change
our core values?
No. But when I saw you standing
in front of the freezer
with a clingy silk dress,
let's just say,
well, that challenged them.
(chuckles)
Well, I thought we agreed
we wanted our wedding night
to be perfect.
Yes, but actors want
opening night to be perfect.
That's why they rehearse.
(chuckles)
It'll be better this way.
Now... can I get you
some more ice cream?
Not in that dress.
Hi.
So I need to ask you
something.
Ian, you know,
from across the hall--
You met him.
Anyway... he sort of
asked me out...
on a date.
I know you're thrown.
I was thrown, too.
But he's really nice,
and...
I could sort of use someone
to talk to...
who also talks back.
the thing is...
I'm sort of lonely...
and the past six months
have been really hard on me.
So what I need is...
I need to know
that it's okay with you
if I go out with him.
Because if it's not,
I won't.
In fact, I'd like nothing
better than for you
to just wake up right now
and tell me
not to go out with him.
Just wake up and tell me.
Wake up. Please!
All right.
(sighs)
I'll see you tomorrow.
I love you.
It is really just dinner.
I'm just dropping off
Carlos,
and then I'll be by
to pick her up.
Okay, thanks, Edie.
Xiao-mei's fine. Crisis averted.
No harm, no foul.
How can you say that?
You endangered the life
of our baby today.
Don't you dare give me
that attitude.
You have no idea what
I've been going through
these past six months.
(sighs) Here we go.
I have had to wait
hand and foot on your mistress.
I mean, imagine if
the day after you found out
about John Rowland,
you had to make his lunch
and rub his feet.
Yeah, well, John Rowland
wasn't carrying our kid.
Forgive me for being concerned
about our surrogate.
Xiao-mei
is going to be fine.
Once that baby comes,
her slate is wiped clean.
She's gonna walk away,
go off and live
her American dream.
Me? I'm gonna be stuck,
a single mother
raising a child alone,
haggling with lawyers on
who gets the kid at Christmas.
My American dream
is officially dead.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
But just so you know,
my dream hasn't exactly--
(tires screech, engine roars)
Okay, so we will see you
Saturday,
and please pretend
to be surprised. Bye.
You told someone else?
Bree, I thought
the whole point of the party
was to announce
our engagement.
I just can't help it.
I like telling people.
Makes me feel...
I don't know.
makes me feel like
I'm starting over.
It feels good.
Feels good to me, too,
though.
Hmm.
(chuckles)
Ah, no hands. See?
Ahem.
Hmm.
Oh, you don't have
to wash those.
I already did that.
Oh, I found some streaks,
so I'm wiping them down
with undiluted red wine vinegar.
I've never heard of that.
Oh, sure.
For tougher spots,
I use a 50-50 mix
of denatured alcohol
and water.
Ah.
And for those really
intractable stains--
I mean, we're talking
shower doors--
I wipe on lacquer thinner
with a towel.
Bree?
(gasps)
(moaning)
(moaning continues)
Oh, Orson.
Ohh!
(grunting)
(giggling)
(groaning)
Uh... excuse me.
Hmm?
Did you lose something?
No. I just thought...
for you...
Oh! Um, I don't do that.
Why not?
I'm a republican.
I'm a libertarian.
I believe in minimizing
the role of the state
and maximizing
individual rights.
But, Orson!
Trust me.
I know what I'm doing.
Okay.
Aah! Oh, no!
What, you didn't just crack
that veneer again, did you?
I have to go.
Go? Go where?
And then it was like
something inside ruptured.
Well, not so much a rupture
as a spasm.
Waves of
this hot clutching.
I think I might have had
a small stroke.
How severe were the pains?
Well, that's the odd thing.
I mean, there was no pain
per se.
In fact,
it wasn't entirely unpleasant.
What were you doing
at the time?
I was, uh, with my fiancé.
We were lying down...
resting.
I'm gonna take
a wild swing here.
Were you having sex?
Sort of.
Ms. Van De Kamp, I think
you may have had an orgasm.
No, no, no.
I had orgasms before.
Mm, how would you
describe them?
Oh, you know,
that warm sensation,
that tingling feeling
of relief when it's over.
No, no, this was much...
Better?
Yes.
That's 'cause
it was an orgasm.
Oh.
Well, I'll be darned.
Hi. Can I help you?
Are you Bree Van De Kamp?
Yes, and you are?
Carolyn Bigsby.
I was Orson’s neighbor.
Oh, well, come on in.
Let's dry you off
and get you a drink.
I didn't come here
to celebrate.
Carolyn.
Engaged again?
That was quick work.
Does she know
you killed your wife?
My wife left me.
And no one ever heard
from her again.
Not me, not her family.
Just dropped off
the face of the earth.
Orson, what is she
talking about?
Didn't tell you that part,
did he?
All right, Carolyn,
you've made your little scene.
You keep your hands off me.
Don't let him fool you.
Get away from him now
while you can.
Please leave my house.
Fine. Be a fool.
Marry him.
Just don't be surprised
when you go missing, too.
I'm sorry you had
to endure that.
Your wife...
disappeared?
I tried to find her.
Her family claimed
not to have heard from her.
Personally, I think she was
just trying to punish me.
So...
are you still married?
No, I was granted a divorce
on grounds of abandonment.
Bree...
you can't possibly
think that--
No, of course not.
I love you.
And I love you.
Orson...
My hand.
(speaking indistinctly)
The buffet is open.
Bree...
Every storm
brings with it hope...
that somehow by morning,
everything
will be made clean again,
and even
the most troubling stains
will have disappeared,
like the doubts
over his innocence...
or the consequence
of his mistake.
Like the scars
of his betrayal...
or the memory of his kiss.
So we wait for the storm
to pass,
hoping for the best.
"Coming Soon...
Our New Pro Shop"
even though we know in our hearts...
some stains are so indelible...
nothing can wash them away.
sync:fisherchen ydy.com
corr:ixquic