My siblings and I are the
first vampires in history...
the Originals.
300 years ago, we helped
build the city of New Orleans.
We were happy here, a family.
Recently, a coven of witches
lured my brother back,
using his unborn child as leverage.
I tried to help him, but he
betrayed me to his enemy...
the vampire Marcel.
Since then, I have been held
prisoner by a powerful witch.
My brother seeks to manipulate
others to procure my release,
but I have my own plan.
If this witch proves to be an enemy,
I will stop her by
whatever means necessary.
You're the one they call honorable.
Yes.
That's what they call me,
and yet I followed my brother here
to New Orleans to engage in a war.
So I ask you,
does that sound honorable to you?
You don't look well.
Well, only this morning,
I had a mystical dagger
embedded in my chest.
So I'd say I'm holding
myself together quite well.
Davina, I believe that
you and I have the power
to end a war between witches and vampires
before it truly begins,
I by keeping my brother in line,
you by behaving as your true self,
not some tool for Marcel or the witches.
And why should I trust you?
Well, for one thing, in
spite of a ravenous hunger,
I have not tried to take your blood.
Why not? I'm the only one here.
Even in my present condition,
I would not feed... from a child.
We had a deal.
You protect my unborn child,
I dismantle Marcel's army,
and whilst I've been busy
fulfilling my part of the bargain,
you allowed Hayley to be attacked
and almost killed by a gaggle
of lunatic witches.
I had nothing to do with it, I swear.
Hayley and I are linked, remember?
She dies, I die.
Then who were they?
They're a faction of extremists.
Sabine stupidly told them about some vision
she had about the baby.
What kind of vision?
She has them all the time.
They're totally open to interpretation.
I'm guessing she's wrong on this one.
Well, how, may I ask,
was this particular vision interpreted?
Pretty much that your baby
would bring death to all witches.
Ah, well, I grow fonder of
this child by the second.
Sophie, look.
I promised Elijah that I would protect
the Mikaelson miracle baby
whilst he tries to win
your witch Davina's loyalty.
Why don't you tell me just
how extreme this faction is?
Elijah is talking to Davina?
Yeah, as we speak, I imagine.
I'm guessing she'll have
plenty to say about that crowd.
Do tell.
I wasn't always an
advocate for the witches.
Drink up, everybody!
This is how they party in Rio!
My sister was devoted like our parents,
and our upbringing was very strict,
which drove me nuts.
The minute I turned 21, I left the quarter
to travel and play, but
I wanted to be a chef.
So I came back to Rousseau's.
Yeah!
Oh, Jane-Anne. Hey! Hey, hey, hey.
That wasn't me. Hi!
Welcome home, Soph.
Can we go someplace to talk?
Just tell me.
The elders called a vote.
We're moving forward with the harvest.
What?
What the bloody hell is the harvest?
It's a ritual our coven
does every 3 centuries
so that the bond to our
ancestral magic is restored.
We appease our ancestors.
They keep our ancestral power flowing.
And why haven't I heard of this?
Because the harvest
always seemed like a myth,
a story passed down through generations
like Noah's ark
or the Buddha walking on water,
the kind some people take literally
and some people don't.
To be reborn, we must sacrifice.
To be reborn, we must have faith.
Do you have faith in the harvest?
Not for a second.
Sophie.
What are you doing?
Saving the community you renounced.
You're all ridiculous.
Monique? Seriously?
My mom told me I had to.
Yeah. Well, you mom and
I are gonna have words.
They had the girls of our community
preparing for months.
4 would be chosen for the harvest.
They said that it was an honor,
that they were special.
I thought it was a myth.
Was it?
Marcel, bit early in the
day for you, isn't it?
I know. I make this look easy,
but I still have an empire to run.
Rather you than me.
All that responsibility
seems like such a bore.
Well, this might spice things up.
I just heard about a bunch
of dead witches out in the bayou
the kind of damage a werewolf might do,
only there was no full moon.
I have an informant out
there I need to meet,
and I would love for you to go with me.
Dead witches in the bayou.
Sounds like less of a problem
and more like a cause for celebration.
Well, something killed them
and may still be out there,
and with your blood the only cure
for a werewolf bite, I would love
for you to accompany me.
Well, why not?
I haven't been to the bayou in ages.
I'm on my way.
Peace out, brother.
This is the one.
You can't go out there now.
I need to gather the witches' remains
and consecrate them.
If I don't get to them before sundown,
we lose the link to their magic.
Those witches tried to kill Hayley.
I prefer for Marcel's
informant not to find anything
that would lead him back to us,
to her, or to, you know, that.
You are all class.
Stay put and save the rest
of your story till I return.
Look who's back.
Here to visit your prisoner in the attic?
Lay off. She's not a prisoner,
and I'm moving her tonight.
Too many people know where she is.
I have been hearing about
what you've been up to
since I've been out of town.
Using that girl to keep the
witches from doing magic?
All respect, Father K.,
if you're gonna defend
the witches' rights,
we got nothing to talk about.
Do you play?
That's... not mine.
Good news, little D.
I'm moving you out of this pile of dust.
Are you serious? When?
Tonight.
I just need to lock in the arrangements.
How's our Original?
Don't disturb the body.
I have a spell in progress.
Bet you do.
Pack up, ok,
only what you want to take.
I'll buy you anything else you need.
All right.
You didn't reveal that I was awake.
We're not done talking yet.
You and Marcel seem very close.
Marcel is my family.
And yet Marcel is someone who delights
in harming the witches,
those people, I would think,
you would consider family.
This doesn't trouble you?
No. They deserve it.
Why would you say that?
Because they're liars, all of them.
They made me and my friends
do this harvest ritual.
They said our participation
would bring our family strength, health...
That we'd forever be celebrated
as saviors of the community,
but all they really wanted was more power.
So I left before they could get it,
and now they're running out of time
because after the harvest
comes the reaping,
and if they don't complete the harvest,
there won't be a reaping.
Soon, all the witches in the quarter
will start to lose their power.
Eventually, they'll cease
to be witches altogether.
So what does it take
to complete this ritual?
I have to die.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Ok.
Hey, what the hell?
You're going out there, anyway, aren't you.
I want to go with you.
No, thanks.
Already got assaulted
by Klaus this morning,
don't need a repeat.
What if whatever is responsible
for all those dead
witches is still out there?
We've already established that
it likes me and hates witches.
So you'll be safer with me.
Sorry if I'm not buying
your sudden concern for my safety.
Listen.
The whole reason I came to this stupid town
in the first place was to
learn more about my family.
Your sister is the one that told me Marcel
ran the werewolves out of the quarter
into the bayou, and last night,
pretty sure that some
guardian angel wolf saved my life.
So I'm coming with you.
Could you two be more idiotic.
Two can play the follow game, you know?
You heard Klaus.
He and Marcel are heading
right where you're going.
So distract them because unless
you want to lock a hormonal,
pregnant werewolf in a tomb,
I'm coming with you,
and wouldn't Elijah be mad if he hears
that the baby and I died of asphyxiation?
What's the matter, Rebekah?
You cross that I'm out with your ex?
What is all that dreadful
hillbilly racket in the background?
According to the dreadful signage,
it's Big Augggie's bayou bar.
Well, order up a few rounds of moonshine
and stay clear of the
dead witches for a few.
The witch is on a burial mission,
your baby mama is on a spirit quest,
and I'm keeping Elijah's
promise to keep her safe.
So stall, please.
Everything ok?
Oh, just the usual... temperamental sister.
So where's your informant?
Tomas? He's out sniffing around.
Grab a drink. Then we'll chase him down.
Well, I suppose it will give
us a chance to talk things over,
like why you haven't returned Elijah.
Maybe your young witch
has grown partial to his company.
She must get so bored.
You never stop, do you?
You never answer, do you?
Why are you so curious about Davina?
If I had a 16-year-old all-powerful witch
at my beck and call,
you would wonder about her, too.
You're never gonna get her.
Ok. Ok.
I'll ask the harmless questions, then.
How did you meet her?
Ha ha ha!
That might surprise you.
This was 8 months ago,
before I banned the
witches from using magic.
Relations between vampires and witches
weren't what you'd call friendly,
by any means, but let's just say,
we were a little less divided.
In fact, some of us were
getting along just fine.
Oh, it's so screwed up.
I'm dealing with whacked
out, militant witches.
Hey, you witches all got
a little crazy in you.
Oh, and my sister has really gone
off the deep end this time.
Yeah. Jane-Anne has got martyr
written all over her.
That's for sure.
They've got every 16-year-old girl
in our coven dying to
be one of the 4 chosen
for this crazy-ass ritual.
Anything I can do to help?
No. You've caused enough trouble with them.
What, little, old me?
You're a dick.
You always stir it up with the witches,
which is why this...
stays between us.
You and Sophie? You hypocrite.
Ha ha ha!
You torture those witches,
and yet there you are, getting positively
"Romeo and Juliet" with Sophie Deveraux.
Oh, it wasn't like that.
It was a mutually satisfying hookup.
So if Sophie didn't turn to you,
her secret vampire lover,
in her hour of need,
what did she do?
She did what any good girl would do.
She went to her priest.
You've never cared about
witch business, Sophie,
and now you have the gall to reveal
our private dealings to an outsider.
You have to find another way.
You think we do this lightly?
The vampire presence in the
quarter is growing stronger.
We need more power to fight them off.
Harsh times call for harsh measures.
This is a little more than harsh, Bastiana.
You don't understand
because you don't believe.
You've never believed, but I believe enough
to put everything on the line for this,
and being chosen for the offering,
it's an honor.
It's a myth, Jane-Anne.
What you are planning
to do is not only wrong.
In my city, it's illegal.
In your city full of vampires?
The vampires and the human faction
have an arrangement, just
like we have with you all.
Protect the locals, protect our homes,
we look the other way.
What you are planning goes too far.
We are simply taking what we need.
Our connection to our
ancestors weakens over time.
You sow, and you reap.
That's the way the harvest works.
I am the only ally you
witches have in this town.
Do you really want to
face Marcel without me?
Because that is what you'll be dealing with
if you go through with the harvest.
Everything ok in here, Uncle Kieran?
We were just finishing, Sean,
right?
I believe I've made myself clear.
We'll take this matter to the elders.
Continue to study, Sean.
Your Uncle is an excellent role model.
The witches were furious with Kieran.
Sophie tells me that the witches put a hex
on his nephew Sean, made it seem like
he was slowly losing his mind,
in order to distract Kieran
while they kept planning for the harvest.
So they attacked Kieran's nephew.
Yeah. Kid wasn't the same after that,
ended up going postal,
killing all his fellow seminary students,
all of them, and then himself.
I might have read about that.
The boy killed a twin,
or he was a twin or something.
Oh, no, no.
They said that he had a twin sister.
So enlighten me.
What did you mean when
you said you had to die?
That's what the harvest was.
They said they'd put us 4 girls
in a state of, like, peaceful limbo
as part of the offering,
and then later at the reaping,
we'd awaken and be reborn.
I never got as far as the limbo part,
which means the harvest isn't complete.
That's why the witches are so freaked out.
The reaping is just around the corner,
and if they don't finish it before then,
it's over.
All I have to do is wait it out.
And then what?
They're punished, and I'm free.
From Marcel?
Of magic.
All our power will drain away.
I'll be normal.
Is that what you want, to be normal?
I just don't want to be what I am.
I can't control it sometimes, magic.
I... hurt people,
even when I don't mean to.
Why don't you tell me about your friends?
You must miss them.
There's Tim.
He doesn't know about
any of this witch stuff.
He's normal.
My best friend Monique...
she was a part of the harvest, too.
She's lucky.
No one ever fought for me,
but someone fought for her.
The only one who ever spoke out
against the harvest was Monique's aunt.
And who is that?
Sophie Deveraux.
So this harvest thingee,
tell me more.
Klaus said to wait.
Yes. He also said to stay out of the bayou,
and yet here we are amongst
the crawly, buzzy creatures.
We're here.
Is that a wolf track?
Who's there?
What the hell?
An Original?
Let me understand this.
Against all logic, you and Hayley went
to the bayou, where you ran into a man
you think may be Marcel's informant,
and then you lost him.
Yes, and now that we've established
that I am a failure as a sister
and a friend and an Original,
you should probably know he's on his way
to Marcel right now to rat me out...
skinny guy in a hurry,
looks like he saw a ghost?
I'll handle it. I'll need a distraction.
I'm on my way.
Your sister again?
She craves attention. So come on.
You were just getting to the juicy bits.
I can't joke around about this.
I've done a lot in my day,
but I do have a rule about kids.
No one but Sophie ever
questioned the harvest,
not even my own mother.
So neither did I.
We thought it was such an honor.
We had such faith. We were so stupid.
So how did it begin?
We were led out like princesses.
My mother was so proud.
Our magic fades
as our ties to our ancestors
weaken over time.
We beseech them accept this offering
as a sign of our faith.
Bastiana, one of the elders,
called upon the 4 elements to bind
our past and future magic together...
Earth to connect us to our ancestors,
water to heal the community,
wind to carry us to our
ancestors and back...
Fire to purify.
After all our preparation,
we knew exactly what to expect.
For weeks, they told us that the magic
in the knife they used to cut our palms
would put us to sleep and that later
at the reaping, we
would all be resurrected.
They said we'd awaken and all be together
and more powerful than ever,
and it was just like we rehearsed it.
All that was left was just a little cut
on our palms for the blood sacrifice.
No! Stop!
Bastiana, stop. You have to stop.
Bastiana, please don't do this.
Even after Sophie tried to stop it,
we didn't suspect anything.
To be born, you must sacrifice.
Do you have faith?
They're gonna kill you!
Oh, my God! No!
Please stop!
Everyone involved in the ritual
knew that this would happen.
Except the 4 of us.
They weren't putting us to sleep.
They were slaughtering us.
Oh! No! Stop! No, no!
Monique Deveraux.
No! No!
Don't go, Monique!
I begged for someone to help.
My own mother turned away from me.
Sophie screamed and
screamed for her sister,
anyone to do something...
What is wrong with you?
But no one did.
Yet you survived.
Therefore, someone or something intervened.
Yes.
Someone finally did.
Monique, run away! Run away.
Marcel.
You're the one who stopped it.
Kieran knew every detail from Sophie.
After his nephew's massacre in the church,
he was so torn up, he left town
just before the harvest,
but on his way out,
he came to me, and he asked me
to stop the harvest.
He knew I didn't want the witches
getting any more power,
and I do have a rule
about people abusing kids.
So I did what he asked, but I was too late.
Oh, God! Monique!
Oh! No!
Oh, let go of me!
Stop it! Stop it! Let go of me!
Stop it!
There was something
about seeing Davina fight.
She didn't just go along to the slaughter,
you know?
I do...
Marcellus.
I felt like she and I,
we were kindred spirits.
Every girl who died released
her power on to the next.
When I was the last one,
I suddenly had all of it,
all the power that was supposed to be
released back into the earth
to appease our ancestors.
So the harvest was actually working.
Something was working, and I knew that I
was supposed to be killed so the harvest
could be completed and we would all
be resurrected, but they lied to us
about how they were killing us.
How do I know they weren't lying to us
about coming back?
But mostly, I just didn't want to die.
So I let him save me. Marcel saved my life.
You're quite the knight in shining armor,
though Davina must realize you owe her
as much as she owes you.
You never could have banned the witches
from using magic without her.
She's not exactly besties with them.
I'm protecting her.
A lot of them would like to get their hands
on her and kill her to finish the harvest.
If they don't, the other girls stay dead,
and they lose their power.
And if they do, you lose yours.
And Davina loses her life.
Ah, isn't this like old times?
Just how drunk are you two?
Skating on the razor's edge.
I'm gonna use the loo.
Back in a tick.
I haven't seen his this
lushy since the twenties.
So you came to take him home?
Why else would I be here?
I don't know.
Maybe to make sure I didn't get too drunk
and spill secrets better left unspilled
about you and me.
I know better.
I hope so because you don't want
to end up on the wrong side of me.
Oh, Rebekah Mikaelson, you do not want
to be on the wrong side of me.
Tomas, I presume.
Marcel asked me to find out
what you know about the dead witches.
I heard they were going after
some pregnant werewolf.
She was stupid being out there all alone.
Yeah. She was. Yeah. She was.
It's amazing how gullible
some people can be.
Yeah.
You may return this now
to its rightful owner.
It's restored.
I don't even know if I'll see him again.
Davina, this power that you contain
drawn from your fallen friends,
it's too much for you.
You need control.
That requires study and practice.
My mother was a very powerful witch.
She left behind her grimoires,
a legacy of books filled with spells.
These books contain all of the tools
that you might need to control your magic.
If you free me from here,
I can share them with you.
However, if you leave now with Marcel,
we'll never see each other again,
and I cannot find you,
and I can't help you.
The witches manipulated me.
You know how that ended.
This is not manipulation.
This is one thing in exchange for another.
I'm offering you a deal.
That was fast work, Rebekah.
Where's Marcel,
in there touching up his lipstick?
Credit me with some taste.
It's filthy in there. Where'd he go?
He didn't tell you he was leaving?
No.
Do you think he realized
we were stalling him?
No...
Unless he was stalling us.
Ok. Now is our shot.
You ready to blow this joint?
Can't wait. All right.
We'll leave Elijah
behind as a parting gift.
Might buy me a little forgiveness
for pulling one over on his siblings.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
What's happening?
I don't know. Something is wrong.
Hey...
Marcel, there's something
dangerous out there.
Take me back.
Damn it.
No one is gonna look for you here.
It's only for a little while
till I can get you out of
town and someplace safe.
For now, I can get you whatever you want.
What do you like to do?
Draw.
An artist, huh? That's cool. Ok.
I can buy out Vincent's for you tomorrow,
maybe get you some curtains or...
Marcel...
You know what I really want?
I want to make them pay.
Elijah?
I'm pleased you stayed.
You'll keep your promise
about your mother's spell book?
I will.
You know, difficulties aside,
I value my family above everything.
I am sorry that yours failed you.
Your brother Klaus handed
you to Marcel in a box,
yet you still don't give up on him.
Well, I've given up on giving up.
It's an affliction.
I will fight for my family
until my last breath.
And I'll fight the witches until mine.
Now what?
You're just gonna leave her
up there for anybody to find?
I'm not in the mood, Kieran.
You were supposed to get
her out of New Orleans
after the harvest.
We failed those other 3
girls. We didn't fail her.
That is why I came to you for help.
That was the plan.
Plans change.
Especially after you found out
how powerful she was.
Let's get something straight.
For 8 months since you left,
I've been running this town just fine.
I don't need you coming back
and getting in my business.
I will do what I want where I want. Got it?
You want to be the boss?
You want to call the shots?
Fine, but I call the
shots with the humans...
and you don't want to make an enemy of me.
So I would suggest one thing...
stay away from my niece.
Fine. Who the hell is your niece?
Cami.
Those people,
all this because of a vision about my baby
you don't think is true.
Look.
I love Sabine,
but she's the witch
equivalent of a drama queen.
I've learned to take little stock
in whatever she says or sees.
Just kind of wish she'd
kept her mouth shut.
The harvest ritual.
You said you didn't believe in it.
Were you right?
No.
I saw it with my own eyes.
It was working. It was real.
So how can you be so sure
Sabine's vision isn't?
Taking me on a field trip to distract me,
pathetic and obvious.
I taught you better than that.
You taught me to protect what's mine.
You'll not take Davina
from me, end of story.
An immutable law of nature, Marcel is,
the strong always take from the weak.
Oh, if you were so strong,
you wouldn't have run away from new Orleans
like a little bitch all those years ago.
You've been playing king with a
bunch of children for too long.
Don't mistake me for one
of your nightwalker lackeys, Marcel.
I can take Davina any time I like.
What the...
Do forgive me, Marcel.
If anyone is to teach my brother a lesson,
it's me.
I don't care if we have to get you a leash.
That was your last trip to the bayou.
What is it with you and
those wolves, anyway?
I feel like we're connected somehow.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just some pipe dream that I have
of finding any real family out there,
but sometimes when I feel
like it's me against the world,
it keeps me going.
Oh, right.
Well, if you ask me,
family is a pain in the behind,
and as for being in it alone,
how dare you?
I don't ruin a perfectly
fabulous pair of boots
traipsing through the
bayou for just anyone.
Nik, finally. What...
Oh, Elijah...
You're safe.
Now that you're home,
is your first plan to kill Niklaus?
Excuse me just a moment.
Where's he going?
You're back.
I am.
Don't make promises you can't keep.
Welcome home.
Everything that brought
us here to New Orleans
was a lie... this story that
Sophie Deveraux fabricated,
this struggle for control
of the French quarter.
This war between vampires and witches
wasn't over territory at all.
This was over Davina.
I swear I had no idea
that the harvest could possibly be real.
But the one thing that you were sure of
is that I was wrong and that I would risk
Monique's life on a maybe,
and now my daughter is dead.
Please tell me how to fix this.
Now that Marcel has Davina,
how are we even supposed to find her?
If we don't finish the harvest,
Monique and those two other
girls are dead for real.
Look at me.
You and I are gonna find a way
to get Monique back.
It'll be our little secret.
We'll do it together.
We'll seal off the cemetery
from the vampires, find Davina,
stop Marcel,
and finish the ritual once and for all,
even if I have to slit
Davina's throat myself.
8 months ago, Sophie Deveraux
and her sister Jane-Anne lost everything.
Now, 4 months after that,
a young, pregnant girl
wanders into their restaurant.
Suddenly, all hope is renewed.
Jane-Anne actually sacrificed her life
so that her sister could
use you to find Davina.
If Sophie Deveraux is
successful in capturing Davina,
she can return Jane-Anne's
daughter back to life.
We thought we'd come here
to wage a war for power.
This is about family.
In order to return her niece to life,
Sophie Deveraux will fight to the death.
That makes her more dangerous than anyone.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -