Previously on Desperate Housewives...
While Ian's wife Jane
was in a coma...
Do we have a deal?
Susan got an ultimatum.
He's not crazy about me
spending time with my ex.
Mike's new hero...
Owe you one.
After those mutts knocked you around
the other day, your boy paid 'em off.
...had a secret agenda
Gabrielle.
Gabrielle learned the identity...
I’m rich now. I can give you
anything you want.
...of her secret admirer.
Tell me everything.
and Orson's mother shared some
family secrets that Bree...
...would later discover.
If there was one thing Orson Hodge
understood, it was teeth.
that's why people stopped him
at barbecues...
during cocktail parties...
and in the occasional men's room.
Yes, when it came to teeth,
people expected Dr. Hodge
to have all the answers.
sadly for Orson,
this was not always the case.
Well, it does look  a little fishy.
Fishy?
It couldn't be more obvious.
Alma killed Monique.
That's why she disappeared.
And I bet she pulled the teeth so people
would suspect her dentist husband.
Well, why would she keep them?
Who knows ? She's probably gonna sneak
in and plant them in our house.
Well, we've saved her the trouble,
haven't we? Is it a full set?
- Orson! Not on the duvet!
- Oh, it's okay. They won't stain.
I don't care! I am not sleeping
in a bed
that had your dead
mistress' teeth in it!
Let's just take them to the police.
And say what? We can't prove
these came from Alma's.
She'll deny ever having seen. And don't
forget, I’m the one they suspect.
Well, we have to do something.
I agree, but not until we put
this back in her house.
And then we'll call the police.
Trust me, she'll never get away with it.
Hello.
You've been very naughty, haven't you?
Orson? Is that you?
I know what you and alma are
up to, and it's gonna stop.
Yes, Orson was an expert on teeth.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
oh, I think you do.
That's how he could tell when
people were lying through them.
Transcript :
Sub-Way.fr
Synchro :
FRM Team & Yellow Sub
Desperate Housewives - Saison 3
Episode no 13 "Come Play With Me"
It can happen so quickly.
In the moment it takes a gunman's bullet
to enter his victim's leg...
in the time it takes to tell a wife her
husband won't be home for dinner...
in the instant it takes a father to meet
his son for the very first time...
yes, life as we know it can change...
in a heartbeat.
Jane's still
running a fever.
Yes,
and she hasn't responded
To any of the meds
that we've tried.
Do you think
we should call her husband?
Uh, not just yet.
Let's try vancomycin.
It worked for her before.
I don't want ian to worry.
(Susan) this is
your new lawyer, alan marcus.
Alan, this is mike delfino.
Hey, mike. Sorry i couldn't
start on your case sooner.
I was wrapping up
an armed robbery trial.
It's nice
to finally meet you.
And you must be ian.
I can't thank you enough
for helping me out here.
Susan and i are happy
to be of assistance.
(Susan)
so should we get started?
Sure.
So, mike,
I've had a chance to review
all the evidence against you,
And i've got a strategy
To ensure your case
never goes to trial.
Don't you love this guy?
What's the strategy?
Pleading guilty?
What kind of a strategy is that?
He'd only be pleading
to manslaughter.
That's still
ten years in prison.
Well, which is better
And that's what mike's risking
if he goes to trial.
With good behavior,
he could be out in five.
With a better lawyer,
He ???
We need to find a lawyer
who believes that he's innocent.
Well, the evidence against him
is very compelling.
You're letting your feelings
for him cloud your judgment.
My "feelings for him"?
Are we gonna do this again?
Do you realize that
every conversation we have
Winds up being about mike?
"Who's the best lawyer for mike?
How can we get mike acquitted?"
I have told you i love you
a thousand times.
Where is all this jealousy
coming from?
Do you know what?
I have to catch
that plane to montreal.
What? No, ian,
we have to talk about this.
I can't be late.
It's business.
Look, i have provided mike
with the best lawyer i know.
If you want to get someone else,
then you're on your own.
(Parker) whatcha doing?
Oh, deciding what to wear
on my first day back to work.
Do i look fat in this?
I think you look good
in everything.
Wow. Your father
has taught you well.
What about the street fair?
If you're going back to work,
who's gonna take me?
Mrs. Mccluskey.
Won't that be fun?
No.
Do y have to
go back to work?
Come on. You and your brothers
will be thrilled.
Don't you get tired of me
yelling at you
To clean up your room
and finish your homework?
Yeah,
But you've been a lot nicer
since you got shot.
Oh.
Well, that's good to know.
When you think about it,
Me going back to work
is not that big a deal.
We're only losing a ttle time
together in the afternoon.
But every hour counts.
I miss you all day long.
Oh, honey...
jeez.
Do you really mean that,
Or are you manipulating mommy
into feeling incredibly guilty?
A little bit of both.
Yep. Your father's
taught you well.
(Vern) the suspense
is killing me.
(Whispering)
shh! Shh! Here it comes.
(Man) and now the moment
we've all been waiting for...
the winner of this year's
Little miss snowflake pageant
is...
sherri maltby!
I'm in shock. I mean, i knew
she had a shot at the top five,
But to actually win?
I was sure she'd lose
to that little blonde bitch
Who sang
that patriotic medley.
I know. She practically had
sparklers coming out of her ass.
(Laughs) totally shameless.
Mm.
Okay, hon,
let's go meet those reporters.
What are y gonna tell 'em?
I owe it all
to "beauty by vern."
Attagirl.
Oh, zach.
What are you doing here?
I came to support you.
Oh. Okay, why don't you
support me from the lobby?
I have some networking to do.
My girl just won the pageant.
Oh, yeah, i know,
and you're welcome.
What did you do?
Don't worry.
I paid the judges in cash.
There's no paper trail.
You bribed the judges?!
Gabrielle, why are we fighting?
We should be celebrating.
I got a limo outside,
a bottle of chilled cristal.
Let's party.
Come on. Let's go.
Listen to me,
U ???
You and i
are never going to "party."
In ft, the only reason
We're ever gonna
be in the same room again
Is ???
God, i love it
when we banter.
Ugh.
(Orson) hello, alma.
Orson.
Uh, i let myself in.
I hope you don't mind.
Not at all.
You seem very cheerful.
Oh, i am,
'Cause the game's over,
and you lost.
I told you what i'd do
if you pushed me away.
Well, i'm afraid that threat
no longer has any teeth in it.
Yes, your mother told me
about bree's little discovery.
What'd you do
with monique's teeth?
Well, maybe i threw them away.
Maybe i hid them here.
You might find them,
If the police
don't find them first.
Oh, i don't think you'll
bring the police into this.
Well, neither will you now.
We're done. Why don't you do us
all a favor and go away?
You shouldn't
treat me this way.
Don't bother crying.
Tears might've worked
when we were married,
After you lost the baby.
They won't work now.
We should have kept trying.
Ife'e'd had a child,
we'd still be together.
I know.
That's why i stopped trying.
Good-Bye, alma.
Well,
here's some sucky news--
Ken just quit.
Your new manager? No.
Yeah,  i'm screwed.
I'm gonna have to drop out
of the street fair.
Tom, no.
You can't. You can't.
The pizzeria opens in a week,
and that street fair
Is the best advertising
we're gonna get.
I know,
but i can't work it alone.
Well, you know,
hire someone else.
Well, there's no time
fothat.
The future of the restaurant
is at stake.
It is time to get creative.
Well,
i do have one option,
But it would require some sacrifice.
Well, whatever it is ???
You could help me.
What?! No.
Unh-Unh.
Look, i'm wearing makeup.
I am holding a briefcase.
What does this suggest to you?
You could call in sick.
I can't call in sick
after eight weeks of sick leave,
Especially when i've been fine
for three of them.
Oh! Crap, that's ed.
Lynette? Lynette, please?
You're the one who said
that we need the street fair.
My boss is waiting for me
outside in his car.
What am i supposed to do?
It's time to get creative.
Oh, there she is.
Oh.
(Weakly) hey, guys.
Boy, didn't expect you
to still be wearing a sling.
Yeah, it heals
a little slower
When the bullet's
still in there.
Oh. They couldn't
get it out?
No, it's too close.
To what?
Everything.
God, i'm so sorry.
Oh. (Chuckles)
Hey, you got a little, uh,
cereal right...
cereal?
I didn't have any, uh...
oh, i know what that is.
I get nauseous
from the pain,
So that's just
a little residual vomit.
Lynette, you sure you're ready
to come back to work?
Yeah! Don't be silly.
I'm fine.
Come on. Let's go
sell some toothpaste.
All righty! Let's go.
(Gasps) ow!
Ow! Son of a bitch!
Oh! No, no! I'm sorry!
Don't touch me, okay?
Anything we can do?
My pills!
My pain pills are in my bag.
Thanks.
Oh! Oh, my pills!
(Whining) i need my pills,
and now they're all dirty!
See ya next week!
Thanks for understanding!
Hey. Looks like
an interesting book.
What's it about?
Never mind.
I'll wait for the movie.
What's eating you?
Those two guys
you saved me from?
I know you paid 'em
to attack me.
That's a lie.
(Grunts) hey!
You wanna take a minute
to reconsider that?
Okay. Okay. I needed a favor,
and i wanted you to owe me.
What favor?
You sure you want
to get into this now?
Yeah.
Okay.
You remember my son zach?
Vaguely. Why?
Turns out you and i share
more than a cellblock.
Hello, bree.
May i come in?
What's a garden
without a snake?
I realize
i'm not your favorite person,
But i thought you should know
why alma's moved here.
She wants orson back.
Thanks for the heads-Up.
Now off you go.
Orson and i
may have our spats,
T i'm still deeply concerned
about the state of his soul.
Adultery is a sin.
I wouldn't worry
about orson's soul.
He won't be
sleeping with alma.
When i said "adultery"...
i wasn't referring
to orson and alma.
I meant orson and you.
Excusee?
Our church
doesn't accept divorce.
In the eyes of god,
you're the other woman.
I'm sure you don't
see it that way,
But alma and i do...
and orson's beginning to.
Are those shoes suede?
Yes. Why?
No reason.
Why the hell didn't anybody
tell me i had a son?
You'd just
come out of a coma.
They probably figured
you had enough on your plate.
Well, why are you
telling me now?
Zach and i
haven't spoken in months.
Every time i've tried to contact
him, he won't return the calls.
I don't know
what you expect me to do.
I barely remember the kid.
Yes, but he remembers you,
And i think if you reach out
to him, he'll talk to you.
Zach is all i have left
in the world.
Through everything
that's happened,
I've never stopped
lovingim.
Can you please get him
to come down here and see me?
That's one hell of a favor.
Man, you got some nerve.
I know.
It's kind of what
got me in here.
Is it gaby's birthday?
No, they're probably
from zach young.
What?
You haven't heard?
He has been begging gaby
to go on a date with him.
He's been sending her
all sorts of stuff to bribe her,
Ev a a diamond bracelet.
Zach young?
Mmmm.
Our zach young?
How does he afford diamonds?
His grandfather
left him all that money.
Yeah, i thought
it was in a trust,
And he couldn't touch it.
Until he turned 18,
which was a month ago.
Wow.
So zach young
is loaded, huh?
No. Absolutely not.
Oh, come on.
Mike needs a great lawyer.
Zach can afford a great lawyer.
I don't care. I'm not
going out with zach young!
It's one little date.
You wouldn't even let your own
daughter go out with him.
You said he was a psycho.
He's matured... to the tune
of a billion dollars.
Please do this... for mike.
Susan, do you know what
Your obsession with mike
has cost you?
First you piss off bree
and then ian,
And--And now you're
pimping me out to a teenager!
Okay, i deserve
the pimping remark,
But let's not pretend that,
you know, we're above teenagers.
Gaby...
you're all i've got.
Oh, fine, i'll do it.
Thank you! This is
a noble thing you're doing.
How n you be so sure
zach's gonna go along with this?
Oh, 'cause he's a great kid,
And he's gonna
want to help mike...
and you're not gonna be wearing
a bra when you ask him out.
Ooh, can you guys
just, uh, take five, please?
(Mrophone feedback whines)
Gabrielle,
what are you doing here?
Wow, you have your own
recording studio in your house?
Yeah, i needed a place
to lay some tracks with my band.
You, um, you see that guy?
He used to tour
with the doobie brothers.
How wild is that?
(Laughs) gee, well...
not as wild
as what i'm about to say.
You can take me to dinner.
Seriously? Awesome!
Yeah, here's how
it's gonna work--
We drive to the restaurant
separately,
We will not have dessert,
And under no circumstances
will you touch me. Capisce?
Um... okay.
Great. In order for
this magical night to occur,
You're gonna need
to help mike delfino.
Mike? What happened?
'S in jail... for murder.
But susan swears he's innocent,
And she wants you
to get him a good lawyer.
All right, we have a deal?
No.
No?
Oh, i-I would love
to help mike.
It's just that, uh, if i'm
paying for a lawyer, you know,
I would like to have more
than just one meal with you.
I'd likeo have
a whole day.
A whole day?
Yeah, here's how
it's gonna work--
Um, it's gonna be three meals
with dessert,
Activities of my choosing
and a...
a good night kiss.
Now do we--
Do we have a deal?
Not quite.
The day starts with lunch,
and that kiss--Off the table.
Did they set bail for mike?
You know, 'cause i-I could
throw that in, too.
$1 million.
It's no biggie.
One call to my accountant,
and mike's a free man.
Or do you
want to tell susan
That mike's gonna stay in jail
because you wouldn't kiss me?
Okay, deal,
you little skunk.
Here you go.
You can come back for seconds.
Our famous pepperoni pizza.
Here's another
canadian bacon.
There yogogo.
Great. Guess what? Our line
is the biggest one at the fair.
I counted.
(Laughs) you know
what i'm starting to think?
What?
This restaurant is gonna be
a big, fat hit.
Here you go.
Can i talk to you
about something?
I think you hurt
lynette's feelings
When you refused to go
to the street fair with her.
She's gonna start to think
you don't like her.
You don't want that,
do you?
Doorbell.
(Under breath) some of 'em should be left
on a hillside to rot.
Hi.
I'm ed ferrara, lynette's boss.
Is, uh, she around?
Uh, well, actually,
She's at the, uh, uh,
the, uh, doctor's.
Oh. Yeah. Well,
could you give h this?
Oh. Sure.
And tell her to get well.
Mm-Hmm.
And she doesn't need
to come back to work
Till she's good and ready.
I will make sure
she gets this.
Okay.
Excuse me. Mister?
I just wanted to tell you
Our babysitter
gets mixed up sometimes.
Lynette's
not at the doctor's.
She's not?
Nope.
Well... where is she?
Excuse me.
Hey.
Try some of that. Hey.
Load me up again,
would ya?
Yeah?
I'm gonna go
poach some customers
Sausage-On-A-Stick guy.
From that
oh, i love it ???
Scavo's pizzeria!
Try the smoked chicken
and sundried tomato. Mmm!
Mmm!
Oh!
This crust is fantastic!
It's cornmeal.
That's the secret. (Laughs)
It's not your only secret,
is it, lynette?
Uh, hi, ed.
How's the arm?
Uh... uh, on the mend,
But i'm gonna be there
bright and early monday morning.
Don't bother. You're fired.
(Gasps) wait, ed!
Ed, please don't go.
Yes, i lied, and that was wrong,
but my husband needed my help.
I need your help. You've been
gone eight weeks, with pay,
While the company's
been falling apart.
Okay--
And now
you pull this on me?
Like i said,
really, really wrong,
But if you take me back,
i swear i will give you 100%.
So... if we have to work late,
you're gonna do it.
If i ask you to miss
your kid's baseball game,
You're gonna say,
"no problem, ed"?
You got it, ed.
Good. I'll see you monday.
Hi. It's--It's me.
Um, listen,
we--We--We have to talk.
Ian, i'm sorry, too. We've got
to stop fighting like this.
Susan, um,
jane's doctor called me.
She's--She's taken
a bad turn.
Oh. Ian...
i'm, uh, i'm on
the next flight out,
But it's not for aew hours,
and jane's parents are in rome.
Would, uh, would you go
to the hospital for me?
The hospital?
Well, i-I know
it's a lot to ask,
But if something
should happen, i--
Well, i don't want her
to be alone.
Oh ???
I can't believe you talked me
into that crème brûlée.
Oh, don't feel guilty.
I'm sure we burned it offon the
I know!
You're such a good dancer!
Mm-Hmm.
Where'd you learn
how to salsa?
I've been taking lessons 'cause
i knew it was your favorite.
When did i say that?
"Cosmo," '98.
And i knew you liked that merlot
from your "vogue" interview.
You researched me?
That's sweet!
In a, uh,
stalkery kind of way.
Thanks again for
a surprisingly enjoyable night.
(Chuckles) see you around.
Uh... gaby?
(Gasps) oh!
Right, the kiss.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to welsh on ya.
All right.
Pucker up.
Aah! Ow!
What the hell are you doing?!
But you said ???
Yes, my lips,not my esophagus!
For your information,
I'm a very good kisser,all right?
By who? The same girl
To use your tongue
like a windshield wiper?
No, by women--
Women with lots of experience--
And every single one of them
said that i was a great kisser.
(Scoffs) how much
did you pay them to say that?
No!
You've paid women for--
It's none of your business,
all right?
It's none of your business.
Uh, yes, it is.
You just vacuumed my tonsils.
I deserve to know
where that mouth has been.
You know what?
I-I-I'm sorry. I gotta go.
Wait, zach.
Zach, i'm not mad!
Ok hey, i'm just a little...
grossed out, that's all!
(Woman) no, you heard me.
You heard me, all right?
Read my lips.
Just go, all right?
Go! You've got no right
to be here!
All right!
What, another one?
You organ donor people
are vultures.
Um, no, actually,
i'm a friend of ian's.
He asked me to come...
for jane.
Oh, you...
you're the girlfriend.
All right, that's okay then.
Come on in.
So, erika, uh, youere fighting
with that guy when i came in.
Have you had a lot of those
organ donor people around today?
Oh, that wasn't about that.
No, that was ted.
What, ian never told you about ???
No. What about them?
Nothing. Forget i mentioned it.
It is not my place.
What?
They had an affair.
Jane cheated on ian?
When was this?
I hate to dish my best friend
on her deathbed...
but gossip was the foundation
of our relationship, so...
it was five years ago.
Ian was traveling a lot
on business,
Jane was lonely,
and along came ted.
I'm just stunned.
So i guess
they worked it out, right?
Well, ian took her back.
But if you're asking, did he
ever really trust her again?
I don't think so.
Poor ian.
Mm. You don't know
the half of it.
I mean, to be betrayed by
somebody you loved that much...
ugh. You're just
never the same
Hey. What are you doing here?
Um, word on the street is
you're looking for a manager.
(Chuckles) yeah.
Here's my application.
I thought ed took you back.
He did. I told him
i wasn't interested.
What?
You're quitting?
I had so much fun
at the fair today,
Working with you
on something that was all ours.
I want every day
to be like that.
Honey, so do i.
Are--Are you sure?
I mean, your career's
always meant so much to you.
When i got shot and i was
lying there bleeding,
I wasn't thinking,
"God, i'm really
gonna miss advertising."
I think this could be
the best thing
That's ever happened
to our family.
We can make our own hours,
we'll be together more,
And, yes, the money
is gna be a little tight,
But i think this place
could be a gold mine.
In that case, you're hired.
You do, of course, realize
you have to sleep with the boss.
I can do that.
Good.
Whoa. It's a little soon
to be gunning for a promotion.
Your mother not home yet?
Uh, i haven't seen her.
Huh.
Hello?
What is it now?
Alma did what?!
No, no.
I'll be right over.
Wait, wait, what--What--
What did alma do?
I just thank the lord
i got here when i did.
But why didn't you
call an ambulance?
I thought it best for all
concerned to keep this quiet.
By the way,
she left a note.
She only did this
to upset me.
She knows my history.
She knows
exactly what buttons to push.
Orson, calm down.
Here.
Our marriage is over.
I will not submit
to emotional blackmail.
Are you all right?
I feel dizzy.
(Clears throat)
Then perhaps
you should just...
sit.
My god.
Did you poison me?
And kill my only child?
You see how he talks to me?
It's my fault.
I upset him.
Sorry about all this.
I ju needed
to get your attention.
Why?
What do you want?
What every mother wants,
dear...
a grandchild.
Wewell, why don't i
give you two some privacy?
Thank you, mother hodge.
You mustn't struggle.
I want this baby
to be born of love.
I've been
injecting myself...
with hormones
To improve our chances.
You wait and see.
This is gonna fix everything.
You're crazy.
Crazy for you, mister!
I won't. You can't make me.
(Grunts)
why, yes, i can.
That drink had
two kinds of pills in it--
One to put you to sleep
And one to keep
the part of you i need
Nice and perky.
Now... how about
a little music?
* we're all alone
* no chaperone
can get our number *
* the world's in slumber
* let's misbehave
(mthing words)
The doctor was just here.
He said her blood pressure's
dropping. She could go anytime.
I, uh, gotta
go call her parents.
Hi.
It's me.
We--We just took off.
I-I'll be there
in about six hours.
Uh, sweetie, i don't think
she's gonna make it that long.
(Exhales deeply)
don't tell me that.
You've done everything
you could.
She knows
that you love her.
Well, it's just there's--There's
things i've got to say to her.
I've carried around
so much anger
About something that doesn't
mean anything now,
And i--And i-I need her
to know that.
I'm gonna put the phone
up to jane's ear,
And you can tell her
whatever you need to, okay?
Okay.
Hello, jane, darling.
It's ian.
I never imagined i'd have to
There's so much i want to say.
You play that pretty well.
What are you doing here?
I had a good time tonight,
But... i hated
the way it ended.
Yeah, me, too.
Gaby...
about those women...
forget about it.
Give a horny kid
a couple million bucks
And the yellow pages,
and stuff is gonna happen.
It's not just them. I...
i'm paying everyone
that i know.
Those guys in my band--
They're not my friends.
I'm... hiring them
to hang out with me.
So stop doing it.
Stop buying people.
Yeah, right,
and then i'd have no one at all.
That's not true.
You'd have me.
As a friend.
A friend friend.
Not a girlfriend.
I really cannot
overstress that.
Come on.
Why do you
wanna be my friend?
We have zero in common.
I don't know.
Maybe it's because
i think we're both... adrift.
Who gets
what i'm going thrgh.
Why don't you play me
something you wrote?
Yeah?
Mm-Hmm.
Okay. Can i sing, too?
Sure. Why not?
All right.
* gaby
* sweet gaby--
Whoa. Why don't you
just hum it, okay?
(Laughter on tv)
Hi.
Sorry.
My book club ran late.
Didn't orson
make you dinner?
Oh, no.
He's been over at alma's.
He's been there
for a few hours now.
What the hell is this?!
Oh, bree. I'soso sorry
you had to find out this way.
Not as sorry
as you are gonna be!
Orson, get up!
Leave him alone.
He wants to be with me now.
Orson,i have caught you cheati
At least have the courtesy
to wake up!
Oh, for god sakes.
Ooh! Aah!
Orson!
Orson?
What have you done to him?!
Nothing. You know men.
The minute it's over--
Wham, off to dreamland.
He's not sleeping.
He's out cold.
Oh, i knew it.
These are sleeping pills,
and these are...
(whispers) oh, my god.
You raped my husband!
We made love,
And when our baby's born,
he's gonna come back to me.
Baby?!
It's true.
I could be expecting
right now.
Were you expecting this?
Oh!
Andrew, i need you
to come over here right away...
and, um...
bring the wheelbarrow.
Hi.
Do...
do you remember me?
No.
No, not really.
But i know who you are.
Okay. Good.
Um...
what you did,
i'm, um... really grateful.
It's cool.
So if you need anything else,
i guess...
just let me know.
Well, i do need something.
But it's not for me.
(Man) take it to the end.
Move.
So how you doing?
You look terrific,
really mature.
Your mother would be proud.
Thanks.
I've, uh,
really missed you a lot,
And i'm sorry for, uh...
for everything.
I hope you can forgive me.
I want us to be friends.
And that's the only reason
you wanted to see me, right?
So we could be friends?
Yes.
Okay.
That's great. That's fine.
Well, there is
one other thing.
Oh. Yeah.
It's just... felicia tillman
faked her death.
She's still out there.
You and i, we both know that.
If you gave--
Or lent me some money,
I could hire someone
to track her down,
And then
i could get out of here,
And you and i could
pick up where we left off.
(Sighs) okay...
you asked me
how i was doing.
I'm actually doing great.
I've got the hottest,
most amazing girlfriend
In the entire world,
and i am gonna marry that woman.
I'm gonna buy her
everything she wants.
So...
i have got to learn to say no
when people ask me for money,
Because i got a future wife
to think about.
She's got
really expenveve taste.
I mean, i do forgive you,
though...
paul.
Hey, susan.
Hey. You're back.
Yeah,
zach young posted my bail,
But i'm guessing you had
something to do with it.
Maybe a little.
Is there any way
that i can thank you,
You know,
for everything you've done?
Actually, yeah, there is.
Good. Good. Just tell me.
I can't see you anymore.
I want you to understand
It doesn't have
anything to do with you.
It's just...
that's okay. It's not...
i think i get it.
Well, i, uh,
i should probably go.
Bye.
Good--Good luck
with everything.
Good luck to you and ian.
Yes,
it can happen so quickly.
Life as we know it can change
in the blink of an eye.
Unlikely friendships
can blossom...
important careers
can be tossed aside...
a long-Lost hope
can be rekindled.
Still, we should be grateful
For whatever changes
life throws at us,
Because all too soon
the day will come...
when there are
no changes left.
_/Yellow Sub\_