Are you OK?
Yeah.
Where's James?
They're taking a statement.
It'll be OK.
OK.
SHE GRUNTS
Do you want a drink?
I'm all right.
VENDING MACHINE WHIRS
'I can't do this any more.'
So if that all looks OK to you,
just sign on the bottom.
And then I can just go?
Yeah.
I've got a suspended sentence.
I know. You're just a witness.
She's confessed to everything.
Right.
OK.
What's gonna happen to Bonnie?
I don't know.
I don't think she's very well.
What can you do?
Uh...
A bit more?
Yeah.
We'll need to speak to you again.
Where can we find you?
Uh...
I'm sort of between places.
OK. Can I give your girlfriend's
address?
She's not...
She's not my girlfriend.
'Though she was my friend.'
Thanks for waiting. That's OK.
Where's Alyssa?
Gone somewhere. What?
We'll see her at home.
OK.
Where are you going?
Thanks for the clothes.
James!
'After Bonnie,
'after everything the night before,
'it felt odd
that Alyssa had just gone.'
Alyssa?
# Need something to hold
# In my hands
# Oceans, rivers and hills
# Hold me back
# Always will be
# Wrong in time
# Each trip a new pair of shoes
# Always blind. #
Who are you?
Hello.
You're James?
Yep.
What, the killer?
Uh, yeah.
Stay inside.
I really wanna punch you.
You can, if you like.
What's the point?
I'm sorry to bother you,
but is Alyssa here? No. Why?
Do you know where she might be?
No. Is she OK?
She's fine.
'At least, I hoped she was.'
OK. Thanks.
'Dread can start as a small thing -
'so quiet, you can
pretend not to hear it.
'But it gets loud.
'Really loud.'
Ducks.
'And you can't ignore it any more.'
'I think you knew my boyfriend.'
People are supposed to get punished.
You think we weren't?
'I suddenly knew where
Alyssa might be.'
Hi. Can I borrow a pen
and some paper?
Thanks.
Can you give this to the woman
in the waiting room?
The awake one. Sure.
'It's easy to feel like you're
not in control of your life.
'That's because you're not.
'You can't stop things happening.
'You just have to deal with them
when they do.'
You should smile more.
What? Well, it might never happen.
It has happened, actually,
so fuck off!
Can you shut your legs, please?
Yeah.
Thanks.
'I used to feel like I knew myself.
'But for a while now, I don't think
I've been properly in my body.
'You can think you've run away
from something,
'but, actually, you've been carrying
it with you the whole time.'
GLASS SMASHES
ECHOES OF MUSIC
# Every time I sit here
# In the last past years
# When I pass through the hills... #
INTERNALLY: It's like a haunted
house.
Only I'm the ghost.
# While images return lying
# For the roots of the woods
# That origin of all my strong
estrangement... #
You can get stuck in a place
and not even realise it.
If you're not careful, you can get
stuck there forever.
Like Bonnie.
# I grew up
# Of this glow up and cities
# Where first love and soul takes
life
# There were times in my life... #
SPLASH
Alyssa?
James?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Why are you wet?
I went for a swim.
I feel better now.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
The note.
You left a note.
Uh, yeah. Saying I'll be back later.
You said to look after me.
I didn't mean forever!
I just thought you were gonna do
something bad.
I wasn't gonna do that, James.
I wasn't.
INTERNALLY: He feels really small.
I'm sorry I scared you.
Can we get out of here, please?
ROAR OF TRAFFIC
This is where they met - your
parents?
Yeah.
What were they doing, dogging?
Sorry.
It used to be a park.
He was sitting on a bench.
Told her he loved her straight away.
She was walking her nan's whippet.
And I was eating a sandwich.
It was like something out of a
film.
That's nice.
You don't have to do it, James.
I think I do.
OK.
Oh, no!
What?
INTERNALLY: I didn't know when, but
my dad had got a bit wet.
Ooh, he's like a paste!
It's still him.
Maybe I'll just sort of pour him.
HE SIGHS
It's shit being dead, isn't it?
Yeah.
You miss everything.
I'm sorry.
What for?
For trying to make you the answer.
It's not fair.
I've been quite shit, too.
I'm really hungry.
Me too.
You should have scattered him here.
I'm joking.
INTERNALLY: I read somewhere that if
you want to talk to someone about
something important,
it's easier if you don't look at
them.
It's less confrontational, or
something.
I heard what you said.
At the car pound.
What?
INTERNALLY: I knew exactly what.
I love you.
I feel the same.
What?
Really?
Yeah.
I... But I need a lot of time.
OK.
And some psychological help.
And I owe my mum about ten grand.
OK.
But, yeah.
I love you, too.
Yeah. Don't go on about it.
# Kiss me each morning
# For a million years
# Hold me each evening
# By your side
# Tell me you love me
# For a million
A million years... #