Kim: I have a case
in Tucumcari.
And there's something
I want to discuss with you.
I'm not
representing Mesa Verde.
In fact,
I'd like to represent you, sir.
Guess who's got a new client
in Tucumcari.
Where is this place?
Where am I?
[Speaking Spanish]
Phone?
Who brought me here?
Did Fring do this?
Look what you've done
to all my fine work.
What am I doing here?
You were meant
to be recovering.
What's he want
with me?
He's asked me
to keep you alive.
Will you allow this?
[Groans]
¶¶
Okay, listen up.
If Acker doesn't leave
on his own by quarter after,
the sheriff's gonna evict.
Once that's done,
utilities will drop
and cut their lines while
we take down the north fence.
Uh, anything inside the place
gets loaded up
and sent to storage.
Debris goes in
the side dumpster.
Concrete's stayin'.
Uh, disposal company's
coming for it.
We good so far?
Mm-hmm.
I-I think I might be
seeing a hitch here.
Wait. Who are you?
I'm Saul Goodman,
attorney at law.
Glad to meet you.
A better question might be,
"Where are we?"
[Chuckles]
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you know what?
[Sighs]
It's coming up on the hour,
so word to the wise --
if you let everyone go
right now,
you might save
half a day's salary and fringes.
What the hell
are you talking about?
[Car door closes]
[Stammers, sighs]
Deputies!
Great.
Perfect timing.
What's going on?
He's a lawyer.
Says there's a hitch.
I'm Everett Acker's
attorney.
I'm just dottin' the "I's"
in due diligence.
Well,
I'm sorry, sir.
Eviction order's
signed by a judge.
I'm sure it is.
Uh, can I have a peek
at that?
It's all correct,
sir.
Uh-huh.
Sir, since you represent
Mr. Acker,
can you make sure he cooperates
with the eviction?
W--can you make out the address
on that?
1130 Arroyo Vista.
There a problem?
Well, I mean,
is that where we are?
[Police radio chatter]
There were house numbers
on that mailbox,
plain as day --
1130.
I don't see any.
Do you, deputy?
No, I don't.
Well,
somebody messed with them.
This is
1130 Arroyo Vista.
This here's
1240 Arroyo Vista.
It's always been
1240?
1240!
My client says
it's 1240.
I got a plat map says we can
straighten this out right now.
Well, all due respect
to whoever drew that map,
but Mr. Acker's been living here
for 30 years.
I think he knows
his own address.
Sir, you got something
with an address on it?
[Mailbox door creaks]
[Mailbox door closes]
[Police radio chatter]
Thank you.
1240 Arroyo Vista.
It's 1130.
Anybody can print out
something like that.
You've got an order
signed by a judge.
Y'know, we could get a surveyor
up here this afternoon.
He'll clear everything up.
That'd lose us
a full day.
Listen, officer, before you go
forcing an elderly veteran
from his home
and take everything he's got,
demolish a half-century
of hard work,
wouldn't you like to know
you got the right place?
Come on.
All we're talking about are
some missing house numbers.
I have to make
a call.
[Birds chirping]
[Whistles]
Everybody take 10!
[Engine starts]
[Police radio chatter]
Kevin: After a year of running
every which way,
now the guy
gets a lawyer?
The lawyer comes in,
the crazy comes out.
We had it straightened out
in a matter of hours.
It was a gimmick --
and not
a particularly effective one.
It's costing us a day.
I call that
plenty effective.
But we're passed that.
Tomorrow they're finally
tearing the place down, right?
That's the plan.
There's more?
Kim: Unfortunately,
there is another complication.
The lawyer Acker hired --
it's Jimmy.
Kevin: Jimmy.
Your Jimmy?
Yes.
[Scoffs] You're...
How did that happen?
Jimmy's been doing some
very aggressive marketing.
Looks like Acker
picked up on it.
Okay.
So what now?
In fairness to you,
I'll withdraw
from everything having to do
with the Tucumcari project.
Stef will step in
for me.
She and Paige
can see it through.
Paige: Kim's brought us
this far.
I think Stef will do
a fine job for us.
Of course, this is just
Tucumcari we're talking about.
I'll continue to handle
everything else as usual.
You know what?
I smell a rat.
Acker hiring Jimmy --
that's no coincidence.
And I heard about the talking-to
you gave that guy.
Sounds like you tore him
a new one.
I-I wouldn't say
that I --
Here's what I think.
This fella saw you
for the killer you are,
and he went
and hired Jimmy
specifically to take you
away from us.
Kevin...
I have to say,
I think that's very unlikely.
Trust me on this,
Kim.
I know a scam
when I see one, okay?
No disrespect.
I'm sure your associate's
more than capable,
but I am not gonna
let this guy deprive me
of the best
in the business.
I-I think
what Kim's trying to say
is that going home
to the attorney
on the other side
of this matter
could get...
awkward for her.
Is that right,
Kim?
This gonna be tough on you
at home?
It's not the personal side
that concerns me.
I just wouldn't
want there to be
any question
of conflict of interest.
Well, I'm not worried
about that.
If you're willing
to stick with it,
I say
why change horses midstream?
Kevin,
are they waiting for you?
Oh, yeah.
Listen.
I need
that call center.
We gotta
get this thing movin' now.
We got a lot of competitors
out there,
and none of them are waiting on
some crabby ol' son of a bitch
to get their damn
call centers built.
Got it?
Got it.
I know you do.
[Birds chirping]
That an MRI machine
I saw back there?
It is.
Ah.
And Fring
paid for all this.
Huh.
And all those nice little houses
out there.
I'm guessing there are
bales of meth inside.
[Chuckles]
There are
no drugs here.
None save the ones
that I prescribe.
No men with guns,
either.
And if I want to get back
to where I belong?
Mm.
You're welcome to leave.
You would go back to the road
where I found you.
Five kilometers
from here,
there's a gate that leads
to the main road.
There are men
at that gate.
Those men have guns,
I'm guessing.
Perhaps.
I've never seen
any weapons.
In any case,
they will not stop you.
12 kilometers up the highway,
there is a small town,
bigger than this place,
but small.
There is a bus stop.
Once you're on
that bus,
you're perhaps a day
from El Paso.
However,
as you are now,
you would not survive
the journey.
My advice
is to rest.
Enjoy some of Señora Cortazar's
excellent cooking
and take in
some clean air.
[Sighs]
[Groans]
Fring carts me
all the way down here.
Why?
Doctor:
That I do not know.
You would have to
ask him.
So you're just
his on-call quack?
I am the quack
who saved your life.
[Pills rattle]
This is
for infection.
Two every four hours
for the next week.
This is
for the pain.
Take it
when you need it.
I'll be back to check on you
in three days.
Then,
in a week or so,
perhaps you will be able
to travel.
I can, uh, get a message
to your family.
They're fine.
[Faucet squeaks, water runs]
¶¶
Buenas tardes.
[Water burbling]
[Indistinct shouting]
¶¶
[Children cheering, whooping]
[Water burbling]
[Bubbling]
[Whistling]
[Exhales sharply]
[Sighs heavily]
[Sniffles]
[Cellphone vibrating]
[Sighs]
Hello, Howard.
Howard:
Hi, Jimmy.
This a bad time?
Um, I'm -- I'm --
I'm, uh, a bit busy,
uh, to be honest, but, uh...
what's up?
Just thinking about you.
How you doin'?
Fine.
Mm.
Glad to hear it.
[Sighs]
What's up?
Just touching base to see
if you've had any thoughts
on what
we talked about.
What we talked about...
Oh, the job!
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
No.
I mean, hey, I've been thinking
of nothing else, really.
Glad to hear it.
Any conclusions?
Uh, no, I'm just --
I'm mulling it over,
you know, reflecting.
I'm trying to give it the
consideration that it deserves.
Fair enough.
I'm ready to discuss the details
when you are.
Sounds good.
And Jimmy --
[Cellphone closes, clatters]
[Sniffles]
[Object shattering]
[Door opens, closes]
Hey.
[Keys jingle, clatter]
Smells interesting.
Oh, yeah, that's, uh --
that's the curry.
I think
it's our unlikely hero.
I'm gonna have to
soak it overnight,
but it'll be ready
first thing.
So, how'd it go
with Kevin?
Well,
I'm still on the case.
No shit.
That's great!
What happened?
Uh...you know,
the more I wanted to go,
the more
he wanted me to stay.
Yeah,
but he was pissed, right?
A little bit.
Right.
So, where were you?
Uh, we were at
his country club.
Ooh!
Cuttin' it close
to tee time.
Pressure.
That's excellent.
He had to move his game,
actually.
[Laughs]
I love it.
Right.
Now what?
Uh,
you're sitting?
You were standing?
I mean...
Hmm?
Paint a picture.
Set the scene.
Come on.
[Laughs] Uh...
Okay, um...
Paige and I meet him
outside the clubhouse.
Mm-hmm.
And the three of us
are at a table,
and he's over here
like this.
And he says --
Wait.
He sits like that?
Yeah,
he -- he sits to the side.
He's a side sitter?
I guess so.
Okay.
Well, you never told me
that he was a side sitter.
And that is gold.
Now, go -- go on.
[Sniffles]
Okay, s-so, he's sitting here,
and he says, um,
I'm not gonna
let him deprive --"
Wait.
Do the voice.
I'm not
gonna imitate him.
Yes. Come on.
Give me a nibble.
I mean,
he's a good old boy, right?
[Southern accent]
So, do he talk like this?
Uh, no, no.
"Ding dang do"?
It's, uh --
It's more like, um...
[Sighs]
[As Kevin] Lawyer comes in,
crazy comes out.
[Chuckles]
I need that call center
real bad.
[As Kim]
Of course, Kevin.
[Normal voice]
Wait. Are you being me?
Yes,
this is you.
Yes.
Go on. Go on.
[As Kevin] Uh, okay. I'm not
gonna let him deprive me.
No, sirree.
Kim.
Hmm?
I need it sooner than yesterday.
Got it?
But, Kevin --
No.
You do
whatever it takes!
I don't like waitin'
one bit,
never have,
never will.
Bottom line,
breakin' ground,
more statues.
Kim, you get him now,
blah, blah, blah, blah!
Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[Normal voice]
What?
[Inhales sharply]
Kevin...
[As Kevin]
Yes, Kim?
[Exhales sharply]
Would you care
to take a shower with me?
Well, shoot.
I believe I would.
[Crickets chirping]
[Animal grunts, owl hooting]
[Bed creaks]
[Dial tone]
[Dialing]
[Line beeps]
[Speaking Spanish]
[Sighs]
¶¶
[Chain creaking]
[Crickets chirping]
¶¶
[Bowl thuds]
[Bowl clatters]
¶¶
Gracias.
[Cellphone beeps]
¶¶
[Sucks teeth]
[Dialing]
¶¶
[Ringing]
Gus: Hello?
You know who this is?
How are you feeling?
Better, I trust?
Uh-huh.
You don't do anything
without a reason.
Why am I here?
Now is not
a good time.
What's going on here?
Sir, sir,
please watch your step.
Stop right there!
What the hell?
Please stay
out of the grid.
The what?!
The area
marked by the stakes.
Step out of it,
please.
So, what about it,
doctor?
Well,
at a glance,
I'd say these pieces
are likely contemporary.
I'll bet they are.
But we need to do
a systematic property search
to be sure.
Really?
Is that necessary?
I'm afraid so.
Gil:
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
H-How long
is this gonna take?
A day or two,
a week at the most.
A week?!
[Scoffs]
Come on!
You know this guy
planted that stuff here.
Whoa!
This is the same thing
with the house numbers
all over again!
Now, that was
an honest mistake.
This is the law.
Says who?
Says the New Mexico
Cultural Properties Act.
[Laughs]
No.
You're not
going along with this?
Seriously?
I have to
make a call.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Whistles]
[Engine starts]
[Stanton Moore's
"Blackbird Special" plays]
[Vehicle beeping]
[Indistinct conversations]
¶¶
Sorry to interrupt.
He's suing on behalf
of the water district.
The water district?
¶¶
[Sighs]
Stef, you're good
with regulatory law.
He's claiming
there's a flaw
in the original land grant
from 1846.
That's ridiculous.
I -- [Sighs]
¶¶
[Sighs]
Pat, you'd better drop
everything else.
He's claiming our prime
contractor's an escaped felon.
You can't be serious.
[Sighs]
Evan, I'm gonna give
this one to you.
...to invalidate the grant based
on what is essentially...
I can see
the Little Dipper.
Everett:
That's the Big Dipper.
Yeah. [Chuckles]
¶¶
Ah.
Right over here.
Is that, uh,
Orion over there?
No.
That's a satellite.
[Both laugh]
[Gamma detector squealing]
¶¶
Man: Officer,
radiation's borderline.
We got to get
soil samples.
¶¶
Do I have to ask?
I'm gonna have to, uh...
you know.
Better safe than sorry.
Paige: Yes.
[Speaks indistinctly]
We have a problem.
[Speaking indistinctly]
Everett: I've always enjoyed
your radio program,
and I never thought I'd see
a miracle with my very own eyes.
That's right --
Tucumcari, right off 54.
There's plenty of parking.
[Chuckling]
Well, thank you!
I'm a long-time listener
and a first-time caller.
[Air brakes hiss]
¶¶
Oh, I see...
Hello, ma'am.
¶¶
[Camera shutter clicks]
[Camera beeps]
Uh-huh.
¶¶
What's your name,
honey?
God damn it.
The crowd's
already thinning out.
Apparently, the image
on the side of the house
has started to fade.
Tomorrow we're bringing in
additional security
and blocking off parking.
Answer me this --
if they're saying
it's radioactive over there,
how the hell is Acker
still in that house?
That was really more of
an OSHA situation.
The concern was for
the construction crew.
Turns out the radiation level
was completely safe.
We should be cleared to resume
construction on Thursday.
Assuming nothing else
comes up.
Kim, [Clears throat]
bottom line me here.
Clearly, this is all designed
to force us back to the table
and put us at a disadvantage
when we get there.
[Scoffs] We've gotta get back in
the driver's seat on this thing.
I say
we sue 'em right back.
Sue Acker.
Sue Goodman.
Take the fight
back to 'em.
Going down that road
could take years.
They know this is costing
Mesa Verde.
Time is
on their side.
[Scoffs]
You got that right.
Rich,
do you have anything to add?
Possibly.
What if there were a way
to turn this around on them?
What if you don't build
the call center?
Or not at that location,
at least.
Suddenly you're holding
all the cards.
There's nothing to delay.
The other side's
the one spending money
with no hope of recovering
their expenses.
Wait. So...
[Sighs] What?
I understand there's a viable
alternative site.
You make the switch,
and you've won.
[Sighs]
Wait. Hold up.
Didn't we let
the other site go?
Lot 2375 is available,
and our permits
still apply.
We'd still
hit our target
for getting the call center
up and running.
We took the liberty
of running the numbers for you.
Paige: The financial hit
would be negligible.
[Sighs]
My dad did not raise me
to run from a fight.
Kevin,
we're not saying --
I'm not gonna roll over
and let some low-life shyster
bully me off my land.
No offense,
Kim.
He's got one lawyer.
I got a room
fulla the best there is.
Here's what
we're gonna do --
you're gonna figure out a way
to get them off my property.
That call center's not movin'
one goddamn inch!
[Door opens]
[Sighs]
You gave it
your best shot.
Yeah?
[Chuckling] Yeah.
You went the distance
for the old S.O.B.,
above and beyond.
You should feel good
about that.
You think so?
[Sighs]
You gave Acker
more than he deserved.
And, uh,
let's be real.
Putting me on this --
that was bad.
I mean,
if anyone found out...
You risked a lot
for this guy.
[Sighs]
Look,
this time next week,
Acker will be living
somewhere else.
Is that really
such a big deal?
Plus,
Mesa Verde --
that's your
bread and butter.
You can only
push 'em so far.
There's always
another play.
[Inhales sharply]
But the rational thing
to do here is close the deal,
get the guy
a few bucks,
pop the champagne
with the other winners,
and smile
like you mean it.
You want a beer?
I'm gonna get one.
Or...?
Jimmy.
There's no reason
on God's green Earth
to take this
any further.
It's not worth it.
[Sighs]
Or...?
Or...
we go after
Kevin Wachtell.
It gets nasty.
It gets personal.
It gets dangerous.
Jimmy:
Hey. It's me.
Yes, it is.
Great.
Uh, listen,
I got something for you.
Hear me out because
this is a good thing.
Um, I'm sorry.
I'm ge-- I'm getting some kind
of reverb or something.
Are you
in a tunnel or...
Yes.
What's that?
[Thunder rumbling]
Yes,
I'm in a tunnel.
Okay.
Um, [Chuckles]
anyway, uh,
this is not like
that other thing, okay?
Um, straight piece
of oppo research.
This is a lawyer
hirin' a P.I.
What do you say?
So you're back
to being a lawyer?
Yeah. Yeah.
Totally legit.
So, uh, did I mention
it's a paying gig?
I'm not available.
Say again?
Ta bien?
Uh, good. Good.
Uh, muy bueno.
[Both chuckle]
Thank you.
[Breathes deeply]
[Hammer pounding]
[Groans]
Aw, man.
[Speaking Spanish]
Uh...it's okay.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
You got
this guy where?
Same place as Huell.
So, it's like some kind of
underground Craigslist?
It's just a guy
who knows people.
People of
a certain type.
He's very discreet.
Well,
he'd have to be.
[Vehicle approaching]
[Brakes squeal,
engine shuts off]
[Sighs]
[Vehicle door closes]
Uh, here goes.
Um,
it'll be fine.
Just watch.
[Keys jingle,
car alarm deactivates]
[Bells ding]
[Door closes, lock engages]
[Keys jingling]
I thought I was going to
a law office.
Yeah,
this is a law office.
Gotcha.
Giselle, um,
this is Mister X.
It's my work name.
Ah.
[Inhales sharply]
Mm.
You know, those things
are full of parasites.
Uh, yeah, duly noted.
Uh, the conference room
is in back.
Ah. Yeah. Yeah.
[Sighs]
I did the full work-up,
as tasked.
And?
Snake eyes.
Bupkis. Nada.
Guy's squeaky clean.
That's impossible.
I mean,
everybody's got something.
Not this time.
You got an Eagle Scout
with a six-figure income.
Arrests?
Mm.
D.U.I...
in college.
Homecoming weekend,
34 years ago.
Is that
what you're looking for?
Girlfriends?
Offshore accounts?
Sobchak: No secret
bank accounts, no extra phones,
no lunchtime quickies,
no lady friend,
no boy toy.
The guy's dull,
like "Saturday night
in Salt Lake City" dull.
No offense,
but your work is sounding
kind of superficial.
[Inhales sharply]
"Superficial"?
Yeah.
Wow.
Yeah,
not hardly.
I went the distance.
I did a self-guided tour
of his domicile,
all seven bedrooms,
four and a half baths --
Hold on.
You're saying
you broke into his house?
Giselle, um,
this is probably
one of those
tricks-of-the-trade things.
Why don't we just
focus on the "what"
and skip over
the "how."
I'd like to know.
[Inhales sharply]
He has
a security system
with a touchy
upstairs window sensor.
I trip it a couple times
with an airsoft.
A B.B. gun.
[Inhales sharply]
The alarm
drives the housekeeper crazy,
so I show up in coveralls,
toolbox, alarm company I.D.,
and she's more than happy
to let me
have the run of the place.
Does that meet
with your approval?
Alright, so you get in,
and you find what?
Like I said,
nothing.
No, there's no such thing
as nothing.
Okay? Uh--
We want specifics.
You want specifics?
Okay, well,
I got specifics.
That's the home office.
I spent an extra four minutes
opening the floor safe --
nothing but
life-insurance policies,
a couple of rings,
and a commemorative half-dollar.
The guy's old-school.
No computers,
motel art on the walls,
paperwork on his desk.
What kind of paperwork?
[Chuckles]
[Folder thuds]
You knock yourself out.
Now, I may not be
a nail-salon lawyer,
but I know legit
when I see it.
So, you gonna withdraw
the "superficial" now, hmm?
[Sighs]
You think you could get into
his downtown office?
Sure.
I could.
But there's a better way.
Yeah?
Yeah. [Chuckles]
I get
two more guys,
guys who know how
to handle themselves.
Now, we roll up to the subject
in an unmarked van.
We grab him,
put him in a bag,
and we take him out
to the desert.
Yeah, we're done here.
We're done.
Now, by the end of the day,
the banker's giving you
everything you're after,
alright?
No,
we're done here.
No, no, no, l-l-look,
you get keys to the kingdom,
guaranteed.
Okay,
Sergeant Slaughter,
back to the paintball field,
okay?
The grownups need to talk.
Let's go.
Alright, that's fine.
I am just providing options
for you here.
Alright,
this is the way out.
Okay?
Exit through
the gift shop.
Alright.
Don't touch anything,
please.
I will not.
Let me say
on this one...
[Indistinct conversation]
[Door opens, bells ding]
[Bells ding, door closes]
I don't know
what to say.
I'm gonna complain to management
about that clown.
My usual guy
is very reliable.
What?
What is it?
[Indistinct conversations]
[Telephone ringing]
[Mouse clicking]
[Knock on door]
Got a minute?
Sure.
How's everything?
[Door closes]
All good.
Kinda crunched.
Still dealing with
the Tucumcari situation.
Mm-hmm.
And the pro bono work?
It's good.
Something up?
Listen.
I'm thinking you could
take a break from Mesa Verde.
A "break"?
Actually,
a pair of mineral-rights beefs
just came in.
They practically
have your name on them.
You can split your time
between that
and your
pro bono clients.
Mesa Verde is my client.
And they still will be.
I'll just step in
and take point,
just on
a temporary basis.
And, of course,
it goes without saying
this won't affect
any of your compensation.
And that includes
your bonus.
You know Mesa Verde
is fully informed
of any
potential conflicts.
Kevin signed off himself.
Still, I think you're going to
need to take a break.
I don't understand
where this is coming from.
Don't you?
[Sighs]
Kim...
sometimes the less said,
the better.
And why is that?
Do we have to?
Yes, we do.
Alright.
First I had to
twist your arm
to get you down to Tucumcari
for the eviction.
Then you put
the full-court press on Kevin
to change sites.
That doesn't work,
and, abracadabra,
your boyfriend's
opposing counsel.
I told you --
I explained the situation
to Kevin and Paige.
Yeah.
I know you did.
And, I'm sorry to say,
I'm just not buying it.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door closes]
Rich? Rich!
Hold on!
What are you
saying exactly?
Let's talk
in my office.
You are accusing me
of something.
Go ahead and say it.
Are you
talking about malfeasance?
Working against
my client's interests? What?
Please --
Rich, tell me.
You know I worked my ass off
to get here.
You know that.
Yes,
I do know.
So tell me.
Please tell me
why I would risk everything
for some squatter.
Why?
I don't understand.
Are you -- Are you trying to
protect the firm -- from what?
Kim, I am not trying
to protect the firm.
I am trying
to protect you.
I don't need
your protection.
I need
to represent my client.
If that's
how you want it.
[Keyboard clacking]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door closes]
[Telephone rings]
[Conversations continue]
[Birds chirping]
Woman: Está seguro de que
no gusta quedarse a cenar?
Gus: Desafortunadamente,
no puedo.
Me da mucha lástima tener que
perderme de su comida.
Cómo están sus hijos?
Oh!
Pedro se acaba de casar,
y creo que pronto seré abuela.
No me diga.
iQue increíble!
[Metal squeals]
[Dog barking in distance]
[Birds chirping]
[Water burbling]
So, what do you want
from me?
I think it best
that Señora Cortazar doesn't
know about our association.
I like to keep my business
as far from here as possible.
[Dog barking in distance]
You look much better.
I am glad.
So I'm here to see
what a big heart you have.
Is that the idea?
You throw money
at these people,
they bow low?
As far as the people here
are concerned,
I am the doctor's friend,
nothing more.
They have no idea
you financed the whole place.
I prefer it
that way.
The "anonymous benefactor."
Well, that must
make you feel pretty good.
And is that supposed to
balance the scales,
make up
for everything else you do?
It makes up for nothing.
I am what I am.
[Dog barking in distance]
What is this place?
Call it a memorial.
To what?
¶¶
I already told you
what you can do with your money.
You seem like a guy
who can take a hint.
So what are we doing?
It seems to me
that you are at a crossroads.
You can continue
as you are...
drinking...
estranged from
your family...
brawling with street hoods.
We both know
how that ends.
Yeah.
You have
another choice.
Mm.
Work for you
as a button man.
I'm in a war.
I need a soldier.
Mm.
So, I'm gonna work
for one drug dealer
killing
other drug dealers?
That's your idea
of a choice.
You know better.
You have met them.
You know what they are.
Meaning the Salamancas.
And you are so very different
from them?
Yes.
I am different.
Why me?
Because I believe
that you understand.
Understand what?
Revenge.