[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
Now we're looking for two binomials
that multiply to get the given trinomial.
ADULT SHELDON: Whenever I wasn't
being challenged intellectually,
my brain was more than happy
to step up and accommodate.
It was like having the
perfect playmate in my skull.
♪ ♪
Sir, the COBE satellite is
going into an uncontrolled spin.
So fix it!
We can't. Our computer
programs weren't designed
to handle a chaotic system.
Darn it! If only someone
could calculate the maneuver
and make it stable again!
SHELDON: There is someone.
And it's me.
You're just a kid.
A kid who knows to add an x-cubed term
to a simple harmonic oscillator.
If you extend the solar
panel by one meter,
you'll save your satellite.
You heard him. Do it!
INGRAM: Sheldon?
Sheldon?
Were you paying attention
to anything I said?
Yes.
Then what'd I say?
When factoring a trinomial
where the leading coefficient isn't one,
it must be written in descending order
from highest power to lowest power.
Well... yeah.
SHELDON: You'll save your satellite.
You heard him. Do it!
[TYPING RAPIDLY]
[BEEPS]
It worked. The satellite is stable!
Yes!
- [CHEERING]
- [WHOOPS]
[WHOOPING]
Thanks, kid.
You really saved my bottom.
Tell your bottom, "It's welcome."
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
And bless our appetites,
both physical and spiritual,
to honor You in all we do.
In Jesus' name.
What happened to "Bless
the hands that prepared it"?
I thought I'd mix it up.
I miss the old one.
Me, too.
Yeah, what I like about the other one...
And bless the hands that prepared it.
- Amen.
- ALL: Amen.
[SIGHS]
So, how was everybody's day?
I'm done with high school.
What does that mean?
Well, I don't learn anything there,
and I don't want to go anymore.
Well, where do you
think you're gonna go?
Who cares? Let him go.
Shh. Well?
I've been corresponding
with Dr. John Sturgis
at East Texas Tech.
He said I could audit his course.
You're pen pals with a
stranger? Is this okay?
He's not a stranger.
He's a famous scientist.
He carbon-dated the oldest human feces.
That ain't strange.
Now, Shelly, I appreciate that you want
to expand your horizons, but
how would you even get there?
The school's an hour away.
I'm working, your dad's working.
Again, who cares? Let him go.
He could hitchhike.
Perfect.
It's only one day a week,
and I was hoping Meemaw could take me.
I'm gonna start eating
dinner at my house.
You better make a whole lot of money
and take care of me when I'm old.
I'm not interested in money.
I'm interested in the
pursuit of knowledge.
That is the wrong
thing to say to someone
who is spending her Friday
night as your chauffeur.
Did you know the word chauffeur
is French for "stoker,"
because the first automobiles
were steam-powered,
and the driver had to stoke the engine?
Right there. Why am I
driving you to college
when you already know everything?
ADULT SHELDON: I didn't know everything,
but compared to her
friends at water aerobics,
I could see how it felt that way.
Okay, this is you.
Good luck.
Aren't you going to walk
me in and get me situated?
Oh, yes, of course.
Right this way, my prince.
SHELDON: Why are they all looking at us?
I think they're looking at you.
Oh. Hello.
MEEMAW [QUIETLY]: There you go.
Okay, you all situated?
I believe so, yes.
- I'll be right outside.
- Are you sure
you don't want to stay and learn
about quantum chromodynamics?
And spoil the fun of you
telling me all about it
on the ride home?
No way.
Smart.
That's my meemaw.
[WOMAN CRIES SOFTLY ON TV]
- He's really ours?
- Thank you.
Oh, come on, you done all the work.
Adrian, I can't believe you done this.
Can you help me?
With what?
I don't understand my homework.
You're asking me?
I don't understand my own homework.
I know, but you're all I got.
[TV TURNS OFF]
What kind of homework is it?
Grammar.
I ain't great with grammar.
Well, grammar's just talking,
and we both talk good.
I guess. Gimme.
There's a list of sentences,
and you're supposed to say
if each one's a
complete sentence or not.
GEORGE JR.: The first one is,
"Most people in the country""
That doesn't sound like a sentence.
But ask me who drives pickup trucks.
Who drives pickup trucks?
Most people in the country.
Well, now it does sound like one.
I told you, it's confusing.
I can't help you.
[SIGHS]
ROCKY: If you don't want me
mixing with Creed no more...
Do you think we're stupid?
Sheldon's in college right now,
and we can't figure out
your homework.
What do you think?
Sometimes I tell myself
I only look stupid
because he's so smart.
ADRIAN: Win.
Give me the book.
Don't just sit there,
make me a sandwich.
Coming up.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
- Hello.
Forgive me, but is that
pattern a double basket weave?
Um, I suppose so.
I've always just called it a
"loop-loop whoopsie-do."
[BOTH LAUGH]
Well, it's very impressive.
Do you knit?
No, but it's always intrigued me.
Believe it or not,
the first computer was a loom.
Is that so?
It is.
Well, okay.
Okay.
Well, if you'll excuse me, uh,
I have a class to teach.
Oh, you must be my grandson's pen pal.
I'm sorry?
Sheldon Cooper.
The nine-year-old with
the flawless penmanship.
I look forward to meeting him.
Well, he's right in
there. You can't miss him.
- He's about yea big.
- Oh.
An-An-And will you be joining us?
Will you be discussing
quantum chromodynamics?
I certainly hope so.
- Then I don't think so.
- Are you sure?
Every day is a chance
to learn something new.
Can I ask questions?
Well, how else can you learn?
Well, let's do it, then.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
My name's John.
And I'm Connie.
My middle name's Whitney.
And now I know that.
Well, I'm so glad you enjoyed it.
So, Sheldon, what did you think
of your first theoretical physics class?
I think I'm gonna do this
for the rest of my life.
Good choice.
Connie, I would like to see you again.
Perhaps we could have dinner sometime.
Yes, we would love that.
We would?
We wouldn't?
You wouldn't?
We would.
Excellent.
Excellent. So, where are we eating?
Okay, this says "a complete sentence
always contains a verb."
Which one's a verb?
"A verb is a word
that describes an action.
I play checkers. You eat spaghetti."
We suck at homework.
The action is sucking.
So, the first one on your homework is,
"Most people in the country."
I don't see an action word.
Neither do I.
Georgie, I don't think
this is a sentence.
I think you're right.
Now I just have to fix it.
Put a verb in there, girl.
I think you might be getting
a little ahead of yourself.
I don't think so. They're in love.
They were looking into each other's eyes
like there was something in there
other than corneas and irises.
Well, if that's the
case, that'd be wonderful.
It'd be more than wonderful.
If they get married,
we immediately double
the number of smart
people in our family.
That means we go from one to two.
I got that.
So, did you understand any of it?
- Not a word.
- [LAUGHS]
But he had on a tweed jacket
with the elbow patches,
so he must know what he's talking about.
Boy, Sheldon's fired up.
Oh, he loved it.
He sat there for an hour and a half
just as happy as a pig in poop.
He mentioned you were pretty happy
about the whole experience, too.
Well, I guess Mr. Wizard did take
a bit of a shine to me.
What's that mean?
It means he asked me out to dinner.
No big deal.
So, you going?
When have you known me
to turn down a free meal?
Ain't that the truth.
Says the Pillsbury Doughboy.
[MARY AND MEEMAW CHUCKLING]
I do have feelings, y'all.
Don't put on too much of that.
We want him to like you for your mind.
I think I know what I'm
doing when it comes to men.
If that's true, then
why do you live alone?
Because my husband died.
Any other questions?
- [DOORBELL RINGS]
- He's here!
I'll get it.
Maybe that is a bit much.
Hello, Dr. Sturgis.
Hello, Sheldon.
Come in. Meemaw's upstairs
getting ready for your date.
Wonderful.
Oh, my, this is a lovely house.
Isn't it? Can you see
yourself living here?
I can.
Here are some things you might
find helpful about Meemaw.
Her favorite color is purple,
her favorite ice cream: mint chip,
and her favorite food is Mexican.
Excellent. Good to know.
She loves gambling,
bowling, and especially me.
You can't talk enough about me.
Tell me more about you.
My favorite color is blue.
Mine, too.
- My favorite ice cream: vanilla.
- Good man.
My favorite food: spaghetti
with hot dogs cut up in it.
I've never had that.
What's your favorite food?
Grilled cheese.
What about the risk of mouth burn?
It's a perfect excuse
for vanilla ice cream.
If you want to propose
tonight, you have my blessing.
Hello, boys.
- Hello, Connie.
- [CHUCKLES]
These are for you.
Aw, thank you. They're beautiful.
Some of them are purple.
So they are.
I should probably get
'em into some water.
I can do that.
You two begin your courtship.
- Moonpie.
- Yes?
Go home.
So you can begin the courtship, got it.
Go!
Dr. Sturgis,
I just want you to know I
couldn't be more pleased.
[CHUCKLES]
- [CHUCKLES]
- Well, let me take care of these,
and then we'll head out.
I just need to
borrow your phone to call a cab.
Why?
I don't drive.
Well, how did you get here?
I rode my bicycle.
You rode your bicycle?
I have a Schwinn Speedster.
It's got three gears. I only use one.
I tell you what, how
about we take my car?
Excellent.
So, would you be opposed to
me sitting in the back seat?
It's statistically the
safest part of the car.
Actually, I would.
Asked and answered.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
_
MISSY: Did you cry when you saw it?
No.
MISSY: Why not?
'Cause it ain't that big a deal.
MISSY: Okay.
Did you hang it on your wall?
Get out of here!
MISSY: I'm telling people you cried.
Do you like guacamole?
I don't know.
Being from Maine, we didn't
have much Mexican food.
Or Mexican people. Or people.
It's just mashed up avocados.
I think you'd like it.
And they do it right here at the table.
Did they run out of room in the kitchen?
No, it's-it's like, you know, a show.
- Like Benihana.
- Exactly.
I don't like Benihana.
- Let's skip the guacamole.
- No, no.
You like it, and I want this date
to be appealing to
you, so let's order it.
Okay.
I might enjoy it. I might not.
But, uh, I'm willing
to take that gamble.
Which, uh, I'm given to understand
you also like.
Oh, that little rat just told
you everything, didn't he?
Don't feel bad, I enjoy a
little gambling now and then.
Do you?
I sat in your front seat, didn't I?
[LAUGHS]
Good, I made you laugh.
Full disclosure, I
wasn't trying to be funny.
[LAUGHS LOUDLY]
Still not trying.
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
They're not gonna be back for a while.
Go to bed.
I won't be able to sleep.
I'm not telling you to go to sleep,
I'm telling you to go to bed.
You don't think they'll have
relations tonight, do you?
Now I'm telling you to go to sleep.
So, John, you ever been married?
- No.
- Hmm.
Ever been in love?
Seven times.
Seven times?
How come you never settled down?
Well, my feelings were not reciprocated.
Well, that's so sad.
Not for them.
They all seemed pleased
with the outcome.
Especially number four.
She said she dodged a bullet.
That is a very brave thing
to say on a first date.
Why?
If there's a second date, I'll tell you.
I have a chance at a second date?
This is going very well.
Try the guacamole.
No, no, no. With a chip.
Oh.
[LAUGHS] Okay.
Like this.
There you go.
Mmm!
[CHUCKLING]
Now, how do chimichangas work?
I have no idea.
Well, I think we
should try and find out.
How'd it go?
Oh! What the hell?
I wanted to know how your date went,
and I got bored watching you sleep.
How long have you been there?
67 minutes.
Now, tell me everything.
Go away. Let me sleep.
Okay.
But before I go, should I be worried
he's not in your bed?
Get out!
I certainly hope you were nicer to him.
MEEMAW: Out!
So, are you gonna see him again?
I don't know.
He showed up at my house on a bike.
Like a Harley?
Like a Schwinn.
You mean a bike bike?
With a jingle bell on the
handlebar and everything.
Well, that's kind of charming.
He doesn't know how to drive a car.
Doesn't want to know.
Okay, a little less charming.
There's something about him.
I mean, he's smart as
hell, and gentle and funny.
Not always on purpose, but he's funny.
I never met anybody like him.
Sounds like Sheldon.
Now, why would you go
and put that thought in my mind?
Well, I think you should
give him another try.
I agree with Mom.
Sheldon!
Oh, no.
_
Aw.
STURGIS: So, now we can discuss
what the perturbative QCD
corrections to R-bar look like.
So, you can also write it as "R"
divided by the length of "R."
That would be a vector
of unit length...
parallel...
to "R."
I'm sorry, where was I?
"R" divided by the length of "R."
That would be a vector of unit
length parallel to "R."
Oh, yes. Thank you.
So, if you divide "R"
by the length of "R,"
that would be a vector...
of unit length parallel...
to...
I think you need to leave.
So...
when we divide "R"
by the length of "R,"
that would be a vector of unit length
parallel to "R."
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Sir, bad news.
Don't tell me. There's another problem
we're not smart enough to solve?
It's the satellite... the
liquid helium is boiling off.
Well, why the heck would that happen?
SHELDON: I'll tell you why.
The sun must be glinting
off the solar panel
and hitting the dewar.
Why didn't you know that?
I'm a disappointment, sir.
We need to calculate
all the Euler angles
that would cause the sun
to hit the liquid helium.
Can you do it in time?
I can with my new
friend, Dr. John Sturgis.
Hello.
[MAN COUGHS]
Hi.
He's gonna marry my meemaw.
I bought her a bicycle.
A purple bicycle.
Purple? Sounds like love to me.
[GASPS]
Mr. Cooper?!
Huh?
Are you paying attention?
I already know this.
You know this?
But they don't, so by
all means, continue.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --