MORRlS: Mrs Owen's
expecting a lot of guests.
And she chose you.
Welcome to Soldier lsland.
VERA: Mr Lombard, you seem
to be underthe impression
that I am a particular
kind of woman.
And I assure you that I am not.
They're the ten little soldiers.
You know, from the poem.
ACTOR: Ladies and gentlemen.
- Who is that?
You are charged with
the following indictments:
Philip Lombard,
that you did murder 21 men.
What the hell
are they playing at?
Malicious nonsense!
Cyril... I really tried
to save him.
I almost drowned.
21 men.
I'm the only one telling the
truth in a room full of liars.
- (Knocking)
- Who is it?
(Choking)
MACARTHUR: We are cut off.
Rats in a barrel.
- Almonds.
- Almonds be buggered.
Cyanide.
None of you moved them?
- No.
Was it you, Doctor?
No.
How did Mrs Rogers die?
I have no idea.
Did you give her something?
Yes, a mild sedative.
- Did you give hertoo much?
- Miss Claythorne...
I warned you against
becoming hysterical.
It's the poem.
It's the poem, don't you see?
Ten little soldiers boys -
one choked himself,
one overslept himself,
and then there were eight.
There were ten ofthese and
ten of us and nowthere's eight.
(Door opens)
Oh, General? General?
Did you move the figures?
What?
The figures,
did you move the figures?
No, of course not.
Perhaps it was you, Miss
Claythorne. You discovered it.
Of course it wasn't me.
Why would I do that?
To be the centre of attention.
Do you crave it?
- Any kind of attention?
- What are you talking about?
Shall we just have breakfast?
- Mm.
(Emily clears her throat)
It was dreadful news,
about Mrs Rogers.
(Clears her throat)
She was a wonderful cook.
Such a shame.
This egg is four minutes
precisely, is it?
Yes, madam.
Rogers...did you take away
two ofthese figures?
- No, miss.
- (Sighs)
Condolences, Mr Rogers. When
are you expecting Narracott?
Mid to late morning, sir.
His timekeeping
is somewhat erratic.
Will that be all?
Yes, thank you, Rogers.
Thank you very much.
VERA: Tony Marston
was young and strong.
He didn't die
from some stimulant.
Perhaps he was poisoned.
And Mrs Rogers,
perhaps she was given too much.
What drugs do you have
in your medical bag, Doctor?
Why did you even bring it?
You're a guest. It's not work.
Actually, it is work.
I was trying to maintain some
sort of professional discretion.
However...
Mrs Owen suffers
from female neuroses.
My speciality is
women's disorders.
Mr Owen engaged me
in a professional capacity
to tend to his wife!
Gave up on the surgery,
then, Doctor?
People do not just die
out of nowhere for no reason.
They die because something
was done to them by someone.
- I'm going to check your bag.
- Don't you dare!
- What have you got to hide?
BLORE: How about I do it?
I'm not being searched
like some grubby criminal!
EMlLY: What ifthe General
goes with him?
He's an honourable man.
Fine! But while you're at it,
you might want to search...
Judge Wargrave's case as well.
I knowwhere
I've seen you before.
Chap who has the clinic
beneath mine in Harley Street.
He's a cancer specialist.
That's where I saw you.
If anyone has strong painkillers
and sedatives in his case,
it's Judge Wargrave.
Is that true, Judge?
I have had health problems, yes.
Then that's very cruel, Doctor.
Don't blame me. You pushed it.
General, shall we?
(Ticking)
Just mild sedatives.
ARMSTRONG: As I said.
Bog standard.
Nothing special.
My surgery was a success.
This - the house, the island -
is meant to be my recuperation.
Sea air, peace...
..and rest.
- Very sorry. I'm very sorry.
- Hm.
- Well, there's an end to it.
- Like hell it is!
Why shouldn't she be searched?
Equal rights forwomen, hm?
Let's see what you've got.
WARGRAVE: Dr Armstrong,
control yourself, please.
Who the hell
do you think you are?
I'm a doctor,
you're a secretary.
Somebody moved them.
They did!
Someone did that.
(Door opens)
Did you really kill
all those men?
Yes, Miss Claythorne,
I did kill all those men.
And more.
Why?
It seemed like a good idea
at the time.
They had something I wanted.
In this case, it was diamonds.
Worth more than a few lives.
What about you?
What did you want?
I nearly drowned.
I failed to save
a little boy in my care.
And there isn't one minute
of every day
that I am not sorry for that.
Why aren't you?
I know what I am.
I always knew it would
catch up with me.
And here it is.
(lnhales deeply)
(Shells exploding overhead)
WOMAN: I love you,
I love you, I love you.
I think about you and you
kissing me and your hands
on me and in me
and your mouth on my body
and I cannot bear
that you are not with me now.
I wish...I long...
I crave for you, my darling.
And I feel so cruel
to poor dear John.
But the sun rises
and sets in your eyes, Henry.
I love you. I love you.
I am yours.
The men are all ready
for the whistle, sir.
Morale fairly good.
(Shells explode overhead)
Here, er...Iet me.
Henry.
You've been a...
a great friend to my wife and l.
(Exhales)
Perhaps you could call me John.
(Shells explode overhead)
Thank you...John.
(Gasps)
(Exhales heavily)
Myself and Mrs Rogers
were here for a week
without seeing a soul apart from
Narracott with the deliveries.
Lombard.
Where are you going?
We're sat around waiting
for Ulick Norman Owen.
What if he's been here
all along?
Plenty of places
he could be hiding.
Wait for me.
(Breathes erratically)
Please, please, please...
just fucking stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stop.
Now, this is... This is barmy!
No-one could hide down there.
(Gulls cry)
Ever get the feeling
you're being hunted, Tubs?
Stop calling me that.
I ain't even fat.
And, no, I don't.
Really?
Cos Mr Owen...
whoever he may be...
knows a lot about us.
Well, not about me.
Edward Landorwas a degenerate,
he was a pansy.
He fell down the steps
into his cell.
You never touched him?
I wouldn't want to be near
one ofthem dirty bastards.
Come on, Tubs, keep up!
(Gulls cry)
General?
Is your suitcase ready?
She died...
..of Spanish influenza
afterthe war.
Who?
My wife Leslie.
After all that...
she died ofthe Spanish flu.
So many did.
I should have just stepped aside
like a gentleman
and...just let them be happy.
Do come back to the house,
General.
You haven't brought
your case down yet
and we want to get away
as soon as Mr Narracott arrives.
He's not coming, Narracott,
you know.
No-one's coming for us.
We won't be leaving the island.
This is the end.
It's a reliefto come to the
end, to knowthat it's over.
You won't understand that yet
but you will, in time.
I think you're quite mistaken.
The boat will come and
we'll all be waiting for you.
(Exhales)
(Gulls crying)
(Shells booming)
(Voices whispering)
(Shellfire intensifies)
(Bombs exploding)
(Gunfire and bullets whistling)
Ah, Miss Claythorne.
Good.
Bring a couple of chairs,
would you?
(Chairs scraping)
What's going on?
It's a bit early
to be on the sauce.
It's been something
of a morning.
Hey, hey. Ssh.
Bastard's down there.
I heard him.
What bastard?
Owen.
LOMBARD:
I can hear him moving about.
Marston's room.
(Clattering)
(Rogers breathes heavily)
What are you doing?
Camp bed.
Well, we had to find somewhere
to store it.
Young men don't look under beds.
ARMSTRONG: Why do you need a
camp bed? What are you planning?
I can't sleep in my room, can l?
My wife.
No, obviously. Of course.
I've got to find
somewhere else to set up.
What for? We're all leaving!
Well, you might be.
This is my job.
I can't go anywhere until
my employer dismisses me.
Your employer?
Your employer is insane!
Be that as it may,
I've got nothing else to go to.
All right, then,
carry on, Rogers.
Did you know he had a gun?
No.
Do stop.
Mr Narracott seems a sensible
man. He'll be here.
I must say, I understand now
why you teach in such
a sub-standard establishment.
I'm just observing
that most schools
would not want to be associated
with an inquest.
I'm not accusing you. There's
been enough ofthat already.
Yes, there has.
More than enough.
Apart from the egregious
Mr Lombard
and the Rogers,
who I find most dubious,
and the depraved Mr Marston,
it's all nonsense.
Everyone was simply
doing their duty.
As was l.
As were you?
You didn't say anything
last night.
It wasn't for gentlemen's ears.
Beatrice Taylorwas
my maid of all work.
Foundling girl...
an unwanted.
From the war, you know.
I believed herto be a clean,
decent, modest girl.
I taught her needlework skills.
We had quite the little home.
But then she got herself
into trouble.
The family way.
As her own loose mother
had with her.
She begged me for help.
Naturally, and quite properly,
I refused.
(Beatrice sobs)
Miss Brent, please!
I beg you!
What happened to her?
She threw herself under a train.
She killed herself?
Even made the local paper.
And they turned it into some
pot-boiling, sentimental tale.
She asked you for help.
If you had helped her...
It was the weakness
in her character
which drove her actions.
Why should I be reproached?
Ask Rogers for some tea.
Lemon, not milk.
ARMSTRONG: It's a wild goose
chase, ifyou ask me.
A grown man, hiding and
sneaking about. It's ridiculous.
Marston was given cyanide,
though.
Wasn't he, Tubs?
Cyanide?
I'm pretty sure of it.
I don't know. You were convinced
of it this morning.
Claythorne forthe cyanide.
I'd put money on it.
- She don't seem the type.
- She's exactly the type.
What about the old boy,
the General?
Dangerous men come back
from overthere,
their noggins all scrambled.
Let's search everybody, then.
God-bothering Miss Brent,
let's search Wargrave...
- The Judge?
- Mm.
Well-known as a hanging judge.
Infamous forthe black square.
The story goes that he'd watch
every execution he'd ordered.
Tubs, you've looked sideways
at Armstrong all morning
and now everyone's fair game.
- You suggested the Judge.
- I was taking the piss.
Mr Owen is on the island.
And I'm going to find him.
You don't want to pay attention
to what he said.
He's just stirring the shit pot.
And I can stir it right back.
(Wind rumbling)
(Gulls cry)
(Gulls continue to cry)
(Thunder rumbles)
Oh.
(Men grunting)
LOMBARD: Don't look.
Someone did this?
BLORE: Well, it weren't
no bleeding accident.
It's murder.
He said no-one
was coming for us.
He said this was the end.
Miss Claythorne?
"Eight little soldier boys
travelling in Devon.
One said he'd stay there
and then there were seven."
Count them, Judge.
Count them.
(Thunder crashes)
(Wind howling)
VERA: Cyril!
Run!
Find help, a boat!
Cyril!
(Cry echoes) Cyril!
Miss Claythorne!
I just want to go!
You'll drown!
Please!
Come inside. Come, come.
I've got you.
Don't worry, it's all right.
LOMBARD: I told you
Owen was on the island.
What made you so sure?
- lnstinct.
- We've got to be rational.
Stick with procedure.
Who is this Owen?
And Mrs Owen.
I don't think there
even is a Mrs Owen.
BLORE: We must all have
something in common.
- Someone who knows us all.
EMlLY: How can that be possible?
I can imagine crossing paths
with a doctor,
a judge, but...
someone like Mr Lombard?
Well, we've crossed paths now,
haven't we?
Mr Lombard, Blore tells me
that you have a revolver.
Oh, Tubs.
- Why have you got a gun?
- He's got a gun?
I carry it everywhere.
And it was implied
that I might need it.
Implied? By whom?
My client needs a good man
who can handle situations.
- Who's your client?
- Mr Owen.
Ulick Norman Owen.
Never heard of him.
But he has heard of you.
Audrey, the box.
It's dangerous, then?
My client believes
that it could become volatile.
I see.
And howwould Mr Owen
wish me to proceed?
He leaves that
to your discretion.
- But forewarned is...
- Is forearmed.
I understand.
That's who got in touch with me
about the job with Mrs Owen.
Isaac Morris in Soho.
Soho? Hm.
WARGRAVE: I was invited here
by the Owens,
whom I'd never heard of,
to join a mutual friend,
Mrs Culmington.
The perfect place
to recover, it said.
The envelope was postmarked
London, Soho.
A sink of depravity.
A godless desert of vice.
What brings you here,
Miss Brent?
Mrs Owen wrote to me.
She was interested in my work.
The Moral Education of Girls
ofthe lower orders.
They have to be taught
modesty and decency
or society will be drowned in a
rising tide of unwanted babies,
all squalling to be fed.
She wanted to contribute
to my cause.
Blore?
I got a letter...
from Ulick Norman Owen.
He was impressed
by my standing in the force.
He said if I could
see my way clear
to spending some time
keeping an eye out
that he would recompense me
generously.
Keeping an eye out forwhat?
He said that someone was here
underfalse pretences.
He also supplied
a list of guests.
All ofyou - every one ofyou.
What he didn't say was
that Lombard would have a gun.
ARMSTRONG: Is it Mr Owen's voice
on the record?
- Does anybody recognise it?
- Are we forgetting the gun?
There's a Fenian there
with a bloody gun!
- Don't blaspheme.
BLORE: Hand it over.
Surrender yourweapon,
Mr Lombard.
- Not a chance.
- I could make you.
You can try.
Wait. Is lsaac Morris Mr Owen?
No. I'd have found that
sweaty bucket of lard by now.
EMlLY: Jews.
Whereverthere's a problem,
there's Jews
at the bottom of it.
- Something struck me.
- (Thunder rumbles)
I can't think
why I didn't see it before.
Ulick Norman Owen.
Una Nancy Owen.
Or...
WARGRAVE: U.N. OWEN...
..is unknown.
(Thunder rumbles)
It's a riddle, perhaps.
What does it mean?
It means that Mr Lombard
is right to insist
that the killer
is on the island.
And he's getting very wet
out there.
The killer's not out there.
The killer is in here.
It is one of us.
We've never met each other
before now. Why?
How could I possibly be capable?
Oh, anyone is capable,
Miss Brent.
40 years on the criminal benches
taught me that.
Rogers.
Oh, here we go again,
lining up the next suspect.
You mark my words - Rogers.
He's an oily bugger.
Slinking around.
EMlLY: Going back and forth
during dinner.
He could have put something
in Mr Marston's drink.
I heard him tell Mrs Rogers
to shut up.
Well, she's shut up now,
isn't she?
He's the one moving the figures.
But the General, the rest of us,
that record, this house. Why?
Rogers - he's got low cunning
running through him
Iike Brighton
through a stick of rock.
- We need to watch him.
- Any faith I ever had
in the Thin Blue Line evaporated
the second I met you, Tubs.
You call me that one more time,
mate, one more time...
And you'll what?
(Wind howling outside)
We are all being hunted.
There's someone else
on this island.
And when I find him,
I'm going to make him number 22,
with a bullet right there.
- Oh, God.
- How could you say that...
so easily?
I just open my mouth
and it comes out.
(Door creaks open)
I'll see what can be done
about supper.
There's some liver and kidneys.
Perhaps a pie...
with some good gravy.
That would be delicious, Rogers.
Thank you.
Thank you, Rogers.
Well, I ain't eating a mouthful
of his pie.
(Sniffs)
(Thunder)
(Wind whistling)
Oh, well, good night.
(Thunder cracks)
Trust in God.
But perhaps also...
we should lock our doors.
(Electricity fizzes)
(Muffled praying)
He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures.
He leadeth me beside
the still waters.
(Thunder cracks)
(Door blows open and wind howls)
(Male voice recites poem)
(Crack of thunder)
He leadeth me in the paths
of righteousness
for His name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through...
BEATRlCE:..the valley
ofthe shadow of death,
I will fear no evil...
forthou art with me.
..I will fear no evil.
I will fear no evil
forthou art...
forthou art with me.
(Thunder crashes)
Get up! Get up!
Get up!
(Gong resonating)
- I was looking for him.
- (She vomits)
I wanted a coffee.
I looked...and I found this.
It wasn't me.
I just wanted a damn coffee.
- It wasn't me.
- He's been here all night.
"Seven little soldiers
chopping up sticks,
one chopped himself in half
and then there were six."
So she's right.
It is the poem.
But he's fucked,
Mr Unknown Owen,
because "Six little soldier boys
played with a hive.
A bumblebee stung one
and then there were five."
And there is no hive here
and there are no bees.
What are you going to do now,
Mr Unknown Owen? You're fucked!
Now get dressed.
We will all get dressed
and I will make coffee.
- Miss Brent, shall we?
- Yes.
Shit. Shit the bed.
We need to wrap him up
or he's going to go everywhere.
(Ticking)
(Approaching footsteps)
Coffee.
There's no milk, I'm afraid.
Does this...person...
..mean to kill us all?
I believe so, yes.
I've lost a ball ofwool.
I'm quite ridiculously
distressed about it.
It's only wool.
(Rumble ofthunder)
(Sighs)
I'm so very tired.
Drink your coffee, Miss Brent.
I'll bring you a candle
to see by.
Thank you, dear.
(Crack ofthunder)
(Rain pattering on windows)
I'll make some more.
Judge Wargrave,
I feel I owe you an apology
for exposing your illness
in such
an unforgiveable fashion.
We're all feeling
a little ragged.
Understandably.
What's your opinion
ofthe others?
I haven't really formed one.
I don't trust any ofthem.
Blore. That bastard Lombard.
Claythorne.
Miss Brent
and her religious mania.
But you and l...
..we have sharp minds.
Actual intellects.
We should stick together.
Mm.
Very well.
Oh...
Here.
Thank you.
Dribbling down myself
like a child.
(Thunder rumbling)
Miss Claythorne's
making the coffee.
She should be watched.
(Grunting)
Right...
You do the stairs.
I'm going to wash the guts
out ofthe wood store.
(Water splashes gently)
(Crockery clinks)
(Door opens in adjoining room)
Can l?
I rather enjoy domestictasks.
They are soothing.
Normal.
Indeed.
I'll just be a moment.
All right.
(Rain pattering on window)
(Hinges squeak)
(Gong resonating)
VERA: Stung by a bee.
- And then there were five.
- (Crack ofthunder)
Well, I suppose, with no Rogers,
I should think about lunch.
I could eat a scabby horse.
You're actually hungry?
It was heavy work...
dealing with Rogers.
And you're the one
who suggested lunch.
Only because it's what one does
at this time of day.
But I'm not hungry.
How could you be hungry?
Oi, you.
Don't go implying...
..casting aspersions. I've got
nothing to do with this.
I've got nothing to do
with any of it.
Just because I said
I was hungry... I am.
It doesn't prove a single thing.
I'm going to get dressed.
The whole morning,
dragging Rogers around,
clearing up guts,
without so much as a cup oftea
to wet my whistle,
- and you look at me like a...
- Calm down.
You've got some front, love.
You got some right brass neck.
LOMBARD: Don't go downstairs
on your own.
Not with those two.
- What, Wargrave and Armstrong?
- Mm-hm.
You wait up here for me.
LOMBARD:
It was locked,
which means there must be
a master key.
Rogers must have had
- You two dealt with the body.
- And you found it.
Or did you?
You shrieking like a woman...was
that a bit of amateur dramatics?
I did nothing to Rogers.
I didn't take any master key. We
don't even know ifthere is one.
And we only have yourword
that the gun was stolen.
- You could've taken it.
- Why steal my own gun?
I don't knowwhy you'd do
anything, Lombard.
I don't knowwhy
you killed Rogers
- or Miss Brent or MacArthur.
- I didn't kill them.
You would say that,
wouldn't you?
Just like you'd say
that your gun was stolen.
You really are a first-class...
five-star, solid gold
fucking moron.
WARGRAVE: Please.
The lady. Hm?
BLORE: Double bluff.
What, Tubs?
Why you would steal your own
gun. Armstrong's got a point.
It's all riddles and games,
smoke and mirrors. Double bluff.
You were the last one down.
The last one.
Ages behind everyone else.
What took you so long?
- I don't care to say.
LOMBARD: You killed Rogers.
You took the master key.
You went to bed.
You made sure all of us
were downstairs,
got into my room
and took my gun.
You have my gun,
you little prick.
- For heaven's sake.
- I never killed Rogers
and I ain't got your key
or your sodding gun.
Then what took you so long?
If you weren't stealing my gun,
then why were you the last down?
I was in the bloody lavvy
if you must know.
Constipated!
(Laughter)
Oh, yes. Laugh it up.
It's not funny.
I was bound up something rotten.
(Laughter)
Sat there in a muck sweat.
So it weren't me.
It could have been any of us.
Any one of us
could have had the key.
could have the gun.
(Clock ticking)
It is the only way to be sure.
BLORE: It's not like
you've been singled out.
We're all getting the same.
BLORE: No key. No gun.
Well...now you, Miss Claythorne.
Of course.
I'm just being thorough.
You like Uncle Hugo, don't you?
VERA: I do.
I'm in love with him.
I love him so much it hurts.
Silly. Girls are silly.
(Chuckles)
And I'm going to marry him.
I heard Mummy say he couldn't
afford to get married.
Well, I'll find a way, Cyril.
- lfyou marry Uncle Hugo...
- When I marry Hugo.
-..will you be my aunt?
- I will.
Aunt Vera.
And what fun we'll have.
Christmas and birthdays
and summer holidays.
Picnics, parties, pony rides.
How happy we'll be
when we have everything.
(Rain pattering on windows)
(Muffled shouting)
(Muffled scream)
(She gasps)
ARMSTRONG:
Why isn't Lombard doing this?
Blore and I thought it a good
idea to keep you two apart.
Well, well, Miss Claythorne.
Mr Lombard.
Philip.
Vera.
(Door opens nearby)
Nothing.
We'll search the rest of
the house. Every room.
(Cutlery rattling)
(Clattering)
(Thunder)
(Clock ticking)
(Clock chiming)
BLORE: We're in hell...
and we're being punished
forwhat we done.
WARGRAVE: He refused the hood.
He haunts me still.
Look at them. There's something
going on between them.
VERA: And someone has to come
for us soon. They have to.
BLORE: I reckon
we're being watched.
- (Yells)
- We are.