You know, one of the
downsides to a life of crime
is that occasionally you have to do
business with people who are, um...
Well, for want of a
better word, criminals.
Like most things that end
with you hanging upside down
in a deserted warehouse,
it started with a really good idea.
"A Small Cat ln The Garden was
painted by Pablo Picasso in 1903,
"in what was known
as his Blue Period.
"It measures 12 inches by 11 inches and
was stolen from a private collection
"in the early hours
of Sunday morning."
Mmmm...
Value?
- It's been insured for 3 million.
- Wow.
"Police say the gang was clearly
experienced and well informed."
- Meaning it was stolen to order.
- No question.
- Is Mad Dolly still around?
- My thoughts exactly.
- Who? - Dolly Hammond, she's
the best Picasso forger in London.
She's all right, but she's just
a bit.... She's...unique.
Yeah, she's a bit different,
you know.
- Insane.
- Yeah. - Nice.
She's a lovely old bird
really, but, erm...
she used to have
the hots for Albie.
Why would we need someone to forge a
painting that's already been stolen?
Well, because now its theft
has already been reported...
Collectors will believe you if you
tell 'em you're trying to sell it.
It's brilliant!
- Yes, it is. - Yes, it is.
- As always.
Well, potentially brilliant.
Depending on who you try
and sell the fake to.
And here's a little tip
should you ever find yourself
trying to flog a fake Picasso...
Don't try and sell it
to the bloke
who the original was nicked
from in the first place.
Aye-aye.
Here come the cavalry.
Ash!
Gently, Sean, gently!
Oooh...
- Where's Mickey?
- They pulled a gun on us.
- Petre Sava's men have taken him.
- What happened?
Well, it's a very long story,
but the upshot is
the original was nicked
from him in the first place.
He wasn't happy at us telling
him it was us who nicked it,
and then trying to sell him a fake
back instead of the real thing.
This is not Picasso!
This is not my painting!
So Petre Sava is holding
on to Mickey till
we deliver the real
Picasso back to him.
We haven't got the real one.
No, I did mention that,
and we argued for a bit,
then he threatened a
level of physical violence
I wasn't comfortable with,
so I backed down.
He's given us six hours to find it.
So what happens if we
can't find the real painting?
Oh, he was very specific about that.
Mickey's a dead man.
sync and corrections by Bellows
www.addic7ed.com
So no-one's got anything?
- But that's impossible.
- Well, it's not a local crew.
Someone would know if it was.
By now the real painting could've
been shipped out of the country.
Yeah, but, come on, it's weird
that no-one's heard anything.
Or if they have, they
don't want to share it.
What about that Dolly the forger?
Would she know?
If she's a Picasso freak, she
might have heard something.
I suppose...
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, it's worth a try.
- Let's do it.
Can't find a decent
thief these days,
they're all gangsters,
they've got no class.
- Not like you Albert.
- Thank you, Dolly.
I'd string 'em all up.
By the testicles.
Leave them there for
the crows to pick at.
Feed what's left to the
pigs, like we used to.
So you've no idea who
stole the Picasso, Dolly?
- What Picasso?
- A Small Cat ln The Garden.
You've had your copy,
I've already done it.
No, no,
I'm talking about the real one.
He's cute.
Dolly, the painting, have
you any idea who nicked it?
How would I know that?
- Has no-one said anything to you?
- Who? - Anyone.
- Said what? - About the painting.
- What painting?
- The Picasso.
- I don't know who nicked it.
- Well, that's what I'm asking, innit?
- I've told you. Who are you?
Oh... I'm Emma.
What are you doing
in my house?
I'm with Albert.
This your floozy, is it?
No, no, no, no. You're the
only woman for me, Dolly.
Ohhh!
Aah...unlucky.
Dolly, do you know anything
at all about the painting?
Anything that might help
us find out who nicked it?
I mean, was there someone who
really liked it? A private collector?
Or did someone try and
buy it before and failed?
Anything.
I know where every
Picasso in London is.
I can smell them.
Except this one.
Dolly, look, is there any way you
can track it down, you know?
I mean, what's the
word on the street?
Do I look like Huggy Bear?
Dolly!
We need to find it.
I'll see what I can do, if...
..he sings to me,
and he snogs me.
♪ Hello Dolly, well, Hello Dolly
♪ lt's so nice to have you
back where you belong! ♪
SHE LAUGHS
Oh...
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
No.
Forget it. It's...
it's not happening.
Sean, think about Mickey.
- (Forget Mickey.) - (Do it.)
- I don't want to... - Do it.
- Don't want to!
- Sean...
HE WHIMPERS
Naughty!
SHE CHUCKLES
Well?
Erm...well, I should
know in a couple of hours.
Send him.
THUMP
CAR ALARM
HE SIGHS
Now, just in case Dolly
draws a blank,
we'd better cover all the angles.
Albert, use your police contacts,
see if they've got any leads
- on the robbery or any
idea who it was. - Right.
- Sean, take the car. See what else you
can find out about Petre Sava. - OK.
- What about us? - You and me
will go and see Cyclops.
Now, art's not really his thing,
but he might have heard something.
I've got The Dogs Playing Snooker,
if that's any good to you?
It's a classic.
I used to have The Bird On The
Tennis Court Scratching Her Bum,
but it got stiletto damage
in a domestic dispute.
- Well, women don't really get art,
do they? - Is that right?
Yeah, well-known fact.
They've got no patience for it.
That's why all the major
artists are all men.
Women would never be
able to finish anything.
They'd be halfway through
The Laughing Cavalier,
then they'd wander off and start
colour-coding their shoe cupboard.
Look, can we get back
to the matter in hand?
- Which was?
- A Small Cat ln The Garden.
- The stolen Picasso.
- Oh, yeah.
So who nicked it?
- Art's not really my thing.
- I said that, didn't I? - Yeah.
- But I heard about it.
- What?
- I said I heard about it.
- No, no, no, what did you hear?
- That it was nicked. You want a chip?
- No. Thank you.
- Any chance of a date?
- None.
Sympathy shag? Think of it as
charity work, it's been a while.
Look, Cyclops, Mickey's in trouble.
Whatever you know,
you need to tell me.
- We haven't haggled yet.
- What? You're going to charge us?
'Scuse me.
This is still a capitalist society.
I thought Mickey was your mate.
Well, he's more of an
acquaintance, really.
But that said, I'm willing
to make a discount.
How much?
Call it a nifty.
OK.
I can't tell if these
things are related,
but the day
before the Picasso was nicked,
a hardcore jock crew flew in.
Scottish?
The McCrary brothers. They took
over a house in Westbridge Grove.
Now, all I know about
'em is that they nick to order,
anything you like,
usually upmarket.
Paintings, cars, antiques...
I mean they could be here for
something else, but...
It's worth asking the question,
innit?
OK. What do you think?
Well, we could knock
on the door, say "Och, aye, the noo,"
and ask 'em if they've
just nicked a Picasso.
It's direct. But as we
don't know who they are,
I think it's a little bit foolhardy.
Yeah, I know, that's
what I like about it.
Ash?
DOOR BUZZER
- 'Who is it?'
- It's Ash Morgan, I need to talk
to you about the
Picasso you just nicked.
- Have you lost your marbles?
- Yeah. We haven't got much time.
What's the worst that could happen?
They could kill us!
Yeah, well, then at least Mickey
would know we died trying.
- You've got some bottle. - Yeah, well,
needs must, and all of that.
Well, in you come, then.
That's very kind, but if
it's all the same to you,
- we'll stay out here.
- Fair play.
The trouble is, a very good friend
of mine is being held by Petre Sava,
the bloke you nicked
the Picasso from.
Now, it's a long story,
but now he thinks we got it.
- And why would he think that?
- Because we told him we did.
Yeah. We were trying
to sell him a fake.
- We're grifters.
- Yeah. It's what we do.
We read about the
Picasso being nicked,
so we had a copy made
to sell to a private collector,
one who wouldn't
ask too many questions.
If they'd read about it being
stolen, they'd believe it was real.
Exactly.
Trouble is, the collector we
took it to, it was paid to Sava,
who was the one
you'd nicked it from.
Which he wasn't very happy
about, as you can imagine.
It's a beautiful story, and
I'm getting all misty-eyed,
but what's any this
got to do with us?
Well, err...
If you give us the real Picasso,
the one that you nicked from Sava,
we can go and get our mate back.
Well, let's just say that
we had this painting,
not that I'm saying that
we do, you understand...
But he's your friend, not ours.
So what's in it for us?
Well, to be honest, I haven't thought
that bit through. What do you want?
Don't want anything.
I tell you what, 20 grand and I'll
nick it straight back for you.
You know, just for the
sheer brass neck of you,
I'm tempted to help you out.
And I do love a grifter.
Especially a pretty one.
- But it's already been moved on.
- Where? - Oh, I can't tell you that.
- You have to.
- Ash, is it? - Yeah.
Ash.
I can't do it, son.
We've worked years
to build up a reputation
based on complete discretion.
I can't piss that up the wall
for a couple of grifters.
So my lips are sealed.
All right, what about if I
threatened to beat it out of you?
Then I would respect that.
And me and my brother Neil here, would
defend ourselves as best we could,
by ripping your head from the
rest of your body and eating it.
Fair enough, just asking.
You have a nice day.
So, looks like we're
back to square one.
- No, not exactly, now we know
who stole it. - Yeah, but not who for.
- We still don't know where it is.
- Any news from the Old Bill, Albert?
It seems we know
more than they do.
What if the McCrary brothers
haven't delivered it yet?
We could just watch the house and
wait for them to make a move, right?
What if they're delivering
it tomorrow or next week?
We've only got four hours left.
What about Petre Sava?
Well, I did some digging
about, like you said.
Mickey was right about him
being a high-end art collector.
His private collection would rival
most European galleries.
The last we knew, he owned
half a dozen nightclubs
in London, so he was
bound to be a bit dodgy.
- Well, that's a good thing.
- Yeah. Until you find out how dodgy.
- Human trafficking... - Aah.
- ..Class A drug distribution,
and a protection racket
that started in Romania,
and has now spread
over eight European cities.
We need to get Mickey
out of there.
So what did you do with
the black guy?
He's in the boot of my car.
- Can he breathe?
- Sure.
At least I think so.
If they don't bring me
my painting...
..you think we should kill him,
or just cut some bits off?
Or both?
Both is good.
They don't cut people up too
much in the West, you know.
They don't kill them very much,
either. They "beat up".
But if you just "beat up,"
they get better,
they find some friends,
and then they come back.
If you cut bits off and post them to
their friends, this doesn't happen.
No. It's more efficient.
Exactly.
So, both it is.
You cut...
..I kill.
THUMPING
- Where's Mickey? - He's being held
hostage by a Romanian gangster
who won't release him until we find
a painting of a cat in a garden.
Yeah, right, yeah.
EDDIE CHUCKLES
You crack me up, you lot.
Very vivid imaginations,
as my mum used to say.
Mind you, you probably
need them in your line of work.
Cheers, Eddie. Look, give us a couple
of minutes, will you? We're thinking.
I thought I could hear something.
Oh, you had a phone call.
- Nice lady... Molly? - Dolly.
- Dolly. That's it.
She said she's got what you want,
only you have to send the
cute one, whatever that means.
No way.
Oh... No way.
No way!
No...
..way.
JAZZ MUSIC IN BACKGROUND
Ta-daa!
I didn't know if you liked
red or white,
so I brought one of each. Oh.
Ha-ha...
SHE CHUCKLES
It was horrible.
- So, did you actually have to?
- I don't want to talk about it.
Oh...
No, of course not.
She took her teeth out.
SNORTS
So, did she say anything at all?
Take a deep breath, Sean.
It might help to make
the pictures go away.
Petre Sava bought A
Small Cat ln The Garden
by Picasso at an auction in Kensington.
He outbid a private collector
called Matthew Fairchild,
who's an investment banker,
and happens to be the
father of Louise Fairchild,
whose married name is Holmes.
Should we know her?
No, but you might've
heard of her husband.
- Harry Holmes!
- The Harry Holmes?
'Fraid so.
It's all right. It's all right,
calm down. Calm down.
Now, I understand
you're not a grass...
..and I admire that in a man,
I really do.
I need you to open up for me.
One way...or another.
When Harry Holmes found
out it was Petre Sava
who beat his father-in-law
to the painting,
- he wasn't happy. It hurt his
pride a bit. - I bet it did.
I heard he was like a
dog with two whatsits
when he married
into the upper classes.
He's always fancied hunting,
shooting and fishing.
So the painting's about impressing
- the new in-laws?
- Seems like it.
Then maybe those in-laws
are one of the reasons
that Harry hasn't got
his own hands dirty
in order to get the painting back.
He paid the McCrary brothers
to steal it for him instead.
- That's what Dolly said. - And you're
sure that wasn't just pillow talk?
So on one side we've got a violent
Eastern European gangster,
and on the other,
a homicidal maniac?
- That's about the strength of it.
- So what shall we do?
Sensible thing would
be call the Old Bill,
tell 'em what happened and
throw ourselves on their mercy.
- We're not going to do that, right?
- No.
Which leaves us with
one other option.
Which is?
To steal the painting back
from Harry Holmes.
This is the home of
Matthew Fairchild,
father-in-law of Harry Holmes,
who paid the McCrery brothers to
steal the Picasso from Petre Sava.
I still can't believe
you got it back.
It's family, innit?
I know someone who's getting
a special treat later.
Now Fairchild's already a collector,
so the security is a bit nifty.
- That's comforting.
- Yes, they got CCTV, weight sensor pads,
motion detectors, heat imaging
systems and laser webs.
That's if you can get past the
two killer dogs in the grounds.
I hate dogs.
Luckily, although the
system's state of the art,
it was designed
by Fairchild himself.
How does that help us?
Systems like this are only
as good as their design,
and he's made a very common,
but simple mistake.
- Which is?
- Basically it's a domestic system,
and like most domestic alarm systems,
it's designed on the assumption
that a theft would take place
either when the place is empty
or at night under cover of darkness.
Which means when they're
home during the day,
the alarms are switched off.
- Exactly, Albert.
- Because who would be
stupid enough to break into a house
in broad daylight
when everyone's at home?
'OK, so this is all about timing.
'Everything on cue,
like a ballet.
'Firstly, let's make sure the dogs
get their sleeping pills.
'They'll last about 20 minutes.'
Three, two, one.
'Dogs are asleep.
I'm moving into position.'
Albert, you set?
Ready.
Emma?
Sean?
Ready.
- Ready.
- 'OK.'
Go!
POLICE SIREN APPROACHES
Hello, madam. We're investigating
a stolen painting.
What are you doing? We need
to search the property.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I've got your number, fella!
I'll be straight onto the station!
But I think
we should get out of here.
Yeah. I'm with you.
No, look!
This is it, I've had enough!
All right, come on.
Calm down.
Don't you tell me
to calm down!
All right, thanks, Nigel, don't
forget I owe you a big cigar.
A good one?
Yeah, thanks, bye, bye.
All right, the police
have been tipped off,
they've seized the painting and
they've arrested Harry Holmes.
- Is that good or bad?
- Well, it can't be good, can it?
Wait! That's exactly what it is.
- How? - If the police have it,
Sava was the rightful owner.
They'll give him back the painting.
- He'll let Mickey go. - Job done.
- Eduardo, refreshments, please.
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
Yes, Nigel!
I see. All right, thanks for taking the
time to call me back, I appreciate it.
- They've released Harry Holmes.
- That was quick!
Well, they found the painting
in the house and it was fake.
- What?! - That ain't possible.
We know it was the original,
he had it nicked from Sava,
who bought it at the auction.
He wouldn't have angry
enough to kidnap Mickey
and hung Ash upside
down if all he'd lost a fake!
So if the one Harry had was a fake,
where's the real one?
Drinks up.
"Oh, thank you very much, Eddie"
"It's a pleasure to serve you..."
"Yeah, thank you very much"
- Doesn't make sense. - No.
- Let's think about this for a minute.
We have to assume that the
painting the McCrary brothers
nicked from Petre Sava
is the real Picasso.
- Agreed. - But by the time
it got to Harry Holmes
and his father-in-law,
it was a fake.
- Exactly.
- So they switched it?
- Yes, it can't be anything else.
- So if they passed on a fake to Harry,
they must've had another
buyer for the real one.
- Robbing bastards.
- The McCrarys have the real painting?
That's the only thing
that makes sense.
- They must have it!
- Or at least know where it is.
- The gate's wide open.
- Oh, we're too late!
There's no sign of life anywhere...
- No, they're long gone.
- Of course they are.
If you're just about to
stitch up Harry Holmes,
you're not gonna hang
around where he can find you.
They must have moved out just
after we saw them, right?
They could be back in Glasgow by now.
- We're screwed.
- No, you mean Mickey is.
Wait, wait. If you were going to
give Harry Holmes a fake,
you're not going to
risk him spotting it, are you?
I mean, it'd have
to be near-perfect.
So - where would you go for
a near-perfect copy of a Picasso?
- A girl's got to earn a living!
- But why didn't you tell us, Dolly?
Well, I didn't know
there was a connection!
It's the flaming cat in the wotsit,
the painting we was asking you about!
Yeah, but I can't keep
track of everything,
I'm not an accountant,
I'm an artist.
All right, all right.
So...step by step, right?
You did the fake
for the McCrarys, right?
- Maybe.
- Dolly! Stop messing about!
Are you going to let him
speak to me like that?
Eh?
I thought what
we had was special.
We didn't have anything!
You touched my Mabel!
- What? - That-That is what
she calls her ferret.
- Ferret?
- Yes, she keeps it in the khazi.
I don't let just anyone
touch my Mabel.
Dolly!
Yeah, yeah,
all right, all right.
I made the McCrarys a fake,
and they said that they'd got
a buyer, but he was a muppet
and he'd never know the difference.
Yeah, well, that
"muppet" is Harry Holmes.
Oh. That's not good.
No, it's not, is it?
So I need you to tell me
what the McCrarys were
doing with the real Picasso.
They did say something
about a new buyer.
Who?
I don't know.
- Did they say anything at all?
Mention any names? - No.
OK, right, well, the, er,
the fake...
so, when you'd finished it,
did they collect it from here?
- No. - So how did you
get it to them?
I had to parcel it up
and send it in a cab.
Right.
Where to?
- I don't remember.
- Dolly! This is important.
Look, it's all this pressure!
I can't think straight with
you all looking at me!
- Would it help if we all just
looked away? - Yes. Except him.
Oh, come on, Dolly!
Oh. Oh!
Maybe a gin might do it.
It helps me to relax.
What do we have with it?
More gin.
- Go.
- Thank you.
It was a hotel.
Good. Which one?
Up west.
Name.
Have another gin.
- She's no use to us if she passes
out, is she? - I am here, you know!
I could, er...
I could book us a room
while I was there.
It was the Goodridge
on the South Bank.
See if they've got a four-poster!
Is he still alive?
HE GRUNTS IN PAIN
Yes, boss.
You know your friends have two
hours to return with my painting.
If they are late, we cut off something
every ten minutes until they get here.
If they are not here in two hours,
we kill whatever is left.
What do you think of that?
Do you want me to take his gag off?
So he can tell you what he thinks?
No, no.
I'm a people person,
it was a rhetorical question,
I know what he thinks.
You do?
He is thinking he hopes his friends
come before we cut anything off.
Oh.
Then maybe he's thinking about what
we will cut off, and in what order.
True?
- Do you think they're still here?
- Albert, do you know the concierge?
- Yes. Anthony...
Excuse me for a moment.
I thought Dolly sent the
fake painting here.
Yes, because the McCrary
brothers needed a fake
to give to Harry Holmes,
not the real one.
- So it means the real one could be here?
- There's only one way to find out.
All right.
They're staying overnight,
they've booked a car tomorrow
morning to go to the airport.
And right now,
they're in the bar.
They don't look like they've
got anything with them.
- What room are they in, Albert?
- 624.
They've seen me and Ems,
so we'll check the room,
you keep an eye on 'em, give us
a heads up if they move. All right.
- We haven't got a lot of time.
- You go that way. - Yeah.
CHATTER AND LAUGHTER
It's not here.
I'm making a real
pig's ear of this, aren't I?
All those times Mickey's bailed us out,
I can't even find a painting.
We're gonna find it,
it's just a matter of time.
Time we haven't got.
It's less than an hour now.
Know what? I'd rather get tooled up,
go to Sava's and take me chances.
- You can't do that.
- Yeah, well, I can't do this either.
It's a setback, but come on,
you're just as smart as Mickey.
Right. The McCrary brothers
are still downstairs.
Let's just go and
try to talk to them again.
We can get through this.
Let's go.
Now, that's clever.
See?
I told you we'd get it!
Who the hell are you?
CHATTER AND LAUGHTER
So let me get this straight.
Sava is holding your mate
until you bring him this. Yeah.
And he doesn't know it was me
who nicked the painting?
He thinks it was you.
HE CHUCKLES
Sounds like you're up shit creek and
left the paddle at home, sunshine.
And I have had a right result.
Just tell me one thing.
How did you know it was here?
We didn't. We just found the
McCrarys and hoped for the best.
Yeah, well those two
stitched me right up.
Didn't just sell me a moody
painting,
they made me look like a prat
in front of my wife's family.
Where are they?
No idea, there was no-one in
the room when we got here.
All right, seems to me you
two haven't done me any harm,
you've got nothing I need,
and you've got enough
to worry about. So get out.
Go on, sling your hook
before I change my mind.
We can't do that.
- Oh, yeah?
- No.
Without the painting, Petre Sava's
not gonna let our mate go.
So, I don't care who you are.
I ain't leaving without it.
And that's your final word?
Yeah, it is.
No, don't!
HE GRUNTS IN PAIN
Oohh...
Ash.
That wasn't very smart.
So have we got a plan B?
Well, it's more like
plan A revisited. Eh?
Harry will take the painting back
to his father-in-law's like a hero.
And we've got a plan in place
to steal it back from there.
- Clever. - Yeah, more importantly, we
need Harry back at the house pronto,
and finding the McCrary boys
will only slow him down.
So let's make sure
he has to leave now.
FIRE ALARM RINGS
Right.
Like a ballet, remember?
- We all set?
- Ready.
Set.
I'm ready.
Right.
Go!
And you're sure it's definitely
the real one this time?
Oh, yeah. Ooh, I love you
so much, I could burst.
DOORBELL RINGS
I'll get it.
Hello?
Hi, I'm really sorry, but my Bobby
has just run into your garden.
- Bobby?
- He's a white Bichon Frise.
- Oh. Only I was worried in case
you had dogs. - We do!
Oh.
No. Um...
Bobby! Darling, come on!
Wait, I'll come with you.
THEY CALL OUT
OK, two in the viewing room.
'Time to split 'em up.'
PHONE RINGS
Bobby! Bobby!
Hello? Fairchild.
Paul Holland from New York.
'We met at an awful meet and
greet in London last month.'
You do remember?
We've been through here
twice before.
He could be under
any of these bushes. Bobby!
OK, Ash, one left over.
CAR ALARM STARTS
OK, Ash, good to go, mate.
ALARM STOPS
- There!
- What?
I heard something! This way!
Bobby!
Yes. Uh-huh. Yes.
'Which brings me to
my other point...'
REMOTE CAR LOCK BEEPS
Yes, of course,
I'd be interested in looking...
Yes, exactly.
You know, if you don't find
them in the first half...
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
You know, you might...
excuse me.
Oh.
Yes?
Time to go.
Oh, that's amazing. Oh,
thank you, darling, so much.
Yes, I'm coming back now.
All right.
He found his way home!
He's such a clever baby!
Oh, thank you so much for helping.
- It's fine. It's fine.
- Bye, bye! - Bye!
'..perhaps you can call me
at my office tomorrow,
'and I can draw out
some projections...'
Sorry, Matthew, I got the Senator on
the other line, I've got to take it.
I'll be in touch,
thank you so much.
Home, James, and don't spare
the horses!
You won't believe what I've
been doing in the garden.
I've been chasing...
Oh, no.
Yeah, I've got it.
Yeah, the real one.
The same place as you
left me in half an hour.
But if Mickey's not there,
the deal's off. ..OK.
Half hour.
- Well? - All set. We'll meet back
at the warehouse in half an hour.
We give 'em the real painting,
they give us Mickey.
- But can we trust them? - The honest
truth is, Albert, I don't know.
What if Harry realises it was us?
- I don't know that either.
- But Ash, what happens if...
Let's get Mickey back first, and worry
about everything else later, yeah?
Sounds like a plan.
Yeah, well, first,
I need a drink.
Set 'em up.
There you are!
Mad Dolly told us
where to find you.
Oh?
That was you at the hotel, wasn't it?
Hotel?
I saw you leaving.
Just passing, were you?
That's right, yeah, we erm...
Well, we found out where you were
and we thought we'd try again,
you know, to convince you to...
let us take the painting.
That's what I thought.
So it was you guys that
set off the alarm, was it?
- Yeah, yeah, we...
- What did I tell you?
That's why we're here, we
wanted to say thank you!
Eh?
Look, I don't know why you
hit the alarm when you did,
but if you hadn't, we'd
have just waltzed up there
and found Harry Holmes
in our room.
Yeah, well, you know,
don't mention it.
So what happened?
You found us and then you saw Harry
and his goons there too, right?
That's right, yeah.
So...we legged it.
- Only we didn't want to drop you
in it, so... - So we hit the alarm.
Look. All I know is if it wasn't
for you guys we would be screwed.
So, thank you.
It's a pleasure, I hope
you'd do the same for us.
Oh, absolutely!
Well, there you go. We'd love
to stay and have a beer with you,
but we have a flight to catch.
We've got to get home and make
a start on spending this.
400 grand...for the painting.
The painting?
The Picasso.
We sold Harry one of
the duds Dolly made.
- Yeah, I heard. That's why he was
looking for you. - Oh, no doubt.
But we also had another buyer lined
up for the real one. German guy.
Wait. You said you sold
"one of the duds" to Harry?
So you sold a dud
to the German too?
No, no, he got the real thing.
Bid the highest you see.
No, we had Dolly make two duds.
We sold one to Harry,
and the other we were going to sell
to some Aussie guy in the hotel bar,
but he was a no show.
Yeah, yeah, but you can't
have sold the real one,
because Harry
found it in your room.
He would have been pretty
disappointed when he got home.
- Eh? - Did the deal with
the German guy this afternoon,
long before Harry found us.
If he found a painting in our
room, it was the other dud.
Shit, I think we actually
hung it up on the wall.
We were leaving it as
a wee present for the hotel.
Look, like I said, we just came
here to say thank you.
Oh, by the way, how did, er... How
did things pan out with your friend?
Oh, well, we're, er...
We're still working on it.
Well, good luck with that.
Cheers.
DOOR CLOSES
So we stole another fake?
You told Sava we had half an hour.
We've got 15 minutes.
So what do we do now?
Here you are, mate.
CAR ENGINE STARTS
When you live outside the law,
on the fringes of society,
you're always going to have
days like this.
What you might call
a bad day in the office.
Well, the thing is not to panic.
Because people like this lot,
they're like dogs,
they can smell fear.
So the trick is to make them think
you know something they don't.
That way they'll generally
hold off killing you
while they try and
work out what it is.
You have brought my painting?
- You brought my friend?
- Painting first.
Friend first or there's no deal.
I don't think you're in a
position to negotiate, do you?
If you believe that, it could be
the worst mistake you ever made.
I see my friend...
you see your painting.
Now your turn.
Right. Who's got my painting?
This is none of your
business, Harry.
Well, I'm making it
my business, Boris,
I've been dancing around
you lot for too long.
My name is not Boris.
It is when I'm talking to you.
- You know, calling me
Boris is racist. - Tough.
Er, excuse me, can we, er...
Can we get on with this, please?
What are you doing here?
What do you think
I'm flaming doing here?
I've come to swap this painting...
for my mate.
- That is my painting.
- No. - My painting.
I nicked it, fair and square.
And now I'm getting it back.
That's enough!
- Who you shouting at?
- You!
The pair of you!
Have you never heard of
honour amongst thieves?
Some kind of nodding appreciation
amongst your peers?
You're like a couple
of five-year-olds.
"Please, Miss, he's nicked
my painting." It's pathetic.
- And I've had it with both of you!
- Get the painting.
Ah, ah, ah!
I've had a gun shoved up me
hooter, been hung upside down
and kicked up in the air.
I've been threatened
by at least three nationalities
while running around
half of London chasing
some stupid picture of a cat
in someone's back garden
that looks like it was done by
a three-year-old on a sugar rush.
I've been lied to,
cheated and generally abused
just because me and my mate here
were trying to earn an honest crust
when Rasputin here
went and kidnapped him.
- Hey. Rasputin is worse than Boris.
- I said, shut it!
Now, I don't know
whose painting this is
and, to be quite honest,
I don't give a flying toss!
- I've had a very bad day!
- Do you know who you're talking to?
Never mind who I'm talking to.
You ought to worry about who we
are, son. We're grifters. Yeah.
This bloke over here.
He's sold the Eiffel Tower,
the Palace Of Westminster
and the Sydney Opera House.
We broke banks, companies
and political parties.
We took on the mafia in Las Vegas
and we made the London Special
Branch look like the Keystone Cops.
So never mind about you two
threatening us!
Now, I'm threatening you!
We're going to make you our hobby.
Spend sleepless nights
working out how to
take away everything
from you, every penny.
It won't be just a sodding
painting you have to worry about,
you'll be working out where
you're going to sleep at night.
Because we're going to pick you clean.
We'll strip every bit
of flesh off the bone.
Nice speech.
I got just one question.
Yeah, what's that?
How are you lot going to
do that, when you're dead?
Very good.
Now, give me my painting.
No. No. You give
me my painting.
Some people never listen, do they?
I tell you what...
you can sort it out
amongst yourselves.
Get it round the side!
Yeah, that's it.
Watch what you're doing!
Don't damage it!
You didn't phone, you didn't write.
Sorry, mate,
I've been a bit tied up.
Is that who I think it is?
Harry Holmes, yeah.
Good job he turned up.
Yeah, well...I phoned him.
- You phoned him?
- Yeah.
So what do we do now?
IN SCOTTISH ACCENT:
Hello. Harry?
Would you be interested
to know who the McCrary
boys were working for when
they double-crossed you?
Aye, I do know.
Have you got a pen?
Just watch the painting, will ya?
They don't seem to like
each other very much.
No, well, I er...
I phoned the other one 'an all.
IN RUSSIAN ACCENT: Harry Holmes.
Yes, he cheated a friend of mine.
So when I found out
he stole your painting,
I thought it right to call you.
And I phoned the Old Bill
in case it went pear-shaped.
They'll be here any minute.
I've got it!
- Oh.
- Is that the real Picasso?
Oh, no, no.
No, that's a fake.
- Guys. Can I... Can I ask a question?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I mean, I don't want to sound
ungrateful or anything. - No, it's OK.
Wouldn't it have been simpler
to get the real painting?
SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE
It's OK.
Cheers, Ed.
Thank you.
So no-one's looking for us?
No. No, you see, they both thought
that the original
was damaged in the
fight at the warehouse.
But neither Petre Sava nor Harry
Holmes could afford to lose face.
So the only way they could save
face was to have a fake each.
That way, they could both say
they won and honour is restored.
And they all get to live
happily ever after.
Down. Ah.
Yeah, well, you know,
happy as they can be.
Perfect.
It seems the only winners
are the McCrary boys.
Tell me about it. They just
walked off with 400 grand.
Whoa, they might get to go
with all the money
but we got something
much more precious.
- We got Mickey back.
- Oh, yes, that's true.
- Yeah. Ah. Thanks, guys.
- You can't put a price on friendship.
But if you could, it'd
be about 400 grand.
Ignore him - he was beside
himself when you were gone.
He was taking all the blame,
he was full of self-loathing.
It was heartbreaking to watch.
It was. Yeah, yeah.
We may have not made any money,
but apart from the odd bruise,
- everything turned out OK.
- Yes, it did.
Ash, I've got to ask you,
did you really lose it
with those gangsters
at the warehouse?
We hadn't got a lot of
options at that point,
so I thought I'd do
a bit of Mickey waffle.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- "Mickey waffle"?
- Yeah, you know that thing
where you talk a lot but
don't actually say anything.
Sorry, no, I do not "waffle".
- You do a bit.
- When?
Usually when you know you're
wrong but you won't admit it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but
that's far from waffling,
that's just my way of
presenting a reasoned argument.
A way of putting forward the
facts, which in the main, Ash,
I'm sorry to say, is
something you fail to do.
You prefer to use
emotional rhetoric
littered with expletives
to make your point.
No, it's true, it's true.
That was not "waffling".
I wish you'd left me
in the boot now.
Well, it can be arranged.
ED: I brought you tomorrow's papers.
- Oh, cheers.
That was that Dolly bird again.
I was going to give you a
shout but you were waffling.
- Cheers, Ed. I wasn't waffling.
- Course not.
Erm...this Dolly...she sounds
a bit of all right on the phone.
What's she like?
- Oh, now...now...she is special.
- Yeah? Is she a looker?
Oh...definitely.
- Is she a looker?
- Got a lovely set of teeth,
hasn't she, Sean? - Amazing.
Only we had a little bit of a chat.
We got on like a house on fire.
Think she was flirting a bit
when she, er...
when she rang earlier,
you know, she said she
liked me accent and that so,
er...so you know...
- might have a crack at it like.
- "It"?
Yeah, yeah, you
don't mind, do you?
I don't want to tread
on anyone's toes.
No. Good for you,
you go for "it".
She's invited me round for a drink.
Yeah? Edward.
This is a match made in heaven.
You think so?
- Absolutely.
- You knock yourself out, son.
Cheers, guys. I'll let you
know how I get on.
- Do you think that was a bit cruel?
- Yeah. Probably.
Oh, listen to this.
It says here that a Mondrian was stolen
from a gallery in Central London,
and it's valued at £2.3 million.
Doesn't Tucker still
do fake Mondrians?
- It was a joke.
- Yeah!
- Should've seen your faces.
- Oi!
sync and corrections by Bellows
www.addic7ed.com