You'll never believe
what happened to me
at work today.
Hmm?
This old guy was choking on
his food, and I saved his life.
You're kidding.
Did you Heimlich him?
No. I said, "Oh, my God,
I think that old guy's choking,"
and then one of the busboys
Heimlich'ed him.
You're a hero.
Yeah, that was
the point of the story.
Oh, yeah, speaking of work,
do you know
if you have
Thursday night off?
Um, I think so. Why?
What do you mean, why?
It's Valentine's Day.
Oh, right.
Yeah, we can do something.
You could be
a little more into it.
No, I'm into it, I'm into it.
Just, there's so much pressure
to make the night special,
and it never works out.
Okay, well, this time
it's going to be different.
Because I am
like a romance ninja.
You don't see it coming,
and then bam!
Romance, watch out, hearts,
kisses, love, ooh-ya!
You know,
sometimes I think I've made you
so much cooler
than you used to be,
and then you go and do that.
So, in conclusion,
I believe the painful
sensation felt
after passing a meal
of spicy chilies
is proof that the rectum does
possess the sense of taste.
I concur, but you
changed the subject.
What are we doing
for Valentine's Day?
Oh, you caught that,
did you?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x16 ♪
The Tangible Affection Proof
Original Air Date on February 14, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
(quietly):
Okay.
Okay!
(sighs)
Everything okay?
Bernie's a little cranky
since she's been working,
like, 17 hours a day.
And I've got a lot on my plate,
too, because I've been
busting my tail
playing Assassin's Creed.
Hey, Stuart,
you got anything going on
for Valentine's Day?
Not really.
Other than hiding all
the sharp objects around here
and white-knuckling it
till morning.
What do you got going on?
Oh, well, I was going
to spend the night
with my special little lady,
but, uh,
she got worms, and then I
had to take her to the vet.
There must be something
we can do.
Well, uh, how about you keep
the store open late,
and we throw a party
for all the people
who don't have dates?
That actually sounds
kind of nice.
Yeah, the theme will be
that the greatest love
a man can have
is the love he has with himself.
That's good.
Or maybe something a little less
"hand in the pants."
Oh, Alex, excellent.
I have a research problem
that I believe
you can help with.
Oh, Dr. Cooper, thank you.
I've been waiting
for an opportunity
to contribute
to your scientific work.
Oh, no, no.
That's not going to happen, no.
What I need you to do
is find a Valentine's gift
for my girlfriend.
You realize I passed up
an opportunity
to work at Fermilab
to take this job with you.
Well, I guess those chaps
will have to have
someone else buy
their girlfriends presents.
Now, here is...
Let's see.
This is...
This is about $2,000.
Um, I think
she likes monkeys
and the color gray.
Contribute to my work.
(laughs)
Ah, kids say
the darnedest things.
Hey, you coming
to lunch?
Yeah, one second.
Come here. I want
to show you something.
What you looking at?
Well, I was trying
to come up with something
really romantic
to give Bernadette
for Valentine's Day
since she's been
such a pain in the ass.
You can't find a
card that says that?
Check it out.
I used the
atomic force microscope
in the material science lab
and wrote our initials
in a heart 1/1,000
the size of a grain of sand.
(laughing):
Oh, that's cool.
A micro-valentine
for a microbiologist.
From her micro-husband.
That is amazing.
How long did this take you?
Mmm, about 12 hours.
I pulled an all-nighter.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, I know,
it really took a bite
out of my video game time.
What are you
and Penny doing?
Oh, I'm going to take her to
a nice restaurant for dinner.
Oh, that's not bad,
but as far as romance goes,
I think my gift hits it
right out of...
Want to come to
dinner with us?
Yes, please.
Okay.
Amy will be
here shortly,
expecting the perfect
Valentine's gift, so...
you're up kid.
Dazzle me. Go.
Okay, I think I have
some really great choices.
I went on Amy's
Facebook page
and read up on her interests.
Now, see, I never would have
thought to do that.
Clearly, I made a good choice
farming this out to you.
But I am telling you,
Amy hit the boyfriend jackpot.
Anyway, my socks are on.
Let's knock them off.
Well, um, I know she loves
playing the harp,
so I found this
beautiful music box
that plays one
of her favorite songs.
Now, Amy already
has a real harp.
And it can play any song.
What are you trying
to pull here?
No, I just thought
it would be...
Next.
Okay.
Um, I know she's a fan
of The Canterbury Tales,
Mmm.
so I found...
this cool map
that illustrates the character's
journey through England.
I thought we could put it
in a really nice frame.
But she's got Google Maps
on her phone.
I don't know
how to respond to that.
Well, I hope it's
with a third good option,
because these first two... blah.
Okay.
Well, uh, luckily,
I saved the best for last.
Since Amy's a neuroscientist,
I did some research
and found out
that Santiago Ramón y Cajal,
the father
of modern neuroscience,
did lots of hand drawings
of brain cells.
And I managed
to find
this signed print.
Wow.
Oh, this is truly remarkable.
Thank you.
I think I'll keep it for myself.
What about your girlfriend?
It's too late.
I call dibs.
This place is
really beautiful.
Wah... romance ninja.
(laughing)
Hey.
Sorry we're late.
No problem.
We just sat down.
Mmm, would you like some wine?
Yeah, fill her up.
I'll tell you when to stop.
Is everything okay?
Terrific.
Couldn't be better.
Oh, bite me.
Look, we can still
have a nice night.
Just tell me where it is.
Maybe if you did what you said
you were going to do,
I'd tell you.
Uh, where what is?
She hid my Xbox
like I'm a child.
Yeah, and my mom got me
that for my birthday,
so if you don't give
it back, I'm telling.
I've been working
late every night.
All I asked was that he
clean the apartment
and do one load of laundry.
But did he do it? No.
He just kept on
playing that stupid game.
You like pushing
buttons so much,
try pushing them
on the washing machine.
I said I'm sorry.
Sorry doesn't clean
my underpants, buddy.
I told you, turn
them inside out.
And I told you to bite me.
Trying to have
a magical night here, guys.
Oh, son of a bitch.
What?
Nothing. Nothing.
No, tell me.
It's just this guy
I used to date.
LEONARD:
Oh.
Until he cheated on me
with my friend Gretchen,
who's here with him now.
You're kidding.
And it looks like she lost
a lot of weight, damn it.
I know it's not ideal,
but don't let them
ruin our night.
No, you're totally right.
She could be skinny
'cause she's dying.
That's the spirit.
You know what, screw them.
Our night is going to be
way more special than theirs.
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
What?
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Oh, my God, yes.
Of course
I'll marry you.
(applause)
Two can play this game.
Penny...
Get up.
All right.
It's nice that
all the people
who are lonely
on Valentine's Day
can come here tonight
and be together.
Yeah, I'm really
looking forward to it.
In fact, there's no place
I would rather be than here.
Except on a date with anybody.
Literally anybody.
You know, you and I have
so much fun hanging out.
If you were a girl,
all our problems
would be solved.
What?
Oh, yeah, think about it.
We'd hang out,
we'd read comic books,
we'd see movies.
It'd be like the best
relationship ever.
That does sound nice.
Then I'd take you home,
slip off your little black dress
and just pile-drive you
into oblivion.
What?
PENNY:
Oh, I can't believe
he's going to marry the girl
he cheated on me with.
Isn't it kind of nice?
I mean, he was with
the wrong person,
and now he found
the right person.
What, so I'm the wrong person?
Maybe you want to be
with Gretchen, too.
They do look happy.
Yeah, maybe tonight.
But a year from
now, he'll be
crawling under the sink
looking for his Xbox.
Well, he will.
You know what? Why don't we
just forget about them
and enjoy our Valentine's Day?
Yes, absolutely.
(clears throat)
(Penny scoffs)
Now they're doing that phony
link-arm-drink thingy.
I totally taught him that.
I thought we were
letting it go.
We were; it's just...
it's not fair, okay?
They're bad people.
It's not supposed to end
happy for them;
it's supposed to end
happy for me.
Um...
it did end happy for you.
You're here with me.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Okay, this is getting a little
hard to not take personally.
Oh, come on, don't
make this about you.
Oh, I'm not.
It's about you.
Yeah, well, whatever, okay?
I told you,
Valentine's Day sucks.
This one does,
and you're the reason why.
What?
You know, compared to them,
I'm feeling
pretty good about us.
Me, too.
How about we blow off
dessert, go home early...
I'll do that laundry.
Thank you.
I love you.
Love you, too.
So where'd you hide it?
Where you'd never look.
Damn it, it's in the
washing machine.
Hello.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Okay.
Shall we go to dinner?
Hang on.
As you know, I had planned
a traditional evening
of romance and gifts.
Yes,
and as you know,
I planned to pretend
to enjoy it.
I've been working on
this facial expression all day.
And I appreciate your effort,
but upon contemplation,
I decided I was being selfish.
So, I canceled
our dinner reservations
and came up
with an even better way
to celebrate Valentine's Day.
What is that?
By doing none of it--
no dinner,
no romance, no gifts.
We stay here,
order a pizza
and watch one
of your beloved
Star War Trek things.
Really?
Well, that's what
you'd love, isn't it?
More than anything.
Well, then...
that's what we're going to do.
Well...
I don't know what to say.
This is the most thoughtful gift
that anyone's ever given me.
And that's including
an amazing gift
that I gave myself
earlier today.
I'm your girlfriend.
That's my job.
And I know gift-giving
puts a lot of pressure on you,
so whatever you got me,
you can return.
No.
No, after everything you
didn't do for me tonight,
I want you to have it.
What's this?
Read it.
"Sheldon Cooper,
Caltech University
employee information"?
At the bottom.
"In case of emergency,
please contact...
Amy Farrah Fowler."
And there's my phone number.
This is the most beautiful gift
you could've ever given me.
Well, I thought,
if I have a stroke
or a kidney stone,
who would I want
to share that with?
And you picked me.
It's like you said--
you're my girlfriend.
Oh, Sheldon.
Yeah...
Okay.
Stop ruining Valentine's Day
and order my pizza.
Night.
Yep.
(sighs)
(door shuts)
You know what?
That was pretty
crappy of you.
I mean, all I wanted to do
was give you a great night,
and it's like you-you went out
of your way to destroy it.
Yeah, I know.
I'm a total bitch.
I'm not saying that.
Well, I am.
Fine, you win.
You're a bitch.
Why couldn't we
just have a nice time?
I don't know. (sighs)
Maybe 'cause things are going
so well between us lately
and I've been really happy.
Okay, you're gonna have to make
a lot more sense than that.
Obviously, I have
some commitment issues.
Glaringly obvious.
Go on.
As long as things keep going
great between us,
you'll keep asking me
to marry you,
and eventually I'm gonna
end up saying yes,
and then we're gonna be
married forever,
and the whole thing
just freaks me out.
(sighs)
Okay.
I know I propose a lot.
So how about this?
I promise I will never ask you
to marry me again.
What... what do you mean?
Are you breaking up with me?
No.
No, no, no, no.
But if someday you decide
you want to get married,
you have to propose to me.
Really?
Yes.
It's all on you.
But I got to tell you,
when the time comes,
I want the whole nine yards.
I want you down
on one knee, flowers.
I want to be swept off my feet.
Yeah, you got it.
And I'm cool with surprises.
But nothing on a Jumbotron.
I don't want to cry
on a big screen like that.
Okay.
You know what?
This might be the wine talking,
but I have a very important
question to ask you.
You do?
Leonard Hofstadter...
Yes?
...will you be my valentine?
Sorry. Maybe next year.
I'm just kidding!
Romance ninja.
Let's have sex! Wah!
(music playing)
Thank you, guys,
for doing this.
We're glad you
could make it.
Usually I spend Valentine's Day
sad and alone.
This year, I'm just sad.
What is it about this holiday
that makes people so unhappy?
I know.
I hate myself
most of the time,
but tonight's the night
I know everyone else does, too.
I think you're cool.
Great.
I got to tell you,
we've got to stop beating
ourselves up like this.
Excuse me, everybody.
Can I have your attention,
please?
(music stops playing)
We're all here tonight
because...
we have no one to be with.
But... that doesn't
make us mutants.
The only mutants here
are in these comic books.
We've got to stop defining
our self-worth
by whether or not
we're in a relationship.
You know what I see
when I look around?
I see a room
full of great people.
So let's give ourselves a break.
We are a community,
and as long
as we have
each other,
we're never truly alone.
(sighs)
That was cool.
What you said.
You really think so?
Yeah, I do.
Thank you.
Uh...
Would you like to, uh...
get a cup...
a cup of coffee or...?
Okay.
Later, losers!
(phone rings)
Hello?
Another medical emergency?
What's wrong with him now?
I seriously doubt he was bitten
by a Chinese bird spider.
How exactly does a bump
feel Asian?
Just put him on the phone.
Sheldon, I am not driving
over there again.
Because I drove
over there yesterday
for a brain tumor
that turned out to be
an ice cream headache.
Yes, I still want to be
your emergency contact.
Yes, you can eat
your ice cream too fast
and also have a brain tumor.
I'm on my way.
Brain tumor
would explain a lot.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==