[Wheels clacking]
[Steam hisses]
[Brakes squeal]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Sighs]
[Door opens]
Stacey: Mike.
[Door closes]
- Hey.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, yeah, of course.
[Chuckles]
I'm just parked across the street, so...
Okay. I... I was just gonna hit the...
Yeah, sure. I'll meet you out front.
Okay.
[Footsteps depart]
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Horn honks in distance]
Janitor. Anybody here?
[Bag thuds]
[Coin drops]
[Sighing]
[Groans]
[Box thuds]
[Inhales sharply]
[Sighs]
[Groans]
[Exhales sharply]
[Breathes deeply]
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
[Giggling]
Higher!
Mike: Higher? Okay, you asked for it.
- [Chuckles]
- [Dog barking]
Oh, sweetheart. All right. Come on down.
- Pop-pop's getting tired.
- Aw.
Don't "aw" me.
You take a little break... little break.
Go on.
[Giggling]
- A good kid.
- Yeah, she is.
So, how do you like it... Out west?
I like it. Wide-open spaces.
[Chuckles] Yeah.
Mm. Different, anyway.
Yeah. [Sniffs]
How you doing?
I'm... yeah, I'm okay, you know?
Adjusting.
And Kaylee?
Yeah, she's settling in.
She still asks about him...
"Where is daddy?"
She just misses him.
Yeah.
How long you in town for, Mike?
I'm here...
For the duration, indefinitely.
I'm, uh... I'm better.
And I'm sorry it took me so long.
But I'm not like I was.
I'm back. I'm solid.
I want to be here for you,
for Kaylee, for my family.
That's good.
I'm glad to hear you're better.
[Sighs]
What?
What is it, honey?
Mike, I got to ask...
I mean... I know I just
need to move on from this,
but I keep thinking about something.
About what?
How, before Matty died,
like, for a few weeks there,
he was... Different.
Different how?
Different... I don't know.
Moody, you know?
He barely ate. H... He wasn't sleeping.
He snapped at me
about the stupidest things.
I started to think something's up at work
or... or someone's sick,
something like that,
but he wouldn't talk to me.
He clammed right up.
Cops aren't real touchy-feely.
You know that.
No.
[Scoffs] They're not. No.
But this wasn't the normal
"tough guys don't cry" crap.
This was more.
I mean... Did you notice?
I mean, did you feel
anything like that from him?
I don't... as far as I remember,
he seemed okay.
He seemed okay to me.
Well, I started to think... I'm...
I don't know. I didn't know what to think.
But then... Three days
or... or four... I don't remember...
But before he died,
there was this phone call.
2:30 in the morning, I wake up,
and Matty's not in bed.
And I hear him. He's talking downstairs.
So... I go to listen on the stairs,
where he couldn't see.
He gets intense.
Like, he'd be screaming
if he wasn't whispering, you know?
Matty didn't get worked up.
He'd let things go.
But... but this... I mean, he was angry.
He was really angry.
What was he saying?
I couldn't make it out.
It was something about...
I don't know. I couldn't hear it.
[Sighs]
But the next morning, I called him out...
"What the hell was that about?
What's going on?"
And he wouldn't talk to me.
But I think...
I think he was talking to you.
Me?
I mean, who else?
Huh?
For one hot second,
I thought maybe he was catting around...
No, he wouldn't do that.
No, I know. I know that. But you...
He knew he could call you
anytime he had a problem.
You were thick as thieves, the two of you.
And there was something in his voice.
It was... How he was talking.
It makes me think it was you.
Stace, I don't think it was.
I can't recall any late-night
heart-to-hearts with him,
not around then.
Maybe it was a C.I. or a case.
Listen.
I know what you're doing...
replaying it over and over,
thinking, "if I'd noticed this
or changed that",
maybe I could have done something."
You don't think I haven't had
those thoughts? I do.
[Scoffs]
Every day.
You got to quit beating
yourself up like this.
Matty's gone. [Sighs]
That's really all there is to it.
Yeah.
I guess that's that.
It's getting on.
I got to... Get Kaylee her dinner
and put her to bed.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Well, if you want me to drop by
and keep an eye on her, I...
I want to help.
[Breathes deeply]
See you around.
[Door closes]
[Sighs]
Francisco: Where to?
"Francisco."
Yeah.
You know this town?
Yeah, sure.
How well?
- [Dogs barking, whining]
- Caldera: You sew this up yourself?
Not bad.
Bet there's a story there.
- Isn't there always?
- Yeah.
All right. Little sting here.
Okay. That ought to do it.
Now...
[Scissors thud]
You're gonna want to take it easy.
Keep it clean.
Keep it dry. Let it heal.
There's a Walgreens a couple
blocks over on Louisiana.
Maybe go get yourself a sling.
You don't have one?
[Scoffs] [Chuckling] Sorry.
Got a cone you can put around your neck.
Yeah.
It's about the same, right?
So, it's gonna be $500?
$500.
I can, uh, throw some pills in
for the pain.
[Pills rattling]
This stuff's essentially Vicodin.
I can give it to you for $25 a pill...
maybe drop the price to $15
for something a little less human-centric.
I'm an aspirin man. [Sighs]
Tell you what...
take a couple on the house.
In case you change your mind.
You new in town?
Yeah.
Passing through or sticking around?
Why?
No reason.
It's just, if you're relocating
to the land of enchantment,
I know people.
I could get you some work.
I am not looking for that kind of work,
but... ohh... thanks.
Don't know why it has to be this way.
Could have been friendly.
Could have talked in your house.
You really want the formal treatment?
Lawyer.
Come on, Mike.
It's just a couple of questions.
Uh, ain't nothing but a thing.
Lawyer.
You're not under arrest.
Okay, did anybody here say "arrest"? No.
You want to walk, walk.
I got to say, I, uh, expected
more cooperation
from you on this, cop to cop.
Lawyer.
[Sighs]
Fine. What lawyer?
Ehrmantraut... Who's got him and where?
That way.
Hey, fellas. How you doing?
James McGill... here to see my client.
What?
- You look like Matlock.
- Uh, no,
I look like a young Paul Newman
dressed as Matlock.
Where's my guy?
[Beep]
[Sighs] Say hello to Barney fife.
Wrong show, but thanks for playing.
[Sighs]
So, what happened...
the mayor didn't give you enough stickers?
You want to tell me what we're doing here?
Oh, here's your coffee.
Uh, hope it's good to the last drop,
'cause I'm billing you
the full hour for it.
That's for you.
Oh. That's very thoughtful.
[Sighs]
You serious?
Why did you have me bring it to you?
Mike: All right, here's
what's gonna happen.
Those two cops out there
are from Philadelphia.
They've come a long way to see me.
When they come in here,
we're all gonna have a little chat.
And when it's over,
the young one, who's been
writing in his little notebook,
he's gonna take it
and put it in his jacket.
And when he does that,
I want you to take that coffee
and spill it on him...
little accident, that's all.
- And why, pray tell, would I do that?
- Because I'm asking you to.
- It's the only reason you're here.
- [Sighs]
So I'm here because you want me
to assault a police officer.
I am asking you to take
a few ounces of lukewarm coffee
and spill it on him.
I doubt that satisfies
the definition of "assault,"
but, hey, you're the lawyer.
Right. How silly of me.
All you want is for me to aid and abet
you ripping off that guy's notepad,
'cause that's what
you're doing here, right?
Huh? What... are you nuts?
You can't be serious.
Hey, I hate to remind you
of this, but you owe me one.
The assist I gave you with
the missing-persons problem...
one good turn and so forth?
You want a good turn?
Here's your good turn, okay?
I'm gonna behave
like an honest-to-God,
law-abiding, licensed attorney,
'cause, clearly, you need one
with whatever the hell is going on here.
Now, those two jokers out in the hallway...
I'm gonna make sure they dot
their I's and cross their t's...
everything square and above board.
That's what I'm gonna do,
and you're gonna be
happy as hell that I'm here.
But this little Juan Valdez
bump-and-dump... no.
Not gonna happen.
[Knock on door]
Hey, gentlemen,
we're prepared to indulge you.
[Clears throat]
Abbasi: Detective Escalara
will be sitting in with us,
as per APD policy. Okay with you, right?
Fine with me.
Okay.
You got your lawyer, Mike.
Can we talk already?
Great. So, like we said,
we're here looking into
this Hoffman and Fensky thing.
Yeah, and whatever you can
tell us... anything at all.
Uh, hold on. Hold on.
"Hoffman." "Fensky."
[Smacks lips] Fill me in.
Assume I know absolutely nothing
about my client here, all right?
- Start at the beginning.
- Jesus. Seriously?
Look, don't let
Mr. Ehrmantraut's dancing eyes
and bubbly,
bon vivant personality fool you.
He's actually... believe it
or not... somewhat taciturn.
Shall I fan you gently,
so you don't go into shock?
Start at the beginning, okay?
We're talking book of genesis.
[Pen scribbling] Okay, Mr. McGill,
as you probably gathered,
we, Detective Sanders and I...
work for the Philadelphia
Police Department,
as did Mr. Ehrmantraut for nearly 30 years.
Philadelphia? Go, Eagles.
Mr. Ehrmantraut had a son, Matt.
He, too, was with Philly P.D.
He was a rookie officer with
about two years on the job.
- He was a good cop.
- Yes, he was.
About nine months ago, he responded
to a shots-fired call
in some West Side rattrap.
Matt went in with his partner,
officer Troy Hoffman.
They had sergeant Jack Fensky
backing them up.
Unfortunately, things got out of hand.
The three of them were ambushed,
and, uh, Matt didn't make it out.
Hoffman and Fensky returned fire,
but the shooter got away.
We chased a few leads,
shook up the usual suspects...
came up short.
I'm very sorry to hear it.
Anyways, we kept beating the bushes,
kept coming up dry until three months ago.
That's when Hoffman and Fensky
both turned up dead
in a vacant lot out in nicetown...
Again, an ambush of
some kind, it looks like.
And with whoever killed Matt
out there in the wind,
we're thinking...
Well, it's our operating theory
that Hoffman and Fensky
were mixed up in something,
some bad business,
and maybe that got Matt killed.
Yeah, sorry. I got to do
my lawyer thing here.
Uh, what does my client
have to do with any of this?
Uh, Mike, this is a hail Mary.
Uh, beyond that.
I mean, if we had
any hard evidence or leads,
we wouldn't be out here.
Now, there's anything you can tell us
about what Hoffman and Fensky were into?
Yeah, help us out, Mike.
Help us catch the bastard who killed Matty.
I don't know much about Hoffman and Fensky.
They were Matt's people.
I'd see them around sometimes.
I saw them in a bar the night they died.
It was Mcclure's...
maybe the Red Dog... Probably Mcclure's.
Were they drinking with anyone?
It's a cop bar.
They were drinking with everyone.
Yeah, but did you see them
with anyone in particular?
I couldn't tell you. I was...
You know how I was.
How you doing these days?
Feeling like I crawled out
from the bottom of a bottle
and working hard to stay there.
Although I've got to say...
doesn't help much,
dredging up the past like this.
Let me ask you,
uh, when did you come
out here to Albuquerque?
It couldn't have been, uh, too much later.
I think it was the very next day.
Yeah? The day after Hoffman
and Fensky died, huh?
You didn't think
to, uh, stick around
once you heard the news?
I don't think I heard the news
till I was west of Kansas City.
Still, you, uh...
you didn't come back
for the funerals, correct,
even though Hoffman was Matt's partner?
Sanders: Uh, do you remember anything
about that night at the bar?
Uh, did you talk to
Hoffman or Fensky at all?
Sorry. I got nothing.
They weren't my people.
I'm sorry you guys took a flier on me.
I wish it'd have paid off.
That it? We done here?
We're done here, yeah.
Hey, that wasn't so hard, huh?
Thanks, Mike. Yeah.
Listen, we're probably
gonna kick around
for another couple of days,
in case you think of something, all right?
You know, I've never been out west before.
[Beep]
Oh, hey.
Oh! Oh, shit!
Jesus. Sorry. Sorry. Come on!
Here. I can get most of it.
You got any paper towels?
You know what? Hey, hey. I-I got it.
- I got it. Thank you.
- Sorry.
[Sighs]
[Scoffs]
[Engine turns over]
Oh, for the love of...
You got to do that right here,
right in front of me?
What's so important in there
that we had to pull
that third-rate Marx brothers routine?
You really want to know?
And risk getting a piece
of an obstruction rap?
No, thank you.
Anything else you want to ask?
How did you know?
Know what?
That... that I would do that, that...
[clears throat]
How did you know that I would,
uh, spill that coffee?
[Chuckles]
What the hell's that?
What's [chuckles] supposed to mean, huh?
Okay, great.
You're the strong, silent type.
Hooray for you.
But in case you missed it,
your friends from Philly back there...
they think you killed two cops.
Yep. [Sighs]
[sighs]
[Dialing]
Yeah, it's me.
We need to talk.
[Insects chirping, dog barking in distance]
[Knock on door]
You call the cops?
What?
Philadelphia P.D. Did you call them?
- Y-yeah, I did.
- Why?
Well, I told them I heard
about Hoffman and Fensky and...
and what?
And you don't think it's strange?
First Matt, then not six months
later, his partner and his sergeant?
Yeah, I called them
to help catch Matty's killer.
Mike, what if the same person,
if the... what if
the piece of shit who got Matty
- got them, too?
- And what exactly did you tell them?
- I told them...
- You tell them Matt was dirty...
- Is that what you told them?
- I...
How could you possibly think that?
That's your husband,
the father of your child.
I didn't say that. I s...
I told them I found money.
After Kaylee and I moved here,
when I was unpacking,
it was in the lining of an old suitcase.
Matt must have tucked it away in
there, 'cause this was cash...
$5,000, $6,000 from God knows where.
I mean, we were basically
paycheck to paycheck.
Where the hell did he get it?
Why didn't you ask me?
- [Sighs]
- Why didn't you come to me?
I couldn't.
- I knew what it would do to you.
- [Sighs]
First, he's murdered,
and then for you to think...
I... it would have burned you to the ground.
There would be nothing left.
And you wouldn't talk to me.
Every night, you were
drinking yourself unconscious,
like you were the only one who lost him.
Look, I don't care.
He was dirty, he was clean... I don't care.
All I want is for whoever killed Matty
to rot in a cell
for the rest of their life,
and then I want whatever's left of them
just dumped in the trash...
that's what I want.
I don't care where it leads,
what it uncovers.
I mean, what difference would it make
if he was... Anything?
I'd still love him.
I'd still miss him. He'd still be gone.
Matt wasn't dirty.
Well, so be straight with me!
Right now. This is it, Mike.
What was that phone call before he died?
Don't bullshit me.
[Voice breaking] That was
between me and my son.
So you're admitting it was you.
He wasn't dirty!
God damn you!
You get that through your head!
My son wasn't dirty!
[Door slams]
[Insects chirping]
[Rock music plays in distance]
[Horn honks in distance]
[Siren wails in distance]
♪ Oh, it came out of the sky ♪
♪ landed just a little South of Moline ♪
♪ Jody fell out of his tractor ♪
♪ couldn't believe what he'd seen ♪
♪ laid on the ground, a-shook,
fearing for his life ♪
♪ then he ran all the way to town ♪
♪ screaming, "it came out of the sky!" ♪
♪ well, a crowd gathered 'round ♪
♪ and a scientist said it was marsh gas ♪
♪ spiro came and made a speech
about raising the Mars tax ♪
♪ the Vatican said,
"woe, the lord has come" ♪
♪ Hollywood rushed out an epic film ♪
♪ Ronnie the popular
said it was a communist plot ♪
♪ whoa ♪
♪ oh, the newspapers came
and made Jody a national hero ♪
[Distorted indistinct conversations]
♪ And my mind goes back to a girl I left ♪
♪ long years ago who told me ♪
♪ just hold on loosely ♪
♪ but don't let go ♪
♪ if you cling too tightly ♪
♪ you're gonna lose control ♪
♪ your baby needs someone to believe in ♪
♪ and a whole lot of space to breathe in ♪
♪ it's so damn easy ♪
♪ when your feelings are such ♪
♪ to overprotect her ♪
♪ to love her too much ♪
♪ and my mind goes back to a girl I left ♪
♪ long years ago who told me ♪
- ♪ just hold on loosely ♪
- [Sighs]
♪ But don't let go ♪
♪ if you cling too tightly ♪
Just let him cry it all out, okay?
- ♪ You're gonna lose control ♪
- [Chuckles]
Hey, Mikey.
Young Hoffman. Mikey boy.
- What's going on, my brothers?
- How you doing?
Brothers, huh?
Good to see you, too. It's been a minute.
Yeah. [Breathes deeply]
[Chuckles]
I know. I know it was you.
♪ Sentimental fool ♪
[Laughs]
♪ Don't let your heart get in the way ♪
♪ you see it all around you ♪
♪ good loving gone bad ♪
♪ and usually it's too late when you ♪
♪ realize what you had ♪
Closing time, Mikey.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
Hey, how about I give you a lift home?
Mnh.
I'm fine.
No, I can't let you drive. Get you a cab?
No, I'm good. I'm good.
Don't worry.
Anyway, I sold my car, so I'm walking.
Thank you.
Albuquerque, New Mexico.
- You ever been?
- Nope.
Well... That's where I'm headed.
- Tarantulas, they got.
- [Chuckles]
That's a big minus in my book.
[Chuckles] Well, I will be on the lookout.
You take care, my friend.
Take care.
[Vehicle approaches]
Hoffman: Hey, Mike.
Mikey.
You want a ride?
I'm walking.
Pull over here.
Hoffman: What are you doing out here?
Come on. Let us drive you.
It's colder than my ex-wife's tit out here.
Come on. Come on.
I'm walking.
Come on. Don't... don't be an ass.
- Come on. Let us take you home.
- Get in the car already.
It's cold out here.
Come on, Mike. Come on.
- [Grunts]
- Come on.
Okay. Easy.
[Groaning]
We're gonna have you home in no time.
Oh, God.
Hey. What are you doing?
Hey. Give me that. That's mine.
Later.
We don't want you to shoot
your foot off, now, do we?
[Mumbling]
- Fensky: Hey, Mikey.
- What?
Mikey, you with us?
Why?
You really tied one on good
back there, buddy.
Shit, yeah, he did...
put it away like they were
fixing to bring back prohibition.
[Grunts]
Hey, hey, back at Mcclure's,
you were talking out your ass, hmm?
"I know it was you." [Chuckles]
What's that supposed to mean, huh?
You think you know what?
You got something
you want to get off your chest,
something you want to say to us?
You killed him.
You killed Matty.
And you killed him for nothing.
You killed him because you were scared
of what you thought he might do.
You got him in that crack house...
And you staged it...
made it look like a junkie with a gun.
But it was you.
And I know it was you.
And I'm gonna prove it.
[Sighs]
Help me get him out of the car.
[Engine shuts off]
What?
Come on. There you go. Watch your head.
[Sighs]
All right, come on, Mike, huh?
One, two, one, two, buddy.
Now, you wait there one second.
We're gonna work this
whole thing out, okay, Mikey?
What do we do now?
Hey. Grief... it's a bitch.
He couldn't live with it...
Matt dying the way he did.
It's too much for the old man.
So Mikey here decided to eat his gun.
It's tragic, but anyone
could see this coming, hmm?
He's drinking himself to death.
We're doing him a favor.
Smart. That's what I would
have done if I were you.
[Gun clicks]
[Breathing heavily]
[Groaning]
Mike, I...
You let some things slide
and you look the other way.
You bust a drug dealer
that has more cash than
you'll ever earn in a lifetime.
Some of it doesn't make it
back into evidence... So what?
You took a taste. So did everyone else.
That's how you knew you were safe.
It's like killing Caesar...
Everyone's guilty.
Matt wasn't dirty.
I was.
Everyone was in that precinct.
That's how it worked.
You turn in your buddy,
you're screwing yourself.
You go along to get along.
And you went along.
[Chuckles, clicks tongue]
I did.
Yeah.
Okay. But you said Matt didn't.
No.
Not Matt.
Fensky got to Hoffman early...
kickbacks from some gang or another...
protection, basically.
And Hoffman went to Matty
and offered to cut him in.
Only fair, right? They were partners.
And Matt did what you would think...
He agonized.
And then he came to me,
wanted to go to the I.A.,
do the right thing, shut 'em down.
Oh, my God. And you let him?
That's why he got killed...
'cause he was gonna turn on those guys?
No. No.
I told him...
[Sighs]
You know what a cop fears most?
More than getting shot, more than anything?
Prison...
getting locked up
with everybody you put away.
You threaten a cop with that,
you make him dangerous,
and that's what I told him.
I talked sense.
No one was getting hurt.
But if you go to the I.A.,
if you even look like you're going...
He had a wife, a kid, responsibilities.
Take the money. Do something good with it.
[Chuckles]
Well... I tried.
I tried.
But he wouldn't listen.
[Chuckles]
My boy was stubborn.
My boy was strong.
And he was gonna get himself killed.
[Voice breaking] So I told him...
[Normal voice] I told him I did it, too,
that I was like Hoffman, getting by,
and that's what you heard that night...
me talking him down,
him kicking and screaming
until the fight went out of him.
He put me up on a pedestal...
And I had to show him,
that I was down in the gutter
with the rest of them.
Broke my boy.
[Voice breaking] I broke my boy.
He went to Hoffman, he took the money,
but he hesitated.
Even looking like you're doing
the right thing to those two
meant that he wasn't solid,
that he couldn't be trusted.
I got Matty to take the money.
And they killed him two days later.
[Breathes deeply]
He was the strongest person
that I ever knew.
He'd have never done it,
not even to save himself.
I was the only one...
I was the only one that could get him
to debase himself like that.
[Scoffs]
And it was for nothing.
I made him lesser.
I made him like me.
And the bastards killed him anyway.
Hoffman and Fensky...
if they killed Matty...
Who killed them?
Pop... What happened?
You know what happened.
The question is...
can you live with it?