Previously on " Desperate Housewives"
THE NEW NEIGHBOR...
OH, MY GOD. KATHERINE.
TURNED OUT TO BE
AN OLD FRIEND OF SUSAN'S...
AND THAT PINE TREE
IN THE BACK YARD...
IT'S MY PRIDE AND JOY.
WHO HAD A PROBLEM
MAKING NEW FRIENDS.
OH, IT ABSOLUTELY KILLS ME TO
HAVE TO ASK YOU TO CUT IT DOWN.
HER DAUGHTER
COULDN'T RECALL THE PAST.
I'M JULIE'S MOM.
WHO'S JULIE AGAIN?
YOUR BEST FRIEND
WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE.
BUT HER HUSBAND HAD NEWS
FOR SUSAN.
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
LYNETTE REVEALED
HER CONDITION.
I HAVE CANR.
GABY AND CARLOS
BEGAN A SECRET AFFAIR.
CAN YOU GET AWAY TONIGHT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
AND EDIE UNCOVERED A SECRET
OF ANOTHER SORT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU EVER TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR OFFSHORE
BANK ACCOUNT--
THE ONE WITH $10 MILLION
IN IT?
(Mary Alice) THE GREAT
CRIME WAVE HIT WISTERIA LANE
ON A TUESDAY AFTERNOON.
THAT'S WHEN RESIDENTS FOUND
THEIR BARBECUES UPENDED...
THEIR CLEAN LAUNDRY TRAMPLED...
AND THEIR SKATEBOARDS MISSING.
NATURALLY,
EVERYONE BEGAN TO ASK
WHO COULD BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR SUCH CARNAGE.
THE ANSWER
LAY IN THE HOME OF A NEIGHBOR
WHO, 20 MINUTES EARLIER,
HAD BEEN ENGAGING IN...
AN ALTOGETHER
DIFFERENT TYPE OF CRIME.
OH, I GOTTA GET BACK.
I TOLD EDIE I WAS JUST
GOING FOR A JOG.
DO I LOOK SWEATY ENOUGH
FOR A 5-MILE RUN?
YEAH. UNFORTUNATELY,
IT'S MY SWEAT.
MMM. MMM.
WHEN ARE YOU GONNA DUMP HER?
(sighs) IT'S COMPLICATED,
OKAY?
BESIDES, I DON'T SEE YOU
IN ANY BIG HURRY
TO DUMP VICTOR.
GENERALLY SPEAKING,
WOMEN DON'T LEAVE THEIR HUSBANDS
FOR GUYS WHO HAVE GIRLFRIENDS.
JUST BOOT THE BITCH.
WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF?
HEY, I AM NOT AFRAID OF--
(car door shuts in distance)
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT THE HELL'S
THE MATTER WITH YOU?
(lowered voice) EDIE!
(Edie) GABY, YOU IN THERE?
(whispers) OKAY.
(normal voice) ONE SECOND!
EDIE! WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE?
I'M LOOKING FOR CARLOS.
HE WENT FOR A RUN,
BUT IT WAS HOURS AGO.
SORRY. HAVEN'T SEEN HIM.
REALLY? BECAUSE IDA GREENBERG
SAID THAT SHE THOUGHT
SHE SAW HIM ON YOUR PORCH.
UH, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE, BECAUSE
HE'S THERE! THERE HE IS!
WHAT?
CARLOS!
HE'S AT YOUR HOUSE.
OH,
HE JUST LET HIMSELF IN.
OH.
THERE YOU GO. HE'S HOME.
OKAY. WELL, THANKS.
YOU TOLD HER
I WAS AT HOME.
SO?
SO I'M NOT AT HOME.
I'M HERE.
WHAT THE HELL
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
EDIE! EDIE, WAIT!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
DON'T GO!
WHY?
UH, YOU, UH,
HAVE A BIRTHDAY COMING UP,
AND, UH, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO GET YA.
OR MAYBE A COFFEEPOT
OR SCENTED HANGERS
OR... A NICE CLOCK RADIO.
GABY, I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SURPRISE ME?
UH, WAIT, BUT DON'T GO!
(tires screech)
I-I NEED A LITTLE MORE GUIDANCE!
DAMN IT, BOYS! YOU SHOULD NOT BE
SCREWING AROUND IN THE STREETS!
SOMEBODY'S GONNA GET HURT!
(both yelling)
CARLOS!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
SOMEONE BROKE INTO OUR HOUSE.
OH, MY GOD.
AND SO ENDED THE GREAT
CRIME WAVE ON WISTERIA LANE.
NO ONE EVER FOUND OUT
WHO WAS RESPONSIBLE...
EW. HONEY, YOU'RE ALL SWEATY.
GO CLEAN UP.
BECAUSE IT WAS AN INSIDE JOB.
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
绝望主妇 第四季第2集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：
校对：
时间轴：松鼠 白二 小L Uranus
YOU WILL NEVER SEE
DESPAIR HERE...
(dog barks)
OR RAGE.
YOU WILL NEVER SEE
THE TINIEST BIT OF REGRE
YOU SEE, THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVE HERE HAVE LEARNED
THERE IS ONE SURE WAY
OF HIDING THEIR SECRETS...
HEY.
FROM THEIR NEIGHBORS.
THAT'S WHY, IN THE SUBURBS,
THERE IS NOTHING MORE DECEPTIVE
THAN A SMILE.
SO WHAT DID JULIE SAY,
EXACTLY?
SHE SAID DYLAN'S
NOT THE SAME GIRL.
NOT THE SAME GIRL
LIKE SHE'S CHANGED,
OR NOT THE SAME GIRL BECAUSE
SHE'S BEEN REPLACED BY A ROBOT?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS WEIRD,
BUT JULIE SAYS DYLAN
DOES NOT REMEMBER ANYTHING
ABOUT LIVING HERE.
WELL,
MAYBE SHE BLOCKED IT OUT.
DID SOMETHING BAHAPPEN
TO HER WHEN SHE WAS YOUNG?
I'M NOT SURE.
BUT THERE WAS SOMETHING ODD
ABOUT THE WAY THEY LEFT.
SO...
IF IT ISN'T THE EARLY MORNING
GOSSIP BRIGADE.
WHO ARE WE DISHING TODAY?
UH, SUSAN.
SHE'S STANDING RIGHT THERE.
OH, MY GOD. HAVE YOU BEEN THERE
THIS WHOLE TIME?
ANYWAY, I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU GIRLS ABOUT LYNETTE.
WHAT ABOUT HER?
WELL, SINCE SHE'S BEEN
SO TIRED FROM CHEMO,
I THOUGHT IT'D BE NICE
IF WE DID SOMETHING FOR HER,
LIKE BRING HER LUNCH?
UH, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
YEAH, LET'S DO IT.
UM, GABY, WHY DON'T YOU BRING
YOUR VEGETABLE LASAGNA?
SUSAN, YOU DO BEVERAGES,
AND, UH, KATHERINE, WHY DON'T
YOU BRING A SIMPLE GREEN SALAD?
I'D RATHER BRING DESSERT.
OH, NO NEED, DEAR.
I ALWAYS BRING DESSERT.
OH, I'M THINKING
MY LEMON MERINGUE PIE.
OH, YUM.
YEAH, HERE'S THE THING.
THE MOVERS LOST MY SALAD BOWL.
MY PIE PLATES,
ON THE OTHER HAND--
WILL NOT BE NEEDED.
AS I SAID,
I ALWAYS BRING DESSERT.
I KNOW.
I WILL LEND YOU
MY SALAD BOWL.
YOU REALLY DON'T WANNA MISS
BREE'S PIE. IT'S PERFECT.
WHO AM I TO ARGUE
WITH PERFECTION?
SORRY. IT'S JUST, SOMETHING
HAS BEEN DRIVING ME CRAZY.
NOW YOU'RE PERFECT.
D-DOES IT HURT?
IT'S A LITTLE UNCOMFORTABLE,
BUT I'M FINE.
TAKE A CARD.
HEY, I TOLD YOU
I'M COLLECTING QUEENS.
PAY ATTENTION.
YOU REMEMBER WE PLAYED THIS
WHEN YOU WERE IN LABOR
WITH PARKER?
42 HOURS WITHOUT MEDS.
I'LL NEVER FORGET
WHAT A TROUPER YOU WERE.
WELL, LET'S NOT COMPOSE
MY EULOGY JUST YET.
I'M STILL TROUPIN'.
TAKE A CARD.
RIGHT.
IT'S FUNNY.
WE PLAYED CARDS ON OUR HONEYMOON
THE DAY THAT IT RAINED.
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT?
WE--WE LIT A FIRE--
YOU'RE DOING IT AGAIN.
SORRY.
HEY, I TOLD YOU
I'M COLLECTING QUEENS.
SHOOT. THAT'S RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU LETTING ME WIN?
I JUST WANNA MAKE YOU
FEEL GOOD.
BY TAKING ALL THE FUN
T OF THE KILL?
HONEY, I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST...
(voice breaking)
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
OUT.
WHAT?
YOU ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE DISTRACTING ME,
NOT DEPRESSING
THE HELL OUT OF ME.
YOU'RE KICKING ME OUT
OF CHEMO?
I'LL SEE YOU AT HOME.
HONEY, I'M YOUR RIDE.
JUST GO. I'LL CAB IT.
THERE'S THAT TROUPER
THAT I ADMIRE SO MUCH.
OUT!
CARLOS! HI!
HEY,
THERE'S MY BIRTHDAY GIRL.
OH. MMM!
(chuckles)
IT'S A NICE CAR.
WE GOT COMPANY?
NO.
THEN WHOSE IS IT?
(chuckles)
IT'S... YOUR BIRTHDAY PRESENT
TO ME. SURPRISE!
A CAR. I WAS GONNA GET YOU
EARRINGS.
SO? GET 'EM.
AND I WILL DRIVE AROUND
WITH THE TOP DOWN
SO EVERYONE CAN SEE THEM.
EDIE, I CAN'T AFFORD THIS.
OF COURSE YOU CAN.
JUST MOVE SOME OF
YOUR OFFSHORE MONEY ONSHORE.
I TOLD YOU,
THAT ACCOUNT WAS A SECRET,
WHICH IT'S NOT GONNA BE
FOR LONG
IF I START BUYING
$80,000 CARS.
NOW I'M SENSING THAT
THIS LITTLE NEST EGG OF YOURS
IS A TEENSY BIT ILLEGAL.
WHERE'D IT COME FROM?
YOU DON'T NEED TO KNOW THAT,
D THE I.R.S. DOESN'T, EITHER.
YOU WANT ME TO GO TO JAIL?
GOODNESS, CARLOS.
I-I HAD NO IDEA
THAT YOUR SITUATION WAS SO...
PRECARIOUS.
WELL... I GUESS
I'LL JUST HAVE TO TAKE THIS
BACK TO THE DEALERSHIP.
THANK YOU FOR UNDERSTANDING,
BABE.
LOOK, IF... (sighs) IF YOU
DON'T WANT THE EARRINGS,
JUST PICK SOMETHING ELSE OUT
INSTEAD.
JUST NOT TOO EXTRAVAGANT.
DON'T WORRY.
I HAVE A THOUGHT,
AND IT'S RIGHT
IN YOUR PRICE RANGE.
OH! HI. HI.
HEY, KATHERINE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY IS THERE A MOVING VAN
IN YOUR DRIVEWAY?
OH, I MEANT TO CALL YOU.
I, UH...
IT'S JUST BEEN SO NUTS.
I GOT A NEW JOB... IN CHICAGO.
WHAT? YOU'RE JUST LEAVING,
LIKE THAT?
I KNOW! IT'S CRAZY, HUH?
I REALLY WISH I HAD TIME
TO TALK,
BUT I GOTTA FINISH PACKING.
OH, WHOA. NO, HANG ON.
LET ME JUST RUN AND GET JULIE SO
SHE CAN SAY GOOD-BYE TO DYLAN.
OH, WE'RE REALLY IN A RUSH.
I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TIME--
(glass shatters)
TH-THAT'S OKAY, GUYS!
KEEP PACKING! I'LL CLEAN IT UP!
KATHERINE?
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU SEEM A LITTLE JUMPY.
I JUST HAD A-A LONG NIGHT,
AND I-I HAVE A LOT TO DO.
I'M REALLY GONNA MISS YOU.
KATHERINE, HI.
OH, UH, I BROUGHT YOU
THAT SALAD BOWL.
OH, THANK YOU.
YOU'RE SO THOUGHTFUL.
NO PROBLEM. HEY, YOU KNOW,
I WAS MEANING TO ASK YOU,
HOW DID THAT JOB
IN CHICAGO WORK OUT?
JOB?
YOU KNOW, THE ONE THAT
YOU LEFT SO SUDDENLY FOR.
OH, RIGHT. YES, OF COURSE.
UH, GOOD.
UH, IT WORKED OUT WELL--
VERY CHALLENGING.
OH.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING IN THE STOVE.
I'VE GOTTA GO.
OH.
SUSAN.
WHAT?
I'M EATING FOR TWO.
WELL, DO BOTH OF YOU
WANNA BE FAT?
OKAY, WHEN I'M IN LABOR
AND I AM PUSHING AND SCREAMING
TO BRING YOUR CHILD
INTO THE WORLD,
DO YOU REALLY WANT ME
TO REMEMBER
THAT YOU DENIED ME SYRUP?
CARRY ON.
MOM, I NEED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT TONIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
IS IT ABOUT MATT'S PARTY?
YEAH. IT TURNS OUT
IT DOESN'T START UNTIL 10:00,
SO CAN I STAY OUT TILL 1:00?
WELL, UH, WELL, THE JOHNSONS
LIVE RIGHT DOWN THE ROAD.
YEAH, I GUESS THAT'S FINE.
THANKS.
WHOA, WHOA. IS THIS
THE JOHNSONS OVER ON CRESTVIEW?
YEAH.
YEAH, I-I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD GO TO THAT.
WHY NOT?
WELL, I'VE DONE A COUPLE JOBS
AT THAT HOUSE,
AND THEY HAVE SOME
REALLY WILD PARTIES.
I DON'T EVEN WANNA TELL YOU WHAT
I'VE SNAKED OUT OF THAT TOILET.
THOSE RE
MATT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
ALL 17-YEAR-OLD GUYS
ARE LIKE THAT.
THE ONLY REASON MY BUDDIES
AND I EVEN HAD PARTIES
WAS TO GET GIRLS WASTED.
WELL, I DON'T DRINK.
NEITHER DID MISSY TAYLOR,
AND FAST-FORWARD TO HER TYING
HER BRA ON MY CAR ANTENNA.
I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOUR CONCERN,
BUT MY MOM ALREADY TOLD ME
I COULD GO.
(clicks teeth)
WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
JUST GIVING MY OPINION.
IT'S UP TO YOUR MOM.
UH, WE...
I MEAN, YOU BOTH MAKE
A-A GOOD CASE.
UM... BUT I THINK I'M GONNA
HAVE TO AGREE WITH, UH...
AND YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU BOTH--
DECIDE.
MIKE. I'M GOING WITH MIKE.
WHAT?
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE THIS PARTY
COULD BE ON THE WILD SIDE,
AND IT IS STARTING VERY LATE.
THIS IS SO UNFAIR.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
YOU WANTED AECISION.
THIS IS MY DECISION.
MORE SYRUP?
MISSY TAYLOR?
CARRY ON.
LOOK AT YOUR LITTLE DYLAN,
ALL GROWN UP.
KAREN McCLUSKEY.
I BABYSAT YOU
WAY BACK WHEN.
YOU WERE A BITER.
WELL,
I HOPE I DIDN'T HURT YOU.
NAH, YOU WERE A CUTIE...
BUT LOUD.
I REMEMBER THE RACKET YOU USED
TO MAKE ON YOUR TRICYCLE.
I GAVE YOUR DAD HELL
FOUR PUTTING THAT HORN ON IT.
MY DAD?
MM-HMM.
HOW COULD
YOU KNOW MY DAD?
HE LEFT
WHEN I WAS A BABY.
NAH, HE USED TO COME AROUND
ONCE IN A WHILE.
ANYWAY,
NICE TO HAVE YOU BACK.
PLEASE LET ME HELP.
I FEEL SO GUILTY
JUST SITTING HERE.
DO NOT MOVE. WE WANT TO
PAMPER YOU, SO PLEASE LET US.
THANK YOU.
HEY, SO HOW'S
THE CHEMOTHERAPY GOING?
OH, NO, NO. SHE DOESN'T
WANT TO TALK ABOUT THAT.
I DON'T MIND.
OH, COME ON. LET'S DIG IN
TO THE PIE. LOOKS AMAZING.
WOW.
OH, MY GOD. BREE, THAT IS, LIKE,
THE BEST PIE YOU'VE EVER MADE.
WELL, THANK YOU. I DON'T THINK
I DID ANYTHING DIFFERENTLY.
THIS IS NOT MY PIE.
(laughs) OKAY,
YOU CAUGHT ME. IT'S MINE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE PIE
THAT I BROUGHT?
OH, I WAS A LITTLE SNEAKY,
AND I PUT IT IN THE FRIDGE.
I JUST WANTED YOU TO TRY MINE.
WELL, DID WE
OR DID WE NOT AGREE
THAT I WOULD BRING
THE DESSERT?
I KNOW, BUT EVERYONE SAYS
YOU'RE SUCH AN AMAZING BAKER,
AND I WAS HOPING
YOU WOULD GIVE ME SOME TIPS
TO IMPROVE MY RECIPE.
WELL, CLEARLY NO TIPS
ARE NEEDED.
AS MY FRIENDS SAID,
"BEST PIE EVER MADE."
WELL, THEN PERHAPS YOU
SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID ANYTHING.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN HAPPY FOR
EVERYONE TO THINK IT WAS YOURS.
SO BACK TO CHEMO--
HOW'S THAT BEEN?
YEAH, SO FAR...
NOT THAT BAD.
THOUGH I DID HAVE TO
KICK TOM OUT YESTERDAY.
WHY?
HE WAS GETTING SO EMOTIONAL.
IT FELT LIKE THE LAST 20 MINUTES
OF "BRIAN'S SONG."
SO... I GUESS I'M IN THE MARKET
FOR A NEW CHEMO BUDDY.
WELL, I WOULD BE MORE
THAN HAPPY TO GO WITH YOU.
COUNT ME IN.
I'LL SIT WITH YOU.
I VOLUNTEER AT THE HOSPITAL,
SO I'LL BE THERE ANYWAY.
OH! MY GOD, YOU GUYS.
I'M SO TOUCHED YOU'RE ALL
WILLING TO DO THIS.
WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
GABY?
???
STAGED
YOUR LEMON MERINGUE PIE?
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING.
I'M NOT.
THAT DESPICABLE WOMAN
WAS JUST SUPPOSED TO BRING
A SIMPLE GREEN SALAD.
SHE NOT ONLY BROUGHT
A PIE--
SHE HID MINE
AND SERVED HERS.
WELL, THAT'S BEYOND DESPICABLE.
THAT'S CULINARY TERRORISM.
OH, IT GETS WORSE.
HER PIE WAS BETTER THAN MINE.
(mixer whirring)
IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S TRUE.
EVERYONE THOUGHT SO.
EVEN ME. OH, AND THAT
SIMPLE GREEN SALAD--
MACHE AND BABY ARUGULA WITH
DUCK CONFIT AND CANDIED WALNUTS!
MY GOD, SHE PLAYS TO WIN.
I HAVE BEEN HERE FOR HOURS
TRNG TO REPLICATE HER RECIPE,
AND NOTHING HAS
EVEN COMCLOSE!
DON'T BE SO HARD ON YOURSELF.
THIS ONE'S FANTASTIC.
THAT'S HERS!
SORRY.
ORSON, WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
YOU MIGHT HAVE
TO BITE THE BULLET
AND ASK HER FOR HER RECIPE.
WHAT? SURRENDER?
DEBASE MYSELF?
BREE,
IT'S YOUR SIGNATURE PIE.
YOU MAKE IT FOR PARTIES,
CHURCH SUPPERS, BAKE SALES.
IF SHE'S ALWAYS RIGHT THERE
BEHIND YOU
WITH HER SUPERIOR VERSION,
STAKING OUT HER CLAIM
AS FAIRVIEW'S NUMBER ONE
HOMEMAKER...
SHE WILL HAVE STOLEN
MY ENTIRE IDENTITY.
WELL,
I WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR.
NO, IT'S TRUE.
THE ONLY THING ABOUT ME
THAT'S SPECIAL
IS WHAT I CAN DO
IN THE KITCHEN.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE GOT
TO GET THAT RECIPE...
BY ANY MEANS NECESSARY.
HEY, GABY.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WELL...
I FELT A LITTLE WEIRD
ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED AT LUNCH,
AND I THOUGHT
WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT IT.
I KNOW. DO YOU BELIEVE
THAT PIE BUSINESS?
I THOUGHT BREE'S HEAD
WAS GONNA EXPLODE.
(chuckles)O, NOT THAT.
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO SAY THIS,
SO I'M JUST GONNA SAY IT.
WHEN EVERYONE WAS OFFERING
TO COME WITH ME TO CHEMO--
EVEN KATHERINE,
WHO I DON'T EVEN KNOW,
YOU SORT OF CLAMMED UP.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
WELL, IT JUST SEEMED LIKE PEOPLE
HAD IT PRETTY WELL COVERED.
YEAH, BUT BETWEEN US,
YOU'RE THE ONEI REALLY WANT THERE.
OUT OF EVERYONE,
YOU'RE THE MOST FUN,
AND I NEED THAT NOW.
OH, THAT'S SWEET.
BUT TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T LIKE HOSPITALS.
NOBODY LIKES HOSPITALS.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT'S THE PLACE
YOU HAVE TO GO
WHEN YOU'RE SICK,
OR YOUR FRIENDS ARE.
YOU ARE MY FRIEND, RIGHT?
WHAT, IS THIS A TEST
OF OUR FRIENDSHIP?
YEAH... KINDA.
CAN I PENCIL YOU IN?
I CAN'T WAIT.
(lowered voice) PSST! COME HERE.
OKAY, I'LL COME THERE.
ARE YOU STILL MAD AT ME
ABOUT THE PARTY?
OH, YOU PICKED UP ON THAT,
DID YOU?
OKAY, LOOK, I'VE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT THINGS, AND...
(whispers) JUST FORGET
WHAT I SAID EARLIER.
(loudly)
YOU MEAN I CAN GO?
SHH! JEEZ! OOH,
MIKE'S IN THE OTHER ROOM.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL HIM?
NO, AND NEITHER ARE YOU.
(scoffs) WHY ARE YOU
WALKING ON EGGSHELLS?
YOU ARE MY MOTHER. YOU HAVE
EVERY RIGHT TO OVERRIDE HIM.
I KNOW.
I JUST--I THINK IT'S SWEET
THAT HE WORRIES ABOUT YOU,
AND I WANT HIM TO FEEL
LIKE HE'S PART
OF THE DECISION MAKING
PROCESS.
WELL, CLEARLY HE'S NOT IF
YOU'RE GOING BEHIND HIS BACK.
DO YOU WANNA GO OR NOT?
YES! YES, I REALLY WANNA
GO TO THE PARTY.
PARTY? YOU GUYS STILL
TALKING ABOUT THAT?
(sighs) CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
UGH! LET IT GO.
YOU KNOW, MIKE AND I DECIDED--
NO PARTY, AND THAT'S FINAL.
BREE.
I HOPE THIS ISN'T
A BAD TIME.
I JUST WANTED TO BRING YOU
A HOUSEWARMING GIFT.
IT'S THE RECIPE FOR
MY SPECIAL MINCEMEAT PIE.
IT WOULDN'T BE THANKSGIVING
AT MY HOUSE WITHOUT IT.
WELL...
AREN'T YOU THOUGHTFUL?
LET ME JUST FILE THIS
IN MY RECIPE BOX.
WELL, AS LONG AS WE'RE
SWAPPING PIE RECIPES,
I WOULD LOVE THE ONE FOR
YOUR FABULOUS LEMON MERINGUE.
REALLY? I'M SO FLATTERED
YOU'D ASK.
BUT I DON'T SHARE THAT.
EXCUSE ME?
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND--
I EXPERIMENTED FOR YEARS
BEFORE I CAME UP
WITH MY SECRET INGREDIENT.
WHICH IS WHAT?
VANILLA? NUTMEG? CARDAMOM?
IF I TOLD YOU, IT WOULDN'T
BE A SECRET ANYMORE.
IT WOULD JUST BE
AN INGREDIENT.
WELL, THAT, UM,
HARDLY SEEMS NEIGHBORLY.
AFTER ALL, I JUST GAVE YOU
THE RECIPE FOR MY MINCEMEAT PIE.
YES, AND IT'S A VERY GOOD ONE.
I HAVE THE BOOK IT CAME FROM.
THAT RECIPE IS NOT
FROM A BOOK.
THAT RECIPE WAS HANDED DOWN
TO ME FROM MY MOTHER.
WELL, UNLESS YOUR MOTHER
WAS BETTY CROCKER,
SHE GOT IT FROM A BOOK.
OH, DEAR.
NOW I'VE UPSET YOU.
NO. NO, I AM NOT UPSET.
I'M JUST CONFUSED AS TO WHY
YOU SEEM SO DETERMINED
TO GET OFF
ON THE WRONG FOOT.
FIRST YOU BRING A PIE
TO LYNETTE'S,
WHEN I CLEARLY ASSIGNED YOU
THE SALAD--
NOW, SEE,
THAT'S WHERE I'M CONFUSED.
JUST WHAT, PLEASE,
GIVES YOU THE RIGHT
TO DECIDE WHO BRINGS WHAT
TO A LUNCHEON THAT I SUGGESTED?
WELL, IT'S TRADITION.
I ALWAYS ORGANIZE
OUR LITTLE GET-TOGETHERS,
AND I ALWAYS BRING DESSERT.
WELL, THEN
HOW LOVELY THAT I'M BACK
AND CAN SHOUER
THAT BURDEN FOR YOU.
JUST... GIVE ME THE RECIPE!
SORRY. I CAN'T.
I DO HOPE THIS DOESN'T
KEEP US FROM BEING FRIENDS,
BECAUSE I LIKE YOU, BREE.
AND I'M SURE
IF YOU PUT YOUR MIND TO IT,
YOU CAN COME UP
WITH AN EVEN BETTER
LEMON MERINGUE PIE THAN MINE.
THE TRICK IS FINDING THAT
PERFECT BLEND OF SWEET AND SOUR.
WELL, YOU'VE CERTAINLY
MASTERED THAT, DEAR.
SO WHEN DO I GET TO SEE
MY BIG SURPRISE?
WAIT FOR IT. WAIT FOR IT.
TA-DA.
WHOA.
ALL THAT SYRUP WENT STRAIGHT TO YOUR BOOBS.
SO IT'S NOT MY IMAGINATION.
THEY'RE BIGGER, RIGHT?
UH, YEAH.
ESPECIALLY THE RIGHT ONE.
MIKE!
JUST KIDDING.
PICK THOSE UP AND BRING 'EM OVER HERE.
WELL, I'D BETTER WARN YOU.
I MAY HAVE TO WORK THE SHOULDERS.
MMM. HEY.
THAT THING WITH JULIE AND
THE PARTY THIS MORNING...
MM-HMM?
THANKS FOR BACKING ME UP.
IT MEANT A LOT,
AND I KNOW IT WASN'T EASY FOR YOU.
UH, YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA HANG TOUGH.
MM, WELL,
YOU DID THE RIGHT THING.
I DROVE BY THAT HOUSE TONIGHT.
MM-HMM?
THAT PARTY WAS OUT OF CONTROL.
WHAT?
YEAH, THERE WERE KIDS STAGGERING AROUND DRUNK...
PUKING IN THE GUTTER,
AND THEN I SAW SOME GIRLS RUNNING AROUND TOPLESS.
I'M SURE THE COPS WILL BE THERE ANY MINUTE.
WE NEED WHIPPED CREAM.
WHAT?
WELL
I DON'T THINK THAT
YOU CAN HAVE SEXY DATE NIGHT WITHOUT WHIPPED CREAM.
CAN'T AND WON'T.
WELL, I...
I CAN GO GET SOME.
NO, NO, YOU'VE, UH, WORKED ALL DAY.
YOU STAY HERE.
I'LL GO TO THE STORE.
COULD YOU GET MORE SYRUP?
MAKE A WISH.
SO I'M DYING TO SEE WHAT I GOT YOU.
HOW THOUGHTFUL WAS I?
VERY.
OPEN IT.
"YES!"
NOT YET.
I HAVEN'T ASKED THE QUESTION.
WILL YOU MARRY ME, CARLOS SOLIS?
AND YOU SAY...
YOU'RE PROPOSING?
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T WANT TO SPEND TOO MUCH.
SO WHAT'S MORE AFFORDABLE THAN A PROMISE?
LOOK, EDIE--
I'M DOING THIS FOR YOU.
IF THE I.R.S. GETS WIND OF YOUR...
RAINY DAY FUND,
THEY COULD MAKE ME TESTIFY AGAINST YOU.
BUT IF I WERE YOUR WIFE...
HOW ARE THEY GOING TO FIND OUT?
OH, HONEY, PEOPLE TALK--
ANGRY PEOPLE, DISAPPOINTED PEOPLE.
COME ON.
SAY YOUR LINE.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
FINE.
WE'RE ENGAGED.
OH! CARLOS!
I THINK I'M GONNA CRY.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
I MEAN, HOW WEIRD IS THAT?
MY MOM ALWAYS TOLD METHAT MY DAD TOOK OFF
RIGHT AFTER I WAS BORN.
SO DID SHE EXPLAIN WHAT McCLUSKEY SAID?
I DIDN'T TELL HER.
SHE KINDA FREAKS OUT ANYTIME I BRING HIM UP.
DYLAN, YOU HAVE A RIGHT TO KNOW ABOUT YOUR DAD.
YOU'VE GOT TO CONFRONT HER.
YEAH, RIGHT.
I COULD NEVER DO THAT.
SHE ISN'T COOL LIKE YOUR MOM.
HI. IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
OH, THAT MUST MEAN YOU'RE MATT.
I'M SUSAN MAYER, AND I'M--
ALL RIGHTY.
YOU MAGNIFICENT BASTARD!
YOU ACTUALLY DID IT!
IT WASN'T ME,
BUT HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MAN.
WELL, IT WAS SOMEBODY.
WHO CARES? GATHER 'ROUND, MEN.
SO YOU LIKE THIS MUSIC?
AH, IT'S FINE.
WOULD SOMEBODY JUST TELL ME WHERE I CAN FIND--
HEY, ENOUGH TALKING.
JUST TAKE IT OFF.
WE'RE FEELING GENEROUS TONIGHT.
OH, MY GOD!
I'M NOT A STRIPPER.
YOU'RE NOT?
IS THIS GONNA HAPPEN OR WHAT?
BOOMER, SHE'S NOT A STRIPPER.
WHAT'S WITH THE IMPLANTS?
I'M PREGNANT.
THAT'S HOT.
SORRY.
SHOULD'VE KNOWN YOU WERE JULIE'S MOM.
YOU'RE WAY TOO GORGEOUS TO BE A STRIPPER.
IF THAT'S YOUR LAME ATTEMPT
TO KEEP ME FROM CALLING YOUR PARENTS...
IT WORKED. WELL PLAYED.
EXCUSE ME. OH. AAH!
UH, UH...
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I AM TAKING YOU HOME.
THIS PARTY IS OUT OF CONTROL.
NO, IT'S NOT.
WELL, OF COURSE
YOU DON'T THINK IT IS
BECAUSE YORE KNOCKING BACK A BIG CUP OF...
MM... ORANGE SODA.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
WELL, BELIEVE IT. WE'RE GOING.
YOU, TOO, DYLAN. COME ON.
AND WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
YEAH, WELL, BOOMER LIKES IT.
CALL ME TOMORROW.
WE'LL GO TO A MOVIE MY MOM CAN DRAG US OUT OF.
LOOK, I GET THAT YOU'RE UPSET.
NO, I'M CONFUSED.
FIRST, I CAN GO TO THE PARTY,
THEN I CAN'T BECAUSE MIKE SAYS NO.
THEN I CAN, BUT "DON'T TELL MIKE AND BEHAVE YOURSELF."
SO I BEHAVE MYSELF,
AND YOU PUNISH ME.
OKAY, I ADMIT THAT
THERE'S A CERTAIN LACK OF
CONSISTENCY THERE.
IT'S LIKE...
EVER SINCE YOU GOT MARRIED,
I CAN'T WIN.
DO YOU THINK THIS IS EASY FOR ME?
TRYING TO KEEP PEACE
BETWEEN A NEW HUSBAND
AND A TEENAGE DAUGHTER?
YOU'RE ALWAYS PUTTING ME IN THE MIDDLE.
UGH. I DON'T DO THAT.
PLEASE.
EVERY TIME YOU AND MIKE
DISAGREE ON SOMETHING,
YOU GIVE ME THE LOOK--
THAT PITIFUL FACE
THAT SAYS IF I DON'T BACK YOU UP,
I LOVE THE OTHER ONE MORE.
I DON'T EXPECT YOU TO SIDE
WITH ME EVERY TIME.
JUST MAKE A DECISION AND STICK TO IT.
AND NO MORE LYING.
WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M AN ADULT, AND I NEED TO BE
HONEST ABOUT THESE THINGS,
AND I WILL BE... STARTING TOMORROW.
HEY.
LOOK WHO I PICKED UP COMING
OUT OF THE MOVIES--
A P.G. MOVIE.
IS THIS THE PERFECT TEENAGER OR WHAT?
OH, THE MOVIES, HUH?
THAT'S FUNNY.
'CAUSE ONE OF JULIE'S
FRIENDS JUST CALLED
TO MAKE SURE SHE GOT
HOME FROM THE PARTY.
SHE WAS WORRIED
WHEN SHE SAW YOU LEAVING
WITH A STRIPPER.
THE JIG IS UP, MOM.
NO, NO, WE CAN SALVAGE THIS.
JUST WORK WITH ME.
I DID GO TO THE PARTY.
MOM WENT BEHIND YOUR BACK
AND TOLD ME I COULD.
BUT I-I DIDN'T DRINK OR DO
ANYTHING I SHOULDN'T HAVE.
GLAD TO HEAR IT,
AND, UH,
THANKS FOR YOUR HONESTY.
YOU KNOW,
THIS PERFECT TEENAGER THING
IS REALLY STARTING TO CHAP MY ASS.
I'M GOING TO BED.
PLEASE TELL ME THIS ISN'T
GONNA BE ONE OF THOSE THINGS
WHERE YOU LEAVE ME AND I GO
SCREAMING DOWN THE STREET.
WHY'D YOU GO BEHIND MY BACK?
I'M SORRY.
YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND, FOR SO LONG,
IT'S JUST BEEN
JULIE AND ME,
AND I'VE MADE
ALL THE DECISIONS ALONE.
YOU FELT SO STRONGLY.
IT WAS JUST AN OPINION, REALLY.
SHE'S YOUR DAUGHTER.
I COMPLETELY RESPECT
YOUR RIGHT
TO RAISE HER
HOWEVER YOU WANT.
THANKS.
NOW THAT BEING SAID,
THIS BABY IS OURS.
SO WE'LL GET TO MAKE
ALL THOSE PARENTING DECISIONS
TOGETHER, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
SO CAN WE GO BACK
TO DATE NIGHT?
LY IF YOU WORK
THE SHOULDERS.
OH.
MMM.
GABY, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU WENT TO THE BATHROOM,
LIKE, HALF AN HOUR AGO.
OH, SORRY. I STOPPED OFF
TO GET YOU SOME MAGAZINES.
"TOP TEN NEW HAIRSTYLES."
YEAH, WELL, I'M KINDA BALD
RIGHT NOW, BUT THANKS.
WHY N'T I GO CHECK
IF THERE ARE SOME OTHER ONES?
NO, NO, I DON'T NEED MAGAZINES.
I NEED YOU'VE BEEN BOUNCING AROUND
SINCE YOU GOT HERE.
SO...
HOW DO YOU LIKE BEING
THE FIRST LADY OF FAIRVIEW?
IT'S GOOD.
ARE YOU COLD?
THEY KEEP IT COLD IN HERE.
I'M FINE.
SO TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHEN YOU GO TO A RIBBON CUTTING,
DO YOU GET TO KEEP THOSE
GIGANTIC NOVELTY SCISSORS?
YOU MUST BE FREEZING.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE
THE CUTEST SHAWL IN THE CAR,
SO I'M JUST GONNA RUN OUT
AND GET IT FOR YOU.
BOY, YOU REALLY DON'T WANNA
BE HERE, DO YA?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TRYING TO HELP.
YEAH, IN ANY WAY
THAT GETS YOU OUT OF THIS ROOM.
I'M SORRY. IT'S JUST
HOSPITALS ARE HARD FOR ME.
YEAH, YOU TOLD ME,
BUT, JEEZ, GABY,
DON'T YOU CARE ENOUGH
TO MAKE AN EFFORT?
YOU THINK I DON'T CARE?
I GET IT.
YOU'RE UNCOMFORTABLE.
JUST GO. I'M FINE.
I'M FINE.
DID I EVER TELL YOU
ABOUT MY FATHER?
HE HAD CANCER, TOO.
STARTED IN THE LIVER,
WENT INTO HIS BONES,
AND TEN MONTHS LATER,
HE WAS DEAD.
THANKS FOR
THAT ENCOURAGING STORY.
I'M NOT FINISHED.
THOSE LAST WEEKS,
EVERY DAY WE THOUGHT
WE WERE GONNA LOSE HIM.
AND EVERY DAY, BEFORE I
WOULD GO INTO HIS ROOM,
MY MOM WOULD SAY,
"NO TEARS.
"DADDY WANTS TO SEE YOU
SMILING.
IF YOU'RE GONNA CRY,
YOU CAN'T GO IN."
sO... ON THE LAST NIGHT...
I SAT THERE
AND I WATCHED HIM DIE.
HIS EYES WERE CLOSED,
BUT I THOUGHT
HE COULD STILL SEE ME.
SO I KEPT SMILING...
ALL NIGHT.
I WAS 5.
OH, MY GOD.
BUT ON THE PLUS SIDE,
I MADE A PRETTY GOOD CAREER
OUT OF KNOWING HOW TO SMILE
WHEN I DIDN'T REALLY FEEL
LIKE IT. (sniffles)
BUT I CAN'T PRETEND
WITH YOU.
NOT WHEN I'M SCARED
I'M GONNA LOSE YOU.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LOSE ME.
YOU PROMISE?
'CAUSE IF I DID...
THEN...
(laughs)
GOD! I'M SUCH A MESS.
IT'S OKAY. COME HERE.
LET IT GO. OH.
(Katherine) HONEY?
I'M GOING TO GET ADAM.
BE RIGHT BACK.
??
CAN I TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING?
SURE. IF YOU DON'T MIND
TALKING IN THE CAR.
BREE HODGE PERSISTED
IN HER EFFOR
TO UNLOCTHE SECRET
OF KATHERINE MAYFAIR'S
LEMON MERINGUE.
BUT AFTER
SEVERAL FAILED ATTEMPTS,
IT OCCURRED TO BREE
THAT WHILE SHE MIGHT NOT HAVE
THE KEY
TO KATHERINE'S RECIPE...
SHE DID HAVE THE KEY...
TO KATHERINE'S HOUSE.
OH, HEY, WHAT'S UP?
I WAS DOING A LITTLE BAKING,
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF I COULD BORROW SOMETHING.
SURE. WHAT DO YOU NEED--
FLOUR, SUGAR?
YOU CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT
KAREN McCLUSKEY TELLS YOU.
SHE'S AN OLD WOMAN--
PRACTICALLY SENILE.
SHE DIDN'T SOUND SENILE
TO ME.
DYLAN, MAYBE THIS IS NOT
THE TIME, OKAY?
YOU SAID MY FATHER
DIDN'T CARE ABOUT ME,
BUT SHE SAYS HE CAME HERE.
HE WANTED TO SEE ME.
WHY WOD YOU NOT
TELL ME THAT?
HE'S MY FATHER.
I DESERVE TO KNOW.
THE ONLY THING YOU NEED
TO KNOW ABOUT THAT MAN
IS HE WAS A MONSTER.
I CAN DECIDE THAT FOR MYSELF.
WHERE IS HE?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE LYING.
NO, SHE'S NOT.
YES, SHE IS.
SHE HAS BEEN LYING TO ME
MY WHOLE LIFE.
I'M STARTING TO THINK
MAYBE YOU'RE THE MONSTER.
SHE CAN'T TALK TO ME
THAT WAY,
NOT AFTER EVERYTHING
I'VE DONE FOR HER.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S
THE PROBLEM.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE DONE FOR HER.
NOBODY DOES,
AND IT'S GONNA STAY THAT WAY.
ARE YOU SURE? SHE'S JUST
GONNA KEEP ASKING QUESTIONS.
THEN WE'D BETTER START
COMING UP WITH BETTER LIES.
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
I WAS WONDERING
WHERE YOU'D GONE TO.
I JUST LET MYSELF
INTO KATHERINE'S HOUSE
TO GET THAT RECIPE.
WELL, THAT SEEMS
A BIT EXTREME.
WELL, AT LEAST
YOU KNOW HER SECRET NOW.
YES, AND IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH PIE.
AHH. HERE'S THE THING.
I GOT A REAL CHANCE AT GETTING
BACK TOGETHER WITH MY EX,
BUT THIS WOMAN
IS STANDING IN MY WAY.
AND SHE KNOWS ABOUT THE MONEY,
AND SHE'S MADE IT CLEAR
THAT IF I LEAVE,
SHE'S GONNA BLOW THE WHISTLE.
YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND...
I REALLY DID CARE
FOR EDIE,
BUT I CAN'T LET HER
RUIN MY LIFE.
THAT'S WHERE YOU COME IN.
YOU GUYS, WE BETTER BEHAVE,
OR THE NURSES
ARE GONNA KICK US OUT.
HEY, IT'S OUR CHEMO PARTY,
AND WE'LL LAUGH IF WE WANT TO.
GABY, THIS WAS
A WONDERFUL IDEA.
I CANNOT TELL YOU
HOW MUCH IT MEANS TO ME.
WELL, DON'T GET SAPPY ON ME.
I WON'T STAND FOR IT.
ALL RIGHT, SUSAN,
IS THE CAMERA READY?
YEAH.
GOT IT.
OKAY, ONCE THE LIGHT
STARTS BLINKING,
WE'VE GOT THREE SECONDS,
SO, EVERYBODY, SAY, "CHEESE"
AND HOLDT.
OKAY.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
(all) CHEESE!
THERE IS NOTHING MORE DECEPTIVE
THAN A SMILE,
AND NO ONE KNOWS THIS BETTER
THAN THE PEOPLE
WHO HIDE BEHIND THEM.
SOME FLASH THEIR TEETH
AS A POLITE WARNING
TO THEIR ENEMIES.
SOME PUT ON BEAMING FACES TO
KEEP THEIR TEARS FROM FALLING.
OTHERS WEAR SILLY GRINS
TO MASK THEIR FEAR.
MM!
BUT THEN
THERE IS THAT RARE SMILE
THAT IS ACTUALLY GENUINE.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
IT'S THE SMILE OF A PERSON
WHO KNOWS HIS TROUBLES
WILL SOON BE OVER.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入