My siblings and I are the first
vampires in history, The Originals.
300 years ago, we helped
build New Orleans.
In our absence, a
new king arose.
Now I've returned and taken
his kingdom as my own.
I had hoped this would
bring our family together.
I was wrong.
I wanted our home back, so
I'm going to live there,
and the two of you,
you can stay here
together and rot.
You're coming with
me, little wolf.
Why would I go
anywhere with you?
Now you can fight me on
this, but you will lose,
As will anyone else who tries to
stop you getting in this car.
Let us begin with a toast
to our shared gift--
immortality.
After 1,000 years,
one might expect for life
to be less keenly felt,
for its beauties and its
sorrows to diminish with time,
but as vampires,
we feel more deeply than humans
could possibly imagine--
insatiable need,
exquisite pain,
Our victories,
and our defeats.
You can't afford
your wounded pride.
With Klaus in control
of your empire,
You need to give him
what he craves most--
Loyalty, or at least
the illusion of it.
I ambushed him,
tried to bury him alive.
He's not gonna trust me.
He will because he
wants your allegiance.
Speaking from experience,
I know that if you play the
part, all is forgiven,
but if you give him any
reason to doubt you,
He will strike back.
Make me a promise, Marcel.
You do whatever it
takes to stay alive.
To my city, my home again.
May the blood never cease to flow.
And the party never end.
I just don't get it, man.
You know we would've stood
with you till the end.
Letting you do that would've
been letting you die,
and you're still my people.
For now, just follow my lead.
Trust me, it ain't over yet.
To New Orleans.
- To New Orleans.
- New Orleans.
I understand that some of
you may have questions
regarding the recent
change in leadership,
and I invited you here
tonight to assure you
that you are not defeated.
No. My intentions moving forward
are to celebrate what we have,
What Marcel, in fact, took...
and built into this--
a true community of vampires.
What about her, the wolf?
Had you let me finish, Diego,
you would know that
there is, of course,
one further matter I
would like to address.
As many of you know,
the girl is carrying my child.
Consequently, I trust
you will all pay her the
appropriate respect.
However, I understand that
some of you are concerned
by this vicious rumor that I intend
to use the blood of our child
to create hybrids.
I assure you, I do not.
Father of the year.
It appears I will have
to earn your trust.
Very well.
We'll eliminate the
root of your anxiety.
You see, how can I
sire any hybrids
if there are no more werewolves
alive in the Bayou to turn?
What?
Klaus, no.
So eat, drink, and be merry,
and tomorrow I suggest you have
yourselves a little wolf hunt.
Go ahead. Have fun.
Kill them all.
Absolutely not.
I paid for that.
Please. Never paid for
anything in your life.
I hardly see how
that's relevant.
Nik's just punishing us.
Well, we've hurt him,
deeply, it would appear.
We believed the worst
about him the one time
in a million when the worst
wasn't actually the truth.
Where do you think you're going?
To ensure that Hayley doesn't
suffer for our mistakes.
Niklaus is feeling vindictive.
We cannot trust
that she is safe.
And so then I bit Elijah
and left him in the bayou
with my hybrid venom
in his veins.
Serves him right for making such
vile accusations against me,
and let--
Are you taking this down?
To be clear, if the
quarter is yours now,
you still need me why?
My memoirs.
1,000 years of history
isn't gonna write itself.
Cami, what are you doing here?
My question exactly.
Oh, it's quite all right.
She knows.
She does?
That you're vampires?
Don't worry.
He's compelled me to forget
everything as soon as I leave.
That way, I'm too
busy agonizing over
whether or not I'm
losing my damn mind
to realize I'm playing spy
for an immortal egomaniac.
You compelled her to go
out with me, didn't you?
And I thought you
really liked me.
So did I.
Well, I mean, to be clear,
I only compelled you
to give him a chance.
Anything you felt for
him was quite real.
And, for the record,
the level of awkwardness
We're all currently experiencing
is entirely genuine.
You think you're so
clever, don't you,
compelling the poor,
naive bartender?
Look what I found,
real me, not your
compelled therapist.
Well, actually I prefer
devoted stenographer.
You think this is funny,
messing with my mind?
My sanity is not a joke.
No, Luv, I don't believe it is.
You never found this.
You will remember
nothing of our life
as vampires when you leave here.
Do you understand?
I think that just about
does it for the day.
You may go.
Going somewhere?
Elijah.
You shouldn't be here.
Klaus has his guys watching me.
I wouldn't worry about them.
Come. We mustn't linger.
Let's get you someplace safe.
No. You don't have to worry about me.
I'm fine.
I've been deemed under protection
by the almighty Klaus.
It's the werewolves
who need help.
He ordered a wolf hunt as some
jacked-up peace offering
to Marcel's crew.
You have to help them.
Out in the Bayou?
Do we look like a bloody
vampire rescue squad?
I think you should be
grateful we came to save you.
Listen, Rebekah.
All my life, I've wanted to
know who my real family was,
and just as I find out that
they're out there in the bayou,
Klaus orders them killed.
You want to help me?
Help my people, please.
Humans have called a meeting.
They're not exactly thrilled
with the new status quo.
How unfortunate for them.
Look. It's your show now,
but you want to know how
I built what I built?
Politics.
A little diplomacy
goes a long way,
especially with the
human faction.
Duly noted.
I haven't thought about
this night in ages--
1919, the opera house
just before it burned.
This was the end of an era.
Now, in the interest
of new beginnings,
I feel there are some things I
should probably confess to you,
but where to begin?
Thierry was never
disloyal to you.
I set him up in an attempt
to locate my brother.
He's your friend,
and, consequently,
he can return to the compound
at your discretion.
Cami's part you just learned,
and then there's young Joshua.
I've been compelling him
from the beginning,
although I suspect you
already knew that,
as he was the one who
led me into your trap.
I may have fed the kid
some misinformation.
Mm, and then there's Davina.
She's a powerful weapon.
At this point, I'd like to
keep her close at hand.
I think we should have her move
into the compound here with us.
Eh, she can't leave the attic.
I already tried
to move her once.
Yes. About that, turns out,
your little witch is
quite the actress.
She made a deal with Elijah
while he was in captivity,
tricked you into
letting her stay put
in exchange for some spells
from our mother's grimoire.
Good to know. Is that all?
I do believe it is.
Appreciate the honesty.
Meeting is in an hour.
--- BELIEVE NOTHING KLAUS TELLS YOU ---
--- YOUR BAG INSIDE POCKET ---
And so then I bit Elijah
and left him in the bayou
with my hybrid venom
in his veins.
Serves him right for making such
vile accusations against me.
You're gonna love
it at the compound.
I already got the best room
in the place picked out.
I can't leave.
Remember what
happened last time?
I know about your
deal with Elijah.
Can't be lying to each other.
I'm trying to protect you.
With the witches still looking
to kill you for the harvest,
believe me, you're
safest with us.
Plus, there's excellent
light in the afternoon.
I see you're an artist.
Wonderful.
I look forward to witnessing
your many talents.
Was this his idea?
Davina, please.
I understand you're
devoted to Marcel,
but Marcel is devoted to me.
I assume you want what's
best for all of us.
We have a meeting to
attend downstairs.
Look. I'll get someone
to pick up your things.
We'll get you settled in right.
Trust me.
Klaus, Marcel,
Thank you for coming.
Now, we are aware of the change
in leadership in your community,
and we thought it was time to make
the appropriate introductions.
We want to be sure you understand
how things work around here.
Is that so?
What the mayor means
is that we just want
some assurance that
this new development
isn't gonna endanger our
city or its inhabitants.
Look. You freaks do your thing,
and we'll look the other way.
As long as our
pockets stay full,
we won't have a problem.
More importantly,
there are rules.
No feeding on the locals.
Don't bring any unwanted
attention to the city.
Now, history has proven that
we can coexist peacefully.
However, if you cross the line--
You answer to us.
Ha ha! Ok. I'm sorry.
Let me get this straight.
I'm to play supplicant
to this pompous ass
and his ridiculous group
of petty thieves?
Ah, Here are my terms.
You will take whatever scraps
I see fit to leave you,
and you will be grateful.
If that doesn't suit you,
I may decide you've
outlived your usefulness.
Hey,
They were obviously just here.
Fan out, find them, and
bring me some heads.
I'd rather you didn't.
What the hell are
you doing out here?
I've come to suggest you
seek other hunting grounds.
Suggestion noted.
Well, Diego, it would
be such a shame
to have to rearrange
that pretty face.
What the hell you
care about wolves?
Generally, I don't.
However this particular
clan is not to be touched.
Good-bye.
Bye.
Nothing here, anyway.
Great. I guess our
job here is done.
Not quite.
We're not here to harm you.
Hello again.
Eve, was it?
One of Hayley's little
mate, I presume.
Hayley sent you here to
protect us, didn't she?
Tell her we appreciate
the concern,
but we've been looking out for
ourselves for a while now.
Nobody finds us
unless we want to be found.
Well, we found you, so...
Like I said...
There's something I thought you and
your family should know about.
I think I was far more
gracious than they deserved.
You're disappointed by
my lack of diplomacy.
Well, you, above all people,
should need no reminder
of the human capacity
for cruelty.
Hello?
Mr. Mikaelson,
just wanted to let you know,
the faction has
considered your terms.
We've reached a decision.
Have you?
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
Oh, this is on you.
Now that you're in charge,
those are your guys laying dead,
Your guys.
You're gonna run this city, that
better mean something to you.
Otherwise no one worth a damn
is gonna follow you, no one.
I was beginning to
worry about you.
I don't think I could've taken
any more of this
deferential nonsense.
I mean, clearly, I
underestimated the faction.
That won't happen
again, but tell me,
now that we've arrived
at this point,
now that they have
come into our home,
visited this upon our people,
how would you counsel
me to respond?
Let's go kill them all.
We're surrounded by
20,000 acres of swamp.
The ones born here know it
like the backs of our hands.
We'll be fine, but here,
newcomers from out of state,
not Hayley's and mine kin,
but word spread about
that baby of hers.
Lot of werewolves want to see
this miracle pregnancy
for themselves.
Only now the vampires are
out looking for blood,
and all these werewolves
new to the bayou,
they might not know
where to hide.
You say that like we're
supposed to care.
Believe me, you're gonna
want then kept alive.
And why is that?
See for yourself.
I know you're in here, Josh.
I can sense your fear.
I heard you were moving in.
What are you doing in here?
Uh, you know,
I'm hiding out,
You know, incognito.
Got to run for the hills,
but I'm stuck here
until it gets dark.
Are you ok?
Yeah. Yeah.
No, not really.
I mean, I totally led
Klaus into a trap
that was like the most
epic failure of all time.
So, yeah, I'm kind of
crapping my pants right now,
Figuratively... so far.
It's OK.
You can trust Marcel,
and if Klaus tries to hurt you,
I'll hurt him.
I'm sure if you could
actually stop Klaus,
you would've done it already.
You're Hayley, Klaus' wife.
Ew.
No. Never.
I'm the pregnant werewolf,
and you must be the all-powerful
super witch Davina, and
let's not forget Josh,
newbie vampire way
out of his element,
voted most likely to die next.
Oh, fantastic.
Hey, I'm just another one
of Klaus' prisoners.
Of course, it would
suck if he found out
you were still lurking around.
Maybe there's a world
where we can all look
out for each other.
I called you hours ago!
I-I came as fast as I could.
What's going on?
Your voicemail sounded...
What, paranoid, unhinged?
Upset.
That picture I found,
the one that was, I don't know,
a hundred years old,
you said it was
just a coincidence,
but...
My sanity is not a joke.
No, love, I don't believe it is.
That's my voice, but
I don't remember it.
I think it's...
some kind of mind control.
I think he's erasing my memory!
Yes?
They what?
Um, we will talk
about this later.
Why wasn't I consulted on this?
You've been gone for
over 8 month, Kieran.
We got used to doing
things on our own.
This Klaus Mikaelson,
I don't care who he is
or what the rumors say.
He needed to be taught a lesson.
You are gonna start a war.
I'd like to see them try,
Oh, and, Kieran,
this is the last time
you call a meeting.
Next time you want to criticize our
leadership, send a damn e-mail.
I thought you called
this meeting.
The hell we did.
Actually, I called it.
It appears I made a grave error
during our earlier conference.
My friend Marcel offered
me wise counsel,
and I failed to heed it.
Hmm, well, I'm glad to hear
you've learned your lesson.
Oh, I won't be making
that mistake again.
Marcel?
Shall we?
After you.
There he is,
our lone survivor.
Such a sad day for our city,
some of its best and brightest
killed in a tragic boating
accident on the Mississippi.
Rather nasty explosion, I heard.
What am I going to do with you?
OK.
Hold up.
I've known Kieran
for a long time.
He's smart, and he's fair.
He can do us more
good alive than dead,
not to mention
he's Cami's uncle.
Don't see you care about much.
It's kind of hard not
to notice when you do.
Very well.
Use this reprieve to
remake your human faction.
And how do you expect
me to remake the mayor?
Well, surely, there's
a deputy mayor.
Choose new leaders
then we reopen negotiations.
Wow, these wolves really
travel in style, don't they?
- Empty.
- Behind on their payments, perhaps.
Shall we proceed then?
Let's not and tell
Hayley that we did.
Then you get to impress the
girl, and I can go home.
You know how hovels depress me.
I'm not trying to
impress the girl.
I should bloody hope you are.
Why else are we out here?
Come on, Elijah.
You've fallen for her.
Admit it.
May do wonders for the stick
that's lodged up your enduringly
stoic ass if you did.
If I admit to you that
it's complicated,
would that suffice,
or are you determined
to torment me throughout
this endeavor?
Darling, we're gonna have
to stop meeting like this.
This is how rumors begin.
You can go now.
Damn it!
Perhaps I'm not making
myself clear here.
This is a threat.
In precisely 3 minutes time,
your little hunting party
will become the prey.
Now, based on your recent failure
to subdue my baby
brother Niklaus,
this despite are better
than 100:1 advantage,
I recommend you heed my warning.
Impressive.
Well, I thought the situation
demanded something a little dramatic.
Who are you people?
I would say the better question--
Is: Who are you?
To a united front.
This act of yours,
the imitation of friendship--
Don't get me wrong.
You play the part well enough.
I should know, having
played it myself,
but there was a time
when the affinity
between us was quite real.
Oh, sure, and then you
got it in your head
to take what I created.
When I picked up that coin,
I swore loyalty,
Klaus, not friendship.
All right.
I'm holding up my end.
The other one has to be earned.
Fair enough.
Then you should probably
know the whole story.
My decision was not
entirely my own.
If I didn't agree to
usurp your power,
the witches swore to
kill my unborn child.
At first, the promise
of an offspring
meant little to me,
but then I recalled my father,
how he held me in contempt
from the moment I was born.
As yours did with you.
I will not do to my child
what was done to me,
to us.
All this--the spying,
the manipulation--
That's just something
you were forced into.
Is that it?
And what now, you
feel kind of bad?
"Hey, buddy, it's
nothing personal."
Is that it?
I admit...
I was jealous.
I saw the empire you created
on your own without me.
I saw it, and I wanted it.
You're wrong, you know.
I didn't do it on my own.
I stood in the
shadow of my father
my entire human life, and
I never would've gotten
out from under it
if not for you.
You're the one who
taught me that a man
can't be defined by
anyone but himself.
So...what now?
This community
that you've built,
you have their respect,
their love.
I can rule them, but
I cannot win them,
not without you.
So rule with me side by side
as equals...
friends...
brothers...
Those werewolves you
ordered killed,
that's my family.
Not for long, Luv.
I mean, this so-called
family of yours,
they haven't done you
much good, have they?
You said it yourself.
They abandoned you,
left you on your own.
Now it's simply your
turn to do the same.
Maybe they had their reasons.
Yes. Well, I have reason,
too, little wolf.
If the werewolves are
dead, then the vampires
have less desire to kill you.
I am trying to keep you safe,
not that you appreciate the effort.
And as soon as I have this baby,
what happens to me then?
Right.
Well, lucky for me,
I have a little while
before I find out,
and in the meantime, I will find
a way to pay you back for this.
As long as I'm in the
family way, well,
you can't do a damn
thing about it.
What are you looking for?
My Violin.
I must've left it in the attic.
So just go get it.
I can't. It's not safe
for me out there.
Funny, I was under
the impression
everyone was afraid of you.
The witches are after me.
You mean, that
crazy witch Agnes?
Yeah. She tried to kill me, too.
The thing is, she's dead.
Elijah killed her.
But...
Agnes was the last living elder.
If she's dead, then I'm safe.
Marcel would've told me.
Maybe he didn't want to lose
his secret weapon
against the witches.
You're lying.
Why would I lie to you?
Because you want
something from me.
Everyone does.
Do I want something from you?
Yeah, Davina.
Actually, I do.
Thanks to your friend, Marcel,
most of my family is cursed.
They're stuck in their wolf
form except on a full moon.
Now, I'm smart enough to know
that every curse has a
loophole, and, well,
You're the strongest witch
i've ever heard of,
but I wouldn't lie to
you to get what I want.
I'd ask you.
I guess that's the difference
between Marcel and me.
Looking for something?
I figured with you vacating,
the attic would be a safe zone.
Found this there.
It was dangerous for you
to come back, Josh.
Yeah. Well, what are
friends for, or whatever?
Hey, what did Hayley want?
Do you trust her?
I don't know.
Why?
She told me about a
witch being killed,
An elder, but I don't know--
Oh, yeah. Crazy Agnes?
I heard about that.
Elijah went all
berserker on her crew.
I guess it was super gross,
just, like, heads and guts.
What?
You hate the witches.
Hayley was right.
Marcel is just using me.
Josh, I can't stay here.
I'm not gonna be their puppet.
You have to get me out of here.
Ok, but where else
are you gonna go?
I stink of the bog.
Serves you right for
your pathetic attempt
to undermine my rule.
Nik, listen.
When I order werewolves to
be hunted to extinction,
I expect you to stand aside
and let the blood flow.
How delightfully
democratic of you.
Do you recognize it?
Perhaps you don't.
It has been 1,000 years
since you last saw it
grace the hand of our mother.
The ring was in possession
of one of the very wolves
whose extinction
you just ordered.
So, naturally, I questioned him.
He spoke of a legend,
a legend wherein long ago,
a chief of theirs had
fathered a child
to a very powerful witch.
Their mythology further states
this child, a son, was
later transformed
into something this clan
had never before seen,
something werewolf and vampire.
Nik, we're trying
to make amends.
We found remnants
of your family,
the bloodline of
your true father,
and we saved them from
being slaughtered
at the hands of the
vampires you command.
Niklaus, your
ambitions have come
before this family
for far too long.
I beseech you, please come home.
What home,
this pathetic substitute?
You see, despite
all your doubts,
all you attempts to thwart me,
I've reclaimed our true home.
I took back the entire city.
You have the audacity to
boast of your victory
when the mother of your child
remains your prisoner?
It all comes down to the
pretty, little wolf,
doesn't it, brother?
Stop it, both of you.
Even if this is
what you say it is,
I have had enough of family
to last me a lifetime.
Why would I possibly
want any more?
Ah, good. You're awake.
I have a favor to ask.
I am saying prayers
for the dead.
I request a moratorium
on favors for the king.
Well, you'll like this one.
It involves helping people
who need protection.
And whom, may I ask, do
they need protection from?
Me.
You see, I recently
ordered the slaughter
of a group of vagabonds
out in the bayou.
Turns out, I may
have been too hasty.
Thing is, if the
vampires find out
I'm protecting them,
it won't sit well.
I think I can arrange
something...
on one condition.
For her own good,
I believe it is time
for my niece to leave town.
Oh, It's quite all right.
She knows
She does?
That you're vampires?
Don't worry. He's compelled me
to forget everything
as soon as I leave.
You are tenacious.
It's one of the things I
like most about you...
Klaus, you can't keep--
But you're looking for truths
you don't want to find.
Monsters better left as fiction.
It's time for you to leave
this place, Cami...
For your own good.
You are such a coward.
This isn't about me.
You have kept me here for weeks
just so someone, anyone,
would see who you really
are, and now that I have,
It scares the hell out
of you, doesn't it?
If you knew even a
fraction of who I am,
it would break you in two.
Then show me.
Niklaus!
It hurts. Aah! Aah!
He's a beast.
Elijah, hold him down.
Brother, please,
Don't let them do this to me.
Do it now, boy.
Now!
Help me.
Oh, my God.
No one should have to
experience things like that.
Knowing what you do
about this world
will only get you killed,
and I cannot allow that.
Leave New Orleans.
Forget everything you've
learned here today.
Forget me.
You have no reason to stay.
I have no reason to stay.
Look. Things are good with
your brother right now.
He wants to run things
with me as partners,
but if we keep meeting like
this behind his back--
You said it yourself,
whatever it takes to stay alive.
Oh, this is about survival, is it?
If you were this pathetic
a liar with my brother,
I'm surprised he hasn't
killed you already.
Come on, Rebekah.
The only reward anyone ever
gets from loving Niklaus
is suffering and death.
You're choosing him
over me, aren't you...
again.
Rebekah, I got people
to look out for...
and Klaus is offering
me a chance to do that.
With Davina working her
magic against the witches
and an original by my side,
that's not something I can
just turn my back on,
not even for you.
When you were reliving
history with my brother,
did you happen to revisit
what came next in 1919,
or have you forgotten
our little secret?
I know the words that will
make him hate you forever.
Remember that when you're
embracing your new family.
Are they--
They're safe...
All of them.
Thank you.
What you did, Elijah,
it means a lot.
You should keep this covered.
I will.
If any of the others saw this--
I promise.
I should go.
Right.
Haven't you had your fill
of telling me all the ways
I've disappointed you, Elijah?
Well, there is something important
we neglected to discuss.
I accused you of having ulterior
motives regarding the child.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
I imagine that must have
been hard for you to say.
You don't make it easy
to love you, brother.
And yet you're obstinate
in your desire to do so.
When you're ready,
should you be so inclined,
both you and Rebekah,
are welcome to join me here.
It is, after all,
our family home.
Cami, I need your help.
Marcel has been lying to me,
and I can't trust him anymore.
I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
Oh, you've been compelled.
Ok. What are you doing?
It's OK.
I can fix you.
I'm really sorry,
but this is gonna hurt.