♪ We face the music together ♪
♪ And throw our hats
in the ring ♪
♪ Facing all kinds of weather ♪
♪ And not afraid of anything ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When the sun comes up,
we'll be on our way ♪
♪ And we don't care
where we land ♪
♪ And the waves are high,
but we won't turn round ♪
♪ 'Cause your hand
is in my hand ♪
♪ And, oh-oh ♪
♪ You make me feel invincible ♪
♪ 'Cause it's you and me ♪
♪ Through the wind and hail ♪
♪ Setting sail into the world. ♪
♪ ♪
[tennis balls thwacking]
[horns honking]
SARAH:
I'm tired, I'm unhappy,
I don't see the point in this.
It's, uh, expensive,
it's time-consuming,
it's not working.
I mean, you wouldn't keep going
to a yoga class
if it was making you stiffer.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, my God.
Oh, come on,
it was a nervous laugh.
You know what?
I think it's over.
- I think I'm done with this.
- Fine.
That's it then. I'm done, too.
- So why don't we...
- SARAH: No.
[grunts]
[sighs]
[emotional music playing]
MORGAN FREEMAN:
From now on,
the couple has
but a single goal:
keeping their egg alive.
They've practiced this clumsy
ballet dozens of times,
if need be.
This couple's partnership
is now over.
The long march in vain.
With no reason to stay,
they will wander back
to the sea.
- [crying, sniffling]
- Other couples...
have lost their egg as well.
As for the others...
I'm just gonna go
and call the kids real quick.
The partnership
is about to change.
The exhausted female
must depart quickly.
She must eat soon,
or she will die.
Hey! You okay?
You missed, like,
the last 20 minutes.
- Oh...
- The snow was black
with all their shits at the end.
Yeah, I just thought
it was kind of...
I really didn't want to...
Oh, no, there was
a happy ending.
Oh. Oh, good.
Yeah, but even when it was sad,
you were like,
"Oh, bet it stinks there."
Oh, you want to go?
Yeah.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Is that what we are?
- Is what what we are?
Like a penguin couple?
[chuckles]
Like, together to keep
our kids alive?
What? No, we're...
You didn't even see the ending.
Listen, I-I-I just keep
getting this feeling
that when they leave, you know,
like, when the kids are gone,
that... we're done.
Well, that's a shitty thing
to say.
No, it's not. It's not
a shitty thing to say.
It's a totally reasonable
thing to say.
What if we don't have enough
in common anymore
to fill the many, many, many
days and nights,
many nights,
that we will be together,
just us, just the two of us,
when there's
no more kids around?
Well...
we'll go on a cruise
or something.
We'll go on a 40-year cruise?
[laughs] Yeah, why not?
Okay. What will we talk about?
What?
He's an actor,
so he is inherently
self-involved and childlike.
And when he works,
he has everything done for him.
I mean, he's driven around,
he has his hair brushed,
and they bring him breakfast and
snacks and lunch and more snacks
and then they bring him dinner,
and-and if he's cold,
they wrap a coat around him
and bring him a hot snack.
She makes it sound like...
[laughs]
You know, first of all,
this is not something
you ever stop appreciating,
by the way,
and then they do all that stuff
because you're on set.
You can't go home
and make your own lunch.
And they brush your hair
because it's someone's job
to brush your hair.
Jesus Christ, it's insane
that I have to justify this.
Why are you getting
all worked up?
Well, because,
what do you want me to do?
Brush my own character's hair?
"Hi, I'm sorry,
"you mind if I brush my own hair
even though it's your job
because I don't want
to upset my wife?"
Okay, it doesn't upset me.
I'm just pointing out
that your life
has privilege in it.
You know, you are used to people
asking you what you want
and then giving it to you,
and you're emotionally and
mentally stunted because of it.
Why? What do you want me to do?
Nothing.
What about when Dennis
isn't working?
- I take care of the kids.
- That's true.
He does take care of the kids.
He's very good with the kids.
Well, maybe you should
take the...
But also, when he's not working,
he's needy and
full of self-doubt and bored.
I don't think
that's fair or true.
Okay, and-and even if
it's a little true,
I don't think it interferes
with how I am with my family.
- I didn't say it interferes.
- A-And when I'm between jobs,
she loads me up, like she wants
to make absolutely sure
that I do my part. You know,
which I would do anyway.
I-I'm very, very aware that
when I'm working, I'm gone,
I'm not present, I know that,
but it's like
she keeps a mental list
- of all the days and hours...
- Um...
and minutes I'm away and then
she checks off each task
and she times it and measures it
against the time I'm away
until it's even.
It's never even.
Do you make time
for one another?
In what way?
Do you have date night,
for example?
- Yes. Yeah.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah.
- What do you do?
- This.
This is date night?
Yeah, because we grab
a movie afterward.
- Yeah.
- Sometimes.
I mean, if, you know,
if we're not too tired.
So maybe you could do something
that isn't therapy.
Something fun, easy.
It could be a day thing.
You know, uh,
a shared common ground.
[Dennis sighs]
- Can you suggest something?
- Well,
some couples I work with
enjoy a drawing class,
- for example.
- Oh, yeah, I don't know.
I wouldn't want to, um, I mean,
do you mean life drawing, naked?
Because I don't know,
that would just be...
It doesn't have to be
life drawing. It could be fruit,
it could be bottlescapes,
I mean...
Let me think...
I had some clients
who took dancing classes.
- I mean, they learned how to dance.
- Jesus Christ,
- that'd be a little cheesy.
- Oh, that could be kind of fun.
Do you have any hobbies
that can be shared?
- I play tennis.
- Uh, food, cooking.
- [laughs]
- What?
Your hobby is not cooking.
No, he doesn't need a hobby
because his job is his hobby.
Well, if Dennis says his hobby
is cooking, then...
- It's not.
- F...
Cooking is my hobby, Sarah.
Fine. My hobby's
using the toilet.
Nice.
Make time for one other.
Do something together, anything.
[taking deep breath]:
Okay.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Okay, don't do that.
Don't do what?
Don't win a point?
No, we haven't even
started a game.
No, don't whip it past me
so I can't possibly return it.
I-I just hit the ball. How do
I know whether you will or won't
- be able to return it?
- Oh, my God. All right.
Let's get a game going.
You serve first.
Okay, listen.
How about, if the ball bounces
twice, it's minus a point,
but if you hit it without
the ball bouncing at all,
you get an extra point.
First one to 20.
What? No. Let's just play
a regular game.
So how can I play
regular tennis fairly
if I don't know the rules?
Come on, this will be fun.
Dennis Tennis.
I don't want to play
I want to play regular tennis.
- Well, I'm just gonna lose.
- Who cares?
It's not about winning;
it's about playing.
Sure.
- Fine.
- [Sarah sighs]
Okay, why don't you try
to serve properly?
I think it's best if we at least
try to play properly.
Yeah, I think the rules just get
in the way of the fun.
No, it's fun when you play
by the rules
because then you're
really playing.
Yeah, well, you're-you're not
really playing if your opponent
is telling you how hard
you can hit the ball.
- Oh, my God. All right.
- And I doubt that Billie Jean King
ever, uh, told, whoever... what's
her face... Christie Evans,
to go easy on her.
[grunts]
DENNIS [laughing]:
Yeah!
Come on, give me your best shot.
What?
Where you going?
Sarah, where you going?
Home.
And it's Chris Evert.
Chris Evert!
Christie Evans isn't anyone,
you moron.
Well, uh, I'm sure
she is someone, actually.
- Sarah!
- [Sarah groans]
Why couldn't we have just
done the dancing thing?
What is so awful about
learning to dance with me?
[weak gasp]
Let me have your attention
for a moment.
So you're talking about what?
You're talking about...
Ha-Hang on a second.
Are you gonna smoke
in this thing?
Oh, they're-they're gonna get us
fake things.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You know.
Yeah, I know those.
- Okay. Okay, go ahead.
- Okay.
Bitching about that deal
you shot,
- how some son of a bitch don't wanna buy...
- NANCY: Bitch.
- Son of a bitch. Bitching.
- Shh. Shh.
Somebody that doesn't want
to buy what you're selling.
Some broad you're trying
to screw.
[chuckling]:
Hang on. This is good.
This is, like, really good.
But you're playing, like...
[groans]
A much older guy, right?
So, you know,
try and give your voice
a bit of depth.
You know what I mean?
Like, weight yourself.
- [sighs]
- What's that?
- What's that for?
- It's just drama group.
Well, it doesn't matter
if it's just drama group.
You're good.
Like, really good.
Uh, sorry. Go ahead.
Give it another shot.
Let me have your attention
for a moment.
'Cause you're talking
about what?
You're talking about...
talking about that bitch
you saw?
Some son of a bitch
who's trying to buy land?
Somebody that doesn't want
what you're selling?
Some broad you're trying
to screw?
Put that coffee down!
Coffee's for closers only.
You think I'm fuckin' with you?
I am not fuckin' with you.
[singing indistinctly]
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ There's a jungle cat
inside my door ♪
♪ That's how it's been ♪
♪ That's how it'll be. ♪
WOMAN [on TV]: Okay,
I have all my herbs here.
- [door opens] - And I'm gonna
just pick through and...
[Dennis sighs, shuts door]
Hopefully not get
any stems in there.
- That looks good.
- DENNIS: Hmm. Hey.
Okay, so...
- How was your screening?
- [TV volume lowers]
Uh, good. Yeah.
Good-good response.
Oh. What's this?
Oh, I don't know.
I fell asleep.
- [sighs]
- What time is it?
- Um, I don't know. 1:00, 1:30.
- Oh, my God.
How was the party?
It was fun. Yeah.
[TV droning]
- Who was there?
- Uh...
You know, you wouldn't know
any of 'em.
Usual crowd of assholes.
[chuckles]
But it was fun.
[siren wailing in distance]
I'm gonna get some water.
You want some water?
[Dennis grunts]
[footsteps departing]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- Out!
- That doesn't matter.
- You hit it.
- It does matter.
That's an instinct,
or a reflex or whatever.
You hit it a mile out.
No. Doesn't count.
Nice catch.
Two points.
Ah! Fuck!
- Ow.
[scoffs]
Out.
So, do you want to see a movie,
or are you too tired?
I'm a little tired
from last night, actually.
Oh, that's fine.
- You mind?
- MAN: Dennis!
Hey, man.
Who's that?
- [horn honking]
- DENNIS: Hey, hey. Hey, fellas.
- Hey, how you doing?
- How you doing? Great to see you.
Yeah, what's going on?
[indistinct conversation]
Over there, with my, uh, wife.
DENNIS:
Yeah. So, what's new?
[indistinct conversation]
Um, hanging out.
Kids are good.
- [tires screech]
- MAN: Really, lady?!
- [horns honking]
- All right. Fuck. Shit.
Goddamn it!
- [bicycle bell rings]
- Christ. -MAN: Yo!
- Fuck!
- DENNIS: Yeah, they're good.
- Everybody's good, you know.
- Awesome. Here we are.
- Yeah, so...
- Fantastic. -Hi.
- Hey.
- What's up?
Uh, we were, um... I'm...
Listen, man,
I'll love you and leave you.
Check in with you later,
next week.
- You gonna be around then?
- Yep.
And I'll see you
at that opening on Friday.
- Right. Right, right, right, right. Right, okay.
- Friday?
Um, uh, see you later, man.
- Definitely.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah.
- Give my best to Gio.
- Will do.
- Great to see you. Be well.
All right. Okay. Bye.
That was humiliating.
- What? Why?
- Why? You didn't introduce me.
You left me on the other side...
I mean, what the fuck?
- Are you ashamed of me?
- What? No.
I didn't remember
the guy's name,
so I couldn't introduce you.
I know the guy's name.
That was fucking Ted Allen.
Not him, the other guy.
I didn't remember
the other guy's name.
So what? Take the bullet.
Don't leave me standing there
like a spare prick
because you don't want
to ask some guy
to remind you of his name.
I mean, I would have liked
to meet Ted Allen.
You did meet him.
♪ ♪
That's you, Nancy.
Nice!
[Dennis groans]
15-40! Boom.
Okay, three points to anyone
who can hit it as high
as that light tower.
No. Let's just keep the game...
DENNIS:
Three points.
NANCY:
Dad!
Oh, shit.
Nancy, go get the ball.
You get the ball.
Come on.
Jack, go get the ball.
[scoffs]
I don't even want to play.
You've literally been doing
nothing this entire time.
- Just go get the ball.
- Go get the ball. You haven't moved.
- Shut your face.
- Hey, I don't like that.
- That's not nice.
- [grunts]
- Oh...
- SARAH: Are you all right?
Do I look all right?
She hit me in my penis.
- DENNIS: You all right?
- Nancy, that was not appropriate.
- All right?
- Why'd you hit him in the penis?
I didn't mean to hit him
in the penis.
I meant to hit him
in the balls.
- Okay, that's great.
- DENNIS: That's great.
- Could we go back to playing, please?
- That's nice.
Are you happy you derailed that?
That was an amazing
derailment, Dennis.
- JACK: Oh, yeah, that's really funny.
- NANCY: I know, it's so funny.
DENNIS:
Anyone else bored? I'm bored.
You're the only one that wants
to play the regular rules.
First, you hit the guy
in the penis,
and then you wouldn't
go get the ball.
SARAH: Okay,
could we stop saying "penis"
on the public court, please?
JACK: You can't close
the leads you're given,
you can't close shit.
You are shit.
So hit the bricks, pal,
and beat it,
'cause you are going out.
- The leads are weak.
- The leads are weak?
Fucking leads are weak?
You're weak.
I've been in this business
15 years.
- What's your name?
- Fuck you. That's my name.
You want to know why, mister?
'Cause you drove a Hyundai
to get here tonight.
I drove an $80,000 BMW.
That's my name.
And your name is "wanting."
You can't play this man's game.
You can't close 'em,
then go home
and tell your wife
your troubles.
Because only one thing counts
in life.
Getting them to sign
on the line which is dotted.
You hear me,
you fucking maggots?!
[audience laughing]
[cheers and applause]
[whoops]
[whistles]
[audience laughing]
I forgot that line, but...
- Nobody noticed.
- Yeah, but I froze.
Did you see?
It felt like 20 minutes.
- No, nobody noticed.
- I noticed.
- Except her.
- You were asleep, so shut your stupid face.
Well, you shouldn't have been
looking at who was sleeping.
You should have been looking
at the actors
- acting to you.
- She's right.
Yeah, well, you shouldn't have
been there anyway.
- SARAH: That's true.
- It's not for kids. -Well, anyway,
- it was so boring it made me fall asleep.
- Okay...
- Shut up.
- Sorry. -That's not true.
- You shut up.
- She was riveted.
- You were riveting.
- Sorry to... interrupt.
- That's okay.
- I saw you in the play earlier today.
You were very good.
- Oh, that's so sweet. Thank you.
- JACK: Thank you.
Could I get a photo?
Oh, uh, I don't think so,
but thank you.
Oh, no, not of him.
Of him.
- I'm sorry.
- Uh, oh.
I am a huge fan.
I loved The Breaking.
- Thank you.
- Are you gonna be making more of them?
Uh, no. I mean, yeah,
they're gonna make more,
but my character, uh,
the arc finished last season.
WOMAN: Oh, no. Why?
You and Alison, I mean, that is
actually the relationship
I found the most believable.
- You know, I couldn't agree with you more.
- I-I was so rooting for them.
DENNIS:
That was a good pairing.
And the audiences liked it.
But, you know,
Thomas's character, they had to
figure out a way for him
to get back in, and so...
WOMAN: What? We've seen it.
It's run its course.
I think the audience
wants something new.
I agree with you, you know?
What... So what was it like
to step into the whole...
What are you doing?
Sorry, I...
- We're having a family meal.
- DENNIS: Sarah.
- Sorry.
- No, don't be sorry. I'm sorry.
And-and you, why don't you say,
"I'm sorry, I'm with my family"?
It just takes a minute.
You're his exact fan base,
by the way.
Normally, he's embarrassed that
all his fans are single women
over 50,
but nobody's stopped him
in a while,
so he's taking what he can get.
I-I'm sorry.
Okay, well, you know what?
Let's go.
- Wait, we're going? I don't...
- Yeah, we're gonna go.
Um, come on.
Come on, Jack.
[quietly]:
I'm sorry.
I'm married.
I'm 47.
♪ ♪
- I think it's over. I think I'm done with this.
- DENNIS: Fine.
That's it, then. I'm done, too.
Ow.
[Sarah groans]
[sighs]
- SARAH: Can I just...?
- Oh, sure.
So, what happens now?
I don't know.
We go home, I guess?
Thing is, I'm kind of hungry.
Wouldn't mind eating.
Well, let's get
something to eat.
I really thought we'd get
to the end somehow, right?
I mean, I really did,
but I hate
who I am with you now.
I catch myself sometimes
looking at you,
and I'm just waiting
for you to fuck up.
It's just...
It just seems easier to be you.
And... I envy you.
I, I envy your life
and how you get to be.
It just looks
like a lot more fun.
I know there's things that you
worry about, too, but...
they seem like small things,
and I get to carry around
all the big heavy shit,
and you just let me do it.
You just let me take that role
because I'm good at it.
Maybe I don't want to be
good at it, you know?
Maybe I never wanted that role.
Maybe you never
cared enough about me
to stop and ask me
if I wanted it.
I think you push me away.
I think you've always
pushed me away
from your life
and the fun stuff and...
Like, you never ask me to come
out with you to your parties
or premieres or...
like I wouldn't like it,
like, "Oh, I hate those people
'cause they're such assholes"
and I'm so sensible."
I think you tried to separate me
from the fun stuff in your life
because you knew
if you saw me there,
if you saw me in it,
you would realize
that that's where I should be.
And then you'd have
to feel bad about it.
You made it impossible for me to
be a part of your life, Dennis,
so don't act surprised
when I say
that we have nothing in common,
because you engineered that.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
If I could go back and change
any of that, I would, but...
but I can't.
But you're right.
You're right, and I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm an idiot.
I'm like a child.
A-And, and, you know,
if I'm not careful,
I'm about five years away
from being tragic.
I really don't want to be that.
How was the soup?
I, uh, didn't even taste it.
I don't know. Uh, hot?
[laughs]
I-I think I'm,
I'm gonna get something.
What can I get you guys tonight?
Um, can I have a burger, please?
You like it medium,
salad instead of fries, right?
Yeah, no, um, yes, medium,
but, uh, I'll have the fries.
Fries...
Where's the kids tonight?
- At home.
- I like those guys.
Thank you. That's very sweet.
No, really, I like them.
Don't like many kids,
but I like those two.
[laughs]
You don't believe her?
- No. Somebody else's kids.
- [laughs]
- DENNIS: Well, I like them.
- [Sarah laughs]
[conversation continues
indistinctly]
♪ ♪
- Yes?
- Bye, Mom.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Call me when you get there,
college boy.
- [laughs]: Okay. Call me up every day.
- Yeah. I will.
- Bye, kid. I'll miss you.
- NANCY: I'm taking your PlayStation.
No, you won't. Touch any
of my stuff, and you're dead.
All right.
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking indistinctly]
NANCY:
No, she said I could have it.
You're gonna be in college.
She said I could have
your PlayStation, your Wii
and your room for four years.
I know your password.
[car doors close]
♪ ♪
[groans]:
Oh... Shit.
♪ So here we go again... ♪
- All right.
- Get right to it?
- Yeah. Let's do it.
- All right.
♪ Backwards and forwards
and forwards and backwards ♪
♪ You can say anything,
just don't say that word ♪
♪ Play up and play the game ♪
- ♪ Changing to stay the same... ♪
- Ooh...
- [chuckles]: Sorry. Sorry.
- No, that was nice.
Good. 15-love.
All right.
♪ All this remembering,
we're none the wiser ♪
♪ It's time to let go and say ♪
♪ Don't mention the war ♪
♪ Don't talk of those days... ♪
- [groans]: Oh...
- Sorry.
[laughs]:
No, no. That was a good shot.
♪ Don't mention the war ♪
♪ Let history lie ♪
♪ Kiss the old days goodbye ♪
♪ They're no help anymore ♪
♪ Don't mention the war... ♪
SARAH:
Oy.
What time is it?
Uh, ten to 6:00.
[exhales]
Want to keep playing?
Yes.
Your serve.
Five-four.
For the match?
♪ Don't mention the war ♪
♪ Don't talk of those days... ♪
- DENNIS: Wow. That was good.
- Yeah.
SARAH:
That was good.
♪ What good is it for? ♪
♪ Don't mention the war ♪
♪ Let history lie ♪
♪ Kiss the old days goodbye ♪
♪ They're no help anymore ♪
♪ No, don't mention the war ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Don't mention the war ♪
♪ Don't talk of those days ♪
♪ What good is it for? ♪