gaby found a new calling...
yes, i'm unbelievable.
close your mouths.
someone new moved in...
(lette) he's a bachelor who
lives with his invalid sister.
but lynette found
a dark secret...
(lynette) our neighbor
is a pedophile.
you can't sit on this,
lynette.
orson's mother
revealed his past...
he cheated on alma,
broke her heart
for his precious monique.
monique polier?
and the police couldn't find
the evidence...
we couldn't find a toolbox.
(man) the man's a plumber.
until mike tried to hide it.
i'll take those.
(mary alice)
the annual block party
was a winter tradition
on wisteria lane.
it was a way for the residents
to spread holiday cheer.
everyone was invited...
including art shepard,
the newest resident
of wisteria lane.
but as the big night
drew near,
more than holiday cheer
was being spread around.
hey, did you hear about
the new guy that just moved in?
unh-unh.
well,
get a load of this...
apparently, the perv's
got all this weird stuff
in his basement.
no, seriously.
it's like this
big kiddie trap full of toys.
by sunday evening,
most of the gossiping
had subsided,
and the neighborhood
was once again
consumed by
the spirit of the season.
friends laughed over eggnog,
lovers kissed under mistletoe
and the mood was jolly.
that is,
until a certain guest
made his appearance.
(deep voice) ho, ho, ho!
look who's here!
merry christmas, everybody!
merry christmas!
now, kids,
who's been good this year?
(chuckles) oh, come on,
everybody was naughty?
what am i gonna do with
this fire truck?
joey, get back here.
what's going on?
(normal voice)
i'm not sure.
(woman) let's go, girls.
art, maybe we should go.
yes, for the residents
of wisteria lane,
it was the most wonderful time
of the year.
but for arthur shepard
and his sister,
it had turned t to be
a very silent night.
for the residents
of wisteria lane,
the holiday season
could only begin
once the decorations
came out.
for some, that meant
pulling out the colored lights.
for others, it meant
locating that holiday wreath.
and then there were those
eager to display
their nativity scene.
but for a romantic few,
it was all about
the mistletoe.
oh!
you have to kiss me.
it's the law.
(chuckles)
mmm.
while you're in
a good mood,
i thought
i'd spring something on you.
my parents
are coming to town.
your parents? really?
and i wondered
if you might be free
to join us
for dinner saturday.
absolutely. uh, so i assume
this means they know about me?
but of course.
and they know
about me as in...
(british accent)
"mum, dad, bloody good ns.
i've got melf
a smashing new girlfriend."
(laughs) that's adorable.
please don't do it
in front of them.
(normal voice) right.
so, um, do you want me
to make reservations
at that little french place?
we--we could do that,
but it's a--
it's a 4-hour layover
and they're
going to be exhausted,
and i thought we might have
a more enjoyable time
if they came here and--and you
made dinner for them.
okay, i guess it's time
we have the conversation.
ian...
haven't you ever wondered
why i've never cooked for you?
?????
no, i wish.
my cooking...
is not good.
well, my parents won't
be expecting a gourmet meal.
will they be expecting
stomach cramps,
acid reflux, night sweats?
(laughs) come on,
you can't be that bad.
oh. oh,
it is really important
that i make them
a home-cooked meal?
well, it's just that
they're very old-fashioned
hearth-and-home types,
and they might wonder why--
why you didn't make the effort.
oh, but it's okay. you--you--
you'll win them over...
eventually.
okay, i'll give it a shot.
(laughs)
thank you.
now nothing elaborate.
just a simple roast
and, uh,
and something appropriate
to go with it.
right...
like an ambulance.
**
no, amy, small steps.
small!
little miss snowflake glides.
she doesn't stomp.
is that better?
getting there, sweetie.
(under breath)
if she was a horse,
we'd have to shoot her.
(under breath) poor thing,
she tries so hard.
(normal voice) yeah, she's
a trooper. let's dump her.
(normal voice) what?! why?
pageant consultants are judged
on the strength of their roster.
you know,
we can't afford to bounce
every nose-picking
no-talent,
but we can definitely lose
the one
who's dragging us down,
and that's amy.
(under breath) we can't do that!
her mother died last year.
yes, i know, i know,
and it's tragic,
but we are running a business.
amy is sucking up
all of our time,
and we should be
focusing on sherri.
she actually has
a shot at winning.
how will i tell her family?
we'll do it together.
we'll be very diplomatic.
are you sure about this?
the poor kid's been through
the wringer and--
amy! for god sakes,
little miss snowflake
does not scratch down there!
(sighs)
well, then again,
her mother died a year ago.
how long
is she gonna milk it?
ahh... mother hodge,
i have your breakfast.
just put it over there.
i'll pick through it later.
(gloria) merry christmas.
(alma speaking indistinctly)
what are you watching?
home movies.
aw. it's fun looking back
at the past, isn't it?
well, it's one way to kill time
while you're waiting for death.
we also have cable.
have you decided what
you're gonna do about orson?
decided?
yes. have you
called a lawyer yet?
i don't think
that's any of your concern.
i don't mean to pry,
but i think
you're a good christian woman,
and you deserve better
than my son.
well, i will take that
under advisement.
if you give him a chance,
he'll draw you back in.
it's whahe does.
just walk away.
it's not that easy.
i love him.
you'll get over it. i did.
(alma) oh, hi!
(gloria laughs)
mwah!
(women chuckle)
oh!
merry christmas!
(alma) oh, wait.
wait, wait, wait, wait.
okay.
well, believe merita,
he scares me, too.
you know what?
we should have a meeting,
get all the moms together
and figure out
what to do about this guy.
yeah, saturday, your house.
sounds good.
(pounding on car)
(pounding)
hey, rita, i gotta go.
sorry, i can't talk now.
i have somewhere to go.
well, my brother doesn't.
the youth center just fired him.
are you happy?
i'm not sad.
he shouldn't be around kids.
i saw those pictures.
those boys
were on his swim team.
he was proud of them.
turning that
into something dirty
says more about you
than him.
you can defend him all you want.
i know what i know.
ar engine starts)
did you know
my brother got spit on
athe hardware store
yesterday,
that they refused
to serve us at the diner,
that our tire got slashed
at the church parking lot?
(exhales deeply)
i am not a well woman.
i don't need this stress.
well...
i am sorry that happened.
have you considered
even for a moment
that you could be wrong,
that you misinterpreted
what you saw,
that you are ruining
my brother's life and mine
over nothing?
i have kids, okay?
better safe than sorry.
so i'm cooking dinner
for ian's parents
tomorrow night,
and it's the first time
i'm meeting them,
so i sort of
wanna impress them.
and yet you're cooking?!
well, that's the thing.
uh, so i was hoping--you know,
if you're not too busy...
oh, no, no, these things
practically build themselves.
thank you.
you are a lifesaver.
actually...
i could probably use
the distraction.
oh?
(sighs) i asked orson
to move out last night.
oh, come on! why would you
bury your toolbox in the woods?
i knew the cops were
looking for it, and i panicked.
i was just trying
to buy myself me time.
well, you may have
bought yourself 20 to life!
oh, let the guy
enjoy his breakfast.
stay out of this, carlos.
mike, i want you
to look at me.
yeah, you look me in the eye
and you swear to me
that you
didn't kill anybody.
how many times do i have
to tell you? i can't remember.
you can't remember,
or you don't wanna remember?
um, guys.
bree, you have got to go
to the police with all of this.
i can't. not yet.
i-i need some time to think.
his wife goes missing,
then his mistress turns up dead.
what is there
to think about?
(bree sighs)
i know it sounds suspicious,
but in my heart of hearts,
i just can't believe that
orson could do such a thing.
sweetie,
we all wanna believe
the best of the people
we care about,
but you cannot
let your feelings for a man
blind you
to cold hard facts.
what in the world?
oh, my god!
what's going on?
they just arrested mike
for murder.
what?!
they're saying he killed
that woman othe news,
that monique person.
oh, thank god!
i can't believe we're gonna
break that little girl's heart.
do not
wimp out on me here.
we gotta do
what's best for the business.
what if the father
yells at me?
then i will jump in
and defend you.
okay, but if you do,
try and be diplomatic.
i'm always diplomatic.
now just get in there,
you spineless 'mo.
excuse me, mr. pearce?
i'm so glad
you could come today.
this is
my partner gabrielle.
pleasure to meet you.
(laughs)
(vern) shall we?
so, uh, what did you
wanna talk to me about?
is there a problem
with amy?
not a problem, per se.
we're just
a little concerned
that she might not
have the, um...
temperament
for pageant competitions.
and what does that mean?
well, when it comes
to performing,
she's not exactly...
well, she tends to be--
feel free to jump in.
i have no idea
where you're going with this.
well,
as gaby and i discussed,
amy has certain limitations
and her odds of winning
are slim.
vern!
(scoffs)
he is so competitive.
i constantly have to remind him
they're just kids. (chuckles)
when did you lose the joy?
oh, i think you know.
wait, i'm--i'm confused.
are you--are you dumping amy?
of course not, bill.
can i call you bill?
(chuckles) it's just,
we feel that amy would benefit
from some private coaching.
maybe i could
come to your house?
say, friday, 5:00?
sure.
(laughs) yeah, i guess.
great! it's a date.
(laughs)
maybe i should come, too.
after the harsh things
you said about amy?
i don't think so. (laughs)
i'm gonna need
a good lawyer
and that may take
a lile research.
uh-huh.
and whoever takes my case
will need a retainer,
so if you don't mind,
i promise i'll pay you back.
oh, okay.
and makeure
he knows about my wrench.
apparently, they tested it ??????
what's wrong?
i don't know if you
picked up on this, mike,
but...
i haven't been happy.
no, i didn't
pick up on it.
well, i wanted
to tell you this weeks ago
and i wish that i had,
because now i know
you're gonna think that
i'm breaking up with you
over this whole
blood on the ax thing.
wrench.
whatever. but believe me,
that's not it.
it's jus..
we are moving too fast.
what are you trying to say?
well, may--maybe
we should just... take a break.
you know...
date other people.
you're telling me this
on the day
i'm put in a men's prison?
well,
i said the timing was bad.
i am sorry.
i... i really am.
(whispers)
i just can't do this.
they told me
somebody was coming,
but i did not expect it
to be you.
is edie
getting you a good lawyer?
(chuckles) i doubt it.
she dumped me today.
what? why?
well,
i was arrested for murder.
still...
it's tacky.
(chuckles)
well, okay then, uh...
i-i'll help get you out.
uh... what's your bail?
a million dollars.
oh. (laughs)
you don't
have to help me, susan.
i want to.
aren't you gonna ask?
what?
if i killed that woman?
i don't have to.
i know you didn't.
i wish i was that sure.
i... i have these flashes
where i see her face,
so i must've known her.
and if i did,
maybe something happened.
maybe i got angry, maybe--
there's an explanation f this,
and we're gonna figure it out.
n't worry about a thing.
miss gabrielle!
when are you gonna
come outside and watch me?
oh, um, the grass, honey,
and my allergies...
go ahead and practice.
i'll watch you from here.
are you sure
i can't help with anything?
ah, i've been a single dad
for a while now.
i got
the nner thing down.
mmm, i've got
the restaurant thing down.
i can't bring myself
to cook for one.
not that i ever
cooked for two. (chuckles)
well, no restaurant tonight.
you are having dinner with us.
oh, that's sweet.
it's the least i can do
to thank you for helping amy.
oh. it's nothing.
yeah,
she's a special girl.
so...
how is it for you,
being single again?
oh, honestly? um...
mm-hmm.
i hate it. it's like
i've forgotten how to date.
me, too. you know,
i even let a friend of mine
talk me into one of
those speed dating things.
how was it?
mmm, i didn't even go in.
i just sat
in this hotel lobby.
i watched all these
lonely, desperate
single people filing in,
and then it hit me--
i'm one of them.
i know what you mean.
did you see that?
it spun three times
and then i caught it.
um...
you didn't see.
yeah, i-i'm sorry, sweetie.
i-i was distracting gabrielle.
oh, no, no,
it's totally my fault.
i'm sorry, sweetie.
go outside and do it again.
i promise this time
we're gonna watch.
(knock on door)
come in.
(door closes)
hey. wow, oh,
those are gorgeous.
well, i, uh, i figured
you'd be too busy cooking
to manage a centerpiece.
well, you, uh,
you may not be a good cook
but you're--
you're certainly a tidy one.
don't worry.
dinner's all taken care of.
we're having...
blanquette de veau
and a grand marnier soufflé.
well, that's
very ambitious of you,
and, uh, when will bree
be done making it?
5:30. (chuckles)
but i am rewarming it
all by myself.
oh, what's, uh,
what's all this?
um, mike was
arrest for murder.
my god.
i-i mean, of course
he's totally innocent.
i'm just trying
to help him find a lawyer.
oh. shouldn't, um, shouldn't
his girlfriend be doing that?
yeah. edie dumped him.
hmm.
okay, i know how this looks,
but i just feel bad.
he's just a friend now.
(sighs) yes. yes, a friend
you sat by for six months,
hoping he'd wake up
and ravish you again.
you are the only one
allowed to ravish me these days,
so stop worrying.
(lowered voice) orson,
it's me again. please call.
we need to talk.
(sighs)
i'll do the chips.
you deal.
you got it.
guys, why has it been so long
since we've played poker?
i really need this.
oh, me, too.
there's nothing more relaxing
than an afternoon
of finger food and girl talk.
hi, ladies!
(lynette)
hey! how you doing?
(sighs) so did you
tell the police
that you think
orson killed monique?
what?!
no, i did not,
and i don't plan to.
but mike is in jail,
and you said yourself
you thought orson did it.
i said i had concerns,
concerns that have disappeared
now that mike has been arrested.
what are you saying?
you think mike is guilty?
hey, why don't we start
that girl talk?
i'll get the ball rolling.
anybody have a yeastnfection?
they found monique's blood
on the wrench
that mike
was trying to dispose of.
i mean, that hardly screams
innocence.
her teeth were pulled.
you don't think
that's worth telling the cops
she was messing around
with a dentist?
orson was slipping it
to the dead chick?
mike is innocent.
i know that in my heart.
we all have
convictions, susan.
i believe mike's last one
was for manslaughter.
okay, okay, we've all made
some excellent points
and blown off
a little steam.
whoo!
let's play some cards.
if you're so sure
that orson is innocent,
why don't we go through
his things? where's his desk?
at his office.
and what did you think
you'd find there anyway?
i don't know.
a blackmail letter,
a necklace made of teeth?
we're not gonna play cards,
are we?
nope.
well, i am certainly not
playing with a woman
that is willing to let mike take
the fall for her psycho husband.
well, needless to say,
i won't be cooking dinner
for ian's parents.
fine. i'll cook myself.
good. let me know
if there are any survivors.
and if you take orson back,
you do the same.
(exhales deeply)
(bree) well, that was
incredibly awkward.
i'm sorry you both
had to sit through it.
was it me?
was i out of line?
hey, come on in.
you're just in time.
thanks so much, rita.
i think
it's such a good idea
that we all get together
and talk and...
wow. wow.
what is all this?
oh, we decided
to stage a protest
in front of art's house.
a protest?
mm-hmm.
rita, i want the word
"pedophile" to really stand out.
do we have any glitter?
say "molester."
it sounds scarier.
i'm sorry.
i-i-i thought we were
all gonna talk about
how to keep an eye
on this guy.
we're past talking.
the guy's a menace.
well, that's what we think,
but we don't exactly have proof.
the youth center just fired him.
how much proof to you need?
but, see,
the only reason they fired him
is because
people were gossiping,
and the only reason
they're gossipg
is because
of what i told mrs. mccluskey.
yeah, and you told me
to spread the word.
so--so that people could watch
their kids and be vigilant.
so you wanna wait
until he actually molests
one of our kids?
whose side are you on,
lynette?
knock it off, gert.
remember,
if it weren't for lynette,
we never would've found out
about this cre.
she's our hero.
(door opens)
(door closes)
(susan sighs)
(man) ...the 22-yard line,
the give is to harrison,
who is hit immediately
and dropped for a loss
in his own backfield...
(amy) bye-bye, daddy.
(bill) see you, sweetie.
have fun. mwah.
so i was, uh,
i was thinking you--
you wanna grab a cup of coffee
or something after class?
i'd love to grab
a cup of coffee...
or something. (laughs)
(sighs) amy, you are so lucky
to have such a nice dad.
yeah, i know.
leave him alone.
excuse me?
you heard me.
i don't want you dating him.
oh, sweetheart.
i have a feeling
i know what this is about.
no u don"t
i think you do
miss your mommy,
and it feels funny
seeing your daddy
be nice to somebody else.
but believe me, i'm not trying
to replace your mom.
well, i am,
and i have someone
all picked out.
what?
i want my dad
to marry sherri's mom.
sherri from class?
we're best friends,
and we have it all planned out.
our parents
are gonna get married,
and then
we'll be real sisters.
what about your dad?
???
my mom died.
all my dad wants
is for me to be happy.
now get in there and teach me
how to work the runway.
that's what
we're paying you for, right?
(man) ...runs it left,
swings it around.
he fights his way to the 25
for another first down,
and that should
just about do it.
i tell you, with 1:12
left on the clock
and no time-outs remaining...
(turns off television)
(orson sighs)
(bree) orson?
(orson) bree?
orson. why haven't you
returned any of my calls?
i was afraid you were calling
to ask me for a divorce.
(sighs) no, i wasn't.
they arrested mike
for the murder
of monique polier.
they did?
the other night,
you wanted a chance
to explain everything.
well, here it is,
and i want it all.
if i find out
you've left anything out,
then i will ask
for that divorce.
okay.
(sighs)
you're working
so hard, sherri.
you must really wanna
win this pageant.
more than anything.
aw. well, i think dedication
should be rewarded,
so i have
a little surprise for you.
what is it?
well, you know how the pageant starts with
a big opening number?
this year, all the contestants
are gonna dance in pairs,
and i've arranged
for yoto dance with
your best friend amy!
what's wrong, sweetie?
well...
amy sucks.
well, i thought you two
were practically sisters?
we are...
but she still sucks.
and first impressions
are everything.
you said so yourself.
well, that's true--
and this is
the opening number.
if the judges see me
tripping all over that klutz,
there's no way
i'm gonna win.
that's a good point.
now i wish i hadn't told amy.
you already told her?!
she was so excited.
(sighs)
well,
she's your best friend.
why don't you just tell her
the truth? she'll understand.
what if she doesn't?
well, friends come and go...
but a crown is forever.
i never loved alma.
my mother
pushed us together,
and... i was stupid enough
to get her pregnant.
you had a child?
alma miscarried
a month after the wedding.
i was trapped.
well,
you could've left her.
mother wouldn't hear of it.
divorce is a sin.
so i stayedin the marriage,
hoping i would come to feel
what i was supposed to,
but i never did.
so i resigned myself
to a life without love.
and then i met monique.
it was wrong. i didn't care.
i loved her more than
i'd loved anyone...
till you.
so why couldn't you
tell me this?
because you told me
about rex,
how he cheated on you,
how hurt you were.
bree, i needed you
to feel safe with me.
(bree) well, you haven't done
a very good job.
handling the truth would have
been a hundred times easier
than dealing with
all the doubt and suspicion.
(orson speaking indistinctly)
so you stayed in a loveless
marriage because of your mother?
i know how it sounds.
but after my father died,
she s all i had.
his death caused me
so much pain.
(orson speaking indistinctly)
i would've
done anything for her.
(bree speaks indistinctly)
(orson speaks indistinctly)
she saw that weakness,
and she ran with it.
(orson speaking indistinctly)
you--you've got no idea
how manipulative she can be.
she ruins lives.
now i've told you
everything.
what happens now?
well...
first you pack up your things
and come home,
and then...
we toss your mother out
on her evil ass.
god, i love you.
hi!
i'm sorry i'm late.
where are your folks?
they're not coming.
their plane was snowed in
at o'hare.
oh. well, that's too bad.
well, no harm done then, huh?
you're 40 minutes late.
but they're not here.
you didn't know that.
and where's dinner?
uh... bree and i
sort of had a fight.
um... look, i'm awfuy sorry
that i'm late.
i-i had an emergency.
did this emergency
have anything to do with mike?
i'm pretty sure
that bree's husband
murdered the woman
the cops think mike killed.
i went to his office--
oh, for god sakes, susan.
no, no,
i found evidence. look.
orson was committed
to a mental institution
for over a year.
i mean, doesn't that suggest
he's some sort of--
i don't care!
tonight meant a great deal
to me, and you blew it off.
i said i was sorryian.
i have to help mike.
i'm all he's got.
actually, you're wrong.
he's got me.
what?
tomorrow, i'll hire the best
lawyer in town to defend him,
and i'll pay
every cent of his bill.
you would do that for mike?
yes, on one condition...
you can't see him anymore.
why?
if you start visiting him,
being a friend to him,
he'll fall in love
with you again.
then you'll have to decide whose
heart to break, his or mine.
as jealous ultimatums go,
that's very flattering,
but i don't think
that's necessary.
mike and i are done.
then you should have no problem
accepting my generous offer.
you would really get him
the best lawyer in town?
an absolute piranha.
do we have a deal?
well, okay then.
you know,
mike barely remembers me.
what makes you so sure
he would fall in love
with me again?
what a perfectly asinine
question.
how could he not?
(all shouting at once)
(shouting continues)
god, i was only
in the house 15 minutes.
are there more of them now?
yep.
(shouting continues)
go ahead, say it.
i know you want to.
this is all your fault.
you should've listened to me.
i know, but be fair.
there is no way
i could've anticipated this.
you tell people
frankenstein's on the loose,
then you're surprised to see
the torch-wielding villagers?
i'm putting the kids
to bed early.
i don't want 'em
to see this.
(siren wailing)
is that an ambulance?
(amy) i can't believe
you're doing this!
???
god, i hate you!
i hate you!
don't ever talk to me again!
hi. bill?
i was wondering, do you
have plans saturday night?
(crowd speaking indistinctly)
excuse me. i'm sorry.
what--excuse me, can you--
can you tell me what happened?
ma'am, i need you
to step back.
okay.
we're brinng in
a female, late 30s.
and get crash ca ready.
she's in cardiac arrest.
there he is.
(crowd speaking indistinctly)
(all shouting at once)
stop it! stop it!
you can't do this to people!
have you lost your minds?!
well, excuse us for wanting
to feel safe in our own homes.
well, that's my home,
and i don't feel
very safe right now.
please, please, all of you,
just leave this street.
please, i beg of you. go!
just get off my street, please!
wait, wait!
art, wait, i'm sor--
(shouting continues)
i'm sorry.
you're an idiot
to take him back.
i am no longer interested
in your opinion.
i thought
i made that clear.
where are you sending me?
oh, we've rented you
a condo
in a lovely
retirement community.
it's our christmas gift
to you.
so you're exiling me?
cutting me off
from my new grandcldren?
that's our gift to them.
you think you can
be rid of me that easily?
it's over, mother.
i told her everything.
oh, i doubt that very much.
you still have secrets, my boy.
so do you, mother,
and if you want them kept,
you'll keep mine.
it's me. i have some bad news.
she's taking him back.
meet me on the corner
in an hour.
we need to deal with this.
i heard about rebecca
on the news.
if there's anything
i can do to help,
i...
uh, with
the funeral arrangements
or, uh...
help you call relatives...
wow.
you must be feeling
really guilty.
oh! of course!
i-i-i feel just terrible.
i-i mean, if you knew,
if you could just know
i'm--how sorry i am.
hey.
you know, in a weird way...
i should thank you.
my sister was...
a really wonderful person.
she always saw
the best in me.
but there were things
she couldn't see...
or chose not to,
god love her.
what do you mean?
i think you know.
see, i always knew
that i had
to take care of rebecca,
so i could never
let myself...
slip and do something
that would hurt her.
but now...
(exhales deeply)
i'm free...
(whispers)
and all because of you.
you--you can't stay here.
oh, don't worry.
i'm already packed.
where are you going?
why, you gonna write?
well...
(sniffles)
good-bye, lynette.
you take care of that
beautiful family of yours.
there's a reason people
can't wait for christmas,
and it has little to do
with fily reunions...
or curling u
with a cup of eggnog...
???
or receiving a present
from that special someone.
??????????????????
????
??
???
?
??