5 Years Ago,
Susan Delfino Gave Birth To A Son
In Delivery Room A In Hospital.
Moments Later,
Lelar Dash Gave Birth To A
Daughter In Delivery Room B
Around 10 Ten At Next Morning,
As The Two New Mothers
Were Leaving The Hospital.
They Nearly Ran Into Each Other.
Of Course, They Never Knew This.
In Fact, Susan And Lelar Would
Have Been Surprised To Know
How Often Their Pasts
Would Cross Over The Years.
They Almost Met In
The Local Coffee Shop
And Another Time At
Their Veterinarian Office.
And Again In The Bleacher
Of Fairview Flyers.
But Despite These Close Calls,
Susan And Lelar Never Met.
Until One Tuesday,
When Susan Decided To Take Her
Husband To A Fancy Restaurant
For Their Anniversary.
At The Same Time,
Lelar Decided To Take Her
Daughter To Buy Some Ice-Cream.
That Was The Night That
Susan Delfino And Lelar Dash.
Finally, Ran Into Each Other.
Mike.
It Will Happen To
All Of Us Eventually.
The Moment Will Come
When We Ask Ourselves...
Where Did The Time Go?
How Did The Children
I Once Cradled...
Grow Up So Very Quickly?
How Did The Life I Dreamt Of...
Turn Into A Career I Never Expected?
And How Did That Woman I
Saw Each Day In The Mirror...
Become Someone I
Don'T Even Recognize?
Juanita, This Dress Is Awfully Tight.
I Don'T Think You Can Get Into It.
No, It'S Pretty. I Can Do It.
How'S That One Fit? Oh, I Think
We'Re Gonna Need The Next Size Up.
Uh, There Is No Next Size Up.
They Don'T Make Princess
Dresses For Girls Over 7.
She'S Only 4 1/2.
Look, My Daughter Was
Invited To A Princess Party,
So I Can'T Let Her
Be The Only Girl There
Without A Princess Dress.
Did You Try The Costume Section?
I Bet They'D Have A Mrs.
Shrek Dress That Would Fit Her.
Juanita, Take Off The
Dress! We'Re Going.
No! I Can Do It.
Look, I Feel For You.
My Niece Also Has A Weight Problem.
My Daughter Does Not
Have A Weight Problem
She Has A Little
Baby Fat, That'S All.
In Fact, The Only Problem She Has
Is This Store Being
Completely Unprepared
For A Perfectly
Average 4-Year-Old Girl.
Just Ring It Up.
No, No, No!
Oh, For God Sakes. What'S Wrong Now?
Once Again,
The Concept Is, Sweetie,
You'Re Taking The
Pie Out Of The Oven,
Your Face Aglow With Surprise.
Why Am I Surprised? Because
It Turned Out So Perfectly.
Well, That'S No Surprise.
My Pies Are Always Perfect.
All Right. It'S Your Best Pie Ever.
You'Ve Topped Yourself. Hmm?
Mm. And I Know This
Before I'Ve Tasted It?
Sweetie, Just Make
Whatever Face You Want.
I Just Think You'Ll
Sell More Cookbooks
If You Don'T Look Like
You Just Made Love To An Ice Cube.
Andrew, Dear, I'M Going
To Take A Little Break.
Would You Please Tell This Gentleman
That If He Calls Me
"Sweetie" One More Time,
I'M Gonna Grab His Camera
And Take Picture Of His Colon
You Got That, Right?
Katherine, Hi. What Are You Doing
Here? The Waiters Need To Be Paid,
And You Took The Key
To The Cashbox... Again.
Oh. Sorry. Paid For What? The
Armenian Wedding? Lunch For 300?
It Was Right After The
Breakfast For The Garden Club,
Which You Also Missed.
Look, I'M Sorry.
I Didn'T Know A Photo
Shoot Would Take This Long.
I Mean, Who Knew It'D Be This
Hard To Pose For A Book Cover?
Oh, You'Ll Be Fine.
If There'S One Thing
You'Re Really Good At,
It'S Posing As A
Chef. Okay, Katherine.
I Know This Book Has
Been Monopolizing My Time,
And You Feel Overworked
And Undervalued.
But I Do Appreciate You. In
Fact, I Have A Gift For You.
It'S The Galleys Of My New Book.
Read Page 2.
"For Katherine
Mayfair--
"A Wonderful Cook
And An Even Better Friend."
You Dedicated It To Me?
Well, You Make This All Possible.
It'S The Least I Could Do.
Ahem! Excuse Me.
Time Is Money. Chop-Chop, Sweetie.
Andrew... Do We Have A Backup Pie?
Yes. Yes, We Do.
Good.
And The Big Blind...
Catches A Jack On The River.
Preston?
Mom!
What The Hell'S Going
On Here? Don'T Freak Out.
We'Re Just Playing Cards. Oh,
Yeah? Why Didn'T You Play At Home?
Why Did You Have To Sneak In Here?
Tequila Shots! 5 Bucks!
Asked And Answered.
Okay, That'S It!
Everybody Out. Game'S Over.
Can I Have Your Chair For A Second?
Hey! Look Up Here!
Mom'S Here. Party'S Over.
Door'S Open. Out You Go. Go On. Shoo!
You Guys Have Pulled
A Lot Of Stupid Stunts.
But This?
This?
Risking Our Liquor
License, Our Livelihood?
Who'S Going To Find Out?
I Mean, We'Ve Been Running This
Game For A Month, And Nobody--
Unbelievable. You Guys
Are Grounded For Two Weeks.
But We Have Mecoming.
Yeah, Yeah! Keep Complaining.
I'D Love To Make It A Year.
Now Clean This Place Up. Now!
Wow. That Was Fantastic.
Amazing.
Whew. You Were Incredible.
So Were You.
Oh. And...
Time To Go.
Susan?
So It'S Been, What, Four Months?
Are You Ever Gonna
Let Me Spend The Night?
I Don'T Know. Come On, Zippy, Zippy.
Okay. It'S Just, You Know...
Girls Usually Beg Me
To Spend The Night.
Well, Good, Then You
Shouldn'T Have Any Problem
Finding A Place To Sleep.
Fine. I Know The Drill.
I Can'T Spend The Night.
I Can'T Meet Your Friends.
I Can'T Meet Your Son.
I'M Just Wondering--
Is This Ever Gonna Turn Into Something
Normal? You Know, You'Re A Guy,
And We Just Had Hot Sex,
And I Didn'T Force You To Cuddle.
So Run! Go! Brag To Your Friends.
Look...
I Like You, And I Know You Like Me.
So Why Can'T We Be A Couple?
'Cause I'M... Not Ready For That.
And What We'Ve Got--
That'S All I Can Handle.
Go.
Okay, But That'S
Only Gonna Work, Like,
500 Or 600 More Times.
Good Evening. Can I Help You?
Wrong Question. The
Question Is, Can I Help You?
Look, If You'Re Trying
To Sell Me Something,
I Don'T Have Any Money.
You Do Now.
I Don'T Understand.
I'M Here To Buy You
Out Of Your Lease.
What?
I Know. It'S Sudden.
But There'S Something
About This House That...
Well, It Just Feels Like Home To Me.
So I'D Like To Move In... Tonight.
Tonight? Areou Crazy?
A Little Bit.
Okay, Here.
I Will More Than Cover
Your Moving Expenses.
Look, Uh... I-I'M All Set Up Here.
Besides, My Landlady
Would Never Allow It.
Why Don'T You Let Me Worry About Her?
Mm, No. I-I Don'T Have
Anywhere Else To Go.
I Think You Should Leave.
Look, Raymond...
How Do You Know My Name?
I Made You A Very Generous Offer,
And I Just Know You'Re Going
To Make The Right Decision.
Five.
Five What? What Are
You Talking About?
Four.
Are You-- I
Don'T Understand.
Three. O-Okay. Hang On For A Second.
Two.
Well, Raymond, Thank You Very Much.
Here You Go. Take Care.
All Taken Care Of... Mrs. Williams.
Thank You... Mr. Williams.
The Next Morning,
Edie Britt Decided To Announce
Her Return To Wisteria Lane
In A Way... That Was Guaranteed...
To Make A Big Splash.
Okay, You'Re Not Gonna
Believe This, But...
She'S Back.
Edie? Is That Really You?
You Know Someone Else My
Age With A Body Like This?
So You'Re Back?
What Happened To Your Tenant?
He, Uh, Came Into Some
Money And Decided To Move.
We Thought, What The
Heck? Let'S Move Back!
"We"?
Oh, You Don'T Know.
I Have A Husband Now.
Really? Whose?
So I'M In Vegas Talking To
This Real Estate Convention.
I Do A Little Motivational Speaking.
And There-- Sixth
Row, Center Aisle,
Is The Most Beautiful
Woman I Have Ever Seen.
So After I Finish,
I Walk Into The Audience
And I Ask This Goddess Out.
His Seminar Was Called
"Getting What You Want,"
And He Did...
Three Times. Hmm. Before Dinner.
Well, It'S Certainly
Nice To Meet You, Dave,
And Let Us Be The First To
Welcome You To Wisteria Lane.
Oh, You Know What? We Should
Have A Dinner Or Something.
Oh, Let'S Make It A Party.
We Could Do It At My
Restaurant. We'D Be Honored
Thank You.
So, Gaby, I Have To Ask.
What The Hell Happened To
You? I Mean, Look At You.
Your--Your Clothes,
Your--Your Hair.
Carlos Might Be Blind, But The Rest
Of Us Aren'T. I Had Two Children.
For What? Breakfast?
Edie? On Your First Day
Back In The Neighborhood?
You'Re Right.
I'M Sorry, Gaby.
It Was Rude And Insensitive,
And It Won'T Happen Again.
Really?
Are You Okay.
Now Shouldn'T We Offer Your
Friends Something To Eat?
Ooh! I Baked Some Muffins.
Please Don'T Take This
The Wrong Way, But...
We Love You.
Mijita! Lunch Is Ready.
Go Get Your Sister.
Carlos, What'S With All The Cheese?
You Know How Juanita Feels
About Brussels Sprouts.
I'M Just Trying To Make Vegetables
More Fun. Well, Next Time,
Give Her A Carrot And Put
Her On A Roller Coaster.
Have You Tried To Lift Her Lately?
I Know She'S Gotten Chubby.
She'Ll Grow Out Of It
Ha! We Can Only Hope
With Your D.N.A. Running Through Her
Veins. Hey, I Do Not Have Fat D.N.A.
Oh, Don'T Make Me Pull Out
The Solis Family Photo Album.
It'S Like A Bunch Of Sea
Lions Posing On A Rock.
Well, I'M Sorry My
Relatives Don'T Measure Up To
Thgroup Of Stick-Thin
Drunks That You Come From.
All I'M Sang Is That Our
Daughter Has A Weight Problem,
And The Sooner We Admit It,
The Better. She'S Only 4.
But, You Know, You Want Her
To Develop A Weight Problem?
Go Ahead. Nag, Criticize,
Make Her Feel Self-Conscious.
See What Happens.
And Obviously I Am Not
Getting Through To The Twins,
Because No Matter What I Say,
They Keep Pulling This Crap,
And I Am Sick Of It.
Honey, Could You...
Sorry.
Yeah.  So You-- You
Want Me To Talk To Them?
You Have To. I Am Tired
Of Being The Bad Cop.
You Walk The Beat For A While.
Fine. You Know, Boys This Age,
They'Re More Likely To
Listen To Their Dads Anyway.
I-I Can Handle This.
I Really Appreciate It.
Honey, You Know What I'D
Appreciate? Could You...
Sorry.
So Kirby Has Aces
In The Hole... Yeah.
Whicmeans That Bobby
Will Have To Wear A Dress To
School On Monday. Oh! Oh, My! Okay.
You'Ve Got To Get A Picture Of That!
Tom? Can I Talk To You A Sec?
Yeah.
Don'T You Think
You Were Kind Of Sending
The Wrong Message In There?
I Know We Don'T Approve
Of What They Did,
But You--You
Gotta Admit.
Come On. Starting Their Own
Casino Is Kind Of Creative.
Yeah? "Creative" Like Selling
Fake I.D.S Was Creative.
And Hot-Wiring Mccluskey'S
Car-- That Was A Work Of Art.
Honey, Honey, This
Is Nothing Like That.
I Mean, Look, The Whole School
Is Talking About Their Card Game.
Do You Realize It Was, Like,
The Place To Be On A Monday Night?
Oh, My God.
What?
You Think They'Re Cool.
Well... Yeah.
No, I Mean You Think They'Re Cool
In That You Wanna
Be Them. Oh, Please.
You Do! This Is Tom,
Former High School Nerd,
Living Vicarusly Through
His Awesome-Ass Kids.
Hey, I Was Plenty
Cool In High School.
Are We Redefining "Cool"
To Include Playing Trombone
In The Marching Band?
You'Re Overreacting.
You'Re A Little High-Spirited,
But I Trust Them.
So I'Ve Decided To Unground
Them For The Homecoming Dance.
But I Told Them They Couldn'T Go.
And You Told Me To
Handle It, And I Just Did.
Oh, By The Way, It Wasn'T A Trombone.
It Was A Tuba.
Know Your Brass.
Juanita!
You Said I Could Have Cake.
I Know, But So Much?
You Could'Ve Gone Back
For A Second Piece.
This Is My Second Piece.
And It'S Not Juanita'S Fault.
In This Kind Of Situation,
I Blame The Parents.
Look, My Kid Would Eat Sugar
All Day Long If I Let Her.
Gaby'S Obviously One Of Those
Moms Who Just Can'T Say No.
It'S A Shame, Too. Juanita
Has Such A Pretty Face.
I'M Back.
You Want Something Cold?
Well, Actually,
I'M In The Mood For Something Hot.
You Know...
This Is Why It'S Taking Four Months
To Get My House Painted.
Haven'T You Ever
Heard That Expression,
"You Can Have It Done Fast,
Or You Can Have It Done Right"?
I Think I'Ll Have It Done Right Now.
Hey, Susan?
Mm. Uh, Lynette, It'S
Not Really A Good Time.
I Just Need Five Seconds
To Bitch About Tom,
And Then I'Ll--
Oh, My God.
Your Painter Isn'T Done Yet?
Yeah. He--He'S Hard
To Keep Track Of.
Well, Anyway, Tom
Refuses To Acknowledge
That The Twins Are Turning
Into Juvenile Delinquents.
Just The Other Day, I Was-- Oh,
You Poor Thing! You Need A Hug.
Have You Been Drinking?
Sorry To Have Barged In,
And Thanks For Letting
Me Get That Off My Chest.
Hey, Anytime That You Need To
Talk, You Just Ring My Bell...
And Wait.
Okay, New Rule.
From Now On, Sex Only Happens
In The Bedroom, Door Closed,
Between The Hours Of 7:00
And 10:00 P.M. You Know What?
It'D Be A Hell Of A Lot Easier
For Me To Follow The Rules
If I Knew Why They Existed. I
Just Don'T Want My Friends To Know.
Why? You--You
Ashamed Of Me?
No, Of Course Not.
It'S Just... Complicated.
I'M Just A Simple Guy,
So I Can'T Be Your
Dirty Little Secret.
I Need More From You.
I'M Sorry. I Can'T Give That To You.
Honey, I Know You Wanna Go
Home And Watch Your Cartoons,
But You Had A Lot Of Cake,
So I Was Thinking I'D
Take You To The Park.
That Way, You Could Run Around
And Get Some Nice, Fun Exercise.
No.
You Sure?
Running Around In
The Sun And Fresh Air
Would Make You Feel Good.
Mm... No.
Okay.
Why Don'T You Go Throw
That In The Trash?
And I'M Gonna Get The Car Started.
He Juanita.
You Wanna Play A New
Game On The Way Home?
Winner Gets A New Doll. Okay.
Well, Come On, Then!
Mommy, What Are You Doing?
It'S A New Game I Invented,
And You'Re Winning 1 To Nothing!
Katherine! Fantastic News.
"What'S Cookin' Fairview?"
Is Sending Out A Camera Crew Tomorrow
To Do A Piece On Me And The Book. Oh,
Which I Just Finished This Morning.
You Read It Ready? Yes.
I Couldn'T Put It Down.
But I Have To Tell You,
At Least A Dozen Recipes
Are Missing A Pretty
Crucial Ingredient.
Really?
What?
My Name.
Excuse Me? Bree, Your
Book Is Filled With Recipes
That We Developed Together,
And--And Some Of Them Are
Flat-Out Mine. Oh, Don'T Be Silly.
I May Have Based A
Few On Your Recipes,
But I Always Changed Someing.
Like What? The Font?
Name One Difference Between
This Meatloaf Recipe And Mine.
Well, Yours Calls For
Minced Curly Leaf Parsley.
Mine Calls For Minced Flat Leaf.
It'S Minced! Who Can
Tell The Difference?
Bree, You Have Recipes In
Here You Can'T Even Make.
Never Heard Anything So Absurd.
The Croquembouche Cake
With The Spun Sugar Netting?
I'Ve Never Once Seen You
Work With Molten Sugar.
I Always Make That
Cake. Really, Katherine.
Just Because I Let You Execute
A Few Eye-Catching Garnishes
That Gratify Your Need To Show Off,
Doesn'T Mean That I Can'T
Do Them Just As Well Myself.
You Let Me?
I Thought We Were Partners.
We Are.
That'S Why Your Name Is
On The Dedication Page.
You Were Right About
The Dedication, Bree.
It Really Was Theleastyou Could Do.
18 To Zero!
2 More Points, And
You'Ll Break The Record.
Mommy, I'M Tired!
Really?
Well, I Thought Running
Through That Guy'S Sprinkler
Would'Ve Refreshed You. Now Come On!
No.
Looks Like Mommy'S Gonna
Score Her First 2 Points.
Come On, Juanita.
Show Mommy What A Winner You Are.
Juanita!
What Are You Doing?!
Juanita, Stop!
Juanita! Juanita!
And While I Thought
Grounding You Was An
Appropriate Punishment,
Your Dad Convinced Me
I Was Being A Little Too
Hard On You Guys. Absolutely.
And So We Have Decided
To Let You Go To The
Homecoming Dance Tonight...
That'S Right!
In Your Father'S Convertible.
Um, Um, H-H-Hold
On. What? Wh--
Come On, Tom. I Mean,
We Trust Them, Right?
Yes, Yes.
I-I Would Trust Them More If They
Were Driving Your
Car. No! You Don'T Wan
Two Cool Kids Pulling Up
To Homecoming In A Mom Car,
Especially With That Big Dent
They Put In It Last Month.
Dude! Thanks! Thanks!
Don'T Thank Me. Thank
Your Father. Thanks, Dad!
You Rock! Uh, You--Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Here--Some Ground Rules.
N-No Muddy Shoes On
My Floor Mats. No--
Tom, Relax!
You High-Spirited Kids Do
Whatever It Takes To Have Fun.
And In Three, Two, One.
Welcome Back To "What'S
Cookin' Fairview?"
We'Re Talking With Bree Van De Kamp,
Fairview'S Premier Caterer,
Who'S About To Publish
Her Very First Cookbook.
Bree, Could You Show Us Inside?
This Is My Kitchen,
And This Is
My Staff--
The Most Gifted, Hardworking Team
A Cook Could Ever Have Hoped For.
I Cannot Say Enough
Good Things About Them.
So Which One Of You Has
Worked With Bree The Longest?
That Would Be Me.
So Tell Me, What'S It Really
Like Working With Bree?
It'S Inspiring.
There Is Absolutely
Nothing She Can'T Do.
Katherine, I'M Blushing.
Working With Her Has Been...
Such An Education
That
I--Aah!
Ah! Oh, God. Are You All Right?
I Think I Strained My
Wrist. God, It Hurts.
Oh, You Poor Dear. Could Someone
Please Get Some Ice? Oh, No.
Oh, And I Was Just About To
Put The Spun Sugar Netting
On Our Famous Croquembouche.
Would You Mind Doing It?
Katherine,
I'M Sure Your Wrist Is Just Fine.
No, It'S Really Throbbing.
Okay, It Looks Like
Bree To The Rescue.
Be Sure You Get This.
Really Something To See.
The Secret To Spinning Sugar
Is This Special Whisk
That Makes Lovely Gossamer Threads.
Careful, Dear.
You'Re Clumping. I Can See That.
That Stuff'S Hot!
Sorry.
Oops!
So That'S Your Idea Of Exercise?
Having Her Run After A Car?
Carlos, Our Daughter Sucked
Down Half A Sheet Cake,
And Afterwards, No One
Could Find The Candles.
Wake Up! We Have Got A Problem!
I Just Don'T Think The
Solution Is To Humiliate Her.
Now Even If She'S... Heavy,
Doesn'T She Have The Right
To Feel Good About Herself?
Hey, I'M Protecting Her. She
Doesn'T Know The Truth Yet.
Women Only Have Five Seconds
To Be Young D Beautiful,
And Then It'S Gone.
And Then Before You Know It,
We'Re Old And Fat And Married
And Wondering Where Our Beauty Went.
Gaby...
No, Carlos. I Mean...
Sometimes I'M Glad You Can'T See Me.
Five Years And Two Kids
And No Time For Facials Or The Gym.
It Just... Takes A Toll.
And When Edie Same The Other Day,
It Was Like She Didn'T
Even Recognize Me.
Listen To Me.
Nobody Knows Your
Face Better Than I Do.
And I See It Every Time I Kiss You.
In 5 Years Or 50,
You Will Always Be Beautiful.
Hear Me?
And Now To Finish,
You Simply Transfer Your Spun Sugar
To The Croquembouche
And Gracefully Drape It Around
In A Delicate Swirl.
Did I Meion That You...
Probably Shouldn'T Be Wearing Jewelry
While Working With Spun Sugar? Um...
Well, There'S No Law That Says
It Has To Be A Delicate Veil.
I Mean, It Could Really
Just Be A Beautiful, Um,
Little, Uh, White...
Ribbon.
Turn Off The Damn Camera.
Ah, Actually, My Wrist Is
Feeling A Little Better.
Why Don'T I Give It A Shot?
Whatcha Doing?
Okay, Where Are They? It'S
30 Minutes Past Curfew.
Actually, It'S 32.
If There Is A Single
Scratch On That Car--
I Mean, After All The Time That
I Spent Restoring That Thing...
Yeah. Remember When You Spent
The Entire Day On The Internet
Trying To Find A New Gearshift Knob?
Worst Anniversary Ever.
I Cannot Believe That
You Did This To Me.
I Know.
That Car Is Your Baby.
If Only There Was Something
I Felt That Intensely About.
Oh, Wait! There Is--
My Actual Babies.
You Think I Don'T
Care About Our Boys?
I Know You Love Them,
But Sometimes You Find Them
So Cool And Entertaining,
You Forget To Parent Them.
Lynette--
No, Listen.
This Is Important.
When They Were Little
And They'D Act Out,
And We'D Always Say,
"Relax! They'Re Young.
When They'Re Older, They'Ll Get It."
Well, Tom, They'Re 16 Now.
Not Getting It.
We Have A Lot Of Work To
Do In A Very Short Time,
And If You And I Aren'T In Sync,
I'M Afraid It'S Not Gonna Happen.
Hey, Sorry We'Re Late. Yeah. But,
Dad, You Have To Hear This Story.
We Just Pulled Up At An Intersection,
And There Were These Two Hot
Girls-- I Don'T Want To Hear It.
You Ever Hear Of A Thing
Called A Cell Phone?
We'Re Only, Like, 35 Minutes Late.
Yeah, 35 Minutes, During Which Time
Your Mother And I
Have Been Worried Ck.
But,
Dad--
You Broke The Rules.
There Are Consequences.
You'Re Both Grounded For A Month.
This Sucks! You'Re Only Doing This
'Cause You Were Worried
About Your Precious Car.
You Think? Get Out Of The Way.
Any Other Opinions
You'D Like To Share?
Thank You.
But You Didn'T Have To...
That Mirror Was Scratched.
I Already Ordered A New One.
Mrs. Mccluskey! You'Re Still Alive!
Oh, It'S Nice To See You, Too, Edie.
This Is My Husband, Dave Williams.
So How Did You Two Meet?
You Run A Free Clinic Or Something?
I'M Sorry. Who Are
You? Karen Mccluskey,
Edie'S Best Friend On The Street.
Well, It'S A Real
Pleasure To Meet You.
What Are You Doing Here?
Um, I Just Need To Talk To You.
Not Here. Go Home. I'Ll Call You.
When?
I Don'T Know. Later. Just Go.
I Have To Say, Ladies,
This Is Quite A Shindig.
Oh, I'M Glad You'Re
Enjoying Yourself.
Yeah, I Mean, There'S
Really Not A Lot Of People
Who Go To This Much Trouble To
Say They'Re Sorry. Excuse Me?
Well, The Party. It'S Just
A Beautiful Way To Apologize.
Edie, This Is Not A
"We'Re Sorry" Party.
This Is A "We Forgive You" Party.
You Forgive Me?
Well, I Think What Gaby Means Is
You Were Fairly Awful To
Us Right Before You Left,
And This Is Our Way
Of Welcoming You Back
To Hopefully Not Do It Again.
You Gotta Be Kidding.
You Froze Me Out.
You Threatened To Ruin My Business,
And You Ran Me Out Of Town.
Now It'S Taken Me Five
Years To Stop Hating You.
Great Party, Ladies.
Thank You Very Much.
Now... Mind If I Steal My Wife?
Sweetheart?
Isn'T That Your Painter?
Is It? I Can'T Tell.
Ooh! Excuse Me. It'S Okay.
Didn'T They Pay The Bill?
All Right. Calm Down.
I'Ll Take Care Of It.
You, Come With Me.
Why Would You Humiliate
Me In Front Of My Friends?
Are You A Lunatic?
I-I'M Just Trying To
Get Through To You.
And, Yeah, It'S
Making Me Kinda Crazy.
Susan... Why Can'T
I Meet Your Friends?
I Mean, Am I Really That Horrible?
No, Of Course Not. My
Friends Would Love You.
Then What Is The Problem?
The Problem Is,
If You Meet My Friends,
Then We'Re In A Relationship,
And I Can'T Be In A
Relationship Right Now.
But I-I Promise, I'Ll
Make You Very Happy.
Well, Maybe I Don'T
Deserve To Be Happy.
A Few Years Ago...
There Was This Car Accident...
A Bad One.
Take The High Road?
Did You Hear What Those
Smug Bitches Said To Me?
Edie, It'S Important
These People Like Us.
It'S Our Home Now.
I Never Should'Ve Let You
Talk Me Into Moving Back Here.
Why? Why Were You So
Gung Ho On Wisteria Lane?
Listen To Your Husband.
We Can Be Happy Here,
But We Need These People To Like Us.
Why?
It'Ll Just Make Everything Easier.
That Was An Accident.
Susan, You Can'T
Feel Guilty About It.
You Know What, Jackson?
You'Re Not Gonna Say Anything
I Haven'T Already
Heard A Million Times.
I-I Only Told You Because I...
I Just Want You To Understand
Why I Can'T Let You In My Life.
Well...
Do You Mind If I Hang Out
For The Next Few Months
And See If You Change Your Mind?
Yeah, I Guess I Could Handle That.
Well, Why Don'T You...
Go Have Fun With Your Friends?
And Just Call Me When You'Re Free.
Okay.
Please, Danielle. You
Have No Right To Take Him.
I Have Every Right. He'S My Kid.
Danielle, We Agreed
I Would Raise Him.
We Agreed It Would Be Best!
You Said It Would Be Best!
I'Ve Had No Say In Anything!
But I Am Married Now,
And Leo'S A Lawyer.
So Do Yourself A Favor And
Don'T Try To Fight This!
Please, Danielle, We Can
Have Any Arrangement You Like.
Please, Just Don'T Take Him!
For God Sakes, Orson'S Gone.
You Kids Are Grown.
Benjamin'S All I Have!
You'Re Just Gonna Have
Tfind Something Else.
Honey, Come To Bed. It'S After 2:00.
The Cooking Show Agreed
To Redo My Segment.
I Wanna Make Sure
It'S Perfect This Time.
Well, I Won'T Tell You
How To Run Your Business.
It'S Your Baby.
Yes, It Is.
Hey. Um, M.J. Ready?
Yeah, He'S Upstairs Waiting For You.
I Told You The Brakes Were Squeaking.
I Asked You To Get Them
Checked. And I Checked 'Em!
I Meant A Mechanic...
Not You. It Was Not
The Brakes, Susan.
If It Had Been, It
Wouldn'T Have Mattered.
They Crashed Into Us!
And We Killed Them, Mike!
We Didn'T Kill Them! They Died.
They Were A Mother And A Child.
She Was A Mother, Just Like Me...
With A Child Just Like Ours.
And If It Weren'T For Us,
They Would Still Be Alive.
Yeah, We Have Been Over
And Over This, Susan.
It'S--It'S Like You Want To Suffer.
It'S Like You Don'T Care At All,
Like You Feel Nothing
For Those People.
I Can'T Do This Again! I Just Can'T!
Hey. Did You Pack Your Dinosaur Book
So You Can Read It With
Your Daddy? Sure Did.
Oh, Good. Mmm.
Okay, You Have Fun, Sweetie.
So, Um, I'Ll Probably Bring Him
Back Sunday Around 6:00 Or So.
Fine.
Well, Have A Good Weekend.
Doing Anything Special?
Well, I'Ve Sort Of
Starteseeing Someone.
So I Might Do Something With Him.
Good For You.
It Goes By So Quickly.
In A Flash,
The Life We Knew Is Gone Forever.
And We'Re Left To Ask Ourselves...
How Could He Have Left Me?
When Did My Beauty Start To Fade?
Why Has My Friend Changed?
Was I The Best Mother
I Could Have Been?
Of Course, There Are Some People
Who Understand How
Quickly Time Passes.
That'S Why They'Re So Determined
To Get What They Want
Before It'S Too Late.
Oh, Dr. Heller. I'Ve
Been Meaning To Call You.
Yeah, I Was Getting Concerned.
You'Re Required To
Check In Once A Month.
It Was A Condition Of Your Release.
Oh, Come On. That Was A Year Ago.
But To Be Honest, The
Meds Are Working So Well,
I Kinda Forgot About You. No Offense.
Dave, Once A Month. Not Optional.
Message Received, Doc.
But Seriously, You Don'T Need
To Worry About Me. I'M Great.
I'Ll Talk To You In A Month.
Just Tell Me.
What Are The Magic
Words That I'Ve Gotta Say
So You Will Let Me Out Of Here?
Dave, You'Ve Been Here Six Weeks,
And You Don'T Seem Any Closer
To Coming To Terms With Your
Rage. I'Ve Come To Terms With It,
And I Like It Just The Way It Is.
The Charges Were Dropped
Because You Agreed
To Put Yourself In A Doctor'S Care.
I'M Not Going To
Authorize Your Release
Until I See Some Real Progress.
Wh-What'S Progress Supposed
To Look Like To You, Doc?
I Mean, Should I Just Plaster
Some Fake Smile On My Face
And Pretend This--This
Thing That'S Inside Me
Isn'T Eatin' Me Alive?
'Cause I Can Do That If You
Want. I Need To Make Sure
You'Re Not A Danger To
Yourself Or To Others.
Listen, I'Ve Never
Been A Danger To Myself.
And As Far As The
Others Are Concerned,
There'S Only One Person
Who Should Be Worried.