Jesus, you really don't remember
what happened last year?
Pay some fucking attention
this time.
Your life's not simple, Fiona,
and you're nothing like anyone
I've ever met.
You make me want to enjoy
my life again.
Who the hell is that?
My dad.
In my whole career, I've never
seen such a spectacular display
of alcoholism.
Thank you.
- How much are we short?
- $18.30.
I'm take the PSATS
for some Polish kid.
Are you able to kick in,
like, ten more?
I get paid Friday.
Okay, I'll figure out the rest.
I can loan you the money.
We don't need your charity.
"Fiona, thanks for a night
I'll never forget."
Who the fuck's Tony?
I've waited a long time
for last night to happen.
At least Tony's not coming here
getting all in
my family's business
what the fuck is wrong, Frank?!
Maybe that's what I want.
You know nothing about me.
Then teach me!
I'm gay.
I know.
That's for screwing my husband.
I want another baby.
What?
I get what I want,
and you can have what you want.
Put the candy back, now.
Fuck!
Shit!
I like you, Fiona.
You're a dirty girl, like me.
Jasmine, this is Veronica.
V lives next door.
Hiya, V.
We're only taking in
a foster kid for a week
to get the money to pay
for my stupid parking tickets.
Want to go over to the park,
throw the ol' pigskin around?
Would it be all right if
my son Jonah came? Huh?
I scored you a 2,200.
I'm an investigator for the
educational evaluation service.
This is the robotics lab.
It is the best in the country.
Come by anytime.
Science just turns me on.
What are you hiding?
I left them.
Your house is
Frank's wet dream.
Never gonna get him out.
Dad.
Son.
- What are we?
- Friends.
Just friends?
Friends who like to do this.
I knew that.
It says here you can
re-dedicate yourself as a virgin.
Oral sex, orgy,
big black strap-on dildo.
You whore!
He humiliated me!
Get out!
Don't ever come back!
You're out of the house.
I'm out of the house!
Whoa!
What do you think now, daddy?
Am I still a whore?
Frank? Frank?!
I think I was kind of
falling in love with her.
How long you been stealing cars?
Who says I steal them?
I have to leave town.
Come with me.
Costa Rica, it's beautiful.
I think I might
be in love with him.
Scary, isn't it?
I love you.
I want to be with you.
Come with me.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ know that it's not
for naught ♪
♪ you were beaming once before ♪
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
♪ you're so sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ round up the friends you got ♪
♪ know that they're not
for naught ♪
♪ you were willing once before ♪
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
♪ you're so... ♪
♪ sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
77, 78, 79,
80, 81, 82,
83, 84...
Won't be long now, Frank.
In a few days, she's gonna
make it to the store,
then the hair salon,
alibi room.
Gonna meet your friends.
Ninety-nine...
Ooh.
Hear all those
heart-warming,
scumbag freeloading
Frank stories.
Who the hell is that?
Friend from group.
Group?
Sex addicts anonymous.
Gig's almost up, daddy Frank.
Time to make other plans.
One hundred!
Hey, cut it off, Ernie.
Thanks, lieutenant.
Hey, do you mind if we drop
Cami off early tomorrow?
Teresa's got inventory
at Costco.
No problem.
And tell Teresa thanks
for the case of dented soup.
Bye-bye, Cami. Mwah.
Pool's open!
Eddie goes to the corner
for a pack of Lucky's,
never heard from again.
Goddamn city couldn't wait
to stop paying him.
Wasn't two weeks before
the checks stopped coming.
And now what are we
supposed to live off of?
Sheila's single
disability check?
How does Mr. Osama-Obama
expect us to survive on that?
He gonna try and
tase me. I hit him.
If Sheila does go to work,
what's she going to make?
Minimum wage... at best.
Nobody's heard from Eddie?
He tases me...
Not a word.
Man's got no sense
of responsibility.
Leaving a family of three
to fend for ourselves.
I got tased twice, man.
Bullshit.
What you say?
Uh...
I said bullshit!
I got tasered
for like a second,
I crapped myself.
There's no way
you got tasered twice,
fought off three cops
ran away.
You calling me a liar?
At the very least,
an exaggerator.
A grand says I did.
Kev, you still got
that taser back there?
I'll see your grand
and add nine more.
10,000 in American legal tender
says you can not
get tasered twice
and not soil
your tighty whities,
much less keep standing.
All right, shithead.
Move.
Do it.
Do it!
Again!
What?!
Where's my ten grand,
motherfucker?
Hey, gorgeous, more Diablos.
Oh, you think these boy scouts
can handle that kind
of heat, girls?
No.
No, not a chance.
Not a chance.
Six more Diablos, a JB back,
Ketel One up with a lime wedge,
Maker's Seven, and four Stellas.
Haven't given up
on that one yet?
Every summer needs a challenge.
Man's in love
with his own fabulous self.
Probably masturbates while he
licks his reflection
in the mirror.
Fiona!
Who's that, slutty's husband?
Uh, no. Hal's rounder.
Hi.
Fi, this is my friend, David.
Jasmine's told me
a lot about you.
Only that you're
fabulous, smart,
and unbelievably sexy.
And that you're home
for the summer from Princeton.
I'll get us a table.
Okay.
Princeton?
We're going out later.
You want to come?
What about hal?
Annual Michigan fishing trip
with the softball buddies.
Mosquitos, bratwurst
and gallons of Budweiser.
Sounds pretty brokeback to me.
Come later, live a little.
That a regular thing?
First time I've seen him.
She probably did his
taxes, then did him.
♪ ♪
Kick him back, you're
punching like a fag.
First round. Go to your corners.
You know you're supposed
to hit him back, right?
Fuck, that kid hits hard.
What did you think
this was going to be?
I didn't think he could
punch me with a foot.
You see that? He kicked me
in the top of my goddam head.
Listen, look at me.
You want to throw in the towel?
Round two
I would if I was smart.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna blow a fuse ♪
♪ when my techno music,
pop music, retro music, rock ♪
♪ turn it up on a Friday,
bump it all night long... ♪
He's crazy about you.
Long Island,
two Landsharks, three Mojitos,
Margarita no salt,
Chivas Neat and a Jack Rocks.
All the woman needs is a pole.
Why don't you
come out with us later.
Kev won't mind.
I can't.
I got a shift at the
nursing home in the morning.
This better be somebody who's
about to give me a gigantic tip.
God, I'm so sorry.
I thought your ass
was my drink.
Hey, Justin Bieber.
How's things at Goldman sachs?
Going well enough for me
to afford getting
ripped off coming here.
And it's JP Morgan.
Oh, whatever.
All you mortgage-raping shits
should be in prison anyway.
Yeah, well, I was in grad school
during the mortgage crisis.
Nowadays, we're trying
to short Euros
so Greece will go bankrupt.
Are we on for later?
I haven't decided
if I still like you.
Later, mama bear.
Hey, junior, school night.
In bed with the
lights out by 10:00.
What?
Order's up.
♪ Turn it up on a Friday,
bump it all night long ♪
♪ I-I-I'm gonna party
when you play my song. ♪
How the hell did that little guy
kick Kurt-fucking-Landis' ass?
We make anything on my fight?
Thanks, Rasmik!
Nah, nobody wanted the odds.
What'd you put down?
On the fight you lost?
Nada. Fraternal loyalty doesn't
extend to stupidity, bud.
So, Mickey's out soon, yeah?
In about a week or so
if he doesn't stab anybody else.
Plastic fork--
Barely broke the kid's skin,
but it bought him
another 30 days.
You got to be
looking forward to having
Mickey home again, huh?
I guess.
Hey, I want to stage
another fight night next week.
Go around to the Dojos, round up
some more scrappers, all right?
Sure. Where you going?
Karen's.
Thought you gave up on that.
See ya.
Yeah.
Karen Jackson?
After that thing with your dad?
I'm sneaking antibiotics into
his toothpaste, just in case.
Tomorrow fuckhead!
Jesus Christ!
Fuck!
Friend dropped me off.
Right.
What the hell you doing here?
Came to see Karen.
She went with a
guy to her group.
What group?
Sex addicts anonymous.
Well, can I come in and wait?
No.
Looks like old man Dave is
beating your time, Romeo.
Yeah, well, I'm working without
pharmaceutical assistance.
He was popping little blue
pills-- I counted four.
Four, wow. We could
be here awhile.
Ah, fuck!
I told my boss I'd meet him
for a run in about an hour.
I could run with you.
I ran track in high school.
What? Don't look
so surprised.
I ran distance.
There was a chance I
was gonna make state.
Yeah? What happened?
Life.
Come on.
I'm fast.
Oh, really?
I could beat your ass.
You're on.
Wait!
Okay, ready?
Give it to you.
Okay.
All right.
On your mark...
Yeah.
Get set...
Okay.
Go!
What are you doing?
Are you a valet now?
See you tonight?
Maybe.
Maybe?
Hey, Fiona.
Tony.
How's work?
It's good.
How's your remodel coming?
You really want to know
or just being neighborly?
Neighborly.
Cast iron plumbing's out,
replacing it with copper.
Guy on my shift
moonlights as an electrician,
so he's going
to help me rewire.
You gonna flip it
or live in it?
Waiting to see what happens.
I got to get the kids going.
Whoa. What happened to you?
One of my fighters pussied-out
on me, I had to fill in.
Looks like the pussy
had the right idea.
Get some ice on that eye.
Good morning.
We're out of Mac and cheese.
I can make PB&JS instead,
but I'm gonna need more bread.
How many signed up for today?
Nine.
Romano twins, Cami,
Mangis, that Ulin kid
with the big head.
Whoa, half a cup.
I'm exhausted.
Liam had me up half the night
banging his head.
I need my own room.
And I want a pony
for Christmas.
He's a boy, he should be
in with the boys.
No way, there's three of us
in that room.
I'm a girl.
I'm going to be a woman soon.
I need privacy to undergo
the upcoming
traumatic transformation.
It's not that traumatic.
How would you know?
Video in fifth grade.
What are we talking about?
Moving Liam into our room.
No fucking way.
First day care kid is here.
My own room?
It's not gonna happen, Debs.
Go, go.
"Traumatic Transformation"?
Wow. Ethel, the garden
looks great.
It's all in the compost.
My red worms have been
working overtime this year.
None of God's bounty
ever needs go to waste.
Still on for today?
Think it still runs?
Probably not, but
you can fix anything.
Hey, what are those huge round
green things in the back?
Tomatoes.
Ah.
She's a keeper.
Mmm.
♪ Climb every Mountain ♪
♪ climb every stream ♪
♪ climb all the rainbows ♪
♪ till you find your dream. ♪
Frank! Karen!
Breakfast!
I moved it.
Hey! Good morning.
I, uh, I can't find my watch.
I have looked everywhere.
It's on your wrist.
I had mom move
her rainy day fund
after what happened last time.
Karen, the omelets are ready!
I had nothing to do with that.
Hello?!
I hid her atm card, too,
so don't even try
taking that again.
Her nose has been running,
but I think it's just the glue
that Jeff's been using
on the new kitchen linoleum.
Bye, baby.
Oh, and please, no gluten.
Gluten?
Who knows.
Ooh. Hey,
there you go.
There's Cinderella.
Uh, you all set?
Yeah. Playtime, one hour.
Tv or Bambi--
Skip the dead mom part.
Arts and crafts.
Cheetos and carrot sticks.
Story time, nothing scary.
Free play, lunch, nap,
pool, Dr. Oz, twinkies and milk,
parent pickup.
Oh, and don't wake you
unless there's blood
or exposed bone.
Lots of blood.
Who's ready for tv, guys?!
Okay, let's watch.
♪ I just found out
that your world of stone ♪
♪ was made out of
powdered glass ♪
♪ I thought you'd try
to save your soul ♪
♪ but it's too late ♪
♪ your time has come ♪
♪ ow. ♪
It's about time.
You see Kash last night?
No. He didn't come home again.
Had to open the shop by myself.
Homeless winos
ten deep at the door
trying to trade stolen recycling
for 40s and mad dog.
Uh, pack of Marlboros.
How old are you, eight?
Get the hell out of here.
You handle the store
by yourself?
I got to get upstairs.
The twins are going to be late
for swim team at the mosque.
And no free breakfast.
You come to work hungry,
you pay like everybody else.
Linda gone?
Mm-hmm.
Been waiting across the street
for an hour.
Mm. Late night?
What do you care?
Where the hell have you been?
Kash!
I waited up
until after midnight.
You know the doctor wants
me in bed by...
What are you looking at?
Go microwave me a burrito
and stock the cooler.
A pack of Marlboros?
What?!
Hey, you try
starting this thing
since last summer?
No.
Hey, how's the crop coming?
It's almost harvesttime.
But I'm a bit worried though.
It seems like there's
a lot more cops
in the park this summer.
Yeah, I'm working on it.
Oh.
I'll go chase the rats
out of the coolers.
Hey, guys.
♪ Kimba ♪
♪ who lives down
in deepest, darkest Africa? ♪
What are you doing?
Borrowing Liam.
Where's that,
that backpack thingy?
Borrowing him for what?
Going to take him
to the aquarium.
No, you're not,
it costs too much.
Okay, then, the zoo.
When are you bringing him back?
I'll bring him back
when I'm damn ready.
I'm his father,
we need time together.
Should we wake Fiona?
See any exposed bone?
Stan's yelling again,
so loud you can hear
him through the floor.
Oh, yesterday it was
Nixon and Jimmy Carter.
What's it today?
I turned the tv up after
"fucking colored people."
He keeps going
downhill like this,
you're going to have
to call Becky.
He has his good and bad days.
Bad days?
That's what you call trying
to take out the trash naked?
He forgot his pants--
it happens, all right?
I know you love
the old racist bastard,
but if it were my dad,
I'd want to know
he was going south.
It's probably time
for her to think
about putting him in a home.
I can't hear you.
No.
N-no, I don't want
to watch my language.
I've been speaking this language
for the last 50 goddamn years.
No, you listen to me,
you fucking daughter
of a chink whore.
Hello?
Goddamn cunt,
cunt, cunt.
She hung up on me.
The bitch didn't speak
one word of English.
She's probably in the basement
of some whorehouse in Calcutta.
A-and would you believe
this shit?
What shit?
My electric bill.
$8,700 bucks for electricity.
You know, I've been running
this bar for 40 years
and I never got a bill that
was even close to a grand.
All I want is for them
to send me one of their
taco-eating, wetback
meter readers to come here
and check out
the fucking thing!
Nah, that's it,
get me my shotgun.
I'm going to go down there
and blow the cunt's head off.
Can I see it-- The bill?
Yeah, here.
They must have
made some mistake.
The only mistake they made
was fucking with me.
All right, Stan, would
you please sit down?
Aah!
Stan, sit down before you blow
another ventricle.
Yeah, blow, blow.
I'm gonna take care
of this, all right?
Arizona's got
the right idea, boy--
Take 'em down to the border
and throw 'em
over the goddamn fence!
That's it.
Ian, cover the register.
We have a problem.
We may need to sell some pot.
Isn't that what we always do?
A lot of pot.
So Ethel's been helping us out.
You know how she told you
about that kick-ass worm
shit she's been using
on her tomatoes?
Yeah.
Well, it worked so good,
we decided to use it
on this year's crop.
You know how I usually grow
a couple plants
to get us through the summer?
Holy shit.
Exactly.
Wait, so what's the problem?
Forgot about the electric bill.
We need nine grand
or they're gonna shut
the power off to the building.
Isn't it wonderful?
Mr. Kevin is
going to help
all the old people
who are going blind.
God bless you.
Jesus loves you.
Fuck you, Frank.
- Jesus-- Oh, shit.
- Where's my money?
Okay, okay, okay, stop!
Back to work.
Your fly is down.
So how much do you think
you've got growing down here?
I don't know, a couple
hundred pounds or so.
I'm gonna start drying what I
can, but that won't fetch more
than a couple grand
or so by Friday.
Well, you know what?
Maybe we could, uh,
unload some of the plants?
Yeah, how much
would we have to sell?
Five maybe,
six?
Lip, who the hell around here
has two grand for a plant?
I might know a guy.
V's going to kill me.
She's going to fucking kill me.
I promised her
that I wouldn't sell
more than three or four
this year.
Normally I throw
a bunch of seeds around,
see which looks best,
thin out the rest,
but this year I couldn't.
They're all so beautiful,
I just...
I just couldn't do it.
Where's my fucking money?
That was great last night.
You were having fun,
I was having fun.
Where's my fucking money?
You were serious about that?
Get me the goddamn tin snips.
I-if, if I had won, I wouldn't
expect you to pay me.
Take off his shoes.
But...
It's a turn of phrase,
like, uh, uh,
"I bet it's going
to rain today."
Yeah, let me tell you
something,
if I don't get
my fucking money,
I'm cutting toes off
and cauterizing 'em
with a blowtorch.
You got my panhandling cash.
60 bucks, man?!
I was only out there
for 45 minutes!
We'll keep the kid.
Yeah, as collateral.
Come back with
my fucking money,
you get the kid.
I-I-I'll bring
you your money,
but you can't keep the kid.
You can't keep Liam.
I'll get you your money--
We can work this out.
Oh, we just did.
No, no, no, no, no, absolutely you can't...
Light it up, get him up.
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay.
Keep Liam.
Get up out of here.
I'll be back, buddy,
I promise you.
Well... excuse me.
I gotta go.
Hey.
Gaga, Adele, Rikki,
J.Lo, Nicki Minaj.
Even threw in some old Maxwell.
My guaranteed
clitoris-moistening
aphrodisiac music mix.
I hope so.
All she ever wants to do
is discuss the lake poets.
And who the fuck is Bruno Mars?
May be time to give up on
the 22-year-old grad students,
start banging in
your own decade.
22-year-old
grad students
is the reason
I got into teaching.
I'm too old to start over now.
Hey, you got my SIM board?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
Hey, any interest
in purchasing a
six-foot-tall pot plant?
Chicks love an old
dude with great weed.
Yeah, how much?
Uh, a couple grand.
Pricey.
It's primo stuff.
What the hell is that anyway?
It's a cop locator.
Rigging up a GPS system
that uses police frequencies
for coordinates.
Shows me where all the cops are
in a given area
at any given time.
Is that even legal?
What, trying to make sure
our community is receiving
its fair share of law
enforcement resources?
Why not?
Listen, I-I got
a lunch date, I got to go.
Oh, with who, David Petraeus?
No, I landed
a department of defense grant.
Micro-robotics surveillance
drone prototypes.
Yeah? Yeah, well, who knows
if it'll work, but it'll put
some government-issued pork
in my pocket.
Listen, why don't
you help us with it?
I could probably wrangle you
some ap engineering
or physics credits.
Ah, no, thanks.
You're gonna have to
figure out how to blow up
Afghan shepherds
all on your own.
All right.
What are you doing?
Making a little easy summer
moola the Gallagher way.
Where's Liam?
In the car.
You don't have a car.
A friend's car.
You crack a window?
Left the engine running
for the ac.
You left a toddler
in a running car
in this neighborhood?
That baby laxative?
This, my young progeny,
is Dr. Frank's
magic moneymaking
fun dust.
Oregano?
Fool's gold.
My I've-never-seen-it-fail
summer solstice atm.
Hey, maybe we can talk
the electric company
into taking a down payment,
you know, payment plan
kind of deal.
Oh, watch, customers.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Uh, can I get a watermelon bob-pop,
bubble gum snow cone,
and a chocolate crunch?
You still selling loosies?
Uh, yeah, Marlboro lights--
Buck apiece.
What can I get you, champ?
Lemon-lime shot,
chocolate chip cookie bar,
and a Molson's.
Molson's?
We sell American beer
here to children of age.
Come back for a bud
light when you're 16.
Two frozen snickers,
a bag of beer nuts,
and a couple of joints.
You 14? Got ID?
What's your birthday?
June 3, 1997.
Okay.
There you go.
Hey.
You taking little league book
like you did last year?
Absolutely, what do you want?
Marlins.
U10 or u12?
U10 for $15.
You're not worried
about that Ratkovich?
Kid threw 72 pitches yesterday.
Nah. He's Dominican.
Hey, Lip,
anything on this radar?
Ah...
Nope. Closest unit
is a foot patrol
over by the play structure.
Sorry I'm late. I
slept through my alarm.
Yeah, I came by last night,
waited around for a while.
Well, I didn't get
in till 4:00 A.M.
New guy?
Jody.
He's nice.
I don't know. We got to
talking about music yesterday,
and he showed me a bunch of
bands I've never heard of.
My favorite was
called Guns N' Roses.
Guns N' Roses?
How old is Jody?
Uh, 37, I think.
You know, he laid out
a blanket in the park,
and we listened to his iPod,
and fell asleep in
each others' arms.
Wow. Sex any good?
No sex. It's a part
of this whole
Sex Addicts Anonymous thing.
Right, but you're a teenager.
I mean, all teenagers
are sex addicts.
Yeah, but I've been having sex
since I was 11.
I don't know. Jody and
I don't want the physical
to complicate things for us.
Yeah, but we can still get,
uh, complicated, right?
Sure, I guess.
Oh, shit.
Uh, foot patrol,
nine o'clock.
200 yards and closing.
Never heard of Guns N' Roses?
"Welcome To The Jungle"?
Hey, kid?
Not a fucking chance, Frank.
Still owe you a
beating from last year.
Hey, you get... oh.
Ladies, hey?
Hey, anybody interested
in a little primo bud?
Maybe a little
snow for this hot
summer scorcher?
Shit.
Hey! Hey!
♪ ♪
Hey, guys,
what you looking for?
Grass?
Got to have money
to spend money.
Hey, get off our corner!
What the fuck?
Fiona?
Fiona?!
Oh.
Parent pickup time.
Mm.
Thanks, debs.
You have any trouble today?
Little Charlie had a
major diaper malfunction.
Ellie ate a bunch of carpet.
Normal, normal.
Oh, and, uh, Frank took Liam.
What?
Said he was taking
him to the zoo.
♪ ♪
Hugo.
How's it going?
Go away, Frank.
Is Mr. Todd here today?
I said, out!
I'm in trouble.
You're always in trouble.
Come on, Hugo.
You know me. I wouldn't be here
unless I was desperate.
It's my kid.
I need money.
Which kid?
Liam.
The mulatto?
Yes.
No bullshit this time?
No bullshit.
♪ ♪
Hey, Frank?
Hold on. You got more takers.
♪ ♪
Wait.
Liam and Frank
aren't at Sheila's.
Knock, knock. Hey, debs.
Hi, Jasmine.
Want me to start calling around?
No, I'll swing by
the alibi before work,
see what he's up to.
What who's up to?
Frank took Liam.
Probably has him out
panhandling again.
David has a friend coming
into town from New York.
I thought maybe
I could hook you two up.
Who's David?
Uh, bye, Debbie.
A friend?
Yeah.
I met him.
Forties, handsome.
He's your type, too.
Oh, yeah.
What's my type?
Cute and easily manipulated.
You take money from David?
You mean, am I turning tricks?
No.
He takes me out, he buys
me nice things sometimes.
That's what rich people
like to do.
They like to spend their money.
Rich guys like a pretty
girl on their arm, so,
why not let them spoil us?
Done at 5:00.
Cool if I split?
Kash, I'm off. Can I go?
You okay?
I can't do this anymore.
Live this lie.
Linda,
our marriage.
This life of a lie.
What am I going to do?
♪ ♪
Frank wasn't at the alibi?
No, and Sheila hasn't seen him.
He won't keep Liam long.
A toddler will interfere
with getting hammered
and passing out in
the park before 11:00.
How was last night with
Jasmine and grandpa?
I guess they've been
together for years.
He's married, she's married.
Seems like it works out
for everybody.
Yeah? You think it works out
for his wife and her husband?
Hey, like clockwork.
How serious are you
about this one?
Not very.
Good.
'Cause he's a rebound.
He even looks like Steve.
No, he doesn't...
Mmm.
I got my running shoes
in the car,
and I want a rematch.
Rematch?
Yeah, we raced
on the beach last night.
She smoked my ass.
Hey, wasn't that bad.
She annihilated me.
It wasn't a fair fight, though.
She was a track star.
You ran track?
Distance runner. 1600.
Broke some kind of state record.
No shit.
What record did you break?
I didn't break it.
I mean, coach thought
I might be able to.
What was the record?
The time that you were gonna break?
It wasn't a big deal.
Come on, what was the time?
Coach thought I might be able
to break five minutes, 25.
Who knows?
Long time ago.
I bet that you could
break it now. You know what?
We'll find a track,
and we'll get a stopwatch.
Sure.
Yeah?
I've got a table.
Yo.
Hey.
Got the truck running?
Yup. We are
back in the ice cream business.
How was work?
Weird.
Don't ask.
Hey, don't jerk off in there!
What the hell is this?
Fuck, Lip.
It's an admissions packet.
Oh, West Point?
Going through my stuff now?
Ian, you just graduated
the tenth grade.
Wanted to see what it
would to take to get in.
What, to west point?
You're kidding me.
You're actually serious
about this shit?
Well, I was in rotc
for two years,
so, what did you think, Lip?
I don't know. I thought
it was some kind of stupid,
fucked-up adolescent phase.
I mean, you really want
to get your ass shot off
in some -stan somewhere?
"'Stan"?
Yeah, Pakistan,
Afghanistan, Iraqistan.
I guess I'm a patriot.
Fuck.
Don't worry.
It was really discouraging.
I'd need, like, a 4.2 GPA,
a massive sat score,
and a recommendation
from the president or some shit.
Only thing I know I can pass
for sure is the fitness test.
Oh, so, what, the army requires
straight A's now
to get your leg blown off
in kabul?
You really want this shit?
Yes.
All right, then,
fuck it. Let's make
this shit happen.
Yeah?
Hell, yeah.
President's a local boy,
I can tutor you.
You're a shoo-in.
I still think it's fucking
stupid. Fuck are you...
Uh, get off... Get out of here.
You better run.
♪ ♪
What the fuck?
I know. Baby, I know.
I got carried away.
But now what?
What do you want to do?
You can't sell it.
We got to get rid of it.
This isn't, got pulled over
with a half joint
in an ashtray pot.
This is Mexican cartel, 60 years
in the federal slammer pot.
Wait, wait. What are you
talking about? Destroy it?
Kevin, there's a couple of tons
of weed down here, and I'm black.
Well, what about
the electric bill?
We'll figure something out,
dip into our savings, but this?
This shit's got to be
mulch by tomorrow.
To-fucking-morrow.
Frank?
Frank, where have you been?
I've been worried sick.
You didn't come home for dinner.
I have done everything
I can think of,
and I still didn't make
enough money today.
Oh.
Well, I, I have
$80 in my purse.
No, that's,
that's not-- Well, sure.
I think I might have really
screwed up this time.
It's been crazy
exciting to see these cubs
following their mom like this.
The marsh pride nursery has been
so cool to watch this week.
These cubs are
five weeks old now
and ready to rock off
to a new den.
Debbie?
No Liam.
Frank didn't bring him back?
Where the hell is he?
Frank!
Frank! Frank!
Where's Liam?
Hey.
Where is
Liam?
He's at his first sleepover.
He's two!
They sleep a lot at that age.
Which way?
This one?
Who the fuck are you?
We want Liam back.
Liam stays.
He's collateral.
Then you better start shooting.
Hey, good to see you.
Man, shut the fuck up.
How much is that?
I don't know,
but we're good for it.
Gallaghers pay their debts.
Now, where the hell
is our brother?
Okay, home sweet home.
Good night, buddy,
love you.
Love you, bud.
I'm sorry, Fiona.
It's not your fault.
Get some sleep, okay?
I didn't mean for that to...
It was a joke, you know?
I was in the bar,
I made this stupid...
I tried to make
enough that I...
♪ ♪
Ian.
Oh, yeah.
Yo, Freddie, what you got today,
aluminum or plastic?
Ian, tell Kash to get
his ass up here. I need him.
Now, Ian.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Kash,
Linda's looking for you.
Kash.
Can you do me
a favor, Ian?
Can you give me
a bit of a head start?
You're leaving?
Linda's got preeclampsia.
The ob wants her in bed
for the rest of her pregnancy.
I can't do it.
An hour, two, please.
What do I tell your kids?
Been to bed yet?
You're not going
to believe the night I had.
Kids up yet?
Think I may need
some field hands.
We handed over all the cash that
we'd made so far this summer
and we still owe him,
like, six grand.
That's the money that we count
on to get us through the winter.
Well, what was it,
some kind of bet?
Oh, ten grand,
you believe that?
Now we'll be lucky if we can bank
enough to get us to Christmas.
Yeah, hey, V, can we
at least save some for
the ice cream truck, you know,
keep it stocked all summer?
How much is that?
One bag should do it.
All right, but
less than an ounce
on the truck at one time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
Sure, take a bag.
It's the least we can do to
thank you for your hard work.
No, no,
not you, Johnny appleseed.
Carl, stop pushing.
And don't bite.
Hold it...
Babe, you got it?
All right, that it?
So they don't fall.
Thank you, thank
you, thank you.
Peace.
Thank you.
Bye, Veronica.
Bye, baby,
I'll see you later, okay?
All right, so now what?
To the dump, I guess.
Seems like such a waste.
You got
any better ideas?
You looking for Karen?
Yeah, I am.
She went to the store.
You Lip?
Mm-hmm.
Jody.
Nice shirt.
Should about do it.
Shit.
Well, good afternoon,
sleepyhead.
Where's breakfast?
Oh, it's way too late
for breakfast.
You even missed lunch.
I'm not
a short-order cook, sweetie.
So... I'm off for my walk.
108 steps today is the goal.
I might even make it
to the mailbox.
There's lucky charms
in the pantry
and milk in the fridge.
Okay,
bye.
Great looking tomatoes.
Heirlooms?
Yes, they are, cherokee purples.
Hope I can talk you
- out of a couple when they're ripe.
- Of course.
It's all in the compost.
I can give you some worms
to get you started.
Really? That'd be great.
I was thinking I should start a garden.
You should.
I'll go change, grab a shovel.
Hey, Tony.
Five minutes, 23 seconds?
Be happy with anything
under six.
On your mark,
get set.
Go!
♪ ♪
♪ Well, there's no place
I'd rather be... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ summer's almost gone ♪
♪ but we still keep on
hangin' on ♪
♪ waitin' for the sun to rise ♪
♪ to see the look in your eyes ♪
♪ well, there's no place
I'd rather be ♪
♪ there's no place
♪ there's no place ♪
♪ I'd rather be. ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com