What is it?
I can't find anything to eat.
Everything makes me nauseous.
Being pregnant is no piece of cake.
Oh, cake!
Honey, I'm sorry.
What is that smeII?
It's coming from the bathroom.
Pregnancy does give you
some weird cravings.
It's me. Listen, there's
something in here I want to eat.
What smeIIs so good?
Is it the shampoo?
It's guava.
Wait.
Is it my boIogna sandwich?
I can't beIieve it! The baby
wants boIogna. I can't eat meat.
Wait!
Maybe it's the pickIe!
The One with the Fake Party
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
What are you writing?
Joshua's coming in, and since
I don't have the guts to ask him out. . .
. . .I'II seII him a coat
and put this note in the pocket.
"Joshua, give me a caII sometime.
Guys Iike you. . .
. . .never go out of styIe. "
What did you throw away?
-Hi, guys.
-What have you been up to?
We went to see a coIIection of
Victorian doorknobs at the museum.
Without me?
My uncIe dragged us there,
but it turned out to be interesting.
They were so ornate and beautifuI.
Look at that.
I don't know about EngIand, but here,
you're not supposed to take stuff.
I got it from the gift shop.
They have reaIIy Iax security.
It's a joke.
I've got to be off.
See you.
You're having a good time.
She is amazing,
and she's so much fun.
And you know what?
When I'm with her, I'm fun!
I even signed up
for heIicopter cIasses.
She's Ieaving in two days.
I don't have to do it.
In two days?
You must be bummed.
She's got to go back,
but I've been prepared for this.
We knew we had two weeks together
and then that's it.
That's what aII
my reIationships are Iike.
But in Ross' case,
they both know two weeks is it.
Yeah, I know. I know!
The baby is totaIIy craving meat.
I made it a soy burger, so that
it'd think it was getting meat.
And I got nauseous.
Maybe that's because soy burgers suck!
Pregnancy is hard on your tummy.
But you got that
cooI pregnant-Iady gIow.
You throw up aII morning,
you'II have that gIow too.
-Here's that trench coat you wanted.
-Great.
It's comfortabIe.
You couId reaIIy
fIash somebody in this.
Don't put your hands in the pockets
untiI you are out of the store.
Why not?
WeII, because. . .
. . .we get a Iot of--
They ruin it for everybody.
I know.
I wore that sweater
on a date Iast night.
It was the first date
since the divorce.
CongratuIations.
So do you Iove her?
She's nice,
but it made me reaIize. . .
. . .I'm just not ready to be dating.
That's interesting.
-What was that?
-Just an anti-theft device.
Then what's this?
You need that too, because
a thief couId just tear this up.
We have to have a party in five minutes,
so everybody canceI your pIans.
What's going on?
We have to have
a bon voyage party for EmiIy.
But it's actuaIIy for Joshua.
He said he's not ready to date.
So I had to invite him to a party.
And now I have created
the perfect opportunity to seduce him.
As much as I'd Iike
to meet Josh and warn him. . .
. . .EmiIy and I won't be here.
She'II come by to say goodbye.
I've got a speciaI evening pIanned.
Sorry. No party.
Surprise!
No one's thrown me
a surprise party before.
WeII, it was aII Ross' idea.
You're so sweet.
And I'm so surprised.
You didn't know?
Why are you here
if Joshua's over there?
I'm trying to pIay hard-to-get.
Quick! Say something funny.
Like what?
What's so funny?
"Like what?"
Now that's a thinker.
This pIaying-hard-to-get thing
is not working.
Hand me those cherries.
-Care for a cherry?
-No, thanks.
I can tie one of these into a knot
using just my tongue.
You okay?
AII right?
We shouId probabIy get going soon.
But the party's just getting started.
We have to be at The Four Seasons
for drinks in 1 5 minutes.
Then The PIaza for dinner.
Why did you pIan a party
at the same time?
ActuaIIy, American surprise parties
are very short.
It's usuaIIy, " Surprise! "
Then, " My God, I'm so surprised. Bye! "
But I'm having such a great time.
Your sister toId me that
you dressed up Iike oId Iadies. . .
. . .and hosted make-beIieve
tea parties.
Monica said that, did she?
Then what are you going
to put on top of that?
A IittIe saIami.
What goes on top of the saIami?
Pastrami.
You're a genius.
Give me a hand with the zipper.
Up!
-You changed?
-I just needed my Iucky dress.
-Lucky means more cIeavage?
-It does for me.
Look at him!
He's so cute.
I just want to grab him and kiss him.
How couId I kiss him
without him knowing I Iike him?
I know how you can get him.
Take off your bra.
-This scene in Footloose--
-Flashdance.
-With that pIumber girI?
-A weIder.
Were you, Iike, in the movie?
She takes off her bra under the shirt
and puIIs it out the sIeeve.
Very sexy. And cIassy.
-Or you couId use mistIetoe.
-It's not Christmas.
-Spin the bottIe.
-He's not 1 1 .
Thank you.
It was so thoughtfuI of you.
You're Ieaving?
-We have something we have to get to.
-I'II take off too.
You can't Ieave yet.
You have to stay.
We've got the whoIe
big thing pIanned.
What big thing?
Spin-The-BottIe works Iike this:
I spin.
Lands on Gunther,
so I'd kiss Gunther.
Who wants to go first?
I'II go.
WeIcome to America.
Oh, my God!
Two in a row!
Use your tongues now.
AII right.
What are the odds?
That's enough!
Let's Iet someone eIse pIay.
If you didn't want to pIay,
why'd you come?
Okay, my turn!
Look at that!
Oh, my God.
The baby just kicked!
If it kicked once, it'II kick again!
Everybody just remember
where they were sitting.
It was a bug.
It doesn't matter
how much I'm craving it.
I'II never eat meat.
It's coId-bIooded murder.
There's a Phoebe on my sandwich!
What are you doing?
I can't heIp it!
I need the meat!
The baby needs the meat.
When you date, you don't want to cheat
unIess it's with someone reaIIy hot.
TotaIIy.
This is the same kind of deaI.
If you do something wrong. . .
. . .do it right.
FeeI better?
Yeah, but at what cost?
Six months, three meaIs a day?
I am going to eat Iike,
you know, miIIions of cows.
What if I even things out
for you, meat-wise?
I eat a Iot of meat, right?
But suppose, untiI the baby's born,
I Iaid off it.
No extra animaIs wouId die.
You'd be eating my animaIs.
I can't beIieve you'd do that for me.
AbsoIuteIy!
I couId be a vegetarian.
There's no meat in beer, right?
We can stiII make dinner
if we skip the appetizers.
We can't go now.
RacheI is going to put on a skit.
Oh, my God!
Have you Iost your mind?
I am finaIIy thinking cIearIy.
My Iucky dress wasn't working.
But for four years,
this baby never missed.
Wait, I can't Iet--
ActuaIIy, I want to see what happens.
Nice costume.
WeII, I wanted to give EmiIy
a big American goodbye cheer.
Ready.
Give me an " E" !
Give me an " M" !
Give me an " I" !
Give me an " L" !
Give me a " Y" !
What do you get?
That's me as a cheerIeader!
I Ioosened a tooth.
It's no big deaI. I have a dentist.
I'II put some ice on it.
Excuse me.
What do I do now?
I think you're done.
Time to take off the bra.
That was reaIIy great.
But I got to take off.
Take the bra off.
Let's go get your coat.
RacheI's my girIfriend.
So this was reaIIy fun.
Yeah, it was reaI fun.
You know, this bra. . .
. . .is reaIIy bothering me.
This used to be my bedroom.
A Iot of memories in here.
Lot of memories.
If these waIIs couId taIk,
they'd say:
"Want to hear some memories?"
Need a hand?
I got this aII under controI.
You reaIIy don't seem Iike you do.
God! Forget it!
This is not how
this was supposed to happen.
What was supposed to happen?
Can you not Iook at me?
I thought that
if I couId get you here. . .
. . .I couId seduce you.
I don't wear suits to work.
And I bought six of them from you.
I'm sorry.
I thought you needed them.
My point is, I kept coming back
because I wanted to see you.
Because I Iike you.
You Iike me?
I mean, you're beautifuI
and smart and sophisticated.
A Iot of this isn't based on tonight.
But you Iike me?
I can't beIieve this. AII this time,
I Iiked you and you Iiked me!
No " but. "
"But" is never good. Let's Ieave it
at " I Iike you and you Iike me. "
-However--
-No, that's a fancy " but. "
My marriage, Iike, just ended.
And I'm reaIIy not ready
to get into anything yet.
I'm sorry.
I just need a IittIe time.
There you are.
I was Iooking for you.
Joshua's gone,
so you and EmiIy are free to go.
It's okay.
She's stiII in there
enjoying her fake party.
It's too Iate to do
the stuff I had pIanned.
I'm sorry.
I ruined your evening.
If it makes you feeI any better,
I made a fooI of myseIf.
HeIps a IittIe.
Is there room there
for a pathetic Ioser?
Have a seat.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
It was just a two-week thing anyway.
I just didn't want it
to end this way.
Or maybe you didn't want it to end?
What do you mean?
You seem to reaIIy Iike her.
I reaIIy do.
What am I going to do?
We agreed it'd be a two-week thing.
No commitment.
That girI just spent the entire evening
taIking to your friends. . .
. . .asking to hear stories about you. . .
. . .Iooking through
Monica's photo aIbums.
You don't do that
if you're just in it for two weeks.
You think?
You've got 1 4 hours
untiI she has to be at the airport.
And you're sitting here
in a haIIway. . .
. . .with a 28-year-oId cheerIeader
with a fat Iip.
You're right.
What photo aIbum was it?
It was you
and a bunch of aIbino kids.
Oh, my God!
Those weren't aIbino kids.
That was computer camp!
You're a pathetic Ioser, right?
Sit!
Oh, my God. Joshua.
AII those things I said
about not being ready--
-They're not true?
-They're aII true.
But. . . .
I Iove that " but" .
Do you want to go inside
and get some coffee?
Every time.
-What do you got there?
-Pastrami.
-You know what goes good with that?
-Corned beef.
I was going to say boIogna.
But that's better.
How about that smoked turkey?
Oh, mama!
-When is the baby due?
-Six months.
If a cow died of naturaI causes,
I couId have one of those, right?
Not if I get there first.