[Ted Narrating] In 1994...
Robin's dad took her
to New York City for the first time.
This is amazing! Thank you, sir.
Well, a little father-son
bonding trip never hurt anyone.
I did almost die from malnutrition
on that wolf hunt last year.
I had to almost kill you
for you to learn how to kill.
New York City's the best, eh?
I despise it. It's like Edmonton,
minus the arts and culture.
- Come on. We'll miss our flight.
- I'll catch up.
One day I'm gonna move here...
marry a sophisticated big-city man...
with a sick mullet, like, all the way
down to his shoulder pads.
And at night, he'll let me brush it.
And I'll dig up this locket...
so it can be my "something old"
at our wedding.
[Father]
R.J.
[Deep Voice] Coming, sir.
[Whispers]
I'll be back for you.
Back then, I was too embarrassed
to tell you I'd done that.
But we're closer now.
I feel like I don't have to hide my feminine side
anymore just because you've always wanted a...
Son! Yeah. It's Barney.
Great.
I'll be there in 15, B-dog.
Woof, woof.
- That's our thing.
- Uh, be where in 15?
Laser tag. Never been.
B-dog's gonna teach me.
Look. I think that it's great
that you and Barney are...
B-dog.
B-dog are bonding...
but, um, you agreed to help me with this.
Fine. Where did you bury this tampon?
- It's a locket.
- I'm sorry. I get all these girlie things confused.
Do you need my help or not?
Nah, it's stupid.
[Father Chuckles]
[Ted Narrating] So, while Robin
searched for her "something old'...
Lily and Marshall packed
for their "something new"...
Lily's yearlong
art consultant gig in Italy.
I still can't believe we have
to say good-bye to this place.
Oh, I know, baby.
But look at it as an excuse
to simplify our lives.
We can't bring everything to Italy,
so we gotta throw out some junk.
For example, look.
My old Sasquatch binders that
I could never throw away...
because I was gonna be the guy
who proved the existence of Bigfoot.
These are obviously coming to Italy.
But these handbags? Gonzo.
No way.
These have sentimental meaning to me.
Didn't you shoplift these in your 20s?
Yes, and I get very nostalgic
for that time.
You get older. You have kids.
You stop stealing. It's sad.
Lily, we just don't have room for these.
Oh, but you get to keep
your Bigfoot binders?
Wait. Why is this one just December 1999?
Oh. Y2K was coming.
A lot of people took to the woods...
saw the truth.
Okay, Marshall, we don't have time to argue
over what stays and what goes.
Ooh, you know who we gotta bring in?
Okay, I agree he is good at this stuff,
but he just gets so cocky.
No, he doesn't.
So I heard you guys have a bit of a...
packing situation.
I acknowledge now this was a mistake.
Look. I came here to chew bubble gum
and pack boxes...
and I'm all out of bubble gum.
[Gags]
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I swallowed it.
Is that bad?
Good. Thank you.
Dr. Goldsmith says I should be fine.
I just have to look for it in my stool.
So, as I was saying...
I heard you guys have a bit of a...
packing situation.
d d [Upbeat Pop]
d d [Man Vocalizing]
d d [Ends]
Now, as you know...
I'm a bit of a legend
when it comes to packing.
[Together] We know.
Tales are still told of the time
I traveled all through Mexico...
for two weeks...
with everything I needed...
efficiently packed
into a hands-free belt satchel.
The locals called me...
d El Ganso con la Riñoneral d
It's not a hands-free belt satchel, Ted.
It's a fanny pack.
It's not a fanny pack!
Ted, in Spanish...
"el Ganso con la Riñonera'...
means "Fanny Pack Dork."
No, it doesn't. It means...
"Packer of Great Skill and Merit."
[Ted Narrating] I looked it up.
It means "Fanny Pack Dork."
And as a packer
of great skill and merit...
I will tell you how to pack
with Tetris-like precision.
We get it. You pack a lot in your fanny.
Obvious, yet delightful.
Okay. I got a big interview at 3:00...
about possibly designing another building.
Until then, if you abide by my rulings...
I will tell you what goes to Italy...
and what goes in... the Triangle.
[Ted Narrating]
Kids, as you know...
the Bermuda Triangle was the name we gave
to the curb right outside our apartment...
which possessed the magical ability
to make any item disappear...
instantly.
The biggest rule for de-cluttering is...
"Have you used it in the last year?"
If not, Triangle.
Have you used this jump rope
in the last year?
[Scoffs] Are you kidding?
I hop threads every morning, son.
Do three in a row, and you can keep it.
Well played, Mosby.
Next.
Have you used it in the last year?
Gee, I can't remember.
Are you trying to bribe me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
[Coughs] Take it.
- Triangle!
- [Groans]
Next.
- [Laser Sound Effects]
- Ha-ha!
Wow. You're a natural, Dad.
You know, I love Robin.
And her sister's okay, I guess.
But there's something nice
about finally having... a son.
A s...
Cristalli twins, 9:00.
- [Laser Sound Effects]
- [Barney Chortles]
- Now make like your mommy's ovum and split.
- [Laughs]
Solid biology joke, B-dog.
- [Together] Woof, woof!
- [Laser Sound Effect]
[Ted Narrating]
Now I'll admit, to the untrained eye...
a few of my packing rulings
may have seemed arbitrary.
Let's Go Italy? Triangle.
Triangle. Let's go Italy.
A gorilla suit and a blonde wig.
Have you used either of these
in the last year?
[Grunting]
Please, Queen Kong, be gentle.
[Both Moaning]
- Nope, haven't used those.
- I don't think those even belong to us.
Okay. Here's an easy one.
A leaky, 10-year-old beanbag chair...
covered in beer, bong water and fossilized
Cool Ranch Dorito fingerprints.
Italy.
[Speaking Italian]
Guys, this chair has been here forever.
You gotta take it with you. Italy.
Ted, Italy doesn't need something
that is wrinkled, red and leaky...
and smells like booze and narcotics.
They've already got former
Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi.
[Laughs]
I don't know who that is.
All rulings are final.
Okay, why are things that we like
getting Triangled...
and crap you like sneaks through?
- Like what?
- That old 50-pound karaoke machine.
Come on! We sang in the New Year in '02
on this thing, remember?
We were Destiny's Child.
And since I was Beyoncé, I'm pretty sure
I get final say here, so...
Uh, we were not your backup singers,
bitch. We were a group.
I'm sorry. Are you guys married to Jay-Z,
or am I married to Jay-Z?
- Italy.
- [Microphone Feedback]
- [Gasps]
- [Grunts]
Wow. The way you used that kid having
an asthma attack as a human shield...
that took my breath away.
- [Chuckles]
- Okay, next...
- I'll be point guy, and you lay down cover.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Are you suggesting that
I will not be point guy?
[Chuckles]
Look, if Michael Jordan's healthy...
you don't let Scottie Pippen
run the offense.
Oh, you're from Canada. Right.
If... How do I put this?
If Wayne Gretzky's healthy...
you don't let, uh, François...
What I'm saying is hockey is stupid,
and I'm point guy.
Well, I'm point guy, or I'm off the team.
Oh! You are the most stubborn
human being I've ever met!
You better get used to it.
You're marrying a Scherbatsky.
Your daughter is not even a fraction...
as obstinate, stubborn
and... insane as you are.
Where are you, you son of a bitch?
- Look away, kids. She's about to pee.
- Wh...
I am not some animal.
I peed 20 minutes ago,
and I buried it neatly because I am a lady.
Ted, we haven't used
this chair in the last year.
Ergo, Triangle.
Yeah, I guess I see your point. I mean,
if you haven't used it in the last year.
Oh! Ha-ha! Using it. Italy.
- Triangle.
- Italy.
[Together] Triangle.
- Okay, stop.
Every time he lands, that chair
farts out 10-year-old Dorito dust.
Yeah, it's the chair.
Guys, trust me.
You're gonna want this chair in Italy.
It'll feel like home.
All right, buddy. You win.
- Italy.
- Really?
We asked you to be the judge here,
and we gotta trust your opinion.
She's right. With all the traveling
that we'll be doing...
we could probably use a couple
of your hands-free belt satchels.
- You said they were lame.
- I hate to admit it...
but they actually sound useful.
Could you buy us a couple?
Two hands-free belt satchels
coming right up.
Oh, and don't worry.
I'll get cool colors...
so you guys don't look like whatever the
Spanish term really is for "Fanny Pack Dork."
d d [Guitar Strums]
d El Ganso con la Riñoneral d
Men, it's us... versus them.
Our actions here today...
will echo through eternity.
Stand up straight, Kaden!
I only have one rule,
you worthless maggots.
We all respect each other.
I only have one rule.
For every three 10s you bang,
throw a bone to a five.
They're grateful and hardworking...
and let's face it,
sometimes you just want to lay there.
What's that got to do with laser tag?
Everything!
And we will prevail,
even if it takes all night.
Tanner.
I have to be home by 4:00.
[Laser Sound Effect]
Anyone else have any scheduling issues?
You can take down anyone on their team...
but I want the big man for myself.
What's your beef with oldie?
He's... my father.
- Father-in-law.
- Shut up, Kai.
Wait a second.
We get it. You pack a lot in your fanny.
Obvious, yet delightful.
Oh, no.
No!
[Together] El Gansol
Liars! You sent me on a fool's errand.
Okay, to be fair, buying a fanny pack
is inherently a fool's errand.
Hands-free belt satchels.
And just for that, I will not move
from this chair until you agree to keep it.
Ted, unlike that chair,
you, sir, are full of beans.
You have a job interview in half an hour.
Screw the interview. I'm staying.
And, because the forecast
calls for rain...
this... is a raincoat.
[Grunts, Sighs]
[Beeps]
- [Rings]
- Go for Barney.
Hey. Um, I'm having an issue.
Listen, Robin, is this urgent,
or can we talk about it later?
Nah, it's stupid. Have fun.
[Laser Sound Effect]
So long, losers!
[Cackles]
Um, wait. Can you guys help me down?
I... Um...
Ted, if this chair
really means that much to you...
why don't you just take it for yourself?
No. It's important that you keep it.
Why?
This is the first thing we bought
when we moved here after college.
It... It was the only piece of furniture
we had for a week.
And now you two are moving to Italy.
What if our friendship doesn't pass
the "Have you used it in a year" test?
If you can throw out this chair...
who's to say you can't throw me out too?
- That could never happen.
- You're not a chair. You're our best friend.
You can say that,
but a lot can change in a year.
- Buddy, I...
- Look. I know I'm being crazy.
I just...
I just need a moment with this chair.
You know, to say good-bye.
We'll give you two some space.
[Ted Narrating]
Kids, you can't cling to the past.
Because no matter
how tightly you hold on...
it's already gone.
Hello?
Hi. I'm at the Central Park
carousel, and, um...
I'm having a little bit of an issue.
- Uh, what kind of issue?
- Actually, it's a long story.
Um, Robin, listen. I'm-I'm late for
a big meeting. Is it important?
Nah, it's stupid. Good luck.
[Beeps]
All right.
Here's the bottom line, cockroaches.
There's no end in sight,
and we've got no provisions.
If it comes down to it...
I need a volunteer
to let the rest of us... eat him.
- Barney's team seems way more fun.
- Nonsense.
Candy for everyone!
Okay, Team Animal House.
Who wants to try a cigar?
- Yeah!
I'm not saying we're gonna start
with your face or anything...
but is there seriously no one here
willing to give up a hand or a foot?
We're outta here!
Ted, why are you here? You... You had
that meeting. I told you not to come.
You said, "Nah, it's stupid,"
which is Robinese for "It's important."
Everyone knows that.
Well, not everyone.
But you shouldn't have skipped
that meeting. Was it important?
Nah, it's stupid.
And yet, my future husband...
who I sometimes fear
is troublingly similar...
to my emotionally unavailable father...
is off shooting laser guns
with, oh, yeah, you guessed it...
my emotionally unavailable father.
Oh, come on. That's not fair.
If you told Barney that you needed him,
he'd be here in a heartbeat.
I didn't have to tell you.
And you're here.
You don't even know why.
Seems like I'm here to dig.
[Laser Sound Effects]
Looking for D's?
Long story short,
I promised my future self...
the locket would be my "something old"
at my wedding.
What?
No, I just like that there was
ever a version of you...
who imagined having
a "something old" at your wedding.
Robin Scherbatsky, you're a girl.
- Shut up. You're a girl.
- That's been established.
The new information here
is that you're a girl.
Wait. Is that...
Oh, my God. I found it.
[Exhales, Chuckles]
Okay.
What's really going on with this locket?
I'm gonna admit something
that I couldn't admit until I found this.
I've been having fears
about marrying Barney.
I mean, in many ways,
he's grown up into a mature, caring adult.
I'm gonna shoot you with your own gun.
[Cackling]
But I still don't know
if he's ready for this.
I still don't know if I am.
But if I could find this locket...
I mean, if it was still here
waiting for me...
that would mean that the universe
wanted me to marry Barney...
and that everything was gonna be okay.
And when it was gone, it was like...
every doubt I... I ever had about Barney...
about myself, got dug up.
But I found it.
And everything's gonna be okay.
Any last words?
Seeing you on the field of battle...
ruthless, manipulative, untrustworthy...
you've got all the qualities
I would have wanted in a son.
Now I say to you...
the last words my father said to me...
"Shoot me already."
Or we could keep playing if you want.
Nah, it's stupid.
Okay, Team Animal House.
I got him. Come on out.
You're point guy, R-dog.
[Together] Woof, woof.
[Cell Phone Chimes]
Oh, thank God.
This is a sign from the universe.
- It's not a sign from the universe.
- Yes, it is.
The locket is just gone, and you're
telling me that doesn't mean anything?
You know this is a bad omen, Ted.
- You're Universe Guy.
- And you're Skeptic Girl.
You're not supposed
to believe any of that.
Well, maybe I've grown
skeptical of being skeptical.
This is a sign.
Look, it's not a sign. You're doing
the right thing marrying Barney.
The universe isn't
sending you some message.
[Thunderclap]
As we know from science...
rain is liquid water
in the form of droplets...
which have condensed from atmospheric
vapor and then precipitated.
- It's not a sign.
- Ted, this is a sign, and you know it!
I mean, the universe is
screaming at me right now!
How can you, of all people,
tell me to ignore that?
Because maybe it's dumb
to look for signs from the universe.
Maybe the universe
has better things to do.
Dear God, I hope it does.
Do you know how many signs I've gotten
that I should or shouldn't be with someone?
And where has it gotten me?
Maybe there aren't any signs. Maybe...
Maybe a locket's just a locket,
a... a chair is just a chair.
d d [Man: Rock Ballad]
Maybe we don't have to give
meaning to every little thing.
Maybe we don't...
Maybe we don't need the universe
to tell us what we really want.
Maybe we already know that, deep down.
d Sharpen them with lies d
d And whatever's going down d
d Will follow you around d
d That's how you fight loneliness d
d Doo-doo-doo d
d Doo-doo-doo d d