SHE GASPS IN TERROR
Argh!
SHE SOBS
SHE WHIMPERS
# Say it isn't so
# Ah, say it isn't so... #
Sometimes I hate waking up.
# Everyone is saying
you don't love me, you don't love me
# Say it isn't so...
You can pretend
that things aren't your fault...
# Everywhere I go...
..that you're not a bad person.
But deep down,
you always know what you are.
# But say it isn't so...
That morning,
when I woke up in the bath,
I felt like a new person.
We were together again.
# And it won't be long
before you leave me
# Mmm, say it isn't true
# Say that everything is still OK...
Alyssa?
# That's all I need... #
Hello?
SHE RINGS BELL
Hello?!
Morning!
Morning.
You look nice.
I'm not your nan, James.
There's no-one here. The guy's gone.
I'm sure we can use his phone.
Don't think he'd mind.
SHE GASPS
Ooh!
SHE BREATHES HEAVILY
KNOCK AT DOOR
Bonnie?
Are you awake?
I'm not wearing any clothes!
OK!
The mechanic's on her way.
Morning!
Er...
Yeah.
Will you be ready to leave soon?
Yes.
Also, sorry to ask,
but could we borrow some cash
for the car?
I promise we'll pay you back.
SHE SLAMS DOOR
Is there someone else in there?
Oh, my God.
She had sex with the man.
Wha...?
The owner, from last night.
Thank you. Like I said...
DOOR SLAMS
HE CHUCKLES
Why would she have sex with him?
Her boyfriend died.
She's got low self-esteem.
People do all kinds of shit
when they feel bad about themselves.
You two pissed anyone off?
What?
That...is not an accident.
Probably that guy at the car pound.
Or Bonnie.
What?
I'm joking.
Where now?
Um...turn left.
SHE GRUNTS
You feeling OK, Bonnie?
I think I drank too much last night.
Where are we going?
My sister's.
You didn't mention your sister.
You didn't ask.
Where does she live?
The middle of fucking nowhere?
Just, like, 20 minutes...
How'd you sleep?
OK.
We know what you did!
Alyssa...
What?!
The man. The motel man.
Er... He bought me a drink.
You don't have to tell us.
Then what?
No-one's judgin' ya.
What?
You just slept with him.
I don't care. You had your reasons.
We've all done stuff we regret.
I'm really hot.
Can I open up the window?
WINDOW HISSES
Why not take off your polo-neck?
I think I'm gonna be s...
SHE VOMITS
Jesus! She must've had a skinful
last night.
HE CHUCKLES
INTERNALLY: This was my chance.
I had to say something.
Er...speaking of last night...
What about it?
Mm, well, how do you feel?
I feel like we're literally watching
a stranger be sick into a ditch.
OK. So I probably
don't want to talk about it.
OK.
SHE RETCHES
God, how long is she gonna take?
Are we in a rush?
I need to get back today.
What?
Yeah.
INTERNALLY: I didn't know
I was gonna say that.
Well...can't just leave her.
She helped us out with the car
and everything.
OK. Whatever.
I just wish that she'd hurry up.
Think she's finished.
Are you feeling better, Bonnie?
I need to go to a chemist.
DOOR ENTRY BELL CHIMES
SHE GASPS
BIRDSONG
Do you think it's a bit...weird
she didn't mention her sister?
I think it is. She could've just
stayed there last night.
Isn't a bit weird that she...?
James! Yeah?
She's weird. She does weird things.
It's not that interesting.
INTERNALLY: Sometimes, even when
I'm not looking at James,
I know what his face is doing.
Right now
it's all anxious and sad.
Alyssa...
We should get money.
For Bonnie.
Yeah.
INTERNALLY: I wondered if Alyssa
just needed some time.
And space.
I should never have kissed him.
Good morning!
Yes.
How can I help you?
I need painkillers.
The strongest ones.
Right. Um, can you tell me
what they're for?
Why?
Sorry? Why do you need to know?
Because that's...that's my job.
Back pain?
Yeah. It's very bad.
PAPER RUSTLES
Now... There you go.
Er, no more than six in 24 hours,
and you need to eat
before you take them.
Oh.
If you don't, you'll be sick.
Already been sick.
Are you OK?
What?
You... You're bleeding.
No, I'm not.
Has someone hurt you?
Do you need help?
What?
There's a refuge near here.
Can I just pay?
Is he outside?
Where is he? You can tell me.
He's in the motel.
What motel?
Look, I'm a feminist, OK?
PAPER RUSTLES
Thank you.
Is there a toilet here?
It's just...
HE SIGHS
Wonder what's going on.
You should go and check on her.
Think she wanted to be alone.
She's been ages. She's hungover.
She's probably havin' a flapjack
or something.
In a chemist?
They do healthy ones,
made out of prunes
and seeds and things.
JUST GO AND CHECK ON HER!
What?!
INTERNALLY: I was starting to
remember what Alyssa could be like.
SHE MOUTHS
FAST-PACED ROCK MUSIC
MUSIC STOPS
Why can't you ask nicely?
INTERNALLY: I think maybe
there's something wrong with me.
SHE MOANS
# What's wrong, what can I do?
# How can I go on?
# My baby's left me... #
GUNSHOT
# My baby's gone
# Tell me what to do... #
DOOR ENTRY BELL CHIMES
Good morning!
Morning.
Er, where is she?
Who?
The woman. My friend.
I saw her walk in here.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
No-one's come in.
I just saw...
Shame on you!
What?!
Bonnie's disappeared.
She's actually vanished.
Really?
Yeah.
Really?! Yes!
I need to eat some food.
Now!
DOOR CREAKS
It's quite early for lunch.
Yeah.
Did you not have breakfast?
Er...no.
Do you want to put the plates down?
'I never knew if Alyssa
was aware of it.
'She could make a room feel colder
than it actually was.'
'I used to really like food.'
SHE CRUNCHES
This is for you.
Thank you.
This is called a lazy Susan.
'I often found that tension
could be defused with facts.'
So you can pass the food around
more easily.
They're actually...
Fuck's sake, James.
'Not always, though.'
What?
Look, is something up with you?
Alyssa!
You can tell us if you want.
'And then we can all go home.'
My boyfriend was murdered.
Shit!
Yeah.
Sorry. Are you?
Why?
Because it's...what you say.
When someone gets murdered?
I think so.
Both my parents are dead.
Were they murdered?
Can you stop saying the word
"murdered", please?
Are you OK?
I'm fine. I just need some water.
Are you coming back?
What?
Nothing.
This is my dad.
My parents don't speak to me
any more.
'There's definitely something wrong
with me.'
What's wrong?
Are we actually near your sister's?
We're close. Can we get
some takeaway boxes, please?!
DOOR ENTRY BELL CHIMES
Alyssa, what is the matter?
Nothing's the matter, James.
Why did you kiss me? What?
Is it cos you felt sorry for me?
No, James.
I don't wanna talk about this!
Is it because of everything
that happened to me? No!
For God's sake,
not everything is about you!
Why? Because it has to be about YOU?
You can't...
You can't kiss someone and then be
mean. It's... It's confusing.
Why? Are you 12?
You dumped ME, James.
You dumped me, in a letter,
like a Victorian.
Wait. N-No.
No?
No! That's not what happened?
No, it is, but...
I didn't mean it. It's just...
What?
Your...mum...made me.
She...
She came to the hospital.
She made me write you a letter.
Right.
Looking for something?
Where is it?
What's your name? No.
HE SIGHS
DOORS CREAK
My name is Kevan.
With an A.
What's going on? You can tell me.
Did something happen to you?
I... I understand, OK? I get it.
How can you get it? Look,
I know what you're going through.
You've never met me.
I know women like you.
There's no-one like me.
HE LAUGHS
I didn't call the police, cos
I didn't want to get you in trouble.
Give me...my gun.
OK. Listen to me.
Violence...is not the answer.
What if it is?
It isn't.
What if it is?!
Let's just calm down here.
Has anyone ever killed
someone you loved? No!
Do you wake up in the night feeling
like your skin's been screaming
cos it misses someone so much?
I'm asking!
Oh! No.
Then, you don't get it.
Give me...the gun.
I... Give me the gun!
What?!
Please can you let me say sorry?
HE SIGHS
OK.
I said OK.
Say it!
Go on, say sorry.
Say sorry, and then I can say
it's OK, and everything's all right.
That's what you want, isn't it?
'That was exactly what I wanted.'
No.
It's not OK. It's just how it is.
It wasn't just you...
What's that supposed to mean?
..who had a bad time.
It's not a competition.
I nearly died.
Oh, apparently it is.
I NEARLY...DIED!
I know. I was there.
I'm not the answer, James.
'She was right.
'It was over.'
HE STARTS ENGINE
What about Bonnie?
Fuck Bonnie.
Oh!
Er...
Don't call the police.
If you do,
I'll come back and I'll kill you.
I won't.
What happened?
I was scared. You're scary.
OK.
Good.
MUSIC: I'm Not Like Everybody Else
by The Chocolate Watchband
# I'm not like everybody else
# And I don't wanna ball about
like everybody else
# And I don't wanna live my life
# And I don't wanna say I'm fine
like everybody else
# Cos I'm not like everybody else
# I'm not like everybody else #