Woman over walkie-talkie:
They're coming up on
vinton and 20th now...
Check over that way,
would you?
Will do.
...heading over to salvage
and recycling.
Man over walkie-talkie:
Copy that. I'm about 5 out.
You see a guy
in a corduroy coat go by?
Sir?
Sir.
Young guy, dark hair,
corduroy coat.
How about it?
Hey, Nick.
Come here.
Wanna come on
out here?
Go ahead and open
your jacket for me.
I'm placing you
under arrest, sir.
Put your hands
on your head, please.
Nick, you want
to grab those for me?
Nick:
You got it.
All right, let's go.
Nice job.
Say nothing, you understand?!
Get a lawyer!
Get a lawyer.
Asshole.
Ladies.
Sam:
Hey, gene.
Raquel:
Nice lunch?
Oh, yeah.
Whatcha need?
Rolls about
to come out.
You got it.
Jimmy: So, can I, uh,
tell Howard
you're not quitting
or retiring or whatever?
And can we take all this shit
down off the walls?
I'm gonna go call Howard.
Jimmy.
You do realize
you just confessed to a felony?
I guess.
But you feel better,
right?
Besides,
it's your word against mine.
Ohh!
Ugh!
Jimmy: Absolutely.
Coming back.
What's it matter
what I said, Howard?
Why you lookin' a gift horse
in the mouth?
He just --
yeah, well, whatever it was,
he's over it now, all right?
And by the way, you're welcome.
Well,
Howard's breathing again.
You made him
very happy.
Jimmy!
Jimmy,
if you're gonna help,
a-at least use a little finesse,
would you?
"Finesse"?
Whaddya...
Would --
quit yanking at it.
You're -- you're pulling
the varnish
right off the walnut.
Not pullin'
any varnish off the walnut.
You most certainly are.
Look. Look! See?
Well, maybe you shoulda thought
about the friggin' walnut
before you covered it
in duct tape.
I don't need
your help!
I don't recall
ever asking for it.
I'm sorry,
okay?
Finesse, fine.
Show me. Demonstrate.
Like this.
Gently...
...roll it
with your thumbs.
Left,
and then right.
See?
Alternate the thumbs,
up and down.
Get a nice,
tight roll going.
Chuck,
i think you're the one
that needs a nice,
tight roll.
Come on.
Show me.
Gently.
Left,
then right.
Left, right.
I get it.
Wax on, wax off.
Mr. miyagi.
"Karate kid."
Seriously?
Oh, my god.
"The adventures of Mabel."
I-i haven't thought about this
in forever.
You remember this,
Chuck?
I do.
Harry thurston peck.
Yeah!
Mabel goes
into the mountain,
and she meets
the king of the brownies,
and he gives her...
Some kind of
super delicious jelly and...
Holy crap.
1912.
Yeah. Belonged to
grammie Davenport.
She wrote her name
in it.
She was reading that
to her schoolkids
the year
the Titanic went down.
Damn.
And mom
read it to me.
I read it
to you.
You don't remember.
Yeah, yeah.
I do,
now that you say it.
Yeah.
What was I --
like 5 or 6?
You had
this weird night-light
that you were
so crazy about.
It was, um...
It was daffy duck!
It was some daffy duck rip-off
with this weird red bill.
Mouth. Oh, yeah, yeah,
the bill. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it used to get so
hot, we thought it would
burn the house down, but --
Right.
...You wouldn't
let anybody touch it.
Yeah, that's a --
you got a great memory, Chuck.
That red bill
and everything.
Hey.
What was the name
of that little girl
that lived, uh,
three houses up from us?
She had, like,
a pageboy haircut.
Jimmy.
And she was always in the dirt,
always dirty.
Jimmy!
I liked her.
She was always --
Jimmy.
Don't think I'll ever forget
what happened here today.
And you will pay.
You didn't mention
my garden.
Well, your garden
is part of your backyard,
so it's automatically
included
in the property
that goes to jenn.
It comes
with the house, mom.
Well, I think you need
to mention it by name
in case some dirty judge
decides to play tricks.
Okay,
we can do that.
Let's see.
Garden.
Hey, I'm back.
Oh, hi, ladies.
Jimmy mcgill.
Hey, Jimmy.
We are almost done here.
Great.
Can I, uh...
We're almost done.
I'll be with you
in a minute.
Oh.
And mention
my Lily pond.
It's in my garden.
Lily pond.
Kim:
Okay, ladies.
Jenn: Thanks so much
for your help.
Oh,
you're very welcome.
Thank you both
for being so patient.
And, Mrs. aherne,
if you or Margaret
ever need anything from me --
anything at all --
you can call me
day or night.
This is Mrs. siemasko
and her daughter jenn.
I'm sorry. I got my wires
crossed a little.
Uh...
Bye.
Mrs. siemasko: Bye.
Drive safe.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
You are
a superhero.
I owe you big-time.
So, how's Chuck?
Crisis averted...
I guess.
I mean, he's back to being
the same old Chuck, so...
Wanna talk about it?
Depends.
It may
or may not involve
that thing you said you never,
ever wanted to discuss.
Um.
Okay, then, thanks.
I gotta
get back to it.
How 'bout
we call it a day?
I'll buy you
some dinner.
You're kidding,
right?
You realize
how far behind I am?
Not to mention now I've got
eight entire wills to finish up.
Whaddya talking about?
I'll do the wills.
No, you won't.
'Course I will.
Do the wills.
They're my clients.
You and I aren't partners,
remember?
Once I take
these people on,
I can't just reassign them
to you.
Aw, c'mon.
Why you getting all,
like, legal on me, huh?
Who cares?
Look, I told every single
one of them the situation --
that they'd be getting me
instead of you.
I tried to talk them all
into coming back another day.
Six of 'em left.
Maybe you'll get those back.
I mean, look, if this is about
the money, I have --
it's not about the money.
You can keep the money.
Don't act
like I wanted this.
Jesus, like I need more
on my plate.
Are you mad?
I'm not mad.
I'm just, uh...
...thinking about things.
For 10 minutes today,
Chuck didn't hate me.
I forgot
what that felt like.
Chuck: Jimmy.
You do realize
you just confessed to a felony?
Jimmy: I guess.
But you feel better,
right?
Besides,
it's your word against mine.
That's the end of it.
Howard?
That's the end.
Mm.
Could you...?
Oh, yeah.
Well, now do you
believe me?
I don't even know
where to begin.
But yes,
i believe you.
Your brother is one
world-class son of a bitch.
No offense.
I just -- I really wish
you'd told me
about these plans of yours
before you went out and did it.
I know, Howard,
and I regret misleading you.
It's just that
a certain...
Vérité
had to be established.
I'm not talking about
the heart attack
that you nearly
gave me.
Chuck,
this tape --
I'm not sure
exactly what it accomplishes.
Look, you know evidentiary rules
better than I do,
but a secretly
recorded tape
with a problematic
chain of evidence?
You're gonna have a helluva time
getting that admitted.
I agree.
And if you somehow put it
in front of a jury,
Jimmy'd call
a dozen audio experts,
say that voice
isn't his,
say the -- the tape
had been edited.
He would, indeed.
Are you thinking about
playing this
for Kevin wachtell
at mesa verde?
Because as much
as I would love to,
that ship has sailed.
We're never getting them back,
regardless.
Oh, I doubt we could even
get in the door over there.
Chuck, if that tape is useless
in a court of law
and no help
in the court of public opinion,
what's the point?
Because I can't think of
a single use for it.
I can.
hey, mister,
we're closin' in 15 minutes.
Call me a cab,
will ya?
What about
your vehicle?
Keep it.
Man: Five j's
auto salvage.
Broadway, uh,
at -- at Bobby foster's.
Yeah, ehr-- ehr-- ehr--
how is it again?
Ehrmantraut.
Yeah, ehrmantraut.
Yeah.
Just tell him
to pull up to the gate and honk.
Okay, yeah.
Thanks.
They're on their way.
Thank you.
you sell a gas cap
for an '87 caprice wagon?
Should.
Gm caps should be in the blue
on the bottom there.
Torrent downloaded from RARBG
Now, you're sure
i can't help you
carry those to your car,
Mrs. vankamp?
Don't be a silly.
I only hope I didn't take
too much of your time
with all my
dusty old photos.
Goodness, no.
Your -- your grandson's wedding
was gorgeous.
When I come back,
I'll show you
my niece's confirmation.
Wait'll you see
the flowers!
Ohh!
Roses.
Uh-huh.
Petunias, orchids.
Yeah.
They don't smell,
you know?
Well...
And baby's breath
and bachelor buttons.
Okay.
Lilies of the valley.
Well, I'll believe it
when I see it.
Daisies --
daisies don't tell.
Now I've got something
to look forward to.
Okay.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye.
See ya!
Uh, thank you
for waiting so patiently.
Who do we have next?
That'd be me.
Hello, hello.
It's so good
to see you again.
I escorted you and your clients
onto my base.
I treated you
with hospitality and respect,
and now
i come to find
every word out of your mouth
is a damn lie.
Captain, please.
Why don't -- sit down.
Take a load off.
Hey, I'll get you
a complimentary coffee
or a soft drink?
And your so-called war hero,
"fudge" talbott?
No such person --
never was.
Granted, some artistic license
may have been taken.
You entered government property
under false pretenses, sir.
Whoa, whoa.
I am no expert
on your procedures
and your protocols
and whatnot,
so if -- if we failed to
cross a "t" or dot an "i,"
I sincerely apologize
for any misunderstanding.
N-no, no, no, it's not
a misunderstanding!
Just step back!
B-big picture this, okay?!
It --
what damage was done?!
Hey,
who was hurt, huh?
What was damaged?
The -- the base
is still there, right?
The b-52 is,
i presume, still --
b-29.
Huh?
B-29.
Fifi's a b-29.
I don't...
Oh, this is all just
one big joke to you, huh?
You don't like
the commercial.
No, no, I don't,
but this has nothing to do
with the comm--
well, constructive criticism
is always welcome.
But I didn't --
but you should realize
that most people find it
uplifting -- patriotic, even.
No.
You check
your recruiting numbers.
I-i-i --
i think you're gonna see
an uptick, and you know what?
If it turns out that fudge
wasn't actually in the war --
fudge is not a person.
He wasn't in the war.
Well,
neither was tom cruise,
and look what "top gun" did
for you.
You lied to me,
you lied to my face,
and I can't let you
get away with it.
I-i think we just --
we're just gonna have to
agree to disagree,
so, uh, can I get you
that coffee to go or...?
No, no. I-I'm gonna tell you
what's happening now.
You're gonna take that ad
off the air.
And if you play that ad
one more time,
I'm gonna go
to the judge advocate,
and we will
take you down --
trespassing,
false representation,
stolen valor --
the whole nine yards.
Seriously, for eight seconds
of a TV commercial?
You take that ad down,
or there'll be hell to pay.
That clear enough
for you?
Make me.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Make you?
Yeah, let's do this.
You bring
your commander down here,
and I'll explain to him
how you let us on the base,
red-carpet treatment.
No, b-because you lied
your way in.
Not how
i remember it.
What happened --
and I've got witnesses
to back me up.
Do you like being
an air force captain, huh?
You think
the United States
wants to bring action against
an old man in a wheelchair?!
He was standing on TV.
He wasn't even in a wheelchair!
Well, yeah.
Well, periodically,
he is.
And when he shows up
in court,
you better believe
he'll be in a wheelchair!
Right, because you're an
ambulance-chasing piece of shit,
'cause you're all
the same --
you're the same
as all the others.
Always on a high horse.
Always trying to make me
feel like I'm --
look, um,
I'm a lawyer,
and this is what I do
all day, every day,
so h-how about this?
I-i won't
fly jet planes --
you, uh,
stay out of court.
Does that sound good?
You know,
guys like you --
you think
you're so damn smart,
and you think you don't have to
play straight with anybody.
The wheel
is gonna turn.
It always does.
"A lawyer
you can trust."
My ass!
Thank you
for your service!
3:30 in the morning?
Seriously?
You get me that?
I don't know.
It's a real thing?
Yeah.
Then, yeah.
I know someone who can get it.
How much?
What do I look like --
radioshack?
It's gonna cost you
whatever it costs me,
plus my end.
Well, let's start
with that.
Normally,
be about $500,
but seeing that this is
an after-hours house call,
let's make it
a grand.
Hey,
how's the pup?
Doing okay?
Yeah.
She's not being left alone
all day, is she?
She's got
plenty of company.
Good.
Hey, uh, this is gonna
take me a few days,
so I'll let you know.
And next time,
let's try to make business
happen during business hours.
Mm-hmm.
Well, this will certainly help
my Thursday powerpoint.
Excellent.
That's a draft letter from Kevin
to the Arizona regulator.
I know he likes
the personal touch.
He's gonna love it.
Oh, I can't believe you did
all of this in three days.
Am I reading this right --
did you get the rehearing
moved up?
Yeah. Those are
three possible dates,
pending your
and Kevin's schedule.
The soonest I could get
is the 4th.
You moved it up
almost three weeks.
I'll give it another shot
and see if I can do better.
Are you kidding me?
Kevin'll be
popping champagne!
I knew
you were the right one for this.
Well, I appreciate
the opportunity.
Yeah, you should have heard
how that arrogant jerk
spoke to me
at the hearing.
Right there,
in front of Kevin,
he accuses me
of muddying the waters --
muddying...The...Waters.
I mean,
he's the one
who can't even
get the address right.
Yeah, that's --
wow.
I know you have friends
over at hhm,
and they sure talk a good game,
but come on.
Guys like that,
when crunch time comes,
it's always
someone else's fault.
Paige?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's almost 11:30.
Thanks, Greta.
I'll be right up.
So, are we still on
for lunch Tuesday?
Kim:
Absolutely.
And, Paige, thank you...
For everything.
Paige:
No, thank you
for cleaning up that mess
mcgill left behind.
Actually, would you mind
if I messenger that over
tomorrow morning,
first thing?
I'd like to take one last look
before we submit,
just double-check
a few things.
Sure.
So, tomorrow, first thing?
Absolutely. Thanks.
I'll see you,
Paige.
Okay, bye.
[Telephone ringing in distance,
How's it coming
in there?
Good!
Don't mean
to rush ya.
No, it's okay.
I'm done.
Half a rainbow?
Don't you want
to keep going
till you do
the whole thing?
No.
If you're done, I'm done.
You know, your clients
seem to like that rainbow.
Think they're gonna miss it?
Wait till they see
what's going up next.
They're gonna love it.
You're gonna love it.
Yeah?
Should I be worried?
Nope.
Whaddya say
we get the hell outta here?
Sounds good.
Mm.
You ready ta hit it?
Sorry. I just need
to check one thing.
It'll be two minutes,
tops.
Chuck: Ernesto.
Morning,
Mr. mcgill.
They didn't have
fuji apples,
so I got you honeycrisp.
Hope that's all right.
I'm sure
it'll be fine.
Um, did you get the,
uh...
Yeah.
I got them.
I went ahead and, um --
I figured
i should maybe...
I wrapped them up --
you know, for safety.
That's very thoughtful
of you,
but I need them now,
so, if you...
You sure it's okay?
It's okay.
Um.
Yip.
Perfect.
Ah.
Shit!
Ahh.
Ernesto,
could you come in here, please?
Thought
i could do this myself.
Uh, would you mind, uh,
changing the batteries?
Sure thing,
Mr. mcgill.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Jimmy:
I changed 1261 to 1216.
It was me.
Turn that off!
Turn it off!
Jimmy:
It all went down exactly --
turn it off!
Aah!
You did not hear that!
All right.
Okay, Ernesto...
That'sss my fault,
not yours.
Um, but now that
you've heard it,
you need
to understand something.
You know
about confidentiality, right?
As employees
of Hamlin, Hamlin, mcgill,
you and I are both bound
by the strictures
of client confidentiality --
by law, both of us --
by law.
You understand
what I'm saying?
So I'm not
supposed to tell anyone?
That's right,
no matter who,
no matter what reasons
you think you might have,
you must not --
you cannot tell anyone.
There could be
terrible consequences --
life-changing consequences.
And we don't want you
to get into trouble.
If something were to happen
to you because of this,
I'd feel sick about it.
Okay.
Enough said.
I guess...
I'll go finish
puttin' away the groceries.
Okay?
Thank you,
Ernesto.
Hmm.
Highs for Tuesday --
high temperatures
will be in the mid-60s
with
5- to 10-mile-per-hour winds,
but expect scattered showers
Tuesday night
with lows in the 40s.
Wednesday will be partly cloudy
with high temperatures
in the mid-50s.
The grants area will have
temperatures in the mid-40s,
with southwest winds
15 to 20 miles per hour.
Now let's get back to more
of your favorite
"sound souvenir oldies"
with "the Steve ricketts
program" on kdsk, 92.7 fm.
- Thank you, Derek.
-  Love those  temperatures -- it's almost  like...