He's, um, connected.
I mean, he's a cartel guy.
Do you want to be a
friend of the cartel?
JIMMY: What do you have
to do with Lalo Salamanca?
I need you to get him out on bail.
I represent someone who has an interest.
JIMMY: Witness tampering.
Mr. DeGuzman should be granted bond.
- [GAVEL BANGS]
- $7 million.
I'm gonna need you to pick it up.
[CÉSAR CASTRO Y SU CONJUNTO'S
"DEJAME QUERERTE" PLAYS]
♪♪
♪ Este amor inmenso ♪
♪ Que llevo en el alma ♪
♪ Me roba la calma ♪
♪ Un presentimiento ♪
♪ Pienso que si un día... ♪
[CONVERSING IN SPANISH] _
- ♪ ... De mi te cansaras ♪
- _
- ♪ No resistiría, no resistiría ♪
♪ Que me abandonaras ♪
♪ Por qué ♪
♪ Sin ti no quiero la vi... ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
♪♪
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
[DOOR CREAKING]
♪♪
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪♪
[CELLPHONE DIALING]
Hey.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
♪♪
LALO: [LAUGHING]
JIMMY: What's so funny?
Eh.
Ah, you wouldn't get it.
- Okay.
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna take, uh,
25 South to Las Cruces.
You can pick up 10 West from there.
Hey, write this down,
man... es complicado.
Uh, 10 West at Las Cruces.
A little past Deming,
there's a state road.
It's 146.
Uh, follow the signs to Antelope Wells
until Mile Marker 223.
Turn off at the dirt road
and take it 30 miles south.
30 miles down a dirt road?
Fewer eyes out in the desert, you know?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Actually, it's 31.6,
so make sure that you use
the little, uh, you know,
trip-meter thing on the
odometer or whatever.
Anyway, once you get there,
you're gonna see a well.
It's really old, you know, broken down.
Uh, what does this well look like?
It looks like a well.
It's the only one out there.
And can you see it from the road?
[CHUCKLING] Yeah, you'll see
it... don't worry about it.
My cousins are gonna meet
you there with the money,
9:00 a.m.
You'll like them. They're good boys.
[SIGHS] I'll bet. Um. [CLICKS TONGUE]
Hey, I have an idea...
why not have these cousins of yours
bring the money just all the way here?
Cut out the middle man.
Yeah, see, the thing is,
this whole thing has to be
very, uh, low profile, you know?
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
There are people...
let's say competitors of mine...
people who want to keep me in here.
And so, you know, my
cousins come into town...
those people will notice.
What about Nacho Varga, right?
Would your "competitors" notice him?
He seems like he's got a pretty
good head on his shoulders.
Ignacio?
Yeah, sure, I mean,
he's good for a lot of things.
But with $7 million?
[SCOFFS] Guy like that
could get real dumb real fast, you know?
Hey, you're the right guy for this.
You're nobody... I mean, no offense,
but nobody's gonna look twice at you.
Yeah, sure. Um.
Hey, look, maybe this
isn't your thing, you know?
I mean, that's okay. I get it.
Y-You did good in court...
we'll leave it at that.
[CHUCKLING] Oh, thanks, that's...
I appreciate that.
Don't worry about it.
I'll find somebody else, you know?
Yeah, uh, so, I guess we're done here.
Guess so.
[BREATHES SHARPLY] Alright.
Um, I will... I'm gonna shred these,
and, uh... if there's
anything else you need,
any legal services...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got your number.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
[CLICKS] This is it. Hey.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CLEARS THROAT] A hundred thousand?
Dollars.
Yeah.
That's a lot of money.
To bring back $7 mil?
And I'm the best guy to do it?
Uh, that's actually
less than 2% commission,
and I think it's right.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
So, 100K for a little drive
through the desert, huh?
That's the price.
Done.
[CLICKS]
[DOOR CREAKS LIGHTLY]
[WATER RUNNING IN DISTANCE]
[LOCK ENGAGES]
Hey. I'm home.
JIMMY: Great. I'll be out in a sec!
[WATER STOPS]
Evening shower, huh?
JIMMY: Yeah.
Got an early day tomorrow.
[SIGHS]
Hey, I hope you're hungry.
I'm making fajitas.
You're cooking?
Why not?
I picked up some strip
steak on the way home.
And it's been marinating
for a couple hours
in a secret blend of herbs and spices.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Something I like to call "Old El Paso".
[CHUCKLES]
It sounds exotic.
It'll be delicious... you'll see.
I, uh, I have some business news.
You're a friend of the cartel.
Is that it?
Not exactly.
Maybe.
You got him bail?
Some evidence fell into my lap.
I was kind of obligated to use it,
you know, for my client.
[SIGHS]
When you said you couldn't do it,
I knew you'd find a way.
[CLICKS TONGUE, BREATHES SHARPLY]
There's a complication.
Remember that time you had a P.D. case
with the kid whose
parents kicked him out
because he got caught with a joint?
Yeah.
And you... you had to drive
all the way out to the uncle's house...
I think it was in Moriarty...
to pick up the bail?
- Well...
- Wait, what?
So, what... you're saying
- you're gonna pick up Salamanca's bail?
- Yeah.
Only it's a little further than Moriarty
and a little more money.
How much?
Seven.
- Seven thousand?
- Million.
$7 million?
[CHUCKLING] Yeah.
You're going to pick up
$7 million of cartel money?
I know what you're
thinking, but it's safe.
Completely.
And it's just a quick
drive down by the border.
- I'll be right back.
- The border?
Jimmy, you are an
attorney, not a bagman.
There's no amount of
money that is worth this.
- Can't his people do it?
- He trusts me.
I'm his attorney. That's it.
You're making a bigger deal out of this
- than you need to.
- What?!
- You're gonna...
- I will pick it up in the morning,
I will be done, and I'll
be home before you will.
Okay. Then I'm going with you.
[SCOFFS] Well, they're
only expecting me.
You know, one guy.
I mean, that's kind
of the whole point...
you know, security through obscurity.
- Jimmy, this is insane.
- I don't e...
No, listen, it's just little ol' me
in my little ol' Suzuki Esteem.
And there has never been
more than 50 bucks in an Esteem
in the history of Esteems.
- So, no one's gonna look at me twice.
- [SIGHS]
You sound like you are
talking yourself into this.
I will be okay.
I swear.
If I smell even the faintest whiff
of anything wrong,
I'll be out of there like a shot.
I don't like this.
I don't want you to do it.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
Kim. Listen.
I swear... okay?... I'll be fine.
[WATER DRIPPING]
[BIRDS CAWING]
[WIND RUSHING SOFTLY]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Yo soy abogado.
Yo soy... abogado.
[SIGHS]
[BOTTLE TAPS LIGHTLY]
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[WHISPERING] Yo soy abogado.
Yo soy abogado. Yo soy abogado.
Abogado, abogado, abogado.
Yo...
Yo soy...
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
Yo soy abogado.
A-Abogado.
Abogado.
L-Lawyer?
Fr-From Lalo?
Eduardo.
Sent me to pick up the, uh, dinero?
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'll just take these back to Lalo.
You guys are... are just gonna just go?
Oh, that'll work.
Uh, buenos días.
- [ENGINE REVS]
- Alright.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[SIGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Woof.
[TO THE TUNE OF "99 BOTTLES OF BEER"]
♪ Seven million dollars
of cash in the trunk ♪
♪ Seven million dollars of cash ♪
♪ Take one dollar ♪
♪ Pass it a... rollar ♪
♪ Six million, nine hundred,
ninety-nine thousand... ♪
♪ Crappy service ♪
[CELLPHONE THUMPS LIGHTLY]
♪ Six million nine hundred
ninety-nine thousand... ♪
♪ [GARBLED] ... ninety-nine
dollars of cash in the trunk ♪
♪ Take... a buck ♪
♪ Pass it for luck ♪
♪ Six million nine hundred
ninety-nine thousand nine... ♪
♪ Nine hundred ninety-nine... ♪
Go by!
♪♪
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
♪♪
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Oh, nuts.
♪♪
Okay, yeah.
C-Coming out... slowly.
[KEYS JINGLING]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[CAR DOOR CREAKS]
♪♪
¿Abogado?
I think... I think I have a sense
of what you want here.
- It's in the trunk.
- [KEYS JINGLING]
Yeah, good. Take those.
♪♪
[BAG THUMPS]
[BAG UNZIPS]
[BAG ZIPS]
♪♪
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Tssss!
Whoah, whoah! What? No, no.
That... That's not what he meant.
This is a mistake. It's b-big.
iAbogado! iAbogado!
iEl amigo del cártel!
No!
Ahh!
[GUNSHOT]
♪♪
[THUDS]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNFIRE]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
iMuévanse!
♪♪
[GASPS]
[GASPING, GRUNTS]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[AIR HISSING FROM TIRES]
♪♪
[SHELL CASINGS CLINKING]
[AIR HISSES FROM TIRES]
♪♪
[GASPS]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GUNFIRE STOPS]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNFIRE]
[GUNFIRE STOPS]
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
♪♪
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
♪♪
[GUNFIRE]
[GUNSHOTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪♪
[GASPING]
[GUNSHOT]
♪♪
[VEHICLE DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
You hit?
♪♪
Hit?
Are you shot?
♪♪
Get up.
Shot?
You're in shock.
♪♪
You stay here and breathe.
[FOOTSTEPS]
♪♪
[LIQUID TRICKLING]
[SIGHS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SIGHS LIGHTLY]
[KEYS JINGLE]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE WHIRS IN DISTANCE]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Hey.
You're alive.
Focus on that.
You'll be okay.
[ENGINE SPUTTERS, STOPS]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[BIRD CAWING]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Get out.
The alternator's shot.
Literally.
Alright.
I'm gonna need you to
put your back into this.
Push!
JIMMY: [GRUNTING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[PANTING]
Oh, oh! Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
MIKE: What is it?
[GRUNTS]
Where is it... ?
[GRUNTS] Oh.
Mnh.
[METAL CREAKS]
[THUMPING]
[CREAKING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[GRUNTS]
Did you know all this was gonna happen?
If I did, I woulda brought more guys.
Let's get that to where it belongs.
This way.
Well, uh, home is that way.
One of those guys got away.
In a car.
On the road.
This road.
We gotta get off it.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[PANTING]
[BAGS THUMP]
♪♪
Ohh!
Big mistake.
Discontinuing.
The thousand dollar bill.
Mnh. Big.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
These woulda been so much lighter.
Hey.
[PANTING]
How about we, uh, take turns
with these bad boys, you know?
So we both stay fresh.
Fine.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I got an idea.
Let's dig a hole.
- A hole.
- Yeah.
Walk outta here, get to civilization,
drive back, pick it up.
Work smarter, not harder.
- You'll never find it.
- No, I will,
'cause I'll memorize the landmarks.
Like this tree.
Can't miss it.
That hill? That's distinctive.
It's got a... hill shape.
Yeah, very different from
the couple dozen trees
that we've seen on hillsides
that we've walked past.
I will remember... I will
find this tree.
Hm.
That's hard pack.
If you manage to dig a hole
big enough for those two bags,
you might as well dig one for yourself.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, come on.
That's not gonna work.
[CHUCKLES]
You're wasting energy.
I'm almost there.
[GRUNTS]
[SCRAPING]
It's working. [CHUCKLES]
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
Stop.
♪♪
Put that away. They'll see it.
You take off anything
that'll catch the light.
Is it him?
Oh, yeah.
It looks like they're
doing a grid search.
Meaning?
Meaning they've found your car.
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
[SIGHS LIGHTLY]
MIKE: I'd go easy on that.
Hey, why are we camping?
I mean, shouldn't we keep walking?
- It's cooler at night.
- [BREATHES SHARPLY]
You go out there in the dark,
you're gonna break your
leg in a prairie dog hole.
[GRUNTING]
Hey, we gotta be halfway there, right?
Almost.
[WHISPERING] "Almost".
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
♪♪
[CLICKS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[SIGHS]
I should've been home hours ago.
This will be tearing her up.
Oh, she's just gonna think
you're out cattin' around.
No, she won't.
She gonna think I'm chopped to pieces,
dead in some ditch.
And why is she gonna think that?
Are you saying she
knows what you're doing?
Not, y'know, the details.
Just she knows I'm picking up money
down by the border.
That's all.
You told your girlfriend
what you're doing.
My wife.
Wife.
Yeah. Wife.
Congratulations.
And what's your wife gonna do with
this information, do you think?
- Call the cops?
- No.
No?
People get scared, call the cops.
- Pretty standard.
- She's not calling any cops.
Her mother.
Girls at the book club.
Gonna call her boss,
tell her about her missing husband.
No, she's not doing any of that, okay?
She knows better.
She's just gonna be scared
out of her mind, is all.
Oh.
Well... let's hope you're right.
[CHUCKLES]
She knows...
She's in the game now.
What? No. She's not in "the game".
Alright? She's not even game-adjacent.
I just told her the truth.
A little slice of the truth.
That's all.
Hmm.
She's not in "the game".
Yeah.
[SNIFFLES]
Ah.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
Well, I can't make a fire.
Our guy may still be out there.
Ohh.
I got two of these. You want one?
No thanks.
Gets cold fast.
I'm fine. Thanks.
You suit yourself.
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- [KEYS JINGLE, DOOR UNLOCKS]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
- Ma'am, do you want me to... ?
- Yes, please.
[HANDCUFFS CLICKING]
Thank you.
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[KEYS JINGLE, LOCK ENGAGES]
I know I misrepresented myself
as a member of your legal team.
I apologize... for that.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I wouldn't be here right now
if I didn't absolutely have to be.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
I know who you are...
who you actually are.
We have something in common.
You want to know where your money is.
I want to find Saul Goodman.
If you tell me where you sent him,
I won't alert the authorities.
I won't tell anyone.
I will find him, and
you'll get your money.
[SIGHS]
Mr. Salamanca...
Who the hell are you
that he tells you my business?
He didn't betray your confidence.
We're married,
which means I have spousal privilege...
anything he says to me stays with me.
No one can make me discuss it.
It's as bulletproof as
lawyer-client privilege.
So you're his wife?
Yes.
Una guera.
Bien por él.
[CHUCKLES]
So, you're his wife,
and you... love him.
And he didn't come home last night,
and you got scared enough
to come down here and talk to me.
[LAUGHS]
What makes you think he didn't
run off with my money, huh?
He did not run off with your money.
Yeah, maybe not.
Not without you.
Just tell me where you sent him.
That's all I need.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I don't think so.
Your man... he's, um,
he's like the cucaracha...
you know, a born survivor.
If trouble found him, give it a day.
If he's alive, he'll show.
Mm. And if he's... ?
Well, then, day's not gonna
make a difference, is it?
Alright, well...
nice to meet you, Mrs. Goodman.
Wait, um... Mr. Salamanca...
[THUMPING]
Done!
[KEYS JINGLE, LOCK DISENGAGES]
- [DOOR CREAKING]
- [GROANS LIGHTLY]
[HANDCUFFS CLICKING]
[WIND RUSHING]
[SIGHS]
Hey.
I wouldn't waste that.
Waste what?
I don't have enough of
this for the both of us.
[SIGHS]
[LABI SIFFRE'S "I GOT THE..." PLAYS]
♪♪
♪ Just a lonely soul ♪
♪ Slowly dyin' ♪
♪ I was smilin' hard ♪
♪ But I was lyin' ♪
♪ Then you sailed along ♪
♪ With your sweet dream ♪
♪ When you stole my heart ♪
♪ I was livid ♪
♪ Mornin' come, sun don't shine ♪
♪ I'll get by without you ♪
♪ I was lost, but now I'm found ♪
♪ Tell me, love, it was you ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
JIMMY: [BREATHES SHARPLY]
More.
- No.
- More.
No.
If you want more...
[SIGHS]
Alright.
Come on. Let's go.
[SIGHS]
Hold it.
I have an idea.
[GRUNTS]
That's not gonna work.
It's gonna work.
[GRUNTS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
[WHEEZING]
You gonna get that?
Get what?
Oh.
Got it.
Oh, crap.
MIKE: Oh.
[GRUNTS] Hey...
Ah, shit! Aah!
[GASPING]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
That's it. I'm done.
Done! Done!
Quiet.
Why? I'm quiet, I'm loud...
I'm gonna die in this
dirt one way or the other.
Let's get it over with.
- MIKE: Get up.
- No.
I'm not going.
I'm done.
Everything hurts.
God, I'm so thirsty.
You need to drink.
What's the point?
So they can find a corpse
with a mouthful of piss?
That's not gonna happen.
Now, get up.
Come on.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GROANS]
[THUMPS] Ohh.
Oh, God.
Oh, no. How?
How the hell are you still going?
Because I know why I'm out here.
That's how.
I know what it's for.
And I can't drag that
money out of here by myself.
So you... you get up,
and you get up now.
What it's for?
What... is it for?
I have people.
I have people waiting for me.
They don't know what
I do... they never will.
They're protected.
But I do what I do so they
can have a better life.
And if I live or if I die,
it really doesn't make
a difference to me,
as long as they have what they need.
So when it's my time to go,
I will go knowing I did
everything I could for them.
Now, you ask me how I keep going?
That's how.
Stay down.
He's back.
[BAG ZIPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Lie low.
We're gonna have to wait him out.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
♪♪
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[GROANS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪♪
JIMMY: Hey.
Get that thing ready.
♪♪
C'mon, you asshole.
You want this $7 mil?
C'mon.
I'm just walking here
like a goddamn idiot.
[WEAPON COCKS]
♪♪
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
Come and get some, you dickhead.
♪♪
Come on, you sonovabitch!
Look at me!
♪♪
MIKE: Yeah.
There you go.
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
♪♪
Come on. Come on.
[TIRES SCREECH, GLASS SHATTERS]
[METAL GROANING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[ENGINE RUMBLING SOFTLY]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[RUMBLING CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
[GRUNTS]
[RUMBLING SLOWS, STOPS]
[AIR HISSES]
[WIND RUSHING]