Busy day?
Not really.
I've had a bit of a crazy one!
Oh, yeah?
Did you hear about the murder?
Yeah. A motel owner.
Only an hour up the road.
Nasty.
Really?
Can't really tell you too much
about it, though.
OK.
He got shot through the chin.
Blood - all over the ceiling.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Cleaner found him in the cupboard.
What?
Oh, wardrobe.
Whoever did it, they hid the body
in a wardrobe. Jesus.
Yep. There's some weirdos
out there.
Daughter's birthday tomorrow.
She's three.
Right.
Stay safe.
SHE CLOSES TILL
# I'm your hoochie-coochie man
# Oh, yeah
# Everybody knows, oh, yeah... #
POLICE RADIO:
Control to Sid, over.
Go ahead.
Where have you been?
In a shop.
Attention Code 2.
In the cafe on Forest Road up
by the crossing.
Can you check in?
I was on my way home.
Yes. Can you check it?
Roger. Out.
How did you know where I live?
James told me last night.
'Thanks, James.'
'This is pretty awkward.
'What do you say to someone
you abandoned in a car park?'
Do you want a scone?
OK.
'Maybe I should have been nicer
to her.'
Sit down and I'll bring it over.
'She's pretty harmless.
'She's just strange.'
Can I have a glass of water? Yeah.
Do you have ice?
No.
Shit!
SHE GULPS
Do you want some jam? No, thank you.
I'm sorry we left you.
That's OK.
No, it's not OK.
It's like a really shit thing to do.
I've had a bad couple of days.
Well, you've said sorry now.
Yeah.
MUFFLED WOMAN'S VOICE
Hello?
MUFFLED VOICE
If you can hear me, help...
Hello?
I need help!
Oh, shit!
Did you see your sister?
She was out.
Is something wrong?
TOILET FLUSHES
I'd give it a minute in there.
Sorry.
I thought this place was empty.
It will be soon.
Geri's just a really slow eater.
Are you OK?
You don't look very well.
I'm fine.
Where's James?
He's gone.
Where did he go?
I don't know. I just know
that he's not here.
Well, you could phone him.
What?
You could get him to come here. Why
would I wanna get him to come here?
HE SNIFFS
Do you wanna tell me
what's going on, please?
I told you.
I came to give you this.
You left it.
Well, I'm getting a divorce,
so I probably won't be needing it.
And I wanted to see you both.
Why? What for?
I think you knew my boyfriend.
What?
Yeah. You killed him.
'Oh, fuck!'
Lyss,
can you put that on my tab? Yes.
I get paid Friday. OK. No, wait.
Thursday. OK.
Is Thursday the 4th?
Geri, it's fine.
Thanks.
All right?
Yes.
Night, then! Night.
You sent the bullets? Yes.
Are you scared?
A bit.
You spelled my name wrong. What?
Why did you kill him?
Don't you know?
I want you to tell me.
Cos he was gonna hurt me. Don't lie.
I'm not lying.
He was.
Tell me what you did to him.
Tell me!
We broke into his house.
Whose house? You know who.
Say it!
The Professor, Clive,
we broke into his house.
Why did you break into his house?
I dunno. We were 17.
We drank some of his vodka
and his wine.
We ate some of his food,
put his record on,
and then I went to bed.
Then what?
Then I woke up.
And he'd come back.
And he was there in the room.
Then he shut the door.
You were in his bedroom?
Yeah.
What did it look like?
What?
Nothing.
Then what?
He asked me if I was a virgin,
and then he hit me. Shut up!
Held me down, and then he tried
to get on top of me.
Shut up!
You asked me to tell you.
VEHICLE PULLS UP
Who's that?
How the fuck should I know?
Did you call the police? No!
When would I have done that?
Get rid of them, or I'll kill them
as well as you!
'I'm definitely dying, then!'
Evening.
Hiya.
Hello.
Everything all right?
Yeah, fine.
We, um, had an emergency call from
here. Was that you?
No. Everything's fine.
Oh.
Hmm.
Must have been some kind of mix-up.
Just the two of you here?
Yes.
Mind if I, uh, have a look around?
Sure.
All fine. Yeah.
Right.
Guess I'll be on my way, then.
OK. OK.
Wait.
Is that apple strudel?
Um... Yeah.
Lovely.
Yes, please!
You made that yourself?
No.
Ah.
INTERNALLY: I've never been so happy
and so sad to see someone.
I'd love it warm!
Oven's broken.
Right.
Do you have any cream?
Brilliant.
Thanks.
Mmm. It's lovely.
Mmm.
Best be careful at the moment,
out there.
Yeah.
You heard about the murder?
What murder?
Guy who runs the motel.
Only an hour up the road.
What happened?
I shouldn't really say.
Got shot in the head, and then put
in a cupboard.
Right.
I keep saying cupboard. It's
wardrobe.
Put him in a wardrobe.
INTERNALLY: She wasn't having sex
with him.
She was killing him. Maybe both.
Mm.
It's probably why someone phoned
about here.
What?
Well, there's always hoaxes and
stuff, you know?
After a murder.
Just kids being silly.
Calling us up. Hm-hm.
Right.
That was delicious.
What do I owe you?
£2.
Mmm.
Here you go.
Hah. Don't need that.
What about for your expenses or
something?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that!
OK.
Thank you very much, then.
You all right?
I'm fine.
OK.
Night, then.
Stay safe.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Lock the door.
You killed him.
The man at the motel.
Sort of. What?
Where's James?
I told you I don't know.
INTERNALLY: Please stay where you
are, James.
CLATTER
What was that?
I can see you.
POLICE OFFICER: Come in. Please come
in.
FROM RADIO: Go ahead.
I'm at the cafe on Forest Road.
Suspect is an IC3 female. She has a
gun.
Repeat - she has a gun!
Unbelievable.
Sorry.
See?
You're a liar.
I didn't know he was there till a
minute ago.
So why didn't you tell me?
Because I don't want you to hurt
him.
So, what now? What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna shoot you both.
Why didn't you already? What?
Kill us.
Because. Because what?
I wanted to talk to you first. Why?
So I could hear it from you.
What happened? Your boyfriend tried
to rape me.
So James stabbed him. What else is
there to say?
Why can't you tell the truth?
That IS the truth!
No.
You were waiting for him, you broke
into his house
and you waited for him...
This is bullshit! Alyssa!
It is! She's got a gun!
There were other girls. You must
know that.
That was never proved. What?
There were loads.
There was a video and photos. We saw
them.
You're wrong. It was different with
me.
How do you know he didn't have a
plan?
Maybe you were just lucky.
No.
No!
He loved me.
And you took him from me!
You killed him!
I killed him. Please, let her go.
Fuck off, James.
What? Stop trying to save me.
I... I don't... I...
Yeah, we killed him.
Then you have to get punished.
People are supposed to get punished.
You think we won't?
I'm always in that house.
I'm always in that room.
I can't get out.
Maybe I did some things I shouldn't
have done,
but I didn't deserve that.
Please, Bonnie...
None of us asked for this.
None of us.
INTERNALLY: It's weird, knowing
you're gonna die.
You feel like you're old and you
know everything,
so you don't give a shit any more.
We're not gonna say sorry.
If you wanna kill us, I get that.
What happens next?
What happens to you? She's right.
You might think you don't have a
chance, but you do.
DREAMLIKE: Bonnie?
Bonnie?
What do I do?
What do I do with all the pain?
I don't know.
OK.
No!
No! No! NO!
NO!!
No! No!
No!
SHE SOBS
# ..A dreamer
# I'm a dreamer... #
I'm really tired.
Yeah.
INTERNALLY: The problem with a person
having a lack of love
is that they don't know what it
looks like.
So it's easy for them to get
tricked,
to see things that aren't there.
But then, I guess, we all lie to
ourselves all the time.
Are you OK? Yeah, I'm fine.
SIRENS WAIL
# Are you a dreamer?
# Do you dream alone?
# Would you come upstairs with me? #