Previously on "The Originals"...
I presume I have the misfortune
of speaking to my mother.
I have come to heal our family.
I'd prefer you both to
join me against our mother,
but I'll happily
settle for one or the other.
It is time you bring Camille in.
Esther prepared your body
for someone to jump into.
She was preparing you
for Rebekah.
I have the baby,
and we're on the run.
Esther found us.
Then she made an offer
to make us all mortal again.
[Gasps]
Elijah: We mustn't let
the world ever hurt her.
You're right.
Those daggers
don't work on Klaus.
It's not impossible to change
the dagger itself, so here.
That's a giant diamond.
It's a paragon diamond.
Use them to conduct power.
Klaus, there's something
I need to tell you.
- You can tell me on the way.
- Where are we going?
To see our daughter.
[Singing Christmas carol]
All right, darling.
You know what to look for.
You sly old bat.
Clean up.
Meet me in the cemetery.
This little beauty and I
have a date with a dagger.
Klaus: You're looking
very dapper this evening, Kol.
Though gloves
without a tailcoat.
Unusual, wouldn't
you say, Klaus?
I would unless
of course the gloves
are utilitarian in nature.
I didn't realize
you two lovebirds
were interested in fashion.
Oh, I can take it or leave it.
Mayor Behrman on the other hand,
now his style is impeccable,
especially under present duress.
Do you know he came
to me very concerned
about the rash of
thefts in the city?
So I put Marcel on it.
And after a little digging,
I formed a theory
as to the culprit,
so we followed our suspect.
And he led us here
to the mansion
of the recently deceased
dowager fauline.
She was famous
for her collection
of rare and priceless jewels,
most notably of course
the perfect paragon diamond.
Hand it over, Kol.
[Chanting]
[Banging on doors]
- Kol!
- Get us out of here!
Oh, I wouldn't bother
waiting for them.
You see, those women are never
leaving that house again.
Merry Christmas, brother.
[Screaming]
Rebekah: Well, isn't
this place rather nice?
Nik must have compelled
a wine lover
to keep it up because
I found a 2005 bordeaux.
Fancy a sip?
I appreciate the sentiment,
Rebekah,
but I do recognize when I'm
being handled with kid gloves.
How are you feeling?
Patronized.
I am here to protect you.
I know you mean to, Elijah.
And yet you found it necessary
to render me unconscious
before bringing me here.
Well, you weren't yourself,
and I needed to get us
out of that diner.
What happened back there?
I don't know.
Niklaus sent me to protect hope.
My job is to keep her safe.
Both: Pwoteje sa.
Scandalum subsisto venenatis.
Impedit l'ecoulement.
It's finished,
but I'm worried it's not enough
to protect Cami's body
from Esther's magic.
I might know a way to distract
you from your troubled mind.
Marcel: You can take
this seriously,
or I can lock you
in a coffin like
your brother Finn if you prefer.
Oh. No. I'd prefer
you to bugger off
because this spell needs
time to cook in peace.
Cami doesn't have time.
Esther can jump anybody
into her body right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but she's
not gonna jump anybody, is she?
She's gonna jump Rebekah,
who just happens to be miles
away, but fair dues, Marcel.
Think I'd be a bit testy, too,
if my old ex was about
to jump into my new ex.
I think that would be
a big, uh...
Awkward?
I was gonna say kinky, but...
I appreciate
the chivalry, Marcel,
but he'll have an easier time
protecting me if he's alive.
Keep working.
What is it with you two?
It gets a bit old, plan
out in me own family.
You know, Klaus,
Elijah, Rebekah,
they were always a party of 3.
No room for me at the table.
There always seemed to be
room for Marcel.
You know that diamond,
the one that I showed you?
Mm-hmm.
Well, that was the baby version.
The one that we need
to do the dagger spell,
well it has to be a lot bigger.
100 years ago,
I had it in my hand.
Then Marcel ratted me out
to Klaus, and they took it.
He probably bloody well kept it.
So let's steal it back.
It's a good chance to snoop.
It's like you're
in my mind, Davina Claire.
[Mikael grunting]
[Bird chirps]
You're making a mess of
my werewolf sentries, Mikael.
And you're up
to your old tricks.
Esther...
I missed you, wife.
Have you missed me?
As much as you've
missed me, I imagine.
That would explain why you
brought your lover back
from the other side without
so much as a thought of me.
I will slaughter
every single wolf I see
until I am taken to the dog
you saw fit to bring
back from the dead.
You can stop looking for ansel.
Klaus killed him.
Klaus may not be your blood,
be he certainly has
picked up a few things
from you along the way.
Do not mention the bastard son!
Resolution through violence.
You are nothing
if not consistent.
Go ahead. Strike me.
I imagine you've been
waiting a thousand years
to do so.
Hyah!
Apparaitre apparebis.
Now that you've got
that out your system,
we have things to discuss
about our children.
It's all right, Elijah.
She won't break.
Everything you did was in
the name of protecting her.
I'm not worried.
Is that what I think it is?
It's bonfire season,
and I am reviving a family tradition,
especially since we're
all going to be together.
Only because we're fleeing from
one of our deranged parents,
another Mikaelson
family tradition.
It's a peculiar thing
never to be tired
yet forever exhausted
with the sameness of things.
Why is our family always at war?
I don't know,
but being away with her
made me see things differently.
We're not so bad.
Not the monsters
that our parents think we are.
[Car approaching]
Hi.
Curse on the first born?
What the bloody hell
is that supposed to be?
Well, according to Finn,
our sister freya
didn't die of plague.
She was taken as payment
by our aunt dahlia,
who then cursed all Mikaelson
first borns for eternity.
Is any of this true?
Elijah: It is if
we're to believe Finn,
who learned it from
that bastion of truth, our mother.
Well, no wonder Finn hates us.
He lost the sister
he adored and instead
got a judgy pack of siblings,
who found him unbearably dull.
Great. So is there
any chance of us
running into your loony
aunt dahlia anytime soon?
Fable's over
a thousand years old.
Dahlia's long dead.
Like Esther?
No one's going to hurt hope
because no one's
going to find her.
It's enough wood, Rebekah.
You'll burn down the whole
bloody state of Arkansas.
Well, we're just missing
a key ingredient.
No, we're not.
Yes, we are, Nik.
Back me up, Elijah.
I suspect Niklaus would
rather choke on the ashes.
What are you all talking about?
Well, before we light it,
we write down
our wishes for each other
to burn for luck.
It was Kol's favorite
part when were kids.
Further evidence as to
why we should ignore it.
Hope's first bonfire season.
I like it.
We're doing it.
You ditched me.
You have my fake therapist
locked in that coffin.
What better way to spend
my potential final hours.
Try not to think about it.
I can't help it, Marcel.
At any moment,
I could cease to exist,
and the one person
who can make a difference
is 10 feet away
and locked in a box.
I need to talk to him.
You're not talking to Finn.
Maybe he'll listen,
maybe he'll call his mom off.
It's a million to one,
but it's better than doing nothing.
I said no, Cami.
Marcel, I am hours away from
someone taking control of my body.
I highly suggest you
avoid trying to control me
between now and then.
[Music playing]
Here.
I'm holding
a small child, Hayley.
This silly wish game
will have to wait.
You write, I'll hold.
You do realize it is not
I who is to be the husband
you can boss around.
You do realize I had to
endure horrendous labor
and actual death birthing
the child that you're holding.
Fine.
I wish you would tell Elijah
you're marrying your
werewolf suitor,
at which point I will
pour him a scotch
and congratulate him
on the bullet he dodged.
Marcel: I'm only doing this
because it means so much to you,
but if it's not safe,
I'm staying,
not to control you,
to protect you.
He won't talk to me
if you're here, Marcel,
and he's in no shape
to pick a fight.
I'll be outside.
I'm not much of a cook,
but I do make
a mean grilled cheese.
You're a compassionate
woman Camille.
It's your fatal flaw, and
it will be your downfall.
Well, that got dark fast.
Come on. Eat.
You must be starving.
I will not be tempted
by your beauty,
nor will I be blinded
by your empathy.
You don't leave a girl
much wiggle room.
I would appeal to your morals,
but those seem to be
all over the map.
I'm not the one who was
sleeping with one vampire
while half in love with another.
Your morality is
a moving target.
Mine is not.
You believe people can change.
You're still seeking out
Klaus' redemption
as if that were a thing
that was even possible.
Elijah seeks it out.
Even my own mother seeks it out,
but I do not believe
in redemption.
I believe in right and wrong.
I believe in good and evil.
Maybe in some
comic book universe...
You don't even see it,
but I'm trying to help
people like you.
I don't believe you.
That is to your peril
because when I'm free
I will not stop
until every single vampire
in New Orleans has
ceased to exist,
and I will show
no mercy to anyone
who dares stand with them.
Not even you.
Lock him back up.
[Sighs]
[Screaming]
Hyah!
[Exhales]
Rebekah: Elijah.
Thank you.
What is it you see when
you go away like that?
Things I've done,
images of who I was.
Another gift from mother.
I can't turn it off.
I suppose it's her way
of demonstrating
I'd be better off
taking her deal.
To leave your body behind?
To start over, to
live a mortal life,
have a child of
my own if I choose.
Cursed as your first born if
we're to believe the story.
Not if I am no longer
Mikaelson blood.
See, this is the beauty
of mother, Rebekah.
Sometimes, even her
darkest deeds
possess a logic that's
difficult to refute.
It's a lovely fantasy, elljah.
Rebekah, you and I both know
what mother is capable of.
Now I do wonder if she would
relent and leave us be.
Now what if all that mother
needs is a victory.
Let her find it somewhere else.
Besides, she wants all 3 of us.
She has Kol, she has Finn.
Perhaps in the end,
a simple majority will do.
Is this you?
I was lot better looking
back then.
You wish.
What about Rebekah?
You never talk about her.
There's not much to say really.
She was always their girl.
There was one time,
though, she did me a solid
back in Christmas 1914.
[Music playing]
Doing a bit of pilfering
before cocktails?
Nik stole something
that belongs to me.
I'm simply taking it back.
And I'm simply going
to tell Nik.
Wait!
What if I said I'm close
to finishing a dagger
that would work on him?
You wouldn't dare use it.
Why? It's no more
than he's done to us.
You've suffered at his
hands more than anyone,
and it's not like
we'd be killing him,
just giving you some
time to be with Marcel.
You're entirely serious.
Haven't we both earned the right
to live out of his shadow?
Are you with me, sister?
You can count me in,
but do hurry downstairs.
Throw on one of Nik's jackets.
He'll notice your
absence if you're late.
Hey! Look what I found.
Wonder if it will work.
Oh, bloody hell.
Come on. Let's try.
Hey, Nik.
Do you think you can
cram us into a selfie?
Well, Niklaus is the virtuoso
of cramming his siblings
into confined spaces.
I'm so glad I traveled
hundreds of miles
to visit my
mentally ill brother,
only to have him
insult me to my face.
Oh, come on.
Just take the picture.
Hmm.
Hayley: Aw. See?
I wish that it could
always be like this.
If wishes were horses.
Beggars would ride.
You realize we'll
have to burn it.
You want me to make a wish
for the family, Rebekah,
I wish it didn't
have to be like this,
but it does.
[Music playing]
We can't risk it falling
into the wrong hands.
No. This... this isn't right.
We deserve this.
We've earned this.
I won't let it slip away.
I know what to do
to stop Esther.
Rebekah, no.
I'm gonna take her
deal, and when I do,
I'm taking her down with me.
[Music playing]
Rebekah: It'll work.
She will be distracted
during the spell.
She'll be vulnerable.
No. If we kill her,
she body jumps.
Then stop her from jumping.
If I knew how to bloody
stop her from jumping,
don't you think I would have
happily murdered her ages ago?
Well, ages ago, you didn't have
a harvest girl
or a Mikaelson witch.
Kol knows all of her tricks.
Are you both insane?
Hardly, Elijah.
It was your idea.
You were the one who said
she needed a win,
and if we get this right,
then she'll have one.
And if we do it wrong, you're
no longer in your own body.
Would that be the worst thing?
You were ready
to do it yourself.
It was a foolish moment
and one that you sagely
dissuaded me from.
Hopefully, we'll get lucky
and stop the spell
before I jump.
And if we're not,
you get what you always wanted.
I mean, that's what
you're saying, isn't it?
You're willing to lose.
I'm willing to risk losing, yes.
Well, we need to find
someone for her to jump into,
someone anonymous,
someone who could disappear with hope.
Rebekah, we've been
together for centuries.
If you were human...
When I'm old and wrinkly,
you can dump me back
into my old body.
Nik already has a coffin
he can stall me in.
But to trust Kol?
It's not about trust, Elijah.
It's about finding
the proper leverage.
She's right.
Kol will do what's best for Kol.
We just have to meet his price.
Be happy to help.
In exchange for what?
From all the sneaking
around today,
you're clearly in need
of something.
If you want me to find
a new body for Rebekah,
I want the Fauline diamond you
stole from me back in 1914.
What do you plan to do with it?
Does it matter?
Well, it will matter to Klaus.
You see, I could fib here,
but I want to be
on the up about it.
I need a weapon I can use to
protect myself against Klaus,
and the diamond
helps me make it.
It's not kill him.
Simply a matter of self-defense
only to be use out
of absolute necessity.
It's a fair trade, Marcel.
I get free
of the whackadoodle mum,
I acquire the means by
which to defend myself
against a volatile brother,
should the need arise,
and, uh, well,
if all goes well,
perhaps you'll let me near Davina
without bodily harm.
So should I call him back,
or should you?
You are made to give
Kol that diamond.
Our little brother has been
plotting against me for years,
and he hasn't got
a lick of it right.
I'll take my chances.
Do you know what to do?
Yes, but if it
doesn't go to plan,
will you handle my body with care,
please?
I may miss the old model.
If everything goes south, I'll
be there to pull you out.
We just have to take Esther
down before she body jumps.
I don't want all of this
to have been for nothing.
You and I on the same team.
It must be Christmas.
She's asleep.
It's so quiet with Klaus
and Rebekah gone.
So we didn't get to say
our wishes.
Can I tell you mine?
It's a hope actually
that you'll understand
what I have to tell you.
What is it?
My wolves...
I think I figured out
a way to release them
from the witches.
They could control
their turning without the rings
and bring peace to our home
so that hope could
return to us...
But there's a catch.
I have to marry Jackson.
It's, uh, a mystical ceremony
and an alpha bonding ritual.
Elijah, I know that you
and I haven't been close recently,
but...
You have to know that
this isn't about him.
I don't love Jackson,
but at the same time,
I couldn't marry him
and still be involved with you.
I don't know.
I should just...
[Music playing]
Marry him.
What?
Listen to me.
The only way that the city
will be safe for hope's return
is if you have unified
your people
and I have unified my own,
and Davina will eventually
lead her witches,
and whatever their goal may be,
she is no enemy to your child.
Do what you need to bring
your daughter home.
This is my wish for you.
Done! A per request.
Miss angelica barker.
Good cheek bones and a tummy
you can bounce a quarter off.
She will be Rebekah's new
host body instead of Cami.
Who's angelica barker?
One of my vampire potentials.
Had to turn her down.
She was too lost.
Does she know what's
about to happen to her?
It's better when
they don't know, luv.
Hopefully, we won't
have to use her.
Hopefully, but then my mother
is a wily and vindictive woman,
which is why I've got to
ask something else of you.
You're already getting
the diamond.
Which I'm thrilled about, but
in order for me to help you,
I need access to
my mother's hourglass,
which is in
the lycee with my mother.
So?
Well, I haven't been
back in a while,
and the only way she won't
suspect me is if I bring back
the thing that
I was sent to find.
And that thing is?
The white oak stake.
Are you out of your mind?
Kaleb!
Look. It's the only way
that she's gonna trust me.
She doesn't want to kill them.
She just wants to make
sure that the weapon
doesn't fall in the wrong hands.
I swear as soon as she's gone,
I'll give it
right back to Klaus.
Like hell you will.
Deal's off.
Klaus: Kol!
Whatever grudges
you hold against me,
we are doing this
for the good of our family.
Do I have your word that for
once you will honor that?
You have my word, Nik.
Swear on the fate of us all.
Take the stake.
I wooed her, I won her.
Took a while, but in the
end, she handed it to me.
When I didn't hear from you,
I thought you
might be in trouble.
Nope. No trouble.
Just hard to do espionage
when you're calling
mummy all the time.
So where's Finn.
Is he off playing emperor
to his merry pack of dogs?
I'm afraid Finn may have fallen
into the hands of your brothers,
but I've made a plan to
assist him with that dilemma
while I continue
my search for Rebekah.
Oh. Speak of the devil,
and the devil will come.
Hello, sister.
Kol, it really is you.
I would know
that smirk anywhere.
Hello, mother.
I believe you're
offering a deal.
Kaleb will link this
hourglass to Esther's.
Ours will mirror hers.
When last sand falls, Esther
will try to jump her into you.
That's when I'll redirect
the spell from you to Esther.
It's meant to jam
the signal just long enough
to keep that kind of magic
from working against anyone.
If it works.
It will work.
When Rebekah attacks,
Esther won't be able
to jump her into you
or herself anywhere else.
And we're sure Kaleb
is on board?
He's on board.
He's a thief and a liar,
but like Elijah,
he doesn't give his word lightly.
Rebekah: You can't possibly
expect me to discuss
giving up eternal life over tea.
Give me some of that
red over there.
Pfft.
Well, where's the sales pitch?
I only offer what
you already want.
And how do you presume
to know that?
Elijah is happiest when
there is order and music,
Klaus when he's the center
of attention and in control,
but you are my only child
capable of unfettered joy,
and you're happiest
amongst humans.
I've seen you year for that life,
for love.
And when am I happiest
then, mother?
When you're doing
as you're told.
Our wishes are aligned
in this, my daughter,
mine to free you from this
curse and yours to be human.
I'd be giving up
everything I've ever known
for a memory
of something I once was,
power for weakness,
strength for frailty,
eternal life for a brief
human existence.
The choice is simple.
Another thousand years of
never having what you want
or a handful of years
when you do.
Well, then.
To the end of an era.
I'm in.
Let us begin.
[Whispering]
It's working.
What the bloody hell
is that doing here?
As each of you comes to your
senses and takes my offer,
I will destroy
your vampire bodies.
Mother, you said you wanted
the stake to protect them.
Yes, but not
in their current bodies.
Once they accept my offer, I
will be righting two wrongs...
No.
Having brought this
evil into the world
and having subjected
my own children to it.
No. That wasn't the deal.
Stop the spell!
The spell is already done.
I prepared it to be locked in
the moment I turned over
the hourglass.
Marcel: Now.
Not yet.
Mother, think this through.
You gave birth to this body.
You can't destroy it.
I am only destroying its flesh.
Your beautiful soul will live
on in the body of another.
I have chosen well for you,
a beautiful girl, strong.
Klaus: Mother!
Stop the spell.
You and your traitorous son.
Nik, I didn't know
anything about it, I swear.
Oh, good. I'm glad you two
boys are friends again.
I did wonder what you'd been
up to in your time away.
Now I know.
Stop the blasted spell.
I'm afraid that's impossible.
Anything is possible.
- Take me instead.
- Nik, no!
If only you'd taken my offer
when it was still mine to give.
Unfortunately, you've
left me no choice
but to make a deal with Mikael.
Mikael?
When Finn and Kol went
missing, I needed a new ally.
All he wanted was
the right to kill you.
Kol, I would ask you to deliver
the stake to your father,
but it seems your loyalties
have been compromised.
Stop the spell, Esther!
No. It's ok, Nik.
I can do this.
So you're feeling
murderous again.
You should know
I've already chosen my next body.
Now!
[Chanting]
Cami!
Rebekah!
- Did it work?
- I have no idea.
Cami's not awake yet either.
When she's up,
we need to get her out of the quarter.
She's not safe here.
Somebody busted Finn out.
My mother is using Mikael
to do her dirty work.
Camille?
I suddenly love
that stupid name.
I couldn't stop the spell.
Please tell me that
your mother's dead.
Rebekah and I took
extra precautions.
Esther is exactly
where she needs to be.
Davina: Why are you
in such a good mood?
Remember how I said that Rebekah
had done me a solid back in 1914?
Swore she hadn't told Klaus
that I was taking the diamond back.
I was actually being
a bit facetious.
[Music playing]
You're here with my brother.
A word of advice.
A witch as lovely as you
has no business dating Kol.
Oh, it's not really a date.
You can do better.
Klaus: As you know,
when the Mikaelsons arrived
in Louisiana we brought
with us the tradition
of holiday bonfire season.
Now we invite you chosen few
to join us in our family's
own tradition
of writing wishes for each other
and burning them for lucky.
The holidays are time for
celebrating family and friends.
It is especially
gratifying in times
when treachery runs deep
to know you have someone
you can trust.
A toast to you, my sister.
To Rebekah!
All: To Rebekah!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I apologize for the disturbance,
but what's a Mikaelson
family party
without a little squabble?
No, no! Ohh!
[Partygoers gasp]
I've owed her one for a century.
Today, I got to
repay that favor.
Oh, don't worry, luv.
Not gonna hurt me own sister.
I didn't exactly
prep angelica barker either.
I prepped someone else.
What? Who?
Oh, it's a bit of a story.
You see, Klaus didn't
just punish me
for stealing the diamond.
He also punished
my witch friends,
locking them in
the dowager Fauline cottage.
Over the decades,
it's become quite a catch-all
for an assortment of odd
birds of the witchy variety.
I'm sure Rebekah
will be very comfortable
in the prison created by Klaus.
You didn't.
Oh, I did, and besides,
with Rebekah missing,
Klaus will be occupied,
so we can finish
what we started.
You swear she's safe?
Perfectly.
Seeing as this is
the best day I've had
in the past two centuries,
I've made a wish for you.
Close your eyes.
[Music playing]
Hello, mother.
What have you done?
You sold me to that
butcher Mikael
like I were nothing
more than chattel.
Ask me what I have done.
I've done what every
good son does, mother.
I've followed the example
of my parents.
You taught me exactly
how I should treat you.
You must be feeling a little
twitchy right about now.
That's what happens
when you're in transition.
No.
That's not possible.
Oh, but it is.
You see, you may have thought
you were one step ahead of us,
but the truth is Rebekah
was two ahead of you.
And when am I happiest
then, mother?
When you're doing
as you're told.
The wine.
You died with vampire blood
in your system.
It's a delicious irony
because as you know
you cannot be both
witch and vampire.
So now you either be
the thing you hate the most,
or you can be dead.
Your choice...
Which is more than
you ever gave us.
[Music continues]
Promise is a promise.
[Women screaming]
Let me out!
Someone!
Kol. Damn it!
I'm not meant to be here.
I'm Rebekah Mikaelson!
Let me out!