Look at him. Bres my heart.
Poor little guy, all alone.
I don't see why
- his brother can't sit with him.
- Come on, Mary.
When you were in high
school, would you have lunch
- with a nine-year-old?
- Yes, I would've.
Well, there's something wrong with you.
I'm gonna keep him company.
Hey, hey, hey, Mary. Mary.
Think this through. Right now the kids
are just ignoring Sheldon.
What happens if he's
sitting with his mommy?
They could mistake me for a senior.
Well, I look younger than you.
Just give this time, all right?
It'll work itself out.
My mother never understood
that I actually enjoyed being alone.
Solitude allowed me to
think about important things,
like the effect of gravitational forces
as you approach an event horizon,
as opposed to less important things,
like how many grapes my
brother can fit in his mouth.
14!
Yeah!
Jean-Paul Sartre said,
"Hell is other people."
That's humorous because it's true.
Something wrong?
How come math is easy for Sheldon
and hard for me?
I don't know, honey,
but you have your own gifts.
Like what?
Well, like...
you have very pretty hair.
True.
Georgie.
Would you do me a little tiny favor?
Like what?
Tomorrow at lunch, would you mind
sitting with your brother?
Don't do it, Georgie.
You stay out of this.
I ate with him in second grade.
It really hurt my social life.
Sorry, Mom. Can't do it.
Why are you such a brat?
Maybe I'm crying for attention.
This isn't a joke, young lady.
Yes, your brother may be smart,
but he doesn't have
a friend in the world.
And I am sorry, but I am
very worried about him.
Nice going. You're making
Mom a nervous wreck.
What did I do?
You don't have any friends,
and she is beside herself.
But I'm fine without friends.
I don't know what to tell you, Sheldon.
She said it's your fault.
I'm going to watch ALF.
Science fact:
sisters are the worst.
When you're three foot ten
and in high school,
getting from point "A"
to point "B" can be a
harrowing experience.
But it's worth it when point "B" is...
the library.
Home to the original
information superhighway,
the Dewey Decimal System.
Hey there, Sheldon.
What can I get for you today?
Chemistry?
Quantum mechanics? Astronomy?
No, nothing fun today.
I need to learn how to make a friend.
Aw, honey, you having a hard time
adjusting to high school?
I'm having a hard time
adjusting to Earth.
Yeah. You and me both.
Try this.
It's been around a while,
but it's still quite popular.
Unlike me,
who's just been around a while.
"How to Win Friends
and Influence People."
This might do it.
"Principle one.
Don't criticize, condemn or complain."
The three sharpest arrows
in my quiver.
Thus began the greatest challenge
of my young life.
Hello, George.
What?
I do admire your thick head of hair...
George.
Thanks.
What's going on?
Well, I'm practicing the
principles in this book.
- Why?
- Well, I know Mom is concerned
that I don't have any friends,
so I'm determined to
remedy the situation.
Oh.
George.
Well, good for you.
Do you feel complimented
when I say your name, George?
The book says you should. George.
I suppose.
Kind of overdoing it a little.
- Sheldon.
- Well, thank you
for your criticism.
It also says I should praise
any improvements that you've made.
Okay.
I'll get back to you.
George.
On the heels
of that successful beta test,
I decided to practice
the Carnegie principles
on someone my own age.
- Hello, Billy Sparks.
- Hey, Sheldon.
I am genuinely interested in you
and would like to encourage
you to talk about yourself.
Billy Sparks.
Thank you.
You have the floor.
Looking back, I would've had better luck
making friends with the chickens.
Go Wolves.
What?
You're a cheerleader, and by saying
"Go Wolves," I'm
initiating a conversation
about something that interests you.
Oh, are you one of
those special ed kids?
My mom says I'm special.
Would you like to be friends?
I don't think so.
Are you sure? What if I told you
I admired your boldly-applied makeup?
Greetings from stall number one.
As much as I detest that
odd-smelling cigarette,
I do applaud
your rule-breaking bravado.
My name is Sheldon. What's yours?
Hello, gentlemen.
Did you watch any sports
programs over the weekend?
Or perhaps did some kissing with girls?
Can you hear me?
95, 96, 97.
98.
99, 100.
- You missed 11 numbers.
- I don't need
to be good at math.
I have beautiful hair.
That's the saddest
thing I've ever heard.
Didn't you already read that book?
I'm reading it again.
How come?
I clearly missed something.
I couldn't find one person
who wanted to be my friend.
Did you look at the card inside?
Why?
That's just other people
who checked out the book.
It's a list of losers like
you who can't find a friend.
So?
So they're desperate,
and you have their names.
That's brilliant.
Mm.
Now, how is it that you can't count?
So your father tells me
you've been reading a new book?
I am. It's about how to make friends.
Is that something you're interested in?
Not really, but Missy told me
it makes you sad that I don't have any.
Oh.
I got to sew that girl's mouth shut.
So how's it going?
Well, the principles in the
book didn't work for me at all.
Although Dad does like
being called George
over and over again, so
you might give that a try.
Baby, you don't have to
go to any trouble for me.
But I like doing things for you.
You're a nice lady.
- But if the book's not working...
- It isn't.
But I realized if I
find the other people
who checked out the book, they'd
be looking for friends, too.
That's really smart.
- Missy thought of it.
- You're kidding.
I'm as surprised as you are.
Excuse me, Ms. Ingram?
Sheldon, it's recess.
Go outside, see what it's like.
Are you by any chance Evelyn Ingram?
Yes.
The same Evelyn Ingram
who checked out this book?
- And why is that your business?
- I just
assumed you were
looking to make a friend.
Oh.
Well, that was a long time ago.
I had just gotten out of a
very difficult relationship.
- With a friend?
- Friend.
Ha! I gave that man
three years of my life
and my innocence.
I don't know what that means.
It means men are lying dogs
only interested in one thing
Well, that's not the
dictionary definition.
Mm-hmm.
Always starts the same.
A quick glance across the room,
a casual hand on the shoulder,
lunch at Stuckey's.
Oh, yeah, it's all romance
and flowers in the beginning...
The list proved to be
a double-edged sword.
It turns out self-help
books written in 1936
were only of interest to adults.
You're like, "I'm here because I care.
And by the way, your phone
could make calls, too."
Then tries to turn
this whole thing around
like it's all about you being needy,
and you're like, "Yes, I have needs!
That's what makes me human!"
Emotionally troubled adults.
Child, go outside.
Yes, that's my
signature. Why do you ask?
I'm seeking people who
want to make friends.
I wasn't interested in friends.
I took out that book to help
me become school principal.
- Did it work?
- Are we sitting in the principal's office?
- No.
- And you know why?
Because Victoria MacElroy is not a man!
So to be clear, you're not
interested in making friends?
What I'm interested in
is in living long enough
to see women no longer treated
like second-class citizens.
Well if your goal is a long life,
that chili cheeseburger is a
step in the wrong direction.
Food is all I have.
Like I said,
emotionally troubled adults.
You gonna watch me eat?
Get out of here.
Everybody told me,
"Hubert, don't date someone from work."
But did I listen? No.
Let me tell you
something. She likes to say
I stole her innocence?
Well, what about my innocence?
I was never the same after we broke up.
Two years later,
Mr. Givens became the
high school principal,
which might be why Ms.
MacElroy became morbidly obese.
I had the brains, I had the
charm, and I don't like to brag,
but I was pretty easy
on the eyes back then.
That woman got herself
one heck of a package.
But some people don't
want to be satisfied.
Is that any good?
I'm afraid not.
I failed to make a single friend.
That sucks. I have a tough
time making friends, too.
The worst part is, it
was important to my mom.
My parents pressure me about
making friends all the time.
So you understand
what I'm going through.
Oh, I read that book. It's excellent.
Are you into rocketry?
I started with water propulsion,
worked my way up to solid fuel,
then went back to water after
I set our garage on fire.
- Nice.
- I also tried to get some uranium
and build an atomic engine,
but that stuff's hard to find.
Probably for the best.
Well, good luck on your
quest to find a friend.
You, too.
If you haven't found one
yet, I have good news.
Mom, what do you know
about the drug Prozac?
Not much.
Supposed to make people happier. Why?
I was just thinking
some of my teachers
might benefit from it.
Speaking of which,
you'll be happy to know
I made a friend today.
Oh.
Well, that's nice.
But, as I said, this isn't for me.
It's for you.
He made a friend!
He did it!
Our little boy has got a friend.
- Who is it?
- Who cares?
It's a human being. It's a warm body.
Mom?
Yes, honey?
- Can I come in?
- Of course.
Be cool.
- What's up, sweetie?
- I was wondering
when I could continue my rocketry hobby.
Uh, Sheldon, we've been through this.
You can build them. You
just can't launch them.
But launching them is the fun part.
Tell that to the family of squirrels
who died in the fire.
Okay.
It was just something I was
hoping to do with my new friend.
Hang on.
Uh, yes.
It's fine.
Ban is lifted.
- Mary...
- It's for his friend.
He's got a friend.
Besides, those could have been rats.
Their bodies were so badly burned.
I thought we were being cool, but okay.
Hey, here's an idea.
Why don't you invite your
new buddy over for dinner?
- Why?
- Well, honey,
um, that is what friends do.
My mother asked me to ask you
if you'd like to join us for dinner.
- Why?
- I was hoping you'd know.
He's here!
Everybody, stay calm! Just a normal day,
- just a normal dinner.
- Can I eat in front of the TV?
No, you can eat in front
of Sheldon's friend.
- Aw, fudge.
- I know what "fudge" means,
and you are right on
the edge, young lady.
Welcome.
So, uh...
Tam. What kind of name is that?
Vietnamese. Sir.
Sure. You know, I spent
a little time over there.
Army.
Your mom's name isn't Kim-Lee, is it?
No. Sir.
Good.
I mean, you know, it's a small country.
So...
Mary, how's that food coming?
Almost.
So, Vietnam, like in Rambo.
- Yes.
- That's a cool movie.
Yes.
Are you in it?
- No.
- Hmm.
Why would you think you knew his mom?
All right, Tam.
I decided I was gonna make
you a real Texas dinner.
Barbecued chicken and brisket.
Thank you.
Well, I figured you were probably tired
of stuff wiggling around on your plate.
Okay, let's say grace.
Now, Tam, when I say "Jesus,"
feel free to say the word
"Buddha" in your head.
I'm actually Catholic.
Oh. Well, that's too bad.
Thank you, God, for this food,
and bless the hands that prepared it.
And thank you so much
for Sheldon's new friend.
Amen.
So, Tam, tell us about your family.
What brings y'all to Texas?
Well, after the American War...
You mean the Vietnam War.
We call it the American War.
- Hmm.
- Anyway,
after the war, my father was sent
to a reeducation camp
because he fought on the wrong side.
You mean our side.
I was trying to be nice.
So, for many years,
my mother and my sisters and I
were very poor
and very often didn't have much to eat.
Then, when he was released...
What'd they teach him
at the reeducation camp?
How to be a communist.
Cool, like in Rambo.
When he was released,
we escaped on a small boat
and spent many weeks at sea
dodging Cambodian pirates
until we reached Thailand.
Oh, that's supposed to
be a beautiful country.
- Lovely beaches.
- I wouldn't know.
We were forced to
live in a refugee camp,
where the only thing we had
to eat were pigeons and rats.
Ha! That's a job for hot sauce.
Finally,
we were allowed to come to United States
and start over in Galveston.
My father saved money and
bought his own shrimp boat.
There's a happy ending. Huh?
See, kids? When the going gets tough,
- America provides.
- It did.
Until the Ku Klux Klan burned our boat
and chased us away.
You gonna put a good spin on that one?
So we came to Medford
and opened up a convenience store.
My parents work 16 hours a day,
seven days a week
for very little money.
Well, that was depressing.
I don't understand why it didn't launch.
Me, neither.
Evil Nazi scientists
did it 50 years ago.
How hard could it be?
Can I help you?
Sorry to bother you, ma'am. FBI.
We're looking for a Sheldon Lee Cooper.
George!
I'm on the can.
Now!
- What?
- These gentlemen
are with the FBI. They
want to talk to Sheldon.
What?
We... Uh...
Y-You fellas must have made a mistake.
Sheldon's nine.
Well, someone living at this address
recently called a mining
operation in Canada
and tried to buy uranium.
Okay, maybe it's not a mistake.
It's ridiculous.
Let's just go talk to him. Huh?
He's just a little, itty-bitty thing.
Really, he's harmless.
Sorry!
He's in the garage.