Previously on
Desperate Housewives
Gabrielle tried to
rekindle an old affair.
Gaby, i'm getting married.
And i was married
when we got together.
That is not how
i'm gonna be married.
Lynette got the support she
needed for chemotherapy.
Katherine, who liked
everything in its place... Ooh!
Thought that her husband
was forgetting his.
Oh, i guess you learned
nothing from chicago.
Bree's attempt to keep
Her daughter's
pregnancy a secret...
You are keeping my
grandchildren from me.
Evoked an unexpected response.
We're life partners.
And Susan tried to connect
with the newest neighbors.
Yeah, i've seen a
lot of cable, so i get it.
I hope we can live
up to your stereotype.
I should go.
The odd-looking boxes
Were delivered to the home of
Bob Hunter and Lee Mcdermott
Early on a tuesday morning.
It wasn't long before
workmen had opened them
And begun assembling
the various parts and pieces.
Happily, it only took three hours
to turn the contents
into a finished work of art.
Sadly,
it only took 15 minutes
for the residents
of wisteria lane...
what the hell is it?
To become art critics.
I think it's a sculpture.
I think it's crap.
Of a the gay men
in the world,
we have to get the two
without taste.
What are we gonna do
i say we keep smiling
and look for the hidden cameras.
I think we're about
to get punk'd.
I don't think there's anything
we can do. It's not our lawn.
It's our neighborhood,
and we have rules
against this sort of thing,
or at least we did
when i used to live here.
Who's running
the homeowners association?
Well, it was mary alice,
but as you may have heard...
yes, very tragic. So we haven't
had a president in four years?
No one would volunteer.
It's a pain-in-the-ass job.
I'll volunteer.
We can hold an election
in the next couple of days.
I can get rid of this tinfoil
atrocity by the weekend.
Okay, before we become
an ugly mob,
why doesn't one of us
go talk to the guys?
But not me.
They hate me.
Bree, you talk to them.
You can relate to them.
Why would you say that?
You got a kid who came
flying out of the closet
and a husband who's been
looking for the doorknob.
What? You've met him.
Ooh! They're coming.
Good morning, ladies.
Hi. Uh, we were just talking
about your sculpture.
That's what
i love about art...
the way
it provokes discussion.
Although it would've been nice
if you had discussed it
with us.
What, you don't...
well,
we're not saying that.
It's just a little,
uh...
it's an eyesore.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
You hear that, bob?
We flew to finland
and paid $24,000
to commission an eyesore.
I don't mind it.
Not to brag,
but i went to art school.
Community college.
And they taught us
that art is subjective.
Thank you, susan.
Sun's need
for approval aside,
this clearly is not appropriate
for the street.
Wisteria lane
has a... traditional look.
Well,
maybe you'd like it better
if we covered it
with a gingham throw.
Ladies, uh, i'm sorry.
We honestly thought
that people would like it,
but even if you disapprove,
we hope that you will respect
our right to decorate
as we see fit.
Have a nice day, philistines.
Yes, art came to Wisteria lane
on a tuesday morning,
and by tuesday afternoon...
i think it's time to reconvene
the homeowners' association.
All in favor?
Aye.
War had come as well.
As word of the sculpture
spread,
Bob and lee began to wonder
if any of their neighbors
would be supportive.
But when the sculpture's
true function
was unveiled the next day,
whatever support
they did have...
was quickly washed away.
Come on.
It's 6:00 a.m.
What is that?
I don't know,
but make it stop.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
Wow! It's a fountain, too.
We would have mentioned that
yesterday,
but your friends
were a little uptight.
Yeah,
they can get like that.
So do you think that you can
just turn it off for a second?
What's up?
I was just wondering, um,
do you think you could
move it to your backyard?
Why?
I thought you liked it.
Remember? You said,
"art is subjective."
Yes. quiet art is subjective,
but you see, mike is working
really long hours lately,
and he can't sleep
with all that noise.
We're not gonna turn it off
because we need it to drown out
all the stuff we hear
coming from your house.
Like what?
Let's see. You yakking
to your mom on the phone.
You grunting
through your pilates dvds.
You in the shower, butchering
the score to "brigadoon."
I have a lovely voice.
Whoever told you that
is not your friend.
He's a little cranky. I think
someone needs his french toast.
Come on, lee.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, we're not done here.
As your neighbor,
i have a right to be heard...
and i say
that simple human decency
dictates that you turn off
that fountain right now!
Hey, guys.
Do over, parker.
Hey, guys, i got your snack.
What you playing?
Action figures.
Wanna play, mom?
She does
awesome alien voices.
Thanks, sweetheart.
Hello?
Oh, yeah. Hi, dr. Shiller.
Okay,
that's my white blood count.
Uh-huh, but as long
as it's higher than 4.0,
that means
i don't have neutropenia, right?
Well, that's great.
Thanks for calling.
Yeah, you, too. Bye.
What?
You can't talk about doctors
up here.
Or about being sick.
If you do, you have to go.
That's the rule.
Well...
that's a good rule.
Although it wasn't bad news.
It was actually...
doesn't matter.
We voted. It's a rule.
Got it.
Sick talk done, okay?
You guys have fun.
Freeze power.
Do over, parker. That
guy doesn't have freezing power.
If his guy can fly,
my guy can freeze.
Hi. It's, uh, mrs. Hodge. May i
please speak with danielle?
Mmm. Muffins.
T...
hands off. We're bringing these
to danielle for her birthday.
What do you mean,
she's gone?
And you believed her?
You idiot!
I should sue yourirresponsible
yeah, well, good day to you,
too, reverend mother!
What happened?
Those stupid nuns
at the convent
let danielle's grandmother
kidnap her.
She claimed i'd given her
permission for a weekend visit.
Phyllis! It's me.
You can screen
your calls all you want to,
but trust me, old woman,
you are in a world of trouble.
I know where you live,
and i am coming for you.
Shouldn't we be worried?
No,
i think we're ready for her.
Now show me again
how you kill the zombies.
Oh.
Why can't i go? I play golf.
...-
and i'd love to meet
yo... college buddies.
Edie, me and the guys have only
two rules for these weekends...
no plaidants
and no women.
Fine. Be that way.
And to think,
i got you a gift.
Hey, golf balls.
They're monogrammed.
Wait.
These are your initials.
Exactly. While you're
out there playing,
want everyone to know
who your balls belong to.
Good work, boys, but i have
to head out in a few minutes,
so make sure you put all
the stuff back in the garage.
Hello?
Hey, on my way.
Meet you at the hotel, okay?
I'm leaving in five minutes.
Uh, brett,
could you come here a second?
How long has that van
been parked over there?
Couple hours.
Hours? Are you serious?
Oh, my god.
I think he's just waiting
for someone to come home.
Brett, when's the last time
a cable guy waited for anyone?
I see a lot of lawn mowing
in your future.
Hey, it's me again.
You're not gonna believe this.
Before victor left
on his business trip,
he hired someone to tail me.
Oh, man.
Should we call this off?
No way.
It's gonna take more than
a guy with mini binoculars
and a bag of doughnuts
to keep me under lock d key.
I'll be there
as soon as i can.
Boys, time to get paid.
Come on, eddie!
Bye, mrs. Lang.
See you next time.
Come back here!
Are you taking
the bus home?
As soon as we get
around the corner,
we're gonna have to adjust
this horn.
Gabrielle.
Hey.
H-hi.
Iook at you. What a surprise.
Oh, uh, this is gaby.
This is my wife tammy.
Tammy, this is gabrielle.
Wow, look at you.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
It wasn't planned.
Okay. So... are yoguys
staying here?
No, we just came
for some lunch.
Daddy owns this place.
That's right.
You're a hotel heiress.
Yeah, but not
one of the skanky ones.
How do you two
know each other?
I used to be
gabrielle's gardener.
Oh!
Well, as you can see,
he's certainly married up
from lawn boy.
Tammy.
What?
Forget it.
So i heard
you married the mayor.
You're married
to victor lang?
He and daddy
go hunting together.
I told john if he would
just be nicer to daddy,
he could hang out
with people like the mayor
and make important contacts.
And i keep telling you
that i don't need
to kiss your father's ass
to have a career.
Uh, yeah,
so i married the mayor.
Kooky, huh?
So, um,
is he here with you?
Uh, no. He's away
at a conference,
so i decided to treat myself
to a spa weend.
Ooh! You should definitely
get the full body massage.
Oh, i plan to.
Good to see you.
You, too, gaby.
Sorry about that.
A complete shock.
I mean,
of all people to run into.
Who were they?
Just an old friend
and his idiot wife.
Come on. Let's go.
Bree,
how lovely to see you.
Cram it, phyllis.
You got a lot of nerve
stealing danielle
from a convent we prepaid for.
She didn't steal me.
I'm a mature person capable
of making my own decisions.
Well, good.
You can decide to pack,
because we are taking you
back to the convent.
Mnh-mnh.
I'm turning 18 this weekend,
so you can't boss me around
anymore.
I'm staying with grandma,
and i'm gonna have my baby
delivered here.
We have
it's a retirement village.
All these doctors know
how to deliver is bad news.
I don't care. I'm staying,
and i'm gonna raise the baby
here, too.
What?
Entirely her idea.
A baby
is god's most precious gift.
I will not have mine raised
by a cold, emotionally
unavailable woman like you.
"Emotionally unavailable."
Gosh, i wonder where she
picked up that little phrase.
Hmm.
Like i'm too dumb
to think of it myself?
You're always mean to me,
just like you were to dad.
You emasculated him.
Well, you're not gonna
emasculate me.
You don't even know
what that means,
you petulant sock puppet!
Who cares?
I'm going to the store.
Buy a dictionary.
Would you like
some iced tea?
You aren't joining
the lynch mob?
Uh, you mean katherine's
homeowners thing?
Yeah, i think
i'll sit this one out.
No, no, no. You can't do that.
You've got to pick a side.
Art or mindless conformity?
See, this is one of
the upsides of having cancer.
You get to excuse yourself from
petty neighborhood squabbles.
You won't think they're so petty
when she comes after you.
Me? Why would she do that?
Did the homeowners' association
approve everything in your yard?
The fence? That swing?
The tree house?
I don't ink katherine
will bother herself
over a tree house.
First, they came
for the fountains,
and i did not speak out
because i had no fountain.
What?
Then they came
for the lawn gnomes,
and i did not speak out
because i had no gnome.
You're comparing kathene
then they came
for my tree house,
and there was no one left
to speak out for me.
Thank you, ladies.
I so appreciate your input,
and i think we can all agree
that the fountain has no place
on our street.
Yeah, we gotta show those gays
we mean business.
Ida, again, the issue is not
bob and lee being gay.
It's the fountain.
Well, can't it be both?
Anyway...
if you elect me president,
my first act
will be to eliminate
this so-called work of art.
Hear, hear.
Yes, lynette.
After you get rid of
this fountain, that's it, right?
I don't follow.
I mean...
you're not gonna start
checking everyone's yards
for things that don't fit in?
Oh, of course not.
As long as those things meet
the association's guidelines.
Uh-huh.
And what if they don't?
Are you referring
to something in particular?
My kids' tree house. Can you
promise you'll leave it alone?
Well, it's not up to me.
That's the whole point.
There are rules.
That sounds like a no.
If i make an exception for you,
then i have to make one
for everyone,
and surely, you realize
that the whole neighborhood
can't revolve
around your little tree house.
Now since
i am running unopposed,
i just need someone
to second my nomination.
Oh! Thank you, lynette.
No, actually,
i'm nominating myself.
I am now running
for president...
against you.
You know, running for president
in your condition?
I don't think
it's a good idea.
Tom, i don't want your opinion,
just your vote.
If you want
to save the tree house,
why don't you let me
run instead?
Because you'd never win.
Bossy women rule this street.
You know that.
I know one rules my life.
I'm sorry.
I didn't catch that.
Nothing.
Iook, this is not just about
a tree house or a fountain.
This is about
what kind of neighborhood
we want to live in.
Do we get to make
our own choices,
or do we let the taste police
make them for us?
Ah, now i get it. This about you
wanting to take on katherine.
No! This is
about personal freedom...
specifically,
my personal freedom
to take down
that jackbood hausfrau.
Honey, if you're looking
for something to fight,
how about your cancer?
Hey, a tumor is a tumor
whether it's in your body
or living acrosshe street.
I don't know
why you buy those things.
They just end up on the floor.
Because i want to feel
pretty and feminine.
Ooh! My chili cheese fries!
Just a second!
Gabrielle?
It's me... john.
John? John who?
Uh, okay.
You kn that old friend
i ran into in the lobby?
It might have been
john rowland.
Maybe. I'm not sure.
Gabrielle?
But just to be safe, you may
wanna hide in the closet.
-What? I'm not hiding
from that guy.
-Really?
Because his father-in-law
goes hunting with victor...
you know,
the guy who hired someone
to tail us and possibly kill us?
Okay.
John, what are you doing here?
When i ran into you
last fall,
you wanted to start up
our affair again,
and i wasn't ready.
Well, i'm ready.
Mm! Mm.
Hey.
Listen, i promised tom
i wouldn't knock myself out
campaigning
for this homeowners thing,
so i was hoping
you could help me...
you know, ring some bells,
talk me up, that sort of thing?
I would love to, but...
but what?
This is awkward.
Uh, i told katherine
i'd vote for her.
You're picking her over me?
Uh, it's not like
i'm pro-katherine.
I'm just anti-fountain.
Oh, don't give me that look.
I made her a promise.
Yes, but that was
before your best friend
threw her scarf in the ring.
Uh...
okay. If i vote for you,
do you promi
to get rid of that fountain?
See, that's awkward for me.
This is about personal freedom.
You know? I'm running
as a libertarian.
Well, i'm voting
as a light sleeper.
It's right outside
our bedroom window.
Seriously, lynette, it's like
living next to splash mountain.
But it's my kids' tree house.
They really need it.
Well, we need our sleep.
Why don't you get earplugs?
Why don't you get...
tree house plugs?
What? That doesn't
even make sense.
Yeah, i'm sorry.
You know,
tired people aren't witty.
Seriously, john, you have
got to get out of here.
No. Please.
I need to be with you.
What about your wife?
You met her.
She's dumb, demanding,
totally self-centered,
especially in bed.
I mean, she's awful.
Awfully pregnant.
I know.
I-i'm completely trapped,
just like you were
with mr. Solis.
Wha...
i-i wasn't "trapped."
What do you mean?
All you'd ever talk about
was what a selfish pig he was.
Well, i think
you're paraphrasing.
Okay, riously,
you have to go.
Come on. You know it would
be hot, just like old times.
Remember how great
our sex was?
Oh, i don't think
what about the time we were
doing it in the shower?
Mr. Solis drove up?
Uh, does not ring a bell.
Come on.
And i hid in the closet?
And you looked so hot, mr. Solis
pulled you down on the bed.
And you had to fake an orgasm
just so he wouldn't catch on.
Yeah, good times.
Anyways, uh, that's a negatory
on the affair...
what?
And i will see you later.
Come on, but we're so good
together. Gab...
please!
Boy, that was a close one, huh?
You faked it with me
while that wax job
was hiding in the closet?
Yes, i had an affair.
Old news. Move on.
Where's that room service?
So you're not gonna apologize
for humiliating me
in my own bed?
You deserved it. All you cared
about back then was work.
Hey, i was not that bad
of a husband,
and somebody had to support
your italian shoe addiion.
I shopped because
i was bored and lonely...
same reason i had an affair.
Yeah,
with our teenage gardener!
I should have snapped
that kid's neck two years ago.
Oh, let it go! John Rowland
didn't do anything to you
that you're not doing
to Victor.
You can't even compare the two!
It's completely different!
Is it, Mr. Man in the closet?
Yeah, you heard me.
Who's John Rowland now?
Katherine,
what are you up to?
Just visiting a friend.
Liar. You're campaigning.
Cookies... nice touch.
Ditto on the scarf.
Edie, you got a moment?
I am running for president
of the homeowners' association,
and i want to talk to you
abouthat horrible founin.
Screw the untain.
You want my support?
Make ida greenberg ditch
that screen door.
That rusty,
old tetanus bucket...
Iooks fine to me.
It's hardly ripped at all.
In fact, if you give me
your support...
i'll make mrs. Burkette
prune those roses.
It's a garden, not a jungle,
and you shouldn't have to...
pay for a fence
you don't even want.
That's not how you make
good neighbors,
and i don't care if...
the mustafas
don't celebrate christmas.
You're asking them to hang
a few lights, not convert.
When i'm president, i promise...
you can keep
that satellite dish.
In fact, this is practically
a first amendment issue.
The way i see it...
the entire neighborhood
should be a testament
to symmetry and beauty.
So...
have i got your vote?
Um, i'm not sure yet.
Keep rubbing.
Bree, i know you're upset,
but you've got to eat.
I'm just so mad at myself.
I should have realized
that the maternal instinct
is so strong,
that even danielle
would develop it.
What's so funny?
You know those animals
who eat their young?
Even they have more maternal
instinct than danielle.
Then why
would she want the child?
You've known her how long,
and you still haven't
figured out how that lentil
she calls a brain works?
There's no need
to insult your sister.
Let him talk.
All right, danielle cares
about three things...
danielle, fun, and, uh...
wait. I was wrong.
It's just two.
And a retirement village
is fun?
Compared to what
you're offering her...
a crappy job
and community college.
I mean, you think grandma's
gonna make her do any of that?
So danielle's only doing this
because phyllis
is offering her a cushy life?
Yeah.
If you want that baby,
you're gonna have
to outbid grandma.
What are you doing here?
Hi, john.
I wanted to talk to you.
It'll be very friendly.
No hitting.
What's up?
This is gonna sound weird,
but, uh,
i've been doing some
thinking lately, and, well,
i've decided that it's time
for me to forgive you.
For sleeping with my wife.
Yeah, well, i didn't
just sleep with gaby.
I fell in love with her.
I forgive you for that,
too.
Why are you doing this?
You in some kind
of 12-step program?
Let's just say i've recently
learned how loving someone
makes you forget the difference
between right and wrong.
Anyway, that's pretty much it.
I should go.
Hey.
Do you still talk
to gabrielle?
Occasionally. Why?
I just want to know
if she was happy.
I think she is.
Well...
good for her.
All right, before we vote,
are there any more questions
for the candidates?
Anybody besides lee?
It's not a question.
I just want
to remind everyone
that a vote for katherine
is a vote for fascism.
What is it with you gay people
and clothes?
Fascism, ida, not fashion.
Although if you ever
do want to talk fashion,
we're here for you.
All right, debate's over.
Let's kick this pig.
All in favor of lynette?
Okay,
and those for katherine?
That's 14 for lynette
and 14 for katherine.
So what do we do? It's a tie.
Ah!
No, it's not.
Susan voted twice.
Did i?
Well, that's obviously wrong.
You only get one vote,
sweet cheeks. Who's it gonna be?
Susan, we're waiting.
It's up to you, hon.
Katherine.
Oh!
Okay, it's official.
Katherine is our new president.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone,
and i promise to do my best
for this neighborhood.
And, bob, lee, mr. Mustafa,
i'll be in touch regarding
your various infractions.
Oh.
And you, too, lynette.
Meeting adjourned.
Oh.
I know.
Well, i'm not surprised.
You know, phyllis,
we cannot thank you enough
for accepting r apology.
Well, i think we should try
to stay on good terms
for danielle's sake.
I'm glad you suggested
that we eat out here.
I never think to do this.
Oh, darn,
i forgot the napkins.
Oh, no problem.
I'll go get some.
So now that we have
a moment alone,
your mother and i would like
to say how proud we are of you.
Yeah, right.
Seriously, we hadn't realized
you'd matured enough
to take on the burden
of motherhood all by yourself.
Well, grandma's gonna help.
She'll do what she can,
but you mustn't overtax her.
Her heart is not very strong.
She seems fine to me.
Well, knock wood.
We'd hate to see you forced
to take care of a baby
and a sick old woman.
Whoa! Mah-jongg.
Don't see that much anymore.
Hey, hey.
Danielle,
you should introduce yourself.
These people
are your new friends.
Mm.
And you're going to
learn more
from their experience
and wisdom
than you ever could have learned
at that college in florida.
Wait. I thought
i couldn't go there.
You said it was
just a party school.
Well, actually, we checked
into the curriculum,
and it's very strong,
but no matter.
You' be happier here.
Yes, and with a grandmother's
unconditional love,
who needs frat boys who only
like you for your convertible?
Whoa. When did i get
a convertible?
Well, we were gonna surprise you
with one for your birthday,
but since you're keeping
the baby, you'll want
a more practical gift.
We're thinking
a diaper service.
Oh, look,
they have water aerobics.
Up!
Out. Out.
You should sign up.
You know, maybe i should
go to college.
I mean, for the by's sake.
How can i support it
without a degree?
But you can't raise this child
in a miami dorm room.
You'll need to leave it
with someone you can trust
to take care of it properly.
Sorry.
The elevator's out. I...
oh. I have to catch my breath.
Grandma?
We need to talk.
What's this?
I thought we might toast
my victory.
I'm kind of in the middle
of something here.
Oh.
So... you haven't
congratulated me yet.
I know.
Would you like to tell me
what's bothering you?
I just want you to think
about what you've been doing
for the past few days.
You've mounted a crusade
against a metal thing
that shoots out water.
I'm trying to keep
the neighborhood beautiful.
I love this street.
Yeah, you keep saying that...
how happy you used to be here,
but ever since
we've moved back,
all i've seen
is an unhappy woman
who needs
to control everything.
Well... we've both learned
what happens
when you lose control.
Oh. Chicago again.
Tell you something else
we learned there.
When the chips are down,
it helps to have friends.
And you certainly
haven't made us any lately.
Congratulations.
Bye, grandma.
Good-bye, dear.
Tell your stepfather
i'll be right out.
Ohplease, phyllis.
Even you have to agree
that a girl who'd trade
her baby for a convertible
isn't ready for motherhood.
She'd have changed
once the baby came.
She's her father's daughter.
That's a nice picture
of rex.
Oh, i have
a lot of pictures.
All of the women here do.
They're what we have left
of the things
time has taken from us...
youth, homes and husbands...
and for the unluckiest,
children.
I thought i was getting back
a part of rex.
But now...
i know you're lonely,
phyllis,
but i can't give up this child
just to make you feel better.
You should go.
Your family's waiting for you.
Orson and i go to our club
almost every saturday night,
if you're... interested
in babysitting.
You mean it?
How will you explain me
to your friends?
I'll say that you're broke
and needed the money.
Can't you just say that
you like having me around?
I need something
that will fly, phyllis.
Hey. What's going on?
We need to talk.
So here's the deal.
I think it's time for us
to do the right thing.
I don't think
i like where this is going.
We have to end this affair.
You serious?
All this... sneaking around,
wearing disguises,
hiding in closets...
it's just wrong.
We're better than this.
So what are you suggesting,
we stay with victor and edie?
No, we break up with them.
Iook, it'll hurt,
but at least it's honest.
And then when enough time has
gone by and they've moved on,
we can be together.
How long
are we talking about?
I don't know. Six months?
Six months? Nobody takes
that long to heal anymore.
It's a breakup,
not a face-lift.
Hey, look, i want us
to be together, too,
but i also wanna
feel good about it.
Don't you?
Yeah. I do.
You're such
a good guy, carlos.
I really hate that about you.
I know.
So... i guess this is it.
This kiss has to last
six months.
You better make it good.
His guy can fly.
My guy freeze.
Hey, lynette.
Hey, judas.
Okay, fine.
You're still angry,
but i'm gonna make it up
to you.
When they come after
that tree house,
they're going to have
one susan mayer chained to it.
Don't do that. I wanna be sad
when they knock it down.
Lynette!
What? You think
you can just walk over here
and cute your way
out of what you did?
We're supposed to be friends.
Exactly,
and friends don't put friends
in this kind of position.
I love you,
but you can't ask me
to put your kids
ahead of my husband.
No, parker, that guy
doesn't have freezing...
you're right.
I shouldn't have done that.
But that tree house is
the one place my kids can go
and not hear about body scans
and white blood cell counts.
It is their getaway
from this horrible thing
that i've brought
into the house.
"Brought"? Sweetie, it's not
your fault that you're sick.
I know that... here.
But here...
it feels like
i've ruined their childhood.
Okay, if anybody needs me,
i'll be at the hardware ore
buying chains.
Oh, jeez. Get over here.
Hello there!
Oh, look, it's our new queen...
katherine of arrogant.
Hey,
where's the wrecking ball?
Actually, i came to tell you
the tree house can stay.
Oh, my god.
That's great!
Yes. If anyone complains,
we'll say
it was grandfathered in under
the previous administration.
Wow.
Thanks. Why?
Clearly,
it means a lot to you,
and i wanna be
a good neighbor.
Katherine.
What's with you? Sometimes you
act like an ice queen,
and then you do
something really nice.
You are
one complicated lady.
Well, i've had
one complicated life.
I've had a lot of men
in my life,
but i never let myself
fall in love before.
I thought it was because
i didn't wanna get hurt,
but... now i know
the pain you feel
isn't the worst part.
It's the hate.
Could you make it out
to "cash"?
Hello, katherine.
You here about the fountain?
Yes, but don't worry.
There's no strict deadline.
You can... have it removed
at your earliest convenience.
Yeah, i don't think
it's going anywhere.
Oh, boys, boys,
the war's over.
Yes, it is.
We know
all about chicago.
Come again?
My ex is on the board
of chicago memorial hospital.
Seems your husband
made quite a stir there...
whole hospital still
buzzing about what he did.
Whatever you heard
is a vicious lie...
every word of it.
Still, it was enough to...
make you leave town,
which begs the question,
do you like living here?
Oh, good. We're in agreement.
The fountain stays.
Thanks for stopping by,
katherine.
It's the same for all of us.
We try not to get too close
to the people
who live next door.
It's easier to give them
a polite nod
than to ask what's wrong.
It's safer to keep walking by
than to get involved.
...you right now.
Okay, i don't wanna work...
true, we sometimes do
get to know the people
we share a fence with
and end up lifelong friends.
Thanks for everything.
Thank you.
But mostly,
we keep our distance
because we'd rather
our neighbors
know nothing about us...
than know too much.