It's payday!
And I'm not talking
about the delicious
Little treat with nuts.
Han, not cool to brag
about yourself.
Here, Max, maybe you can use
the money to buy a new attitude.
"New attitude"?
Isn't that the name
of the boy band you're in?
And Oleg, you'll notice
I docked your pay
'cause you didn't even come
in yesterday.
I told you,
I was working from home.
There you go, Earl.
Don't spend it all in one place.
You think you pay me enough
to spend it in two places?
Oh, my God, this is less than
it cost me to get here today.
And I walked.
I know.
That's all I made?
What is this,
"12 Years A Waitress"?
With you it's more like
"12 Beers A Shift".
So many words,
so little everything else.
(peter bjorn and john)
♪ ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
[cash register bell dings]
♪ ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
Man: Whoa!
[Caroline gasps]
Not the face!
Not my beautiful face!
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
I warn you,
I was in the Nutcracker Suite.
- What's that mean?
- This!
[groans]
Don't worry Max, I handled it.
Yeah, I just handled it too.
That's my booty call.
Are you telling me you know him?
No, I don't know him.
He just comes over for sex
on Tuesday nights.
Do you need help up?
Not yet, I'm still crying
a little.
Okay, up you go.
Walk it off.
[groans]
Yeah, I bet that hurts.
Nice going Caroline.
You ruined the best part.
Hi, I'm Caroline, the roommate
and prima ballerina.
Sorry about your sugar plums.
Sebastian.
Ba-Ba-Ba!
No names! No names!
Uh, Caroline, you want a soda?
We have soda?
No, we don't have soda!
Why are you asking him his name?
He doesn't wanna know my name
and I don't wanna know his.
Hey, mind if I use
your bathroom?
I need to check on the boys.
See if they're girls.
How do you not know the name
of the guy you're intimate with?
"Intimate"?
Max, there are certain things
you have to know
About the guy you're engaging
in sexual congress with.
Only you can make sex boring.
Well, not too bad.
One's okay and the other one
left on crutches.
Later.
Sebastian, wait.
This is Max Black.
Max, this is Sebastian.
Nice to meet you, Max.
Yeah, nice to meet you too.
And you can just call me
what you usually do.
"Oh, God."
Hey is that a new shirt, Earl?
Why, yes it is, Max.
I just got it in 1987.
[text message ding]
Oh, great!
Look at this text.
It's from the guy
whose sperm count you lowered.
His name is Sebastian.
Oh, he's inviting you
to come see him DJ.
Oh, damn it! I told you
I didn't wanna know anything
About him,
and now I know he's a DJ.
Which means he's unemployed,
so points for that.
So what are you gonna text
him back?
Nothing!
The only back-and-forth
I want from this guy
Is on his back
and for the fourth time.
The best sex is secret sex.
Then maybe don't talk
about it while I'm eating.
Well, I have a sexy secret.
A crush on a girl.
Oleg, we all know it's me.
That sweat-pant salute
never lies.
Not you.
Don't kid yourself.
You couldn't handle
this beast in the sheets.
I could totally handle you
in the sheets, Oleg.
What are you fighting for,
Caroline?
Hey, everybody!
All right, weather report:
I just came back from a date and
it's raining losers out there.
There's my sexy, sexy,
secret crush.
Who, Sophie?
Not so secret.
You two have already done it in
every public space in Brooklyn.
Yeah, and your apartment, twice.
What?
We didn't even wake you!
Sophie, baby,
I've been looking
for the perfect woman
And it turns out, what I want
is in my own back door.
Backyard.
I think you're both right.
I hear your truck pull up.
But I'm not sure I wanna sign
for your package anymore.
I knew you were going
to say that.
So as a reminder,
I've created a Sizzle Reel
Of our best sex.
So it's an STDVD?
It's the extended version.
Uncut, as you know.
That's it, cancel my brownie!
Sizzle Reel?
I'll watch it tonight
while I eat my fajitas.
[text message dings]
Max, you just got another text
from Sebastian.
Who?
Please, can we go to the club
to see him DJ, Max?
I wanna dance.
The last time I shook my booty
Was when we ran out
of toilet paper.
Max, thank you so much
for taking me dancing.
Well, you signed that paper
that said if I did,
You'd do the side work
for the next six months.
Are you sure this is the address
Of the club Sebastian gave you?
Who?
Sebastian!
This can't be the address.
It's a Whole Foods.
I know what it is.
I can smell the cage-free
body odor.
Let's just go in, ask someone
if they know where the club is,
And maybe rip a grape off a stem.
I'm starving.
Whole Foods, wow.
Reminds me of when
I was a whole person.
Max, we can start looking
for the club.
All right, all right.
I'm gonna lay down some beats
while you check out our beets.
Organic!
See?
This is why I didn't want
to know anything!
You ask a guy his name
and you find out
He's DJ'ing next to radishes.
And what kind of loser
comes here to dance?
Woot! Woot!
Holla!
And I don't mean
the kosher bread!
Oh, no.
How did you find me here?
Whole Foods is my sexy secret.
You know what's not a secret?
The organic Preparation H
in that basket.
Whole Foods is where I come
to get my groove on.
Why?
Is Chuck E. Cheese closed?
As much as I'd love to see
what else you're gonna buy
To rub on your butt,
we're leaving
Before that DJ sees me.
You mean DJ Fresh-and-Local?
The music be bumpin'
and we buyin' pumpkin!
Let's go. I can't believe
I wore these for this.
Wake up.
It's Tuesday, and the DJ
didn't come.
Maybe he just drank too much.
No! He didn't show at all.
There's no DJ Fresh-and-Local
in my ones and twos.
Well, what did you expect?
You ran out of there without
even saying "hi".
We should've stayed at the club.
Stop calling it a club!
He DJs at a supermarket,
Which is the lamest thing
I've ever seen,
Not counting the time
You tried to bring back
the phrase
"Oh, no, you didn't."
I'm surprised at you.
What if I judged you
for some of your jobs?
Uh, bar-back slash captain
of a shrimp boat
In the Gulf of Mexico
isn't the bomb?
What about when you worked
at the Gap?
Who told you about the Gap?
You, that time you were drunk,
folding a sweater,
And you tried to help me
"spring into summer"
With cargo shorts.
Fine! I fell into the Gap.
I needed the money.
Maybe sebastian needs
the money, too.
Who?
[knock at door]
And if you ever tell anyone
about the Gap,
You will have a gap
between your neck
And where your head used to be.
"Oh, no you didn't."
Hey, I wasn't sure
if it was too late to come by
But the Ouija board said,
"Go ahead, the girls are up!"
You use that?
The only spirit I listen
to is Two-Buck Chuck,
And he mostly tells me
to take my top off.
Yeah, Ouija helps me make
all my big decisions.
Like coming to America,
adopting a Chinese orphan,
And leaving a Chinese orphan
at the fire station.
Those boards are creepy.
You never know what you're
inviting in.
I mean, what if we open
a Hellmouth?
Aw, come on, girls, look around.
I mean, you already have.
Okay, now shh.
Okay...
Ouija,
should I take Oleg back?
Yes?
Oh, now, see, that is creepy
Because I was shoving
it to "no".
Do you want to get back
with him?
Well, I'm torn.
And also,
I don't know what to do.
[dance music plays]
Throw your hands in the air
like you just don't kale.
Max, I'm proud of you
for overlooking his job
And giving this guy a chance.
He's making a DJ face.
I'm out.
Oh, my God, Dylan.
No, we can't leave now.
I just saw this girl,
and she is the last person
I want to see.
What is the problem?
It's Hilary Waldare.
We went to Wharton together.
So competitive with me.
Loved it when I lost
all my money.
She even threw a party
to celebrate
And then had the nerve
to invite me.
Worst party ever, by the way.
Uh, worse than being
at a dance club
That has a price club?
Max Black in the house of grain.
And now he saw me.
Well, I'm gonna go hide
before she sees me.
I'll be in Tom's Shoes.
Nobody's ever over there.
I'm bustin' out some free range
electronic dance music.
That's right!
I'm bringing it in my own bag.
Uh, okay, we good?
See you next Tuesday.
Come on, stay.
What's your hurry?
I can't watch any more people
dance-shop.
Max, come on.
Get in front of me.
See what you can do.
Oh, you're behind me this time.
That's new.
All right, everybody,
Frisee, 'cause we got
a special guest DJ
in the hizzay!
Who's so hot it's radicchio.
Go on.
Bob, I'd like to bid $1.00.
$1.00, Bob, $1.00.
Have your pets
spayed or neutered.
Speaking of neutered pets,
here comes Han.
Still counts as a DJ shout-out.
Hey, why wait till Tuesday?
Why don't I take a break
and we can go in the back.
I just need to find someone
to cover me.
Someone bogarted
all the nut butter.
How about half of someone?
Can I help you, miss?
Max?
What are you doing?
I'm thirsty, broke, and they
cut me off at the free lemonade.
What are you doing?
Well, two dudes
were getting it on
In the family restroom, so...
Where's Sebastian?
Who?
Oh, milk.
Bottom shelf.
What's up?
You're not doing it
in the dairy case!
Uh, no I'm not,
'cause you won't go away.
Do you have to ruin sex
everywhere?
Well, Max,
if I wasn't lactose intolerant
Before, I am now.
Oh, my God, Caroline Channing!
Hi!
It's Hilary Waldare.
- Oh, my God! Hi!
- Hi!
I haven't seen you
since your party.
Someone said you left crying.
How are you?
I'm great! I mean,
I'm shopping at Whole Foods,
Buying some organic fuel
that I'll probably take
A couple sips of in spin class
and then throw away, so...
Oh, good, 'cause I heard
you were still poor
And that you were working
as a waitress.
A waitress?
That is insane.
That is so insane it should be
in an ice tub in an asylum.
I'm so glad you're great,
because when I saw you
In those three-year-old
Louboutins, I got worried.
Also, you have
an orange juice mustache.
Oh. Where's Max?
Milk.
- Max, listen...
- Busy!
Hilary's still here.
And she called me a waitress.
How dare her.
She humiliated me,
and I didn't even get
A party this time.
I'm going home.
(store manager) Hilary Waldare,
report to register three.
Oh, my God!
Did he just say...
(store manager)
Hilary Waldare. Register three.
He did!
Oh, my God! Max!
Busy!
What?
Do you wanna just join us?
Hilary Waldare works here,
as a cashier!
So I win!
Everyone knows on the job
humiliation chain,
It goes:
Prostitute, hostess, waitress,
cashier, Princess Jasmine in the
Disney Electric Light Parade.
What happened
to not looking down
On other people
with crappy jobs?
Oh, please, this is real.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have got $14
Burning a second hole
in my pocket,
And I'm gonna spend it here
at register three.
[Sebastian moans]
Whoo!
What, you couldn't wait for me?
This goes out to Kelly
in prepared foods.
The Kelly with the cystic acne,
not the Kelly
with the bald spot.
Now, where my Adele-heads at?
I'm glad you have no line,
'cause I have an exclusive
Private yoga class to get to...
Oh, Hilary!
Yes, Caroline.
I am a cashier.
I'm sorry, a what?
I'm a cashier.
Yeah, turns out things
aren't great.
My husband left me for my dad.
And they didn't even cut me
in on the lifetime movie rights.
It's on in January.
Father is the bride.
Let me just weigh your salad.
Well, I'm sure you'll pull
yourself together like I did.
'cause I'm kind of killing it,
life-wise.
That'll be $28.
There's only $14 here.
$28 for a salad?
Well, that's dinosaur kale.
Oh! Mistake.
Didn't want the Dinosaur kale.
Never liked dinosaurs
and really don't like them
in my kale.
Dinosaur kale gone.
You're just putting it
on the counter?
Oh, I don't usually shop
for myself.
Is that not how it's done?
Caroline, do you not have
enough money?
No, Hilary, I have enough money.
I just don't know why
I have so many eggs.
Here. You're holding up
the line.
You obviously don't have
enough money
To pay for your salad.
Sad.
I don't know what
you're implying.
Oh! Here is my very successful
business partner.
Sorry it took so long.
I couldn't find my pants.
I don't know how they made it
all the way to the loading dock.
Face it Caroline,
you came here to humiliate me
And you can't even afford
that egg.
On your face.
Miss, did you drop
this $20 bill?
Yes! Yes I did!
I dropped some money, too.
Don't push it.
Thank you, sir.
This is very kind of you
And I really appreciate it.
Anything for my favorite
waitress.
[gasps]
Oh, I knew you were a waitress.
Your store sucks!
I just had sex
in your dairy department.
Keep the change.
And buy your dad-husband
a wedding gift.
Okay, one more time.
Ouija, should I be with Oleg?
15 out of 15 yeses.
That's still unclear.
Sophie, this is silly.
You know you two wanna
get back together.
Caroline, we already have
the Ouija board.
We don't need another thing
around here that's flat
And wrong all the time.
Fine. Sophie, if it's not me,
after all I've offered you, go.
Ask the spirits who the man
you are supposed to be with is.
Ouija, please spell out
the name of the man
That I'm supposed to be with.
Oh, look, it's moving.
"V", "A", "N",
This is what the world
was like before the internet.
"K", "O".
"Vanko".
Vanko?
Yeah, that sounds cute.
Yeah, I like it...
I'm sorry, Oleg.
The spirits have spoken.
I'm supposed to be with someone
named Vanko.
And they know the best.
So you're supposed to be with
someone named Vanko?
Mm-hmm.
"Vanko Oleg Golishevsky"?
I go by my middle name
'cause there were seven other
Vankos in my family.
But I didn't even know that.
Yeah, that means the Ouija is...
Oh, uh...
Ohh... Yeah...
Oh, no, no, Vanko.
No!
I...
No, I...
We can... You and I can get back
together, okay?
But I just can't be here
right now.
No, I mean,
this is just too damn spooky!
[shrieks]
I can't wait to tell my brothers
Vanko and Vanko about this.
Uh, uh, uh.
Word on the street is,
you've been talking
some smack about cashiers.