Rebekah, voice-over: My brothers and I
are the first vampires in history...
The Originals.
300 years ago, we called New Orleans home.
I was happy here...
for a time.
Now we've returned,
only to find a miracle...
Niklaus, the girl is carrying your child.
Rebekah, voice-over: And with
it, a new responsibility...
I will always protect you.
You have my word on that.
Rebekah, voice-over: But
our family has many enemies.
Klaus destroyed everything good in my life.
So I'm gonna take away
the thing he wants most.
Rebekah, voice-over: These
threats should have united us.
Instead, Klaus has driven us apart.
Why should I help you after
what you did to Elijah?
You're my family.
Marcel: Klaus will never
stop trying to control you.
What do you want?
Rebekah, voice-over: My
brother expects my loyalty,
as he has for 1,000 years,
but now, perhaps, it's time
to make a different choice.
[Blues music playing]
Rebekah: I should never
have come back here.
This is the town where I fell in love
and where love failed us.
I assume you know who I'm talking about.
You should know, Marcel and I aren't on the
best of terms right now.
But you are an active priest, are you not,
ready and able to hear my confession?
Usually, the word "willing"
falls somewhere in that sentence.
Are you even Catholic?
I've been on this earth for 1,000 years.
I can't say for certain that I believe
in anything like a God, but
I need absolution
from someone,
anyone.
So will you hear my confession or not?
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
I am a liar,
a betrayer.
I have conspired against my own blood,
and I doubt even your God could save me.
Have you spoken to our
good friend Marcel today?
No. Should I have?
Well, he's been mysteriously silent,
avoiding me, some might say.
I thought, perhaps, he may have whispered
reasons into your ear
along with all of those sweet nothings.
If I see him, I'll be sure to ask
if he's still sore at you.
Let me give a voice to
that look in your eyes.
"My saintly, noble brother
lies writhing in agony in the bayou,
victim of my bastard brother's bite
when just one or two drops
of his blood would ease his pain."
One the contrary, Nik.
I am simply enjoying my brekkie
waiting for Elijah's healthy return.
Oh, come on, Rebekah.
You've been giving me the
devil's eye all morning.
Out with it.
Perhaps I'm concerned
that if I voice my opinion
about what you did to Elijah,
I will end up on the wrong
side of your toxic hybrid teeth.
Poppycock. I would never bite you.
Elijah made some very offensive accusations
about my intentions towards my child.
He deserves a day or two of discomfort.
Besides, you know my preferred method
of punishment for your indiscretions
is the dagger.
[Chuckles]
There's something
fundamentally wrong with you.
[Gasping]
Here. Drink this.
- [Coughing]
- Mm.
Forgive me, please.
It's ok.
Remind me to annihilate your
brother once you're healthy.
Yes. Remind me to remind
you to get in line.
Doesn't help that we decided to shack up
in the middle of a swamp, either.
[Elijah coughs]
- Are you ok?
- I'm fine.
Please just...
return to your reading.
Well, I went through
the whole thing. It's...
just a regular Bible
with an entry in the family tree
that may or may not be me,
but you know I've been a little busy
worrying about you.
Hayley, please.
This fever will make me unstable.
Now, once these hallucinations begin,
I'll start to see things.
I will start to say things.
You must leave me here.
I'm not leaving you like this.
[Coughs]
[Blues music playing]
All right. I'm here.
Let's do this.
I'll keep this simple.
This kid is an old enemy
of your favorite person Klaus.
Now, he's got plenty to say
about what that traitorous
son of a bitch has been
up to behind my back.
Now, for those of you faint of heart,
there's the door
because those who stick around,
you're signing up for battle.
Tyler: You all know Klaus
wasn't always the hybrid.
When he broke the curse that
kept his werewolf side dormant,
somewhere in all that,
certain parts were now able
to trump his vampire side,
like the ability to pass
on the werewolf gene.
That's where the werewolf
girl he's been hiding
from you all comes in.
She rolled through my town,
pretended to be my friend,
and ended up hooking up with him.
Now she's pregnant with his kid.
What the hell is this?
Just listen.
When Klaus became the hybrid,
he figured out a way to
turn full-bred werewolves
into creatures like him.
You're looking at one of them.
On the plus side, we had all
the perks of being vampires.
We were stronger, faster,
and the toxins in our bites
could still kill a vampire,
but on the downside, we were loyal to him,
like, supernaturally loyal.
Right, and that's why you're here
spilling all his secrets?
No. That's the point, Diego.
He figured out a way to break free of it.
And I helped the rest of them, too.
Then Klaus killed them for their betrayal.
Because that is what Klaus does.
Don't mind me.
I'm fascinated by this story.
- Hello, Tyler.
- Rebekah.
Long time, no see.
What Tyler is about to
tell you is that my brother
can use his baby's blood
to sire more hybrids.
What you will all figure out is that
vampires don't stand a chance.
So, Tyler, I assume you
were trying to rally this lot
into making sure the baby isn't born.
Yeah.
You don't like it,
go ahead and take your brother's side,
but you know I'm right.
I believe you've mistaken
the lady's intentions.
Diego: All right. What's going on?
You're absolutely right, Tyler.
My brother is a crap
enough individual as it is.
The last thing he needs is
to sire a superior species.
Go on. You can tell them.
She's not here to fight us.
She's here to help us.
That's right,
but first...
[Crack]
[Thud]
Whew,
that is enough talk
about harming that baby.
Klaus is the one we're putting a stop to.
Klaus: They have all forsaken me.
My siblings are as deceitful and diseased
as my parents ever were,
accusing me
of using my baby for my own gain,
trusting others before their own blood.
Ohh, would a laptop kill you?
That typewriter was good
enough for Hemingway.
Can see the resemblance...
booze and random acts of violence.
Elijah and Rebekah have cut to the quick
with their vicious lies about me
when all I've done
is tried to win this battle
of wills over Marcel's control
of the quarter in order
to reclaim our home.
Type, please.
What's the point?
You just repeat the same
thing over and over again.
Rebekah is out to get you.
Elijah is out to get you.
Is there anyone who isn't
plotting your downfall?
I doubt you trust your own reflection.
You know, if the daggers weren't missing,
I would put one in each of their hearts,
rid myself of the burden of my siblings
for a couple of centuries.
Look at you,
repeating the same destructive cycles
over and over again.
You are the architect
of your own unhappiness.
I don't remember asking for your advice.
Oh, really?
So of all the people in New Orleans,
you choose someone with
a master's in psychology
to record your life story.
You're over 1,000 years old.
Pretty damn sure you know how to type.
The truth is, you compel me to come here
because you have no one else to talk to,
and you want to be understood.
Then you compel me to forget everything
as soon as I leave your presence
because you're too scared to trust.
I am scared of nothing.
What is this?
It's an ancient, mystical
plot I'm using to destroy you.
Relax. It's a tattoo design.
Draw on your own time.
This is my time.
You steal it from me.
Where do you want him?
Rebekah: Well, just put him anywhere handy
until Klaus is taken care of.
Where are we gonna put Klaus?
He needs to be away from all the others.
We don't want him fomenting descent.
You know he has a knack with words.
He could talk his way out of hell.
Yeah. I got a spot picked
out for him in the back.
Only person he's gonna be talking to
for the next 52 years is himself.
52?
One for each year that he
kept you daggered in the 1800s.
You mean, you let him keep me daggered.
And I'll spend every year Klaus is in here
apologizing to you for it.
Well, I'll settle for long enough
to experience just
a little bit of happiness
and ensure that my niece isn't turned
into a hybrid breeding machine.
It's gonna be tough to keep him in here.
That little witch of yours
would put the odds in our favor.
I can't risk it.
She's got less and less control
over her magic lately.
I can't even get her
out of the church attic,
much less rely on her to
go to battle against Klaus.
Then we'll need your very best warriors.
Klaus is strong and crafty,
and betrayal makes him particularly nasty.
What we're doing is
nothing Klaus hasn't done
to both you and your brother
a dozen times over.
You're not getting second
thoughts now, are you?
No. These aren't second thoughts.
They're feelings of regret.
I should've buried him a hundred years ago.
It's a hundred years we
could've been together.
Uh!
It's ok. It's ok.
Oh, Celeste.
Hayley, I'm sorry.
I thought you were someone else.
- Celeste?
- Yes.
Whoever she was, she was smoking hot.
How...
Did I let you enter my thoughts?
I'm not well. I should go.
[Coughs]
- This is...
- This is fine.
Elijah, you're sick.
I'm taking care of you.
We're being watched.
Hey!
Oh, man, I'll never get used to that.
Why do I get the feeling
you studied theater?
All the world's a stage, young Joshua,
and it just so happens I have
the role of a lifetime for you.
What do you got, Josh?
What do I got?
Klaus wants me to steal some
dagger from you. It's a test, ok?
He knows I'm working
for you. I'm sure of it.
That bastard wants to dagger us again.
He deserves everything he's gonna get.
Relax.
If he knew, he would've
ripped out your spine
through your nose by now.
Oh, great.
Now I feel totally at ease.
- What am I supposed to do?
- You tell him
you searched high and low but
you couldn't find the dagger.
Oh, God, I'm so dead.
Then you tell him you saw I had it on me,
that if he wants it, he'll
have to come and get it,
which won't be easy because I'm paranoid
and I beefed up my posse.
Josh: All right.
So, not doubting your mad vampire skills
of destruction or anything,
but Marcel is on red alert,
surrounded by, like, an army.
You're totally boned,
- unless...
- Unless what?
I overheard him arguing with Diego.
Apparently, he's clearing out
the compound tonight
for a date or something.
That's where Marcel will be.
When I run New Orleans,
there will be a permanent daylight
ring in it for you, Joshua,
for services rendered
unto your true king...
Cool.
But...
if you ever betray me,
I will make sure you spend
the rest of your eternal life
in exquisite agony
wishing for a merciful death.
Adios, Klaus.
What do you want?
It's poitin.
It'd raise the dead,
kill them, and raise them again.
I'd like to talk to you
about your niece Camille.
I'm sure you suspect this already
by the gaps in her memory.
I compel her.
At first, it was because
she was a useful spy
but now for her own protection.
I assumed a vampire was
messing with her mind,
though I never anticipated a confession.
She won't leave things be.
Her mind churns with the permutations
of what happened in this church
when her twin when on his slaughter spree.
Now, if she finds out what really happened,
that the vampires and witch hexes
were involved, she will dig
and dig and dig until she digs too deep
and gets herself killed.
New Orleans will be the death of her.
She needs to leave,
and, as ironic as it may seem,
I believe it should be her choice.
Yes.
It is ironic discussing free will
with a mind-controlling vampire.
She's a clever girl.
She gave me a piece of
her mind earlier today.
I would've killed others for less.
I care about her survival.
I smell war in the air,
and with every war,
there is the innocent victim
who could have been spared
if they had just walked away.
Please convince her to
walk away from New Orleans,
or I'll be forced to compel her to go.
[Chuckles]
Assistance, please, good sir.
No. I'm much happier
taking in such a wondrous view.
It's perfection.
Celeste: Your brother
is again up to no good.
He's challenging the gentry to duels
as though they have any
chance of a fair fight.
I do grow weary
of sacrificing my joy
to temper my brother's mischief.
Surely, you can cast a spell,
put him in his place.
It will take 100 witches
to put him in his place.
Besides, he only ever listens to you.
Yes.
He certainly needs a little discipline.
Perhaps a spanking of
some kind is in order.
I think I shall need some rehearsal. Come.
[Chuckles]
[Babbles]
Hayley, please.
This fever. My mind
is flooded with these tortuous memories.
You have to leave.
What is your deal?
You don't like people taking care of you?
There are consequences for those that care.
I will not have you pay that price.
So you're having weird retro sex dreams.
Get over it. I'm staying.
So what about our visitor?
What does she want?
I'm guessing she's the one
that left the mystery Bible
on the doorstep last night.
Would be nice if she'd stick around
long enough to tell me why.
Hayley, you came here to gather information
about my family, not to play nursemaid to a
vampire with a temperature. Please...
find her. Learn what you can.
No.
I'm staying.
[Jazz music playing]
Marcel: Klaus.
You've been avoiding my calls.
A little pissed off lately.
Apologies for my behavior can come later.
You have something of mine.
I want it back.
Sorry, but I can't do that.
What is this?
Apologies for your behavior?
You don't apologize, Nik. You just act.
I've had enough.
We have had enough.
Well, look at you,
finally in possession of the one thing
that can take you down.
- How does it feel?
- Great.
[Whistles]
So this is it.
The evil bastard Klaus has gone too far,
must be punished
and by his own sibling, nonetheless.
How positively biblical.
And you, Marcel,
is this your idea of a hit?
I taught you better than this
paltry excuse for a takedown.
You think you can subdue me
with this?
No,
but I think I can with this.
[Whistles]
[Panting]
Celeste...
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
A l'outrance.
Huit, sept, six, cinq,
quatre, trois, deux...
Is that it?
Is this the best New Orleans has to offer?
Brother, please.
This is high folly.
Is it not enough that you have slaughtered
dozens in just these past several weeks?
Well...
Word of a city littered with bodies
will surely travel the oceans.
Do you want to bring our father upon us?
Relax, brother.
I've sent rumor that
the bodies are a result
of the witches seeking blood
sacrifice for their rituals.
You did what?
Have you forgotten Celeste is one of those
that you so recklessly
pointed your finger at?
Who's Celeste?
Oh, yes,
the witch you've been knocking around with.
Well, fear not.
Harlots are like rats in the quarter.
You trip over one every step you take.
Ugh! Agh! Rrgh.
Hmm...
You care about her.
Well, that is unfortunate.
I hear they're rounding up
the town's witches as we speak.
Uh! Aah! Ah! Huh!
Elijah? Oh!
Niklaus, I'll kill you, you bastard.
Elijah? Aah!
Nngh!
Uh! Agh!
Hello to you, too.
Let's end this charade, shall we?
Vampires of New Orleans,
do recall
that I am an Original,
a hybrid. I cannot be killed.
Eternity is an awfully long time.
How long
do you think Marcel will stay in power?
What if one of you lot
were to release me,
knowing I would be eternally in your debt?
Oh, I would pity
those of you who dared to cross me.
I can assure you,
your ends would be spectacular.
To borrow a trick
from an old friend...
Whoever picks up
this coin
gets to live.
Now, which of you magnificent
bastards wants to join me?
Anyone wants that coin,
pledge allegiance to Klaus,
take it now.
Go ahead.
The choice is yours.
Take him.
Hmm...
Nngh!
[Blows continue]
Yaagh!
[Crack]
[Growling]
[Growling stops]
Raagh!
Marcel! Come and finish this!
No.
- Take the coin.
- What?
He won't stop until everyone is dead,
and he will kill you, too. End this.
Pick up the coin.
Yaagh!
Enough!
[Crack]
[Thud]
Well, well, well.
The great Marcel,
self-proclaimed king of New Orleans,
bowing before me.
There.
I hereby pledge my allegiance to you.
You have the keys to my kingdom.
It's yours.
[Scrubbing]
I was on my way home,
saw you duck in here,
knew exactly where you'd be.
This is getting old.
It's the second time this week.
Third,
but I cleaned it off
the day before yesterday.
It's pointless. They'll just do it again.
Folks need time to heal.
Sean killed innocent people.
No one is getting over that any time soon.
I think...
I think I'm losing it like he did.
I found this in my pocket.
The lines,
it's a secret code Sean and I
used to use when we were kids.
I have no memory of drawing it.
Something is not right.
I just can't figure it out.
Come here.
Oh...
Maybe you should
leave town for a while...
Give your head some space.
I know your Dean.
You could put your thesis on hold.
I can't.
This means something.
I just don't know what.
Not everything has meaning.
Sometimes you just have to let go.
You should leave New Orleans.
This town isn't for everybody.
Please.
Woman: I'm sure you got questions.
Only a thousand of them,
like who are you,
why are you following me,
where the hell is everyone,
and if the people in this book
really are my family,
what happened to them?
I'm Eve.
I'm following you because you brought
an Original to werewolf country,
which is pretty much the same reason
why everybody else skedaddled,
and if you want to know what happened
to the people in that family tree,
summing it up nice and quick,
Marcel happened.
What did he do?
He killed most of them.
Later, the
descendents of the ones who dodged death,
he strong-armed a witch
into putting a curse on them.
What kind of curse?
Swap nature around, inside out,
made it so their natural state was wolves.
They only turn back human on the full moon.
We get hunted by the marks we carry,
that Crescent moon birthmark.
That's why I got rid of mine.
I didn't want to get found out.
Elijah: Good evening.
Think...
I might have something
which belongs to you.
Elijah, I've got this.
Are you ok?
The wound had healed, the fever has broken,
but for some strange reason,
I have this sharpened
lingering sensation in my back.
I have to get him home,
but I'll be back, ok?
I need to know more.
Keep that mark covered up.
What happened?
I just met part of my family.
Looking at what you've wrought?
Look. If you're gonna kill me,
let's get this over with.
Why would I kill you?
You picked up the coin.
There are rules of
engagement in battle, Marcel.
Without them, you'd have anarchy.
I would, however, like to talk
about accommodations,
your living quarters, for example.
I believe they used to be mine.
You want all this? Fine. It's yours.
You can put me back on
the street for all I care,
but let's make one thing clear.
You'll never have this...
Loyalty.
You can't buy it. You can't own it.
You can't force it.
It comes only out of love and respect
for the people who believe in you.
You taught me many
things, Niklaus Mikaelson,
but this I learned myself,
and it is something
that you will never know.
Enjoy your kingdom.
So thanks for the ride.
Quite the awkward, little
adventure, wouldn't you say?
I'm sorry I tried to hurt you.
I would never want that.
Elij...
Tell me what happened to Celeste.
- That's not important.
- It is important.
1,000 years of memories,
and that's what breaks
through your fever brain?
I want to know.
Show me.
[Panting]
Aah!
It was a cruel and bloody time
to be a witch,
courtesy of my wonderful brother.
- She died because of Klaus?
- She died because of me,
because I cared too deeply for her.
I had allowed my brother
to slip through my grasp.
I'd loosened the reins while Celeste
consumed my every moment.
I'd abandoned him in the
name of my own happiness.
Celeste paid the price.
I don't get it.
Why are we here?
Why are you trying to
put together your family
when it's so clear that
one part of it is broken?
To me, the very definition
of the word "broken"
suggests that something can be fixed.
I have all eternity
to accomplish one single
task... my brother's salvation.
If I surrender this, then, tell me,
what value would I be to my family,
to myself, to...
to your child?
Please, no, Hayley.
You've seen what happens.
[Footsteps]
Elijah is home. There's only one dagger.
Which one of us will
you be punishing today?
I contemplated a game
of eeny meeny miny...
moe.
You betrayed me,
my own sister.
Niklaus, don't you dare.
Well, perhaps it should be you, brother,
stealing my child away
with every fawning moment
of tenderness you show to Hayley.
This has nothing to do with Hayley.
It has everything to do with her!
She's adored you since she arrived,
and now my child, my blood,
will grow up to call you father.
Is that what this is?
You are once again
worried that you will be left behind?
Has history taught you nothing?
We don't abandon you, Nik.
You drive us away.
Is that so?
What have I done lately
other than cooperate?
I bowed down to you, brother,
to make up for daggering you
for the greater good of our plan
to reclaim our home;
looked the other way, sister,
while you repeat the
same cycle with Marcel,
falling again for a man
you shouldn't be with
while he controls the empire that we built
that he took.
Now, I make no excuses
for past sins,
but in the one moment
when you two could have
chosen to stand by me,
to believe in me
and believe my intentions
for my own child were pure,
you chose to stand against me,
to side with my enemies.
I wanted our home back.
Now I have it.
So I'm going to live there,
and the two of you,
you can stay here together
and rot.
You're coming with me, little wolf.
Why would I go anywhere with you?
Because, Hayley, that child you carry
is the only thing on this
earth that matters to me.
Now, you can fight me on
this, but you will lose,
as will anyone else who tries
to stop you getting in this car.
I figured it out,
the note.
I was thinking about it... my lost time,
my foggy brain.
I thought I must be going crazy like Sean,
but then I thought,
"what if somewhere in my subconscious,
I was trying to send myself a message?"
I was.
I found this in the "Picayune"
newspaper archives from 1919.
Look at this photo.
Cami: Those men, I know them.
I know both of them.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -