Previously on Desperate Housewives:
A reporter just did a story
on homeless teens -- my son is one of them.
- Oh my God!
Orson found Andrew,
Have I done stuff for ney that
I'm not proud of? Yeah, sure.
and the prodigal son returned.
Mike fell into a coma...
What could be more romantic?
- Could think of--of something.
and Susan fell into the arms
of another man...
a bit too soon.
(Mary Alice)
the day Mike Delfino
woke from his coma,
Edie britt
was the first to know.
once she was sure
he was responsive...
Mike?
Aah! Aah!
Edie decided to share
the good news with others.
Code red! Code red!
My friend
just woke up from his coma.
And that is how
word began to spread.
Mike's physician, Dr. Craig,
was busy with a patient
when he first heard the news.
Not long after,
he called his aunt Ida,
who was busy
knitting a sweater.
she told Lynette Scavo,
who was busy watering her lawn,
and she told her husband Tom,
who was busy
playing a computer game.
he then e-mailed
his friend Carlos,
who was busy plotting strategy
with his divorce lawyer.
and Carlos called his
soon-to-be ex-wife Gabrielle,
who was busy
doing the same with hers.
Yes, word of
Mike's miraculous recovery
spread quickly
throughout Wisteria Lane
and stopped cold
everyone's busy, busy life--
everyone, that is...
except for Susan Mayer,
who was busy doing something
she would soon wish...
she hadn't.
Desperate Housewives 3x04
"Like It Was"
Edward Sibley
was the beloved founder
of the town of Fairview.
Prior to that,
he was best known
as a bootlegger...
a womanizer...
and a horse thief.
Of course, no one remembers
those parts of Edward's past.
Luckily for him, history is
designed to be rewritten...
and no one knew this better
than Bree Hodge.
So you're just gonna
lie to people?
Oh, I'm not talking about
a lie--just a polite fiction
to explain to everybody
where you've been.
I mean, we can't possibly
tell them that
you've been living on skid row,
sleeping in a cardboard box.
So why do I have to go
to this history fair anyway?
I mean, it's just
some dumb school contest.
We all know
Danielle's not gonna win.
She never wins anything.
- (sighs) is it weird
eating off plates?
'Cause if you were more
comfortable, you could just
Eat straight out of the garbage.
- This is a family event,
And we're all gonna
enjoy it together.
Now, Danielle, stop sniping
and start thinking of an alibi
For your brother.
- I know. We could say he joined a cult,
And we had to kidnap and deprogram him.
- Well, that would certainly
Spare the family
some embarrassment.
Why not throw in
a killing spree, too?
Well, here's a thought--
We say he was at drama camp.
It reflects Andrew's interest
in the performing arts,
while giving us
a private joke to savor
about the drama
of his estrangement.
Uh, yeah,
he is always like that.
Uh, guys, why can't
we just tell the truth?
Uh, I got out of line,
you kicked me out,
I lived on the street,
and I came back home.
We'll need a name
for this drama camp.
We got ties here, people!
Designer ties,
two for a dollar!
Ooh, do you like
those barbells?
Make me an offer.
- I'm feeling generous.
Here's the customer
I've been waiting for.
(man)
I'll give you $5 for this.
Carlos, I see you got my flier.
- You're having a garage sale
featuring menswear
and sporting equipment.
I need cash,
and you don't expect me
to sell my stuff, do you?
Those are
my good cuff links!
Those are my CDs!
Oh, my God,
This is my baby blanket.
My mamá knitted this!
And it pains me to sell it.
It's just that
my lawyer told me
What you're offering
for spousal support,
And I can't get by on that.
Hey, I am doing
the best that I can.
I've got a few deals
in the pipeline,
But I'm not making
near as much as I used to.
- So I should be punished?
Attention, shoppers,
for the next 20 minutes,
free golf club
with every purchase!
Gaby,
I'm trying to be civil,
But if you don't
knock it off right now,
I swear,
the gloves are coming off.
Oh, honey, the gloves
aren't just off...
They're 70% off!
Get your cashmere gloves!
Hey, Parker,
where's your uniform?
You got your game
in an hour.
No, I don't. I quit.
What?
I hate baseball.
Daddy said I don't have
to play it anymore.
Well, Daddy should have
checked with mommy,
So she could have a chance
to tell him why he's wrong.
Hey, you're playing.
- But, Mom, I suck!
Everybody says so.
That's why they made up
a fake position for me.
- It is not fake.
There is not a team I know
that could get along
Without their backup
far right fielder.
Okay, come on,
Let's go practice.
All right,
let's try it again.
Nice and easy.
Watch the ball hit the bat.
You ready? You can do it.
Here we go.
Okay, Parker,
I keep telling you,
You gotta keep your eyes open.
How are you gonna hit the ball
when you're doing this?
You threw it too fast.
Throw slower.
If I threw any slower,
we would be bowling.
Hey.
Hey, whatcha guys doing?
I'll tell you what
we're not doing--quitting.
Oh, hey, buddy,
did you change your mind?
No.
Lynette, I told him that
he didn't have to play anymore.
He's got five more games
in the season.
He made a commitment.
he's gonna see it through.
- But, Lynette, he doesn't like it,
And if you haven't noticed,
he kind of sucks.
- Yeah, well, that's not the point.
What kind of message are
we sending if we let him quit
whenever the going gets rough?
- Honey, it is kids' baseball.
It's a way to kill three hours
before they eat pizza.
Why you being
such a hard-ass?
- Well, it's called parenting,
Tom. Watch and learn.
Okay, P-dog,
This is a curveball.
Again, opening the eyes--
can't stress it enough.
Are you sure it's okay
if we stay another day?
Well, let's see. What excuse did we use
when we had this conversation yesterday?
That we work hard,
And we deserve to relax.
No, I believe that was
last Thursday's rationale.
Uh, fresh air
is good for us?
- Ah, Tuesday.
Okay, here's one--
Julie needs to spend more time
bonding with her father.
Brilliant!
(laughs)
If we keep this up,
We could stay here
till Christmas. (laughs)
You know, some--sometimes
when you smile like that,
That--that--that really
makes me think that--that...
What?
What were you gonna say?
Well, it makes me think
that I could love you.
I... Don't mean "love"
In the swooning schoolboy
sense--
You know,
fireworks exploding,
Bells ringing.
(chuckles)
To me, it's--it's about this--
A mundane task that--
that's suddenly a joy
because of who
you're doing it with.
That's love to me--
someone to fluff
while you fold,
someone to whisper to
at a boring party,
someone to--to--
Shh. Do you mind?
You're kind of drowning out
the bells.
So I am.
I think
I can feed myself now.
Mm, you said that yesterday,
And I wound up with
a cleavage full of pudding.
You heard the therapist.
It's gonna be weeks
before you're up and running.
I just wanna get home,
unpack.
You just let home
come to you, okay?
The whole street's
dying to see you.
(southern accent) Bree is
even bakin' ya a peach pie.
She's the redhead, right?
(normal voice) right.
Husband's a doctor...
Rex.
Rex is dead.
Really?
When did that happen?
About
a year and a half ago.
What?
Yeah.
You were at his funeral.
What are you talking about?
That's not possible.
I just met him
right before my accident.
Mike...
What year is it?
2004. Why?
It's called
retrograde memory loss.
It's caused by the swelling
and frontal lobe damage.
You say
he's lost two whole years?
Yeah. Is that unusual?
Ah, patients more typically
lose several weeks.
The damage may be more severe
than we thought.
Well, do you think
he'll get his memory back?
He might,
At least partially.
You could be of
some assistance with that.
How?
Bring him
some personal belongings,
Photos, letters.
He's gonna need some help
to remember what he can't.
Oh, I'm sure
I could fill in a few blanks.
Hey, did I tell you
that, uh,
Burnham fox is looking
for a new creative director?
PR? What makes you think
I wanna work for a PR firm?
Easy hours, big paycheck,
access to great parties...
Yeah, what was I thinking?
Honey, we agreed that
I would chase my dreams,
And that ain't it.
Look, I was just
making conversation.
Batter up!
- (boy) Is he up?
- (boy) Oh, come on!
(Lynette) Come on, Parker!
Keep your eye on the ball!
Strike one!
Hey, people,
he's just a kid, okay?
Come on.
Strike two!
Hey, hey,
That is not helpful.
It only takes one, Parker!
Only takes one!
- (boy) come on, Parker!
It's not your son's fault.
He's just up against
the best pitcher in the league.
Yeah, guy's a machine.
Who is that kid?
Nicky Abbott.
He's a neighbor of mine.
The kid's got an arm
like a 13 year old.
(umpire)
Strike three! You're out!
I'm gonna
go buy him an ice cream.
It's okay, P-dog.
You're gonna get 'em
the next inning!
So tell me,
what else do you know
about this Nicky kid?
You're short 50 cents.
Please, that's all I got.
Hey, give the kid
what he wants.
Thanks.
Hey, aren't you, uh,
Parker Scavo's mom?
That's right.
Come. Walk with me.
So...
Money's a little tight,
huh?
A little.
Yeah, I heard
your old man's out of work.
That's gotta be tough.
Yeah, they, uh,
cut my allowance.
No! A kid's gotta have
an allowance.
How else you gonna buy
the things you want, right?
Like that cotton candy.
That's a little piece
of heaven, huh?
(chuckles)
Hey, I got an idea. Maybe we
could help each other out.
My son's having a little trouble
hitting the ball.
Yeah, I saw that.
Yeah.
Ever seen one of these?
Carlos,
What are you doing here?
I mean, besides lowering
my property value.
I had a little news,
And I wanted to see your face
when I delivered it.
- Oh.
I'm tired of fighting,
so I called my lawyer
and told him
to give in to your demands
for spousal support.
Really?
Wow. Well, thank you.
Okay, you've seen my face.
Now you can beat it.
Wait. There's more.
Since I'm gonna be giving you
all that money,
I have to cut back
on some stuff,
like the rent
on my apartment.
But the good news is,
according to my lawyer,
I'm completely
within my rights to do this...
Honey, I'm home.
Wait! You can't stay here!
Now there's the face
that I was looking for.
(umpire) Batter up!
Strike one!
Wow, that was
kind of slow.
His arm
must be getting tired.
Yeah, well,
After all those fastballs...
Come on, Parker!
You can do it!
Strike two!
(gasps) Oh, my God! Yes!
Mr. Faladi.
Yes?
- I cannot thank you enough
for getting Danielle
interested in history.
She has never worked so hard
on a project before.
(chuckles)
Well, don't tell anyone,
but she is
my favorite student.
Oh, and it's so good to see
that Andrew's back.
Where's he been
all this time?
Drama camp--
a very prestigious
drama camp.
Do I know you?
Yeah, uh, you gave me a ride
in your black sedan once.
You know, the one
with the reclining seats?
Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Wasn't that Dr. Keck?
- You know him?
Yeah. Yeah, we, uh...
(chuckles)
Met at drama camp.
Oh, good lord.
You mean...
- Yeah.
I, uh--
"performed" for him once.
Are you all right?
- I'll be all right. I'm fine.
Howard Keck?
You sure?
I mean, he's a very respected
member of the community.
Yeah, well, they all were.
What were you and Andrew
talking about today at the fair?
Uh, nothing.
I was gonna make some cocoa.
Would you like some?
Orson, I saw
the two of you whispering
right after Dr. Keck ran off.
What happened?
Look, Andrew asked me
not to say anything,
But I don't want there to be
any secrets between us,
So please don't
let him know I told you.
Well, of course not.
What is it?
How to put this? Uh...
When Andrew
was on the street,
he, uh, he didn't just
beg for money.
At times, he...
Well, he did things
to earn it.
Oh, good.
I mean, I'd hate to think
he had no work ethic at all.
Uh, what I mean is...
men hired him, uh, to...
uh, do things--
things he wasn't very proud of.
Yard work?
Afraid not.
Orson, you're scaring me.
Did he do something awful?
No! No. Not awful.
I mean,
people do it all the time.
I do it with you.
I just don't pay you for it.
I think someone
could use a cocoa.
Look,
We mustn't judge Andrew.
He was desperate.
I'll never forgive myself.
It's all my fault
for pushing him away.
- Bree, don't do that toourself.
The important thing now is
that he's home and he's safe.
How does this Dr. Keck
fit into all of this?
I mean, is he treating Andrew
for some awful disease?
Actually, I think
he was one of Andrew's...
Clients.
Howard Keck?!
Oh, that's ridiculous.
He's got a wife and a daughter.
He plays on Tom Scavo's bowling team.
- Well, that's clearly not
the only team he plays for.
This is a nightmare,
an absolute nightmare.
Please don't cut into that pie.
I made it for Mike.
Mike? Delfino?
Yes. I left you
two messages.
Didn't you check
your voice mail?
He woke up
from his coma. (sighs)
Who is it ? It is Sharla Banning?
I'm not telling who it is.
I'm just asking the question.
If you know a husband
has been unfaithful,
do you tell the wife?
- Absolutely.
If he's cheating, he could bring home a disease.
- Okay, that's what I was thinking.
I mean, that's how
Bunny Connors got chlamydia.
- (gasps) She told me
she got it from wearing someone else's bathing suit.
- No, that's how she got crabs.
Poor bunny.
It's always something.
If it's not the clap,
It's a botched face-lift.
(laughs)
Be that as it may,
Do we all agree that I should tell this man's wife?
- I wouldn't.
Women always say they wanna know
if their husband's cheating,
and they always resent
the person who tells them.
So if Tom was cheating, you wouldn't tell me?
- No!
But I would hire someone
to beat the crap out of him.
Aw, you're sweet.
(chuckles)
Bree, I'm sorry.
I think you gotta follow your heart on this one,
even if it isn't the easiest thing to do.
Gaby...
Are you and Carlos
getting back together?
Why?
Uh... Would you excuse me?
What are you doing? I told you
I was having friends over!
I'm thirsty!
And this is my kitchen, too.
Hey, ladies!
Oh, for God sakes, put some pants on!
- Well, I wanted to,
But somebody threw my laundry
out of the dryer
While it was still wet.
- Don't act like you didn't deserve that.
What are you talking about?
You peed in my shampoo.
Admit it!
What?!
Yeah, the cap was loose,
And I know how your sick mind works.
- Oh, really?
Well, in that case,
You should know that
If I was gonna
do something like that,
I wouldn't do it
to your shampoo.
I would do it to your mouthwash,
soup and decaffeinated coffee.
Ladies.
To answer your question--
No, we are not
getting back together.
I love this music.
What's it about?
Making love, regret,
cigarettes.
Cigarettes?
That's what I assume.
It's French.
They write what they know.
(chuckles) I'd love
to go to France someday.
Would you like
to go next month?
(laughs) are you serious?
Yeah, I'm going on business.
Come with me.
Oh, Ian,
I just took a week off.
I couldn't possibly justify
taking another.
Oh, you'll manage.
We've already proven ourselves
masters of the flimsy rationalization.
Well... Okay.
You gotta promise me
we'll actually leave the hotel room.
It's Paris, dear. You can
pretty much make love anywhere.
Mmm.
(groans)
I thought you said you didn't
get reception up here.
We, the occasional signal
gets through.
Please don't answer.
Oh, it's Julie.
I have to.
Hello? What's up?
Hey.
(loudly) Uh, I can't--
No, can you say that again?
The signal's really bad.
What?
Oh, my God.
Is something wrong?
Mike woke up.
Um, Julie, when--when did he...
Julie? Julie!
(cell phone beeps)
Oh, damn it!
Oh, my God.
Oh! Oh, my God!
Um...
Uh, I-I... I have to go.
Um, I gotta
get out of here.
Yes, of course.
Uh, I-I think that
you're sitting on my bra.
What'd the coach say?
What do you think he said?
Parker's off the team.
That's not fair!
It's not his fault!
It doesn't matter,
Because his mother bribed
an 8-year-old pitcher,
Who also, by the way,
Was kicked off of his team.
Not Nicky, too!
What were you thinking?
I was trying to repair
my son's shattered self-esteem.
With a $50?
Yeah.
Honey, everything
would've been fine
If you had
just let Parker quit.
Well, excuse me for not wanting
my son to be a quitter.
Yeah, 'cause I guess
having two in the family
would be a bit much.
Whoa.
Where'd that come from?
You say that
you support my decision
to leave advertising
and follow my dream,
but it is obvious to me
that you resent it.
- That is not true!
Why do you keep dropping
all these hints about the job
at Burnham Fox then, huh?
- I just figured, since you're taking your time
figuring out
what your dream even is,
you might wanna make
a few bucks in the meantime.
I have a dream, too.
It includes keeping this house.
Oh, like I don't--
Are you fighting?
- No!
No.
It was excitement,
because we have just decided
you don't have
to play baseball anymore.
Ha! Isn't that great?
But I can't stop now.
Huh?
- Not when I'm finally
getting good.
You were right, Mom. I just
needed a little more practice.
So come on, come on!
Let's go practice!
See you outside.
So what's on the next page
of your parenting handbook?
Ian, can you please hurry?
I am hurrying!
- We should've been
on the road ten minutes ago.
It's not like
checking out of a hotel.
There's doors to secure.
I have to turn the gas valve off.
- Can't you do that stuff later?
When? After the place
is overrun by raccoons?
Of course, the joke would be
on them when it blows up.
Mike is awake! He's lying there
and he's wondering where I am.
Yes, I get it.
You're in a hurry.
Just please
give me a minute.
I bet you'd move faster
If Jane were awake.
Ah, here's the picture
that you took of me
In my bikini
at that pool party.
You could've warned me
I was showing a little nip.
Oh, Susan Mayer.
Remember her?
Yeah.
She's pretty.
Yeah, she is, sorta,
In this picture.
Is there a date
on this thing?
The nurses said that
she visited me a lot.
We were close, huh?
You have just
come out of a coma.
Can we not talk about Susan
till you start to regain your strength?
Why?
Oh, God.
I hate to be the one
telling you this...
Well,
If you don't want to--
That tramp
treated you like dirt.
She strung you along.
She slept with other guys.
You broke up
with her twice.
Well, why did she keep visiting
me when I was out of it?
Well,
She's a bit of a stalker.
I was worried that
she was gonna come in here
and disconnect one of the tubes or something.
But don't worry.
She's glommed on
to some new guy,
And she's up in the mountains
at his place with him right now.
Wow.
She told the nurses
that she really loved me.
That's the one thing
about Susan
that you must never forget--
She is a liar.
You waiting to see
Mike Delfino?
Uh, yes.
I'm a... I'm a neighbor.
But, uh, he already has a visitor,
so I'll come back later.
Well, don't be surprised
if he doesn't recognize you.
He's suffered
significant memory loss.
Really?
Oh, that's too bad.
You sure you don't want
to go in?
Ms. Britt's here all the time.
She won't mind.
No. I've waited this long.
I can wait a bit longer.
Gaby!
Hey, Carlos. What's up?
My key won't work.
That's probably because
I had the locks changed.
Gaby!
- Can't be too safe.
You never know when someone
might move in on you
when you're not looking.
Hello, 9-1-1?
There's an intruder
breaking into my home.
Can you tell them
to come armed?
(whispers)
I think he's Mexican.
I'm telling you,
I'm her husband.
I bought her this house.
My name is on the deed
Ma'am, if you're married,
It's a matter of public record.
I can find out very quickly.
All right, but we're going
through a very messy divorce,
And he moved back in on me.
And everyone knows
the wife keeps the house,
And the husband gets
the crappy apartment.
It's the American way.
Call my lawyer. This is all
totally legal, and s knows it.
She's just trying
to get back at me.
I hear that.
You wouldn't believe the stuff
my wife pulled when we split.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
you can't take sides!
Police officers
aren't allowed to take sides.
I pay your salary.
Ted, did you see that?
This lady just assaulted me.
Oh. (scoffs)
It was a swat.
Ted, does this hurt?
Get your hands off me!
Police brutality!
This is all my fault.
Why punish Parker?
Sorry, Mr.. Scavo.
Rules are rules.
I can't put him back on the team.
- Just one more game.
He'll suck,
the other kids will taunt him,
and he'll wanna quit again.
- See, everybody wins.
I wish I could help, but...
Please? You can't
bend the rules just once?
Did you know the team could use
some new batting helmets?
Are you asking for a bribe?
You pretending
you're above that?
I'll get my checkbook.
Hello, Vera.
I made you some of those, uh,
Shortbread biscuits that you like so much.
How sweet!
Can you stay for some tea?
It's been so long.
We have some
catching up to do.
Yes. Yes, we do.
I know how painful
this must be for you.
It isn't easy
for me either,
Considering
Andrew's role in it.
And why have you
told me this?
Because I thought
you'd want to know.
Why?
So you could do something.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
That I know nothing about
the man I've lived with for 27 years?
I've always assumed
Howard had some... outlet,
A friend
tucked away somewhere.
I didn't know.
I didn't care to know.
But thank you
for painting so vivid,
So indelible a picture
of my husband's activities.
I'm sorry.
I just felt that
if it were me, I--
You'd want to know.
Yes, absolutely.
Then I owe you an apology,
Because I've been
sitting on a little secret
about your family.
Oh?
Actually, it's not much
of a secret.
My daughter tells me
it's common knowledge
among the cheerleaders.
- What is?
The fact that Danielle is sleeping
with her history teacher.
But where are my manners?
I should have brought
some biscuits with that.
Well, aren't we just
the parents of the year?
Sitting in the stands,
Waiting for our son to fail
So we can weasel out
of a bribery scandal.
Two bribery scandals.
Gotta count the batting helmets.
Strike one!
You know, for what it's worth,
I don't think you're a quitter.
Good.
And you don't resent me?
No.
(umpire) Ball one!
Okay, well, maybe a little.
Why?
You get to chase your dream
while I get to spend the rest
of my life in advertising.
Strike two!
Maybe I'd like
to write a book
Or, you know,
start my own magazine.
And then I think,
"No, I can't.
I have a family to support,"
And I am okay with that...
(umpire) Ball two!
- ... most of the time.
You know what?
I'm gonna look
into that job at Burnham Fox.
Don't you dare!
You are gonna
chase your dream,
And I am gonna support you
99% of the time.
It's all I could
really ask for.
How the hell
did he do that?!
(boy)
Yeah! Come on, come on!
Crap, they're cheering
for him.
Oh, he's never gonna
quit now!
What are we gonna
say to him?
(boy) Go, go, go, go!
Ow! Ow!
I don't know, buddy.
Looks like
a pretty bad sprain.
Probably gonna be out
the rest of the season.
Damn.
Hey, but you know what?
That was one heck of a hit.
Sure was.
I posted your bail.
We can go.
(sighs) Gaby--
don't talk to me.
Oh, lighten up.
You were in there
for maybe an hour.
The whole thing is funny,
And you know it.
Come on, Gaby!
We've been going at each other
for months now.
Can we just stop?
You know
as well as I do
we're gonna
end up back together.
Wow, you are crazy.
No, what's crazy is throwing
away the past three years.
I mean,
Why can't we just say
What we really feel
for a change?
Fine, I'll get the ball rolling.
I still love you.
That's too bad,
because I don't love you.
(laughs) yeah, right.
I don't...
And I haven't
for a very long time.
That's a lie. You're just
saying that to hurt me.
No, if I wanted  hurt you,
I would tell you
about last weekend...
When I slept
with John Rowland.
(Gabrielle)
Carlos, what are you doing?
Carlos!
What are you doing?! Carlos!
You can't leave me out here
in the middle of nowhere!
Ah
Carlos!
(Bree) Danielle! Danielle,
he is your history teacher,
and he is 35 years old!
Robert says age is just a number.
- Don't you dare leave this house!
You can't break us up!
I love him, and he loves me!
Come on, Mom.
I am so tired of feeling like
the worst mother who ever lived.
You're not.
There's Grandma.
I just--I've tried so hard
to set a good example.
I've done the best I could
to teach you kids
right from wrong.
Why isn't it taking?
It took.
I mean, we know the difference
between right and wrong.
We just chose "wrong."
Why?
Sometimes when you push a kid
really hard to go one way,
the other way starts to look
more entertaining.
You're awful.
Yeah, I know.
I blame shoddy parenting.
You know, we never discussed
What it was like for you
while you were... away.
I just want you to know,
if you ever wanna
talk about it,
there's nothing
you can't tell me.
Um... thanks.
Not right now. Okay?
I'll pick up my bags later.
It's not my fault
you weren't there.
What?
- It's not. I know what you're feeling, but--
How could you possibly know
what I was feeling?
For six months,
I have prayed every day
For that man to wake up,
And you made me give up on him.
I did not make you.
- Okay, not on purpose,
but you did.
You were sweet
and charming and English,
And that's why
when my prayers were answered,
I was a hundred miles away,
naked in someone else's arms.
This should never
have happened.
You can say
what you want about this,
say that you feel guilty,
say that it was bad timing,
but--but don't you say that
this should never have happened!
Because you're the--
you're the best thing
that's happened to me in years.
Ian, I'm--I'm sorry.
I know how you feel.
It's Mike.
It's my Mike.
Well, then--
Then you should go.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
You are awake.
Hi, Susan.
Oh, God!
It's so wonderful
to hear your voice again.
They say
you've been here a lot.
Yes! Yes, I have.
Almost every day.
I can't tell you
how much I'm kicking myself
for not being here
when you woke up.
Where were you?
I was in the country.
But I'm back now.
(chuckles)
Okay.
Is something wrong?
You... You don't
seem happy to see me.
To be honest,
I don't remember you.
What?
I remember moving to Fairview
and meeting people,
But after that, nothing.
The doctors say
it's the head trauma.
Oh.
But you're gonna be all right.
(chuckles)
And I'm gonna
help you remember.
And if you don't mind,
I'm kind of tired now.
Oh. Okay. (laughs)
Right, you--
you, um, you sleep.
I'll come back tomorrow.
I'd rather you didn't.
Well, I've got therapy.
Maybe next week.
Okay.
We all have our reasons
for rewriting history.
Sometimes we need
to provide ourselves alibis...
Drama camp was awesome.
Uh, we're talking
zero supervision.
Sometimes we wanna hurt someone
who has hurt us...
So you can tell Carlos that
he can have the photo albums.
She says that they hold
no sentimental value for her.
and then there are times
we just wanna spare
ourselves embarrassment...
I don't know how
these rumors get started.
No, Parker only quit the team
'cause he hurt his ankle.
Of course,
there are some who feel
that to rewrite history
is just
another way to lie...
And poor Howard
has to work late again tonight.
Of course,
He does it all for the family.
but what is history anyway...
You say I dated Susan
for a long time.
Do you think
I was in love with her?
but a set of lies
agreed upon?
I don't. I really...
Really don't.