Barney is just a look.
Three blonde drinking drinks
of bad decisions to 8:00.
Nice catch, radar.
This is my wife.
No, I will dispense.
Really? But blondes are
and are drunk.
Not your type?
Maybe I do not
has a type, Lily.
Wow, you think the mind
men are simple is that?
We have a
preferred type?
Credo ...
Asian, with booby.
I go to the bathroom and I have.
Barney has noted how
acted weird lately?
I noticed it.
Remember as Barney always says
not buying flowers for women
why make things
remember the babies?
- Yeah.
- Well, these days
I saw the flowers
buying roses.
- What?
- Now that touched on the subject,
Barney was the one thing
strange at work yesterday.
Okay, until Saturday.
I'm planning a brunch, go to
market and to an escalation.
I love you too.
Bye.
I thought he was
just chatting
with some girl who
were trying to take.
Or with Ted, maybe.
But now, you will know.
Does Barney Stinson
has a girlfriend?
- That I will.
- Wait Barney.
- Where are you going?
- The anywhere.
To the beach. It is winter.
Play laser sight. Home.
Shut up, you
is going somewhere.
My God, he will
meet with her.
To where Barney is going?
We are not
More in Manhattan.
Where this girl lives?
We are talking about a girl who
managed to tie Barney Stinson.
Must be in Narnia.
He is stopping.
- What are you doing here?
- Where is she?
- Who?
- Your girlfriend.
Hello!
You do not have a
same type, huh?
These are my friends.
Ted, Marshall, Lily and Robin.
People, this is Laurette.
My mother.
It is a pleasure to meet them.
I feel like now
you all know.
Barney talks about you all
the days that talk.
You connect all
days for his mother?
No, mother!
So this is your
big secret?
Not that I know
which is the little boy's mom?
Yeah, I got.
I think I can go.
- Hello!
- Oi.
Barney, who are
these people?
Ted, Marshall, Lily and Robin.
I would submit them
Betty, my wife.
And my son, Tyler.
- - = How I Met Your Mother - = - --
- - = S04E15 - The Stinsons = - --
Translation
koe and Joker
This reminds me that you can not
steak, after which the doctor said
on cholesterol.
This woman wants
I live forever.
Guilty!
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- I love you more!
- Get out, pestinha!
- So, I see you at the bar?
- Barney, what the hell is that?
All right, is a
long history.
As I know,
my father had to
leave my mother
when I was a child
for presenter
of "The Price is Right!"
- Oh, yeah!
- Absolutely.
He is your father!
She had to create my
brother and me alone.
And the only dream she had,
was that their children
ended not alone
as she was.
So seven years ago,
she was very sick.
It seemed not
could escape.
Therefore decided
realize the dream of her.
Mom, this is Betty.
We are engaged.
I hired an actress to
interpret my girlfriend Betty.
The real name
it is Margaret.
It shows in the theater of
Broadway one time or another.
Wonderful actress. Was
so to win a Tony.
But as you know, there is much bureaucracy,
then will not go into it.
But has a problem.
Betty has a small
tendency to flee from the roadmap.
See, Mom? I found
someone who makes me happy.
- Just like you wanted.
- This is wonderful.
I live just one more
just to take my grandchildren.
I'm pregnant!
Then my mother improved.
It was a miracle,
but meant that
I have to keep
Betty around,
and a child to climb
interpret my son, Tyler.
This is crazy.
Did you even test
to choose your child?
For a while I was the nanny
the children of my neighbors.
In one Christmas when my mother
was drunk with Eggnog,
I cheated with a bag of
flowers and a mask of Chuck.
But there came a day that I had
to do tests on cast.
4, 8, and 13 can stay.
The rest is not required.
He said that if I sleep with you,
my son would take the role.
It seems that I am better
actor than his son.
Bring them to 11hs.
So that the role
Tyler went to the Grant.
What is the Grant me
looks good actor.
Really?
Look at this.
Hey Tyler! Tyler!
Tyler!
- Grant.
- You?
See? It is an amateur sitting there.
You can call me crazy,
but the actors were children
much better in the 80s.
Barney, it seems that their
Mom kept the room
of his childhood in the same
the way they left.
Yes, and by the way,
beautiful poster of Karate Kid.
Karate Kid is a great movie.
It is the story of a young man
the karate wonder, whose dream
led him across the road
to Karate Championship.
Of course, unfortunately, it loses
in the final round for that nerd.
But he learns the beautiful
lesson to accept defeat.
Wait, when you
watch Karate Kid,
fan for that
blonde boring?
No, I hope for that
loser of New Jersey
you hardly know what karate.
When I watch Karate Kid I
hope for the real karate kid.
Johnny Lawrence.
Connects, Lily.
I just find
where you know.
I saw you showing
Misdirection in the theater,
last fall.
You were a revelation.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
Thank you, not
was sure.
The objective of Braxford,
is alienating the public, of course.
Sorry, here is a fan of him.
You know even the
theater that attends.
The Miss. Theater grabbed my
heart and never released.
Every year I put up a piece
for parents with other children.
Wow, Santa, think
we can leave this snow?
Cut, cut and cut!
Ricky, Grandma and Grandpa
come here in half an hour
and is still using
my words.
Looks like I will have to
manage and operate this thing.
Give me the hat and go sit down.
I always wanted to be
actor, secretly.
One of those dreams that
flee from the hands, I think.
If you like, you can give
some tips of performance.
- Really?
- I love.
Okay.
Rule of Practice 1.
Do not be afraid of ...
At least someone is
encouraged to act.
I miss it.
So you do not like
interpret the son of Barney?
I hate. But the
What can I do?
- I find another role.
- I know what you mean.
I am a news presenter.
But I had to
accept a job
the presenter of
a morning program
which goes to air at 4:30 in the morning.
I should be very well
applicable to that time, you know?
I am almost 30 years.
Ah, speaking seriously. You
is still very beautiful.
I love the plastic
that made the nose.
Never did the plastic nose.
Yeah, me neither.
I do not believe that not
before we know it.
I wish that Barney
had a mother so sweet.
Thank you, honey.
The truth is I never went
the best mother when he was young.
Do not say that I have
sure was great.
No, I was half bitch.
- Excuse me?
- Bitch, baby.
A dirty whore.
I am not proud of it.
Although I had my fun.
There is no greater pleasure than looking
in the eyes of a man thinking
"I do not know your name,
or you know my, "
but in the next 8 minutes
we will put you break.
Then go
in opposite directions.
Continue driving.
Mother of Barney?
Laurette?
Anyway, this is everything
in the past now.
I did the best I could,
but sometimes I wonder
Barney is as
came out so perfect.
You must tell the truth
to your mother, understand?
She is a sweet woman,
sweet, caring,
way too detailed,
you deserve something better.
No, no way.
The fact kill her.
I do not think lying to a
a lady so loving.
She reminds me
my own mother.
Okay ...
- What?
- Baby?
Remember our votes when I
said that we would be forever?
On the way back, she said,
not forever, baby.
The Marshall goes to heaven.
- She was making a joke.
- She hates me, Marshall.
But okay, because ...
Whatever.
What? What say?
Nothing, do what you want
in the room of Barney's New?
- In my carpet?
- The feeling is great, man.
Hey Lily, is now
learned something,
is that sincerity is important
when it comes to family.
Whatever it is you
feel for my mother,
are together for 12 years,
I think I can handle.
- Really?
- Sure.
Okay. I hate his mother.
Guess what?
I hate you!
Two minutes for the cookies
get ready meat!
Meat cake?
Tyler does not like!
Grant, we talked about
that millions of times.
You can not
have a stick.
But it is funny.
Grant, not afraid
to climb another actor.
Go decorate their speeches
to the scene of the dinner.
Wait. You wrote
we have dinner?
Just a short script.
Things will
my mother happy.
For example?
And I really thought
Barney had forgotten that
our anniversary.
So I went to the backyard
spitting fire ...
Huge flames, when she
is angry, which I love.
See them there.
Look them up!
You can stop, good guy.
Sure. Sorry.
Continue.
What is really
a good relationship.
So I left
to the yard ...
and had candles around corner.
And a string quartet.
- Believe that?
- Not a bit.
And my little Ty-ty,
you have done?
Funny story.
Another night, that silly
had a nightmare.
And when he was telling us about
which was, remember what I said?
Page four.
Bones of dinosaur won
life and came chasing me?
Thanks, man, I do not
needed to sleep today.
No. Tyler said:
"My nightmare was
you and Mom did not
knew how much I loved those.
So I came here to say
it was this big. "
- How cute!
- How happy family and baby.
I'll get ice cream
downstairs in the fridge
and comeremos sundae
in the kitchen.
Wow,
no error in that scene.
- Bravo!
- No fills, Barney.
You do not know how
hard work for you.
Grant, I love your story
on the bones of dinosaur.
Can you stop
to talk about it?
- Go eat your sundae.
- I can not.
I am intolerant to lactose.
Guess who is not?
Tyler!
Tyler is in there
and enjoy each bite.
- Time of the ice cream!
- Yummy!
My God!
- Ted!
- Tyler does not like.
You will not
have a stick.
- I understand.
I follow.
I. ..
I was betrayed by
my best friend.
How could you do that, Ted?
Think of the poor
of Tyler ...
trying bravely
hold the tears.
All right, son.
You can cry.
Weep.
I do not want Mom
and Dad divorced.
What has to say
in his defense?
1 rule of action.
Do not be afraid
to improvise.
It was I who betrayed you ...
and you betrayed me?
How?
Rule of action 5.
Make a good story
for your character.
14 November 1998.
The night train
to Monte Carlo.
I was in the car,
taking a few thousand
of the Algerian dinar.
When you seduced
my bride,
who is blind and found
you were me.
Good!
What are you talking about?
Rule of action
number eight:
Do not be afraid
to be aggressive.
You know very well
what I'm talking about.
No, I do not know.
You know, yes!
And, by God,
hear you say:
Mom, can you excuse us?
Sure.
Have chocolate
and butterscotch.
Has several types of
sprinkler and marshmallows.
You lost your mind?
You were great!
Almost become
in character.
Not trying
interpret the Ted,
but leaving
the way of it.
What with?
As I will explain
this to my mother?
Perhaps it is time to count
the truth, Barney.
I do not know, no.
Sometimes, honesty
leads people
to say bad things
about a woman who
always cared about me.
Because I was
the dwarf family.
For the love of God,
I only have 1.93.
- I said well you?
- He very well.
See? Even in a
job you hate,
you still like
of what it does.
Maybe so for you
in his new job.
- You think?
- I'm sure.
Thanks, Grant.
You are very intelligent,
you know?
Sorry, sorry.
I thought I was rolling a climate.
- Honey, you okay?
- Look, Mom ...
must tell you something.
Something I should have
counted for a long time.
Tyler is dying.
And Betty said that
when it is,
it will depart.
And that everything must
happen soon.
- My God!
- Okay, no, no.
None of this is true.
The truth is ...
The truth is that
Tyler and Betty are actors,
I hired to
pretend to be my family.
What?
I thought that I
had the life you want.
I wanted it
proud of me.
I know that sounds crazy,
and sorry for everything.
- So, Betty is not your wife?
- No.
Thank God!
I do not like that woman.
- Really?
- Yes
And Tyler ...
I know that his grandmother
and should love him,
but hate that kid.
"Tyler does not like."
- What is this drug?
- Not?
And those false friends
give me will die.
I know!
They are not horrible?
So, seriously,
is not mad?
No, I'm just confused.
Why think
you should do that?
Barney, I love him with
or no perfect family.
I love you, no matter
what happens.
- Really?
- Really.
I am so relieved!
Because the truth is that I am
as far away from marriage
possible. My history with
women to leave shocked.
No matter.
Still love him.
Seriously, can not imagine
things I did.
When you had three years,
I left with the babysitter
I spent 3 weeks with
round like a ball.
Mom!
Just do me a favor.
If you know
someone special,
not go as I did.
Take a chance.
Barney, the taxi arrived.
I will try.
And so ended one of the evenings
more alien to our lives.
I just wanted to say that
if some day seem cold
or hostile,
sorry.
- Who is she talking about?
- With my mother.
Mean much to me
if we could be closer.
Take a deep breath, as if that
will say now is difficult.
- I love you.
- I love you ...
- Mother
- Yes!
Mother
- Pretend that told me something.
I mean, its really cool
Party say that, Judy.
You, too.
Bye.
Let me get this straight.
You are telling me
when you see "Karate Kid",
- No fan for Daniel Son?
- No.
For those twists
in "Hard to Kill"?
Hans Gruber.
International charming bandit.
In the end, it is hard to kill.
It is the character of the title.
Sure.
"Club of the five"?
The teacher who
takes care of the arrest.
He is the one guy
USA movie that suit.
I know.
"Terminator of the Future"?
What is the name
the film, Robin?
Who among us has
not shed a tear
when the red olhinho it
he did not kill people?
Sorry, this movie ...
Never watch
movie with you.
Not trying to help him.