NARRATOR: Kids, as you know,
Lily and Marshall had decided
to move to Rome after
Barney and Robin's wedding.
We're going to Italy.
Si.
But without telling Lily,
Marshall had then accepted
a judgeship in New York.
Good luck with that...
Your Honor.
Until his always-helpful
road trip companion
Daphne had selflessly (phone ringing)
come to his aid.
You texted Lily
that I took the job?
You're welcome.
You were torturing yourself
figuring out how to tell her,
I just broke the ice for you.
I was standing on that ice.
Now I'm gonna be bobbing,
facedown on a frigid creek.
I do not need to know the nasty
way you apologize to your wife.
And frigid? Maybe you're
just doing it wrong.
Hi, baby.
I can't believe you did this
behind my back.
I know, I should
have talked to you.
Thanks to you, we are stuck
all weekend in the room
with a ghost in it.
Room with a...?
We got 13?
The room that's haunted by
the ghost of Captain Dearduff?
Who got the who
with the what now?
Original Air Date on October 28, 2013
NARRATOR: Marshall had
recently discovered
that the Farhampton Inn
was featured
in an episode of The Ghost
Network's original series,
True & Real Ghost Stories
of the Supernatural.
Ooh, there, see?
The Farhampton Inn.
I told you it sounded familiar.
TV NARRATOR:
In 1843,
the streets of Farhampton,
Long Island
were stalked
by a vicious killer
named Captain Blazeby Dearduff.
Dubbed "Dearduff the Hooker,"
he murdered dozens
of unwary travelers
with his sharpened hook.
Ironically that hook
would prove Dearduff's
own undoing
(laughing maniacally)
one wintry night in room 13
of the Farhampton Inn.
(fly buzzing)
(grunting)
(yells)
Uh-oh.
He was found the next morning,
frozen to death.
MAN: Boom!
Some say you can still hear
Captain Dearduff's cries coming
from room 13.
Cold.
So cold.
Help me... help me...
MAN:
We can see you, Ron.
Some say you can still hear
the thump of his peg
and the scrape of his hook.
Others say
Dearduff the Hooker was just
a popular male prostitute
who murdered no one
and died of syphilis in 1848.
Let's hear
from some people who have
actually survived
a night in room 13.
(thunder crashing)
Did I see a ghost?
Of course...
WOMAN: Yes.
There's...
Are.
...such thing as ghosts.
(Dearduff laughing maniacally)
So, have you seen the ghost?
Not yet, but that might just be
because ghosts
don't exist, Marshall!
So explain the night shirt
we saw flying around our cabin
in the Poconos.
An owl got stuck in it.
We saw it fly out the neck hole.
Yeah, the ghost of an owl
that died in that cabin.
Plus it's a crappy room,
but when I tried to complain...
The thermostat in
my room is broken.
The AC won't turn off.
Ooh!
Sounds like the work
of Captain Dearduff.
He brings with him
the icy chill of death.
So... bad luck there.
Night-night.
It sounds like you're
using Captain Dearduff
as an excuse for a crappy room.
I beg your pardon.
I did not get to be
a 40-year-old night clerk
by making excuses.
Now, if there is anything
wrong with your room
that isn't ghost-related,
I'm more than happy
to address it.
Okay, the Wi-Fi doesn't work.
Ghosts interfere
with electronic devices.
The shower's leaking.
Dearduff likes
the sound of dripping.
Reminds him
of his bleeding victims.
And the door won't lock.
Captain Dearduff
doesn't want to...
you know,
be locked out of his room.
Why would a locked door
keep a ghost out?
Can't he just walk
through walls?
Maybe he's afraid of rats.
There are rats in the walls?
No.
And the inn's booked up
because of the wedding,
so we can't change rooms.
Oh, that sucks.
I'm sorry, baby.
Hey...
but if Dearduff does manifest,
you know the proper way
to harvest ectoplasm, right?
(phone beeps)
Hey, good news-- we're all set
for the dove release.
The what?
When we leave the church,
they're gonna release
a hundred doves.
It's gonna be
avi-wait-for-it-ary.
Aviary!
Oh.
That might be a problem.
Why?
Because when
we leave the church,
a few of the gun enthusiasts
in my family
are gonna fire a 21-gun salute.
(bells tolling, doves cooing)
Hey, man.
(gunfire)
(dove cooing)
Oh, look-- one got away.
(gunshot)
Can't you guys just fire blanks?
At a wedding?
(laughing)
Yeah, that's romantic.
(thunder rumbling)
(thunder crashing)
(thunder crashes)
(screams)
(grunts, groans)
Ted!
What the hell are
you doing in my room?!
Uh...
NARRATOR:
There was an explanation.
You see, after Marshall
got off the phone with Lily,
he'd called me.
(phone rings)
Hey, buddy. What's up?
Ted, listen, I need you
to sneak into Lily's room,
find her phone, and delete
the last text she got.
Why? What's...
Ted, I need you to do this
no questions asked.
And as we both know, you owe me
a "No Questions Asked."
(phone rings)
Hey.
TED: Hey. Listen, I need you
to do something for me
no questions asked, okay?
What is it?
Meet me at the corner
of 53rd and 8th.
Bring your drill.
(click)
TED:
Marshall.
What the hell?
How did you...
No...
questions... asked.
I broke federal law drilling you
out of that mailbox.
Hey, I was a man in need.
I know.
You were a "Priority Male."
You said you'd
stop doing that joke
after the editor
of Bazooka Joe comics
rejected it.
That man is a comedy snob.
The point is,
you owe me
a "No Questions Asked."
Okay, okay!
I'll delete the text.
Thank you.
I just have to figure out
how to get into Lily's room.
Easy. The lock on her door
is busted, so...
The drainpipe!
What?
There's a drainpipe that
runs up near her window,
and, no big deal,
I can totally climb it.
I'll call you when it's done.
Her door is unlock...
(click)
Uh...
Marshall wanted me
to check on you.
He was worried
that you might be scared
all alone in the ghost room.
Remind me to call
you next time
Marvin has a nightmare--
you can calm him
by bursting into his room with
a chain saw and a hockey mask!
Sorry, I didn't want to knock
in case you were already asleep,
so I just climbed the drainpipe
up to your window.
No big deal.
Mm, opened the latch
with this here coat hanger.
I would have called,
but, uh...
well, I didn't know if
you'd have your phone handy.
Say, where is
that old phone of yours?
Ted, I am
not scared,
so why don't you head back
to your room...
(thunder crashes)
(screams): Oh...
kay...
Why, I guess you can stay
until I fall asleep,
if it'll make you feel better?
(thunder crashes)
A-And...
maybe if it'll
make you feel even better,
you can sing me a version
of Marvin's lullaby?
Okay.
♪ Night-night, little Lily
♪ No ifs, ands or buts
♪ No peg-legged ghost
is waiting ♪
♪ To hook out your guts.
Ted!
Sorry. Sorry.
Nighty-night.
(Ted humming lullaby)
(continues humming lullaby)
(continues humming)
ETHEREAL VOICE (softly):
Cold...
So cold.
Help me.
Help me...
Oh, God, the Hooker's here!
Ted,
I am not gonna cheat on Robin.
But you're a hell of a best man
for getting me one, buddy.
Where is she?
All right,
I'll take a lap dance.
Can I borrow some sweatpants?
(whispers): Barney, what
are you doing in there?
Marshall asked me
to do something for him,
no questions asked.
Sidebar-- I forgot
to get my cousin David
something for his bar mitzvah
last week.
Could you send the hooker
to his room?
Wait, Marshall called you, too?
NARRATOR: Turns out I wasn't
Marshall's first call.
Can't you guys just fire blanks?
At a wedding?
(laughing)
Yeah, that's romantic.
I just wish I would've
known about the guns.
Well,
I wish I'd known
about the doves.
That's the problem with
us-- we don't think
about checking in with the other
person before doing something.
Honestly, I think
that's what broke us up
the first time.
We're both... lone wolves--
always off in our own worlds.
That's not gonna work.
Not in a marriage, no.
What? Sorry, I was thinking
about getting the doves
little Kevlar tuxedos,
but that's not gonna work--
there's no time for a fitting.
(phone rings)
Hey.
Listen, I need you
to get to Lily's phone
without her seeing, and delete
the last text she got.
Why? What did you...
And I need you to do it
no questions asked.
As you'll recall, you owe me
a "No Questions Asked."
(phone rings)
Hello?
Marshall, I need you to rush
to the Macy's in Herald Square,
find the utility closet
on the third floor,
and bring me
the following things:
a clean pair of underwear,
a clean pair of pants,
a box of moist towelettes,
hand sanitizer,
and a garbage bag,
no questions asked.
You deuced your pants.
Never mind.
Ha. You didn't wind up
helping me, so it doesn't count.
Yes, I'm the one
Face!
who should be embarrassed
by that story.
But that wasn't
the time I meant.
This was last fall.
Hey, I got here as
fast as I could.
Are you okay?
Yeah, fine.
Th-These quacks said I was...
(scoffs)
unfit to leave on my own.
Blah, blah, blah.
"Danger to myself."
"Whoever signs me out is legally
responsible for my actions."
I just need you to sign me out.
What the hell happened?
Uh-uh!
I said no questions asked.
W...
Star, clover, horseshoe.
Barney, did you swallow
real versions
of all the Lucky Charms items?
No... questions... asked.
Now come on. Let's hit
the bar. I'm buying.
I just won 50 bucks from
a little Irish guy on a dare.
Fine, I'll delete the text.
But how am I supposed to get
into Lily's room?
Easy. The lock on her door
is busted...
Air ducts!
What?
I'll use the system of air ducts
to get in her room,
just like the bad guy
in Die Hard.
Barney, Bruce Willis is not
the bad guy in Die H...
Not important. The point is,
the door is not lock...
I'll call you when it's done.
ROBIN:
Anyway, I was saying,
I think we need to be better
about talking to each other
before doing stuff.
Can't talk. Doing stuff.
(grunting)
(grate clatters)
What is going on?
(groans)
Barney, what are you doing
in there?
Uh, well, there is
a story there.
It involves a trained
Guatemalan kinkajou,
a Bolshoi Ballet
prima ballerina
and Olympic gold medalist
Duke Kahanamoku's surfboard.
Tell her, Ted.
Uh...
uh...
The kinkajou...
the kinkajou...
(knocking)
Oh, God, what is it now?
Good evening,
Ms. Aldrin.
I didn't order room service.
It says right here, room 13.
Lobster, caviar, champagne.
$400?!
I didn't order any of this.
Maybe Dearduff the Hooker
ordered it.
Well, I'm not paying for room
service the Hooker ordered!
I've been there.
LILY: Okay,
you know what? I need to
talk to the manager.
All right,
where's that damn phone?
You, too?!
(groans)
(phone rings)
Hey.
MARSHALL: Robin,
I need you to delete
the last text
that Lily got
before she sees it.
Bro, it's my wedding weekend.
Just because
you didn't know better
than to take a naked selfie
while you were in the coldest
part of the country...
First, I'm an Eriksen.
Cold has a plumping effect.
Second, you owe me
a "No Questions Asked."
All right, I'm-I'm at the alley
near 22nd and 2nd. Now what?
ROBIN: No questions asked. Tell me
about that giant trout
you and your dad caught
ice-fishing that one time.
Well, it was more beast
than trout.
Fought us for three hours
and nearly dragged us both
into Lake Winnibigoshish.
It was this big, and...
(grunts)
Hey.
Run!
I never asked you
who those weirdos were,
why they kept calling you
Night Falcon
or even what was in those darts
that they were blowing at us.
Your vision came back,
didn't it?
(sighs)
Wuss.
Fine, I'll take care of it.
Just have to figure out
how to get into Lily's room.
Her door doesn't lock.
You can just...
Room service!
Night Falcon, you're a genius.
I'll call you when it's done.
Why would he call
you guys before me?
Well, dude,
you're not great in a crisis.
What was that story
you were prattling on about?
What the hell
is a kinkajou?
Okay, let's just find it
before she gets back.
NIGHT CLERK:
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You ordered it,
so you have to pay for it.
Not to mention the room damage
you're responsible for.
I've got
a report here:
broken lock, faulty Wi-Fi,
you've taken several items
from the minibar...
There is no minibar.
Stolen minibar.
It's not here.
Well, where else would it be?
Okay.
I think it's time
I call my lawyer.
Uh-oh.
Okay, we need to get to Lily's
phone before she sees that text.
I'm on it.
Night Falcon is on it.
Good thing I packed my unitard.
(groans)
(panting)
This is exactly
what we always do, isn't it?
Yeah.
We were both gonna bolt off
and lone wolf it
without telling
the other person a thing.
Why do we do that?
I don't know.
Maybe we're just incapable
of working as a unit.
(sighs)
You know...
I bet even lone wolves
can learn to work together.
I'd like to think so.
They could build their little
woodland den together.
Roam together.
Hunt together.
Lure prey into
a tight corner and...
BOTH: Snap its limbs
with our powerful jaws
and watch the life drain
from its eyes.
BOTH:
Aw...
Point is, we're gonna
make a great team.
We'll just need
some practice.
Yeah. Yeah, let's prove
that we believe in marriage
by working together
to help Marshall
hide something from his wife.
ROBIN: First, we take position
in the lobby.
BARNEY:
Then you cause a distraction.
(silenced gunshot)
(vase shatters)
ROBIN: Then you send in a trained dove
to grab Lily's phone.
BARNEY: The dove drops the phone
into your hand.
You delete the text
and toss it back
on the counter.
♪
Wait.
(sighs)
It's absolutely insane...
...how foolproof this plan is!
Sometimes it's best
to just go simple.
Yep.
(coughing)
Wh-Why do you have a gun?
Why do you always have a gun?
(quietly):
Where's Lily?
She went up 20 minutes ago.
You're kidding.
Courtney Dove, no!
I already lost Kurt Coo-bain!
I can't lose you as well.
Great. How are we gonna
get Lily's phone back now?
Oh, I already took care of that.
And now I'm rewarding myself
with some of the inn's
finest brandy.
Bottoms up.
Well, thank you.
No, no, that's a warning.
The dove's about to...
(cooing)
What happened?
Well...
I think it's time
I call my lawyer.
(phone ringing)
Hi, baby.
You are never gonna
believe this, but... (phone chimes)
Uh, someone sent me a text.
TED:
Lily, stop!
Why?
Because...
because...
NARRATOR:
And that's when I realized
that the answer
had been there all along.
Throw your phone on the ground
and smash it with your foot.
What? No.
I need you
to do this no questions asked.
You owe me
a "No Questions Asked."
Hey, Lil. What's...
Ted, I need you
to come
to my classroom right now
with two dozen cupcakes
and a box cutter.
No questions asked.
Lily, I brought the...
Oh-oh, my God.
Ted,
put the cupcakes at the feet
of their leader,
then cut me loose.
Don't make eye contact!
(children chanting)
Ted...
No... questions... asked.
(Lily stomping)
Well, interesting that I was
the one who fixed everything
even though Marshall
called me...
third.
NARRATOR: Ninth,
as I found out later,
but I won't go into it.
The important thing
is what happened
right after the untimely death
of Lily's phone.
So you're saying
you didn't order room service
and you didn't order
Prison Sluts Nine?
I am saying I did not order
room service.
It is done. By me.
Your third call.
Actually, you were...
Thank you. H-How did you do it?
I called in a "No Questions
Asked" with Lily.
But, wait,
why didn't you do that?
You must have, like,
a million of those.
And Marshall thought back.
Hello?
Hey, baby, it's me.
Um, can you come bail me
out of jail?
I thought I saw Bigfoot
in Central Park
and so I tackled him,
but it turned out
to be Russell Brand.
Hey...
Oh, do you mind looking up
our vaccination records?
I tried to hug a raccoon.
Hey, babe, um,
could you dig up our warranty?
I took the TV apart, and I made
a robot out of it.
(phone rings)
Hello?
Hey.
I tackled
Russell Brand again.
I've never asked Lily to do
anything no questions asked
because...
I've never wanted to.
She's the love of my life.
I never keep anything from her.
(sighs)
Ted, put Lily on the phone.
Hey. It's Marshall.
Want to tell me what's going on?
Yes.
I was offered a judgeship
in New York.
And I took it.
Even though we already agreed
to move to Rome.
I'm gonna be a judge.
Lily?
You know, Marshall,
I don't believe in ghosts,
and I'm not sure anyone died
in our room,
but someone's going to.
(thunder rumbles)
(Dearduff laughing manically)
"And I see in your eyes
the emerald reefs
"of the primordial seas afroth
"with the first stirrings
of life,
"infinite in mystery
and miracle.
"Forever yours,
"the guy you met
at the drugstore an hour ago.
"I heard you give your address
to the pharmacist
while I was buying foot powder."
Yeah.
Mailed it.
(grunting)
No! No! No, no!
(grunts)