Watson.
Yes.
Watch.
The chemical reaction
you are about to witness
will solve the mystery
concerning the persecution
of Mr. John Vincent Harden.
Excellent,
the tobacco millionaire,
shall I take notes?
No, I will dictate
in the fullness of time.
There's a young lady wishes
to see you, Mr. Holmes.
This is not
a convenient moment!
She's very well spoken,
a genuine lady.
No doubt.
And persistent, too.
Mrs. Hudson, I, too,
am extremely persistent,
especially when I'm working.
It is a matter
of great urgency, Mr. Holmes,
or I would not be troubling you
on a Saturday evening.
Perhaps you could, uh, delay
your chemical reaction, Holmes.
Very well.
Do sit down, Miss, uh?
Violet Smith.
Dr. Watson.
Thank you Mrs. Hudson.
A genuine lady,
I told you.
Oh, please.
Um, thank you,
I'll be quite happy here.
Very well, Miss Smith,
you must tell us
your matter of great urgency.
It is obviously
not your health.
So ardent a bicyclist
must be full of energy.
Yes, I bicycle a good deal.
Slight roughening on
the side of the soles
caused by the friction
of the pedals.
Excellent, Watson.
The marks on your shoes.
Oh, yes!
Even if I have
to travel a long way,
I take my bicycle on the train
with me as I did today.
You will excuse me,
but it is my business.
Yes, I nearly
fell into the error
of supposing you earned
a living by typewriting,
but of course,
it is obviously music.
You will observe, Watson,
the spatulate finger ends,
which is common
to both professions.
There is a spirituality
about the face, however,
which the typewriter
does not generate.
This lady is a musician.
Why, yes, Mr. Holmes,
I teach music!
In the country, I presume,
from your complexion.
Near Farnham
on the borders of Surrey!
But please, let me explain
why I am here.
I am an only child, and
my father died some years ago.
His name and profession?
James Smith,
he conducted the orchestra
at the old lmperial Theater.
Ah, the old lmperial, Holmes.
Yes.
Please continue.
My mother and I were left
without a relation in the world
except for one uncle,
Ralph Smith,
who went to Africa
15 years ago,
and we have not had a word
from him since,
despite our Christmas cards
and photographs.
Mr. Holmes,
I have to tell you that--
I think you wish to tell me
that you and your mother
are very poor,
not withstanding your obvious
grace, dignity and talent.
We were very poor.
Ah.
About four months ago,
in February,
we were told there was
an advertisement in the Times,
inquiring for
our whereabouts.
You can imagine
how excited we were,
for we thought that someone
had left us a fortune.
I went at once
to the lawyers
whose name was given
in the paper.
Now, this is
Miss Violet Smith.
The solicitor
introduced me to two men,
a Mr. Carruthers
and a Mr. Woodley.
They were on a visit
from South Africa.
I wish I could tell you your
uncle left you a vast fortune,
but as I said...
He died in extreme poverty.
However, I myself
am not without means.
My mother and I
never sought charity.
No, nor do I offer it.
Please.
I have a question
to ask of you.
Your Uncle Ralph
said you were very musical,
do you teach music?
Yes.
Miss Smith, I am now a widower
with a 10-year-old daughter.
Young Sarah.
She needs a music teacher.
So, you see,
I do not offer charity.
A job, he wants
to give you a job!
Whereabouts in London
do you live, Mr. Carruthers?
I don't.
I live about six miles
from Farnham, in Surrey,
at Chiltern Grange.
I couldn't possibly leave
my mother on her own.
I will pay you
100 pounds a year.
A hundred a year?
Yes.
Approximately double
the market price, I think.
Oh, at least!
Which you obviously accepted,
or you wouldn't be here now.
Yes.
I accepted the offer.
Mr. Carruthers agreed
that I should go home every
weekend to my mother in town.
So this is one of your
weekend visits to London?
It is.
Tell me about your life
at Chiltern Grange.
For a while,
it was quite perfect.
Every Monday morning I would
take the train to Farnham
and then bicycle from
the station to the house.
The little girl's
name was Sarah,
and she was delightful,
as well as being
a very good pupil.
That was very much
better, Sarah.
May I try it again?
Of course,
that's why we're here.
Mr. Carruthers was
appreciative of my work,
and an extremely kind
and considerate host.
Sounds idyllic.
It was.
What happened to spoil it?
A visitor.
Mr. Woodley.
However did you guess,
Mr. Holmes?
Miss Smith,
I never guess.
Tell me about his visit.
He arrived
and was to stay for a week.
But to me it seemed
like three months.
Oh, that odious
red mustache!
One evening after dinner,
Mr. Carruthers had
to leave us for a minute
to see somebody
at the door.
A gentleman
to see you, sir.
Will you excuse me?
That's better.
Better, in what way?
It's better to
get the old folk out of the way.
I don't regard
Mr. Carruthers as old.
Oh, yes,
but he isn't young...
like us.
I do wish you wouldn't blow
smoke in my face, Mr. Woodley.
Oh, I don't believe that
for a moment.
What don't you believe?
When women say they wish
you wouldn't do something,
it generally means
the exact opposite.
I mean precisely
what I say!
Mr. Woodley, will you please
leave me alone!
No.
To tell you the truth,
I won't leave you alone,
not until I've said
what's in my heart.
Whatever do you mean?
I'm not very
well up on the social graces,
but I'm prepared to learn,
if you're prepared to teach me.
Oh, this is absurd!
It isn't absurd!
I'm asking you to marry me!
I mean it,
it's from the heart.
Money isn't a problem,
I did very well
out in South Africa.
Whatever you are accustomed to,
I can give you better,
better that
you're accustomed to;
jewelry, diamonds.
You want diamonds,
oh, I can give you diamonds.
I don't want diamonds!
Oh, you think about it.
I won't rush you.
I've thought about it,
and the idea is ludicrous.
Well, you can't
blame me for trying!
You're very beautiful.
Listen, just to show
there are no hard feelings,
what about a little kiss
to be going on with, hmm,
just a peck on the cheek.
Mr. Woodley,
will you please stop it!
Oh, I told you before about
women who say stop it.
No!
The more they struggle,
the more fun it is.
Mr. Carruthers,
will you stop him!
Get out of this house!
All right!
I'm going.
I'm not interested
in old men,
and old maids!
I can only offer you
my most sincere apologies
for what has happened.
If I give you my assurance
that it will not happen again,
for my daughter's sake,
will you stay?
Yes, I will stay.
Thank you, Violet.
Mr. Woodley left the house
and I have not seen him since.
The blackguard!
Has there been any change
in the behavior
of Mr. Carruthers?
No, he continues to be polite
and considerate and courteous.
Now, Miss Smith, please,
please continue.
Yes, there is something else.
Oh, it may be
a mere fancy of mine,
but it seems to me
that Mr. Carruthers
shows a great deal
of interest in me.
Oh, he has never said anything,
he is a perfect gentleman,
but, a girl
always knows.
So I believe.
And I assume
that these feelings that
you sense from Mr. Carruthers
are not reciprocated?
He is a kind and generous
employer,
but I am already engaged.
Oh, the name of this
very fortunate young man is?!
Cyril Morton.
He's an electrical engineer
with the Midland Electric
Company in Coventry.
We're to be married
at the end of the summer.
We wish you joy.
Thank you.
Yet, I am puzzled as to why
you have chosen to consult me.
It is an intriguing story,
to be sure,
but I sense you are frightened,
and do not understand why.
You seem well capable
of protecting yourself.
Please,
help me, Mr. Holmes!
What is it?
I am being followed.
Followed, by whom?
A cyclist.
Every Saturday morning
I bicycle from the house
to Farnham Station
to catch
the 12:22 to town.
There is one very quiet
and lonely stretch of road
that lies between Charlington
Heath on the one hand
and the woods of
Charlington Hall on the other.
Two weeks ago today,
I was passing this place
when I chanced to look back
and saw a man,
also on a bicycle.
The following Monday when
I returned he was there again.
I see.
And again last Saturday,
and again last Monday.
Have you mentioned this
to your employer?
Yes.
Mr. Carruthers
was very concerned,
and has ordered
a horse and trap
so that in the future I should
not travel unaccompanied.
But they've
not yet arrived.
And this morning?
He was following me again.
I slowed down,
but he did the same.
Then I stopped completely,
So, I laid a trap for him.
There is a sharp
turning of the road,
and I pedaled very quickly
towards this
and then stopped
and waited.
But he seemed to disappear
into thin air.
Can you describe this man?
I realize that you've only
seen him from a distance.
Yes.
He wears a dark suit,
dark spectacles,
and he has a beard.
Young, old?
He's about middle-aged.
Now, let me see if I have
the geography correct.
Here is the road,
with a sharp bend in it here.
On this side,
Charlington Heath,
and on the other,
the woods of Charlington Hall.
How long did you wait for him
here around the bend?
Oh, no more than two minutes.
So he could not have retreated
back down the road.
Are there any side roads?
None along this stretch.
Could he have taken a footpath
across the heath?
Oh, the heath
is totally flat and bleak.
I think I would have
noticed him.
So, by a process of exclusion,
we arrive at the fact that
he made his way towards
Charlington Hall.
Now how does Mr. Carruthers
make his living?
Oh, he's a rich man.
But no carriages or horses.
Well, at least
he's very well off.
He goes into the city
two or three times a week,
and he sometimes refers
to his gold shares.
Yes, I see.
You must let me know
immediately
if there are any fresh
developments.
I am extremely busy
just now,
but I will find time to make
inquiries into your case.
Thank you, Mr. Holmes.
In the meantime, take no step
without letting me know.
I'm sure we shall have nothing
but good news for you.
I do hope so, Dr. Watson.
Very lovely girl.
Yes.
And it is part of
the settled order of nature
that such a girl
should have followers,
but for choice, not on bicycles
in lonely country roads.
You really think she may be
in some danger, Holmes?
Oh, yes.
On the following Monday,
Holmes found that
he had business
which detained him in London,
so, he dispatched me on
the early train to Farnham
that I might observe
Miss Smith's passage
past Charlington Hall.
The setting was
just as she had described,
heavily wooded on the side
bordering the hall,
and utterly
exposed on the other.
I selected the only
available cover, and waited.
Watson, you have
wasted your time.
I thought I did rather well.
No, your hiding place
was ill-chosen.
You should have been
in the bracken
on the other
side of the road.
Then that way you would
have had a close view
of this fascinating
solitary cyclist.
Thank you.
As it is, you were
a hundred yards away
and can tell me even less
than Miss Smith reported to us
last Saturday.
You describe him as bending low
over the handle bar?
Yes, quite low.
Thus concealment again,
which in your case
worked perfectly.
Oh know, you really
have done remarkably badly.
He goes back to the Hall
and you come all the way back to
London to call on a house agent.
Well, I found
the information I was seeking.
You found the name Williamson,
which conveys
nothing to my mind.
Well, we know he's elderly
and respectable.
And therefore, unlikely to be
the energetic cyclist
that sprints away from
that athletic young girl.
Well, what should I have done?
Gone to the nearest
public house.
That is the center
of country gossip.
They would have
given you every name
from the master
to the scullery maid.
Instead of which,
you give me--Williamson.
So, what have we gained
by your expedition.
The fact that
the girl's story is true;
I never doubted that.
That there is a connection
between the cyclist
and the Hall;
I never doubted
that, either.
The Hall is tenanted
by a man called Williamson.
Who is the better for that?
I shall go back tomorrow
and visit the public house.
No, my dear sir, do not
commit yourself to rashness
because you are
temporarily depressed.
We can do nothing useful
until Saturday.
Did I really do
remarkably badly?
Yes.
Very beautiful.
Thank you, Mr. Carruthers.
It is a new piece.
I need to
practice it more.
No, I don't mean the music.
Violet, I have
a question to ask you.
Morning, Holmes.
A letter
from Miss Violet Smith.
Now Carruthers has proposed
marriage to her.
Carruthers!
Gentlemen are permitted
to propose marriage, Watson.
Of course he didn't
know about Cyril.
Are you going
to Farnham?
I want to test one or two
theories which I have formed.
Shall I come with you?
No, that will be neither
useful nor necessary.
Try the nearest public house,
always a good center
for country gossip.
Thank you, Watson,
capital notion!
Ah, Good afternoon, Landlord.
May I have half a pint
of your local ale, please?
Certainly, sir.
Here you are.
Thank you.
You may keep the change.
That's most generous
of you, sir, but I couldn't.
I haven't done anything
to warrant such generosity.
I'm about to give you
the opportunity.
I need some information.
Oh, I'm not one
for idle gossip, sir.
Neither am I,
I prefer facts.
Tell me about the people
at Charlington Hall.
You mean
Mr. Williamson, sir?
Yes.
Well, he--he was in here
not more than five minutes ago.
You just missed him.
Tell me about Mr. Williamson.
Is he an elderly,
respectable gentleman?
Oh, he's elderly,
no doubt.
Far be it from me to speak ill
of people behind their backs,
but I'm none too sure
about respectable.
Really?
He is an ex-clergymen,
I reckon.
Ex?
Apparently.
He was struck off,
or whatever it is
happens to clergymen.
That's doctors
that are struck off.
Tell me about the other people
up at the house.
Well, they're
just domestic staff,
and they're all
local and God-fearing.
Of course.
He do have folk up there
at weekends.
Weekends?
Yes, sir.
Weekends.
Ah, no problem.
What sort of folk?
Oh, they're a warm lot.
Warm?
Yes, the sort you
don't want to get too near
for fear of getting
burnt like.
That's good.
Oh, you may
think it's good, sir.
They don't come down well
in the village, I can tell you.
There was one fellow
in particular.
Particularly warm,
is he, this fellow?
He is very particularly, sir.
I'll wager he has
a red mustache.
Hey, do you know him?
I never met the gentleman.
Well, now is your chance.
Mr. Woodley.
None of your damn business!
Our Landlord keeps
a very respectable house,
and your language
is not welcome.
Who do you think you are?
What the hell do you want coming
here asking all them questions?
You're quite right, Landlord,
clearly not a gentleman.
Oh, I'm as much a gentleman
as you are.
Everybody here will
bear witness to the fact
that I am acting
in self-defense.
Swine!
No, sir,
a gentleman!
Only a ruffian deals a blow
with the back of a hand.
A gentleman uses
the straight--left...
and I, sir,
am a gentleman!
It was absolutely
delicious, Watson.
So I see.
A straight left
against a slogging ruffian.
I emerged, as you see.
And the slogging ruffian?
Mr. Woodley was taken home
in a cart.
There's that
horrible man again.
Which man?
I thought I saw Mr. Woodley
in the garden today.
You did.
He's staying in the area.
But do not worry,
I have told him quite firmly
he's not to set foot
inside the house.
"Dear Mr. Holmes:
You will not be
surprised to learn
that I will be leaving
Mr. Carruthers's employment
on Saturday."
The odious Mr. Woodley has
reappeared at Chiltern Grange.
Ah, but at least she won't be
bicycling to the station.
So finally,
the rich Mr. Carruthers
has acquired
a horse and trap.
Yes.
Look here, "all my troubles
will be over on Saturday."
Tomorrow, Holmes,
all her troubles will be over.
Why do I
worry about that word.
Which word?
"Trap."
Oh, what a splendid morning,
Holmes!
It's acceptable weather
for the time of year.
Now who would want to harm that
dear girl on such a morning?
I hope nobody.
So why did you
bring your revolver?
I'm talking about my hope,
not my expec-tations.
What?
I fancy that
is our Miss Smith.
She must be traveling
by an earlier train.
I give her a margin
of half an hour,
but she'll be
past Charlington Hall
before we can
possibly meet her.
So what can we do?
We could run.
Fool, I should have allowed
for that earlier train!
It's abduction,
Watson, it's abduction,
murder, heaven knows what.
Stop that horse.
Good man.
Come on, Watson!
Let's see if I can repair the
consequences of my own blunder!
Up there!
Holmes.
Where did you get that cart?!
Where is Miss Violet Smith?!
That's what I'm asking you.
You were in her cart!
It was on the road,
there was no one in it!
Somebody seems to have
gone through this way!
We must find them!
Come, Watson.
Now look,
do you know who this is?!
That's Peter, the groom,
he was taking her
to the station.
He's alive,
his pulse is strong.
Mustn't be left
lying there too long.
Let him lie,
we can't do him any good,
but we might save her
from the worst fate
that can befall a woman.
Where are you going?!
The house!
They didn't go
to the house!
They went this way
to the left.
Are you sure?
Oh, cowardly dogs!
Too late!
Watson.
Too late by the living Jingo!
For as much
as John and Violet
have consented together
in holy wedlock,
and have witnessed the same
before God and this company...
and have declared the same
by the giving
and receiving of a ring,
and the joining of hands,
I pronounce that
they be man and wife, together.
Congratulations!
Thanks, amen.
They're married!
Welcome to the party,
gentlemen.
Let me introduce you
to Mrs. Woodley.
Don't Carruthers!
Carruthers!
Yes, and I'll see
this woman righted,
if I have to swing for it.
You're too late.
She is my wife!
No, she's your widow.
I told you what I'd do
if you molested her!
By the Lord,
I'm a man of my word!
When you hired me,
nobody told me there'd be
any of this damn nonsense!
Drop that pistol.
Watson, pick it up!
Give me that revolver,
we'll have no more violence.
Who are you
to be giving these orders?
Sherlock Holmes.
Good Lord.
Here, you!
Sir?
Are you well enough
to drive into Farnham?
Yes, sir,
I reckon I am.
Then give this note
to the superintendent
of the police station.
In the meantime,
I must detain you all under
my own personal custody.
How are the patients, Doctor?
Miss Smith's very well,
considering the foul way
she's been treated.
And Woodley?
Alas, I have no doubt
he will live.
What, I'll go upstairs
and finish him off.
No, sit down in that chair,
Carruthers.
You're right.
He isn't worth
swinging for.
But do you tell me
that girl
is to be tied to
Roaring Jack Woodley for life?!
You needn't concern
yourself about that.
I married them
till death do them part.
Under no circumstances can she
be considered his wife.
Are you sure?
For two very good reasons.
In the first place,
we are very safe in questioning
Mr. Williamson's right
to solemnize a marriage.
I have been ordained.
And unfrocked.
Once a clergyman,
always a clergyman.
I think not.
How about the license?
Oh, we had a license.
I have it here.
Undoubtedly obtained
by a trick.
But, in any case, a forced
marriage is no marriage,
indeed, it is a very serious
felony, as you will discover.
Now, while we are waiting
for the police, Mr. Carruthers,
you might tell me
your story.
If you squeal on us,
Bob Carruthers,
I'll serve you
as you served Jack Woodley!
There's no need for you
to get over-excited.
The case is clear enough.
Well, if it's clear enough,
why don't you tell us.
Very well.
Mr. Carruthers will have
to fill in a few details
for my private curiosity,
but I am happy
to do the talking.
In the first place,
the three of you came across
from South Africa.
Wrong, I've never even been
in South Africa!
It's true.
Woodley acquired this creature
after our return.
Very well,
you and Woodley
had known Ralph Smith
in South Africa.
You had reason to believe
that he would not live long,
and you found out that his niece
would inherit his fortune.
How's that?
But you told the girl
her uncle died in poverty.
Well, as he was still alive,
admittedly only just,
and a wealthy man who
I suspect had made no will.
Ralph Smith
could neither read nor write.
So, you and Woodley came over
here and hunted up the girl,
knowing she was
the next of kin,
and that you would
share the plunder.
I was due a share
for services rendered.
And Carruthers,
you made the mistake
of falling in love with her.
The first time that ever I knew
what love was, Mr. Holmes.
Why didn't you tell her
of the danger she was in?
Because--because
she would have left me,
and I couldn't bear
to face that.
Oh, what will happen
to my daughter, Sarah?
We'll see she's
well taken care of.
You see, even if
she couldn't love me,
it meant a great deal
to see her about the house
and hear the sound
of her voice.
You may call it love,
Mr. Carruthers,
I should call it
selfishness.
Maybe the two things
go together.
But I tried to protect her,
I never once let her go
past this house
where I knew those rascals
were lurking
without following her
on my bicycle
to see she
came to no harm.
I kept my distance
and wore that beard
so she should not
recognize me.
Then I presume
the cable arrived?
Cable, what cable?
"THE OLD MAN IS DEAD."
What old man?
I imagine Ralph Smith
in South Africa.
Yes.
But by this time you and Woodley
had quarreled
and he had left the house.
Woodley came back again to ask
me to stick to the bargain.
I refused.
I said I would have
nothing to do with violence.
One last detail,
why was Woodley chosen
as the prospective husband?
I am ashamed to say it...
we played cards for her.
Holmes, I have the results
of the trial.
Listen to this, the judge
in summing up said--
Holmes.
Watson, may I be permitted
an educated guess?
Go on then.
I would expect Woodley
to get ten years,
Williamson seven years,
and Carruthers,
in view of the eloquent speech I
made on his behalf at the trial,
probably six months.
That is exactly right!
Well, I have
certain advantages, Watson,
largely the fact that I sent out
for the early edition.
An undoubted advantage.
Also, we have received
a present,
some wedding cake from
Mr. and Mrs. Cyril Morton,
together with a letter
telling us that Mrs. Morton has
inherited a large sum of money
from her uncle, Ralph Smith,
formerly of South Africa.
The happy couple
are thoroughly enjoying
looking after young
Sarah Carruthers,
while her father
is in custody.
Her piano playing
is improving
and she wants to
take up bicycling.
A splendid day all round,
wouldn't you say?
There is more splendor
yet to come.
More splendor,
what do you mean?
Watch carefully.
Oh, I remember,
the chemical reaction
that will solve the mystery
concerning the persecution
of Mr. John Vincent Harden.
Precisely.
I've spent the entire week
in the lmperial Science Museum
and I think
this is the answer.
Is that the answer, Holmes?
Yes, that is the answer,
Watson.
Well, let me think.