- Previously on Why Women Kill...
- TAYLOR: She was kicked
out of her third home because
her foster mother accused her
of trying to seduce
her husband.
A week later,
that house burned down.
- You did those things?
- You can't believe
- a fucking word he says!
- Jade, watch out!
- (tires screech)
- (car crashes)
NURSE:
Before we put him out,
he wrote you this note.
Said it was
important.
- Did you talk to him?
- DUKE: No.
Taylor came to see me in jail.
You really fucked me this time!
Your membership to the club
has been revoked.
It's because I'm ill.
It was you.
You seduced
my child.
Do you think
that I would be satisfied
just getting you kicked
out of a country club?
I am just getting started,
bitch.
Dad always said
that you were vindictive.
I am still your mother.
No, from now on, you're just
some lady that I used to know.
- You pulling out?
- Not yet.
I'm waiting for someone.
MARY: My husband likes to
threaten me with a loaded gun
he keeps in his bedside drawer.
BETH ANN: Our daughter
died because of me.
I'm the one who's responsible.
The last time I slept
with your husband
was the day your child died.
While you were coming
in the front door,
I ran around the side
of the house.
Did Rob know
you had not closed the gate?
I called him that
night and I told him.
What can I do for you?
I need to buy a gun.
("L-O-V-E" by Michael Feinstein
playing)
♪ "L" is for the way you look ♪
♪ At me ♪
♪ "O" is for the only one ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ "V" is very, very ♪
♪ Extraordinary ♪
♪ "E" is even more ♪
♪ Than anyone
that you adore can ♪
♪ Love is all ♪
♪ That I can give to you ♪
♪ Love is more ♪
♪ Than just a game for two ♪
♪ Two in love can make it ♪
♪ Take my heart
and please don't break it ♪
♪ Love was made ♪
♪ For me and you... ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
So, what do you think?
(exhales) It's impressive.
Square footage?
5,000.
Give or take.
Four big bedrooms upstairs.
Got kids?
We had a little girl.
Her name was Emily.
Was?
Could you excuse us a moment?
You've got to stop telling total
strangers our daughter died.
He asked me a question.
It's been over a year.
How are we gonna
move forward in our lives
if we keep talking
about what happened?
I don't even understand
what we're doing here.
The house we have now is fine.
It's got
too many memories.
We need a fresh start.
I mean, this could be
good for us.
Don't you want to find a way
to be happy again?
Of course I do.
Well, then let me buy this
for you.
If you do that,
I'll spend every day
just trying to put the smile
back on your face.
The one I fell in love with.
I guess we could be happy here.
Of course we can.
Now where's that smile I love?
I bought a gun yesterday.
What?
I'd left an appointment
at my cancer doctors,
and I passed the most
adorable gun shop.
And I bought this
little revolver.
Why do we need a gun?
There have been robberies
in the neighborhood.
Mrs. Betz on the corner?
Some thief smashed her
window, reached in,
and took her new purse
right off her end table.
- Have I met her?
- Anyway,
I don't feel safe.
So I got this gun, and
I'm storing it here.
And I've already
put in the bullets.
You're keeping the gun loaded?
If someone attacks us,
I don't think
we'd want to waste time
looking for bullets. Do you?
This is a nice street.
Nothing bad is going
to happen to us.
You never know.
So...
what do you think?
You were right
to bring us here.
So many possibilities.
Yes, the floor plan's good,
but really,
the color of the walls...
Before we go any
further, state law
compels me to disclose
that a murder took place here.
Someone was murdered
in this house?
Was it the decorator?
- Oh. (laughs)
- (door opens)
Simone!
- Naomi!
- (exclaims)
I saw your car out front.
Tell me that you are
buying this place.
I live a block away.
We would be neighbors.
Karl, this is my friend
Naomi from the country club.
You must be
the dashing new boyfriend
I keep hearing about.
Not just the boyfriend.
- I've, uh, been promoted.
- Stop.
You're engaged?
Oh, well, now you definitely
need a bigger house.
- And who's this charming young man?
- Tommy.
This is my son Tommy.
Tommy, this is Simone.
You're pretty.
- Oh.
- (laughs)
Kids say the
cutest things.
Oh, hands off, young man.
She's spoken for.
Oh, Simone, please tell me
you'll take the house.
I'd absolutely kill
to have you here.
Oh, it would be fun,
wouldn't it?
Being close to my best friend.
(tires screeching)
Simone!
(engine hissing)
(both panting)
Are you all right?
Oh, my God.
What happened?
(bystanders clamoring)
My mother tried
to kill you.
What?
Oh, my God, is she alive?
Tommy.
Someone call a doctor!
- Okay.
- And the police!
So... what do you think?
I mean... I love it.
I say, let's do it.
- What?
- I want to buy this house.
Can I talk with my husband for
a moment in private, please?
Take your time.
What?
Dude, are you crazy?
Are you cra...? Did
you not see that pool?
And that kitchen is huge.
Yeah, and it needs a complete
remodel. We can't afford that.
D-Don't worry about
the money, all right?
My career is taking off.
The reviews for Jenny from
Yesterday are through the roo.
Yeah, I know,
but even so, it's still risky.
Risky? Are you hearing
yourself right now?
- Do you know who you sound like?
- Who?
Me... when we were talking
about having an open marriage?
Okay, that's not
the same thing.
No. I was...
I was nervous.
I was unsure that we could make
it work, but you convinced me.
And now our life is so
much more exciting for it.
Now think about how much even
more exciting our life would be
- with that fucking kitchen, right?
- (both laughing)
Oh, sweetie,
you still have that cold?
It's fine. I'm good. I'm good.
Just, Taylor, trust me.
Okay? Believe in me.
I promise you
I will not let you down.
Take it slow.
- God, everything hurts.
- (sighs)
Well, here's something
to ease the pain.
I went by the house.
All of Jade's stuff is gone.
That was fast.
Yeah. Well, she knows
we're onto her.
She can't just stick around,
waiting for the cops to show up.
Oh, speaking of the house,
I, uh, got you
a little something.
A business card?
Yeah. For Lamar's Realtor.
If it's okay with you,
I want to sell the house.
Really?
Yeah, it just
feels like
every wrong turn
we've made can be traced back
to the moment where I talked you
into buying it.
No house...
wouldn't have
met Jade. No Jade, no relapse.
I mean, we'd lose
a lot of stress.
The mortgage payments alone.
(laughs)
- Look at that smile.
- (laughs)
All right. So how much
downsizing are we up for?
Townhouse? Condo?
Fuck it. Let's just buy a field.
We can pitch a tent.
- Love it.
- (laughs)
Tent in a field.
We'd be living the dream.
And the best part about moving...
Jade won't be able to find us.
Where do you think she went?
I don't know.
Let's just hope she's
a thousand miles away by now.
Who's Duke?
My grandfather.
Grammy Sue gave that to him for
their first wedding anniversary.
He wore it every day,
but he never wound it.
He always used
to say that
"When I met my Susie, it
was like time stood still."
Sweet.
Give you 35.
Hundred?
No. Dollars.
It's worth much more than that.
Sentimental-wise, maybe.
Cash-wise, it's worth $35.
- Well, I need more.
- All right.
I'll throw in
an extra five for the story.
And 'cause I like your... face.
How about a grand?
I don't like
your face that much.
Okay, well, then
a couple hundred.
- Honey, I told you...
- Please.
You don't understand
what I've been through lately.
I've lost everything,
and I just need a little...
What you need is to give
the waterworks a rest.
I made you my offer,
so either take it
or get the hell out.
The fuck?!
I'm calling the cops!
Yeah, I get that a lot.
(doorbell rings)
Beth Ann.
Morning, Mary.
I hope I'm not interrupting?
No, not at all. Ralph
just left for work.
I know. I waited for him to go.
I need to speak
to you privately.
- What's going on?
- I've thought of a way
to solve our respective
marital difficulties.
You have?
I've come up with a plan
on how to kill our husbands.
Please invite me in.
This is the sort of thing
we should discuss over coffee.
That's the plan.
Any thoughts?
It's crazy.
- We'd never get away with it.
- But we would.
Think about it.
Technically speaking,
we wouldn't be doing
anything illegal.
How could we be sure
that Rob and Ralph
would even swallow the bait?
That's the beauty of the plan.
It's tailor-made to fit
their horribly predictable
personalities.
What if someone discovers
what we've done?
I don't plan
on telling anyone.
Do you?
I don't know.
Ralph deserves to die.
And... after everything
Rob's put you through,
he's just as bad.
But the Bible says,
"Thou shalt not kill."
God might not understand.
Maybe not.
But I'm sure God's wife will.
Now, what do you say?
Oh. Tommy.
You seem surprised to see me.
Well, we're
such social pariahs these days,
I'm surprised to see anyone.
At this point,
I'd roll out the red carpet
for a Jehovah's Witness.
How are you feeling?
Delightful.
Simone's
in the kitchen.
♪ ♪
How is your mother's
physical therapy going?
Better.
She took
a few steps today.
I still think that you
should have pressed charges.
She said she lost control
of the car.
I choose to believe her.
Nobody else does.
All of her friends
at the country club,
the ones that she turned
against you and Karl,
they finally found out Mom's
crazy and they dropped her.
Oh. Poor Naomi.
"Poor Naomi"?
Come on.
You must be a little pleased.
The woman I'm trying to become
would draw no satisfaction
from this at all.
Fortunately,
I'm not that woman just yet.
I'm thinking about canceling
my trip to Paris.
You can't let your mother
guilt you into staying.
I'd be staying
for you, not her.
Karl's getting worse, isn't he?
I'll take good care of him.
But who will take care of you?
I'll be fine.
Oh, you should go.
Karl has a doctor's appointment.
I'm sorry our relationship
caused such a scandal.
I try to tell people
I'm the one who pursued you,
but they refuse to believe
it was my fault.
You say that like we did
something we should regret.
I don't regret
one moment we shared.
Now go.
Have the most wonderful summer
of your life.
Study art.
Drink wine.
Think of me every now and then.
I'll think of you constantly.
I love you.
I won't be the last woman
you say that to.
But I'm proud to be the first.
♪ ♪
Here it is.
COLE: Now, you're sure you
want to part with this?
Oh, I'd love to keep it,
but the truth is,
we need the money.
Simone, are things really as bad
as all that?
Once the art gallery went under,
we lost our health insurance.
And Karl's medical bills
have been outrageous.
Is there anything I can do?
You could buy another painting.
Perhaps you'd like to have me
hanging in your living room?
Ah...
Why don't I just pay you
another thousand for this one?
That's very kind.
And somewhat insulting.
Take care, Cole.
KARL:
Simone?
Yes, Karl?
I need you.
Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm just trying
to make myself presentable.
Would you do my neck?
Oh, of course.
Are you going somewhere?
Tim from my support group's
just got out of hospital.
Harold's holding a
brunch in his honor.
Oh, that should be nice.
You haven't tasted
his cooking.
I'm sure we'll all be back in
the emergency room by dessert.
(chuckles)
You are such a bitch.
I should hope so.
I did study with a master.
Oh, I heard the doorbell.
Who was it?
Cole stopped by to
pick up the painting.
Oh, Lord,
I feel so dreadful about that.
I-I know how much
you love that piece.
It's okay.
At least
we can pay the mortgage now.
Or most of it.
(choked up):
I am s... I am so sorry.
Stop it.
We are fine.
Uh, you are right.
We are, uh, two...
bitch goddesses.
And we will
not be defeated.
Now turn.
(birds chirping)
(doorbell rings)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
What did I tell
all you this morning
before we left the house?
Huh?
What did I say?
Not to embarrass you.
I can never go back
to that store ever again
because of what
you little freaks did
to that poor mannequin.
(all giggling)
Go inside.
Now!
(kids chattering and laughing)
Hello.
I'm not sure
if you remember who I am.
I know who you are.
Can you tell me who you are?
Let's start with the headline,
hon.
I'm not Rob Stanton's wife.
Come on in.
I think it's time
someone told you the truth.
Thank you, Lamar.
Your support
means a lot.
Yeah. Yeah.
I will see you
on the other side, man.
Okay. Bye.
So, how you
gonna stay busy
while I'm at rehab?
Guessing the short answer
is "girls, girls, girls"?
(chuckles)
Well, funny you
should mention that.
I thought maybe we could rethink
the whole open marriage thing.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You know, we should
focus on us for a while.
Go to therapy.
And three's a crowd.
Especially
in couples counseling.
Okay.
- What, you don't like that idea?
- No.
It's just...
I mean, obviously,
your sexuality
is really important.
And...
I just don't want you to have
to give any part of that up.
It is important to me.
But like I've always said,
my love story is with you.
And I would
choose you over
a few casual hookups
any day of the week.
It would just be
you and me?
Forsaking all others?
Till death do us part.
(exhales)
Did we just become
Republicans?
I think we did.
Hector, hi.
Come on in.
Karl is taking a nap.
Should I wake him?
Uh, no.
Actually, uh,
I'm here to see you.
Oh. What's going on?
Remember last Sunday,
when I took Karl
to that brunch at Harold's?
Yes.
Thank you for driving him.
So, Harold
called me today.
He thinks Karl stole some pills
from his medicine cabinet.
What kind of pills?
Sleeping pills.
And the same thing
happened two weeks ago
when we went
to Billy's for bridge.
I see.
Karl puts on a brave face,
but I know
how depressed he's been.
And I'm just so worried.
You did the right thing
telling me.
Simone, I'm so sorry
to dump this on you.
But you've always been the only
one who can get through to him.
I will take care of it.
Thank you.
So, while you copy the
letter in your handwriting,
I'll be upstairs
cleaning out your closet.
You said Ralph gets
home around 6:45?
Sometimes as early as 6:30.
Rob gets home around 6:15,
and it's almost 5:00.
We need to
get cracking.
Beth Ann?
When Ralph reads this...
he will absolutely get violent.
We can only hope.
♪ You look like an angel ♪
♪ Look like an angel ♪
♪ Walk like an angel ♪
♪ Talk like an angel ♪
♪ But I got wise ♪
♪ You're the devil in disguise ♪
♪ Oh, yes, you are ♪
♪ The devil in disguise ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ I thought
that I was in heaven ♪
♪ But I was sure surprised ♪
♪ Heaven help me ♪
♪ I didn't see the devil ♪
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ You look like an angel ♪
♪ Look like an angel ♪
♪ Walk like an angel ♪
♪ Talk like an angel ♪
♪ But I got wise ♪
♪ You're the devil in disguise ♪
♪ Oh, yes, you are ♪
♪ The devil in disguise. ♪
I'm going to the farmers market.
Wearing that?
Well, just because
I have to shop with the frumps
doesn't mean I have
to dress like them.
Can I get you anything?
Oh, yes, actually,
um, I could use
a hundred sleeping pills
to replace the ones
you took out of my dresser.
You noticed.
That was fast.
Yes, last year you
were angry with me
because I didn't take
enough pills to kill myself,
and now you won't
let me have any.
You need to choose a policy
and stick to it, my girl.
We have to fight this disease.
We can't give into it.
Have you really forgotten
how bad my last bout
of pneumonia was?
I wasn't sure I was
leaving the hospital.
But you did,
and now you're fine.
Darling, I'm not fine.
If my T cells were people,
I couldn't get up a bridge game,
so please, please
give me the pills back.
I already washed them
down the sink.
Well, then, you'll just force me
to do something more gruesome.
So, hang myself
or blow my brains out.
You choose.
So help me, if you do
anything disfiguring,
I will give you an
open-casket funeral
with no makeup and
fluorescent lighting.
Dear God,
I married the devil herself.
Oh, I know we won't be
together always,
but why subtract even a day
we could share?
Fine. Fine.
You win.
Actually, um, I'm going
to a birthday party
this afternoon.
Maybe you'd like to join me.
- It's for Jimmy Loftus.
- (gasps)
Oh, I'd love to see him again.
He's always a hoot.
How is he doing?
Well, I'm afraid he's
had a bit of a setback.
He's in the hospital.
Oh, no.
Yes, the party's
in his room.
If you come, I'm sure it
would lift his spirits.
Oh, I'd love to come.
I'm so glad.
ELI:
Oh, thank God.
- All right.
- Honey...
Come here, you.
Mmm.
- Ow. Ooh, my ribs.
- Oh.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- No, no. No, no.
Don't stop, don't stop.
I can take it.
(laughs)
(panting)
I thought you said Jade
took the dog when she left.
She did.
(clattering)
Hey.
(quietly):
- What are you doing here?
- I'm making dinner.
Oh.
Okay.
I think you need to leave.
I know things got a little funky
for a minute there,
but there's no reason
that we can't go back
to the way we were before.
Oh, I think there are
a lot of reasons.
- Yeah, Jade, please...
- Her name's not Jade.
Who cares?
Am I not allowed
to reinvent myself?
I mean, fuck.
Okay, you know what,
let's just all settle down.
You guys act like
everything that happened
is my fault; it's not.
I could have gone
to Europe,
but you begged me
to stay.
You pretended to love me,
and you promised that you would
always take care of me.
(voice breaking):
It's not fair.
You're right.
You're right,
it's not fair.
Okay, just stop.
I don't believe
one thing about you.
Least of all your tears.
I didn't pretend
to love you, I did.
But that's because I didn't know
who you really are.
You tried to trick us.
You played us, and you lost.
It's done.
Now get out.
I'll go...
but you have to pay me first.
You think you can shake us down?
- Honey.
- It costs money
to start over.
We're not aiding
and abetting a criminal.
You owe me.
Eli sold our script
for a million dollars.
Give me ten grand, and I'll go.
I'm not gonna pay you to leave.
I'm just gonna call the cops.
All right, you know what,
let's just hold on a second.
Okay? You know what
I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna go talk to her.
We're gonna work this out.
I mean, after all,
you've been through a lot,
but you're not a bad person.
Right? No, no, okay.
(whispers harshly):
How could you leave me alone
with that psychopath?
I can't find my fucking phone.
Where is it?
(smoke alarm beeping)
Smoke alarm.
She's burning down
the goddamn house.
(sighs)
Hey.
So what, exactly,
is Jimmy's prognosis?
Well, whatever it is,
this is a party,
so please try to smile.
Darling, I can smile
through anything.
Karl, Simone, you made it.
Hello, hello.
Oh, let us through,
we want to see
the birthday boy.
(monitor beeping steadily)
KEN:
Jimmy, look who's here.
It's Karl and Simone.
Happy birthday, Jimmy.
And you should see
what Simone is wearing.
I think it's Lagerfeld.
Uh, Karl, Simone,
I wanted you to meet Jimmy's mom
and his sister Terry.
They just got in
from Iowa.
It is so lovely
to meet you both.
I can't tell you how
comforting it's been
to find Jimmy here
surrounded by
such loving friends.
KEN: Oh, you ain't seen nothing
yet, honey.
I made my famous
carrot cake.
You are having
a piece, Mr. Jim,
even if they have to puree it
and drip it into your arm.
Can he hear us?
Of course he can.
Everyone's here now.
Time to sing.
Here we go.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday
to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Jimmy ♪
Excuse me.
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
I don't understand how
he got so sick so quickly.
This is the disease.
I've watched it happen
to Clive, to Harry,
to Alistair...
It's just horrifying.
You know, Jimmy
once told me
he was scared of
ending up like this.
Connected to tubes,
wasting away.
- But here he is.
- (gasps weakly)
You know what
I'm driving at.
You're not that sick.
Yet.
But we've seen my future.
I would rather choose life,
but life is...
...off the table.
The only thing
I can choose
is when to die and...
how.
I brought you here today
because I needed
you to understand.
Do you?
(sobs)
Thank you.
Rob.
You're home.
And starving.
Is dinner ready?
The day got away from me.
I had to order Chinese takeout.
But it's Thursday.
I was looking forward
to meatloaf.
If it helps, I made you
a shaker of martinis.
You could have a few
while we wait.
Now you're talkin'.
Thanks.
Hi.
Are you Taylor Harding?
Yeah. Wow, you got here fast.
Come on in.
Eli, the police are here.
Already?
I'm sorry, were you
expecting us?
Yeah, we reported
a break-in.
That was, like,
ten minutes ago.
We're not here about
any break-in.
We came to talk about
Duke Riley.
What about Duke?
You filed a police report
six weeks ago
accusing him of assault.
- Yes.
- And then four days ago,
you posted his bail.
I did. Why are you asking?
Duke Riley was murdered
yesterday.
His landlord found his body
in his apartment.
He had been repeatedly stabbed.
Do you have any idea
who might have done this?
I think we do.
Whoa, this'll be
my third one.
Oh, who's counting?
Mrs. Stanton, are you trying
to get me drunk?
I just wanted you
to be relaxed
so we could have
a little chat.
About what?
About the day our daughter died.
This will do it?
Yes, just the one dose.
And you won't feel any pain,
you'll just... sleep?
So I'm told.
Are you sure you don't
want Hector here?
No, no. We've, um,
we've said our goodbyes.
I-I mean,
he wanted to be here, but...
well, he's so bloody emotional.
The mere mention of my death, he
starts wailing like a car alarm.
Be nice. He loves you.
I know.
But to be honest, uh,
I just wanted it
to be the two of us.
You deserve to have
more than just me.
You should have a huge, glorious
party to send you off.
You are a glorious party,
all by yourself.
I knew that the first moment
I laid eyes on you.
You'll always be
the love of my life.
So, what happens now?
Well, uh, firstly, I...
I'd like you to change
into the red gown
I bought you in Venice.
(scoffs)
What's wrong with this one?
I prefer the red.
All right.
But this is the last time
I'll let you edit my wardrobe.
When you've changed,
come down to the living room.
I have a nice surprise for you.
I don't want
to talk about Emily.
Well, I do. I've been thinking
about that day a lot lately.
And I've remembered something.
What's that?
I absolutely locked the gate
after I brought in
the trash can.
Huh.
Well, you must not have.
How else did Emily
get out into the street?
Perhaps you could come up
with another explanation.
Think.
I'm not feeling well.
My darling.
You can't possibly imagine how
important this moment is to me.
Please.
Did anything happen that day
you haven't told me?
No.
Thank you.
For what?
You've made this all
so much easier.
Well, she's obviously dangerous.
You might want to think
about staying someplace
for a few days
until we locate her.
We'll check into
a hotel tonight.
FEMALE DETECTIVE: And we'll put a car
on the street outside until you leave.
Don't worry.
She won't get past us.
- Good night.
- TAYLOR: Night.
(exhales)
Okay, I was trying to be cool
in front of the detectives,
but oh, my God,
Jade killed Duke.
- I know. I know.
- Wait, do you think she's actually gonna come back here?
TAYLOR: We can't stick around
long enough to find out.
- What about the dog?
- We'll take it with us.
You feed her first,
I'll go start packing.
- Okay. All right. Come on, Teacup.
- Okay.
Mary, I'm home.
(sighs)
Bring me a beer!
And I want it
in a mug this time.
Mary?
MARY: Dearest Ralph.
I haven't been happy for quite some time.
But that's not why
I've decided to leave you.
I've met someone else.
A man who makes me happy.
So I'm leaving you
for Rob Stanton.
He loves me in a way
you never could.
Your ex-wife, Mary.
- (quietly): Shit.
- (drawer shuts)
(gun clicks)
(footsteps receeding)
(rings)
Aren't you gonna get that?
Must have been a wrong number.
Well, when's the Chinese food
getting here? I'm hungry.
I'm sure it'll arrive
any second.
(pounding on door)
See?
Wait.
Are you sure that's the delivery
guy? He sounds angry.
Who else could it be?
You are so beautiful.
Look who's talking.
Are you ready?
Not just yet.
Have you changed your mind?
No. No.
But I would love
just one more dance.
A tango?
What else?
ELI: Babe, what should I pack?
Just the essentials.
How is this essential?
Look, just 'cause
we're going into hiding
doesn't mean we can't look good.
Hey, have you seen my laptop?
I think it's downstairs.
Check the dining room table.
- Okay, I'll be right back.
- All right.
So it's true.
What are you doing here?
I won't be here long.
I just want to know why.
Now is not a good time.
You have to go.
What the hell?
I'm sorry, Rob.
Uh... honey, this is...
Don't bother lying. She knows
that we were having an affair.
- What?
- BETH ANN: Please.
- You have to go!
- You know how I always talk to you
about my friend Sheila?
This is Sheila.
(groans)
Uh, okay...
I came to the diner that day
to confront you.
But you were so nice. And you
said we could be friends.
Hold on.
You're friends with my mistress?
Fiancée.
Can we talk about this later?
What could you have
been thinking?
Oh, you're a fine one to talk.
You've been having
an affair for months.
You've been planning
on leaving me.
Oh, my God.
Do you even have cancer?
Cancer? You have cancer?
Well, this is just awkward.
(pounding on door)
♪ ♪
(clicks)
Hi there.
You must be Beth Ann?
You must be Simone.
Come in.
- It's nice to finally meet you.
- Likewise.
I have the keys
around here somewhere.
Let me look.
One of the reasons
I wanted to meet
was because I had a question.
It's a bit awkward.
What would you like to know?
The realtor told me
that someone was murdered
in this house?
It's true.
My husband was killed...
right where you're standing.
- Oh, dear.
- Our neighbor broke in
and accused Rob of
sleeping with his wife.
Shot him dead.
He was executed last year.
So sad.
Aunt Beth, I'm packed.
Can we go?
In a sec.
Elsie, this is Simone,
- the woman who bought our house.
- Hi, there.
You're so pretty.
She's your niece?
The daughter of my friend,
April Warner.
But I've been helping take care
of her since she was a baby.
April is a singer, you know.
My mom's gonna be on Broadway.
That's why we sold the house.
We're moving to New York.
Oh, how exciting.
Here are your keys.
I hope to have a very
happy life in this house.
A happy life
isn't hard to come by.
The trick is
to not regret the choices
you made along the way.
Yes.
Well...
good luck with everything.
Likewise.
Take care of my house.
I'll give it lots of love.
There you go.
Thank you.
I just know that we're
gonna love living here.
I certainly hope so.
So when did you
buy the house?
'74.
But after my husband died,
I rented the house out.
Then it was the headquarters
for my foundation.
I raise money for AIDS research.
Yeah, we've read up on you.
You've done such
amazing work.
I ended up living
a very rich life,
once I stopped worrying
about money.
Paulo, I'm ready.
Is that a Thomas J. Harte?
- Oh, you know his work?
- TAYLOR: Sure.
- Yeah, we saw a show of his at the Whitney last year.
- That's right, yeah.
Oh, isn't that wonderful?
I always hoped Tommy
would go far.
Tommy?
Is he a friend of yours?
A friend?
You could say that.
My face is tattooed on his ass.
Paulo, push.
(sighs) Well, it's been
lovely to meet you, Taylor.
And just know that
Andrew and I will
take wonderful care
of your home.
Aw, well, I hope
you'll enjoy it.
We will.
And I'm sorry for everything
that happened to you here.
Can't imagine what
you went through.
It was an awful night.
But it could have been worse.
So you really have
a rifle collection?
Yeah. They're all
in that box over there.
Hey, check this out.
This is me on safari
in Africa.
- Look at that.
- No way.
Well, I-I never knew there were
Jews that were into hunting.
We exist. But it's not
as cruel to the animals,
because we miss so frequently.
TAYLOR:
Oh, before I forget,
here are your keys.
Thank you.
So, what about
the two of you?
Found a new place to live?
- Uh, yeah. Well, actually...
- (phone buzzing)
...we're moving back
to our old condo.
After living in a mansion.
That is some serious downsizing.
Yeah. For us, it turns out...
Less is more.
Well, best of luck
to both of you.
- Thanks.
They seem like nice people.
Are you gonna miss the house?
It's just a building.
Home is where my family is.
Back to the hotel?
Yes. I'm ready
for my massage now.
(chuckles)
All right.
Condo, here we come.
It's gonna be nice.
Just the three of us.
(barks)
Honey?
(gunshot)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org