What time is the Minister
recording this broadcast?
Two p. m., Sir Humphrey.
Can't you stop him referring
to the Solihull project?
- There's not a hope.
- Oh, God.
"It's a shining example
of collaboration
between government
and industry".
- How could he think that?
- You told him itwas.
Can a 74 million
building project
in the middle of a city,
be swept underthe carpet?
- We'll use the Official Secrets
- A secret? It's so huge.
It's a big secret, Bernard.
But you can't use
the Official Secrets Act
with something
everybody knows about?
The Official Secrets Act is not
to protect secrets, but officials.
Why haven't you allowed me
to show
the Solihull Report to the
Minister, tell him the truth?
He hasn't asked.
Why bothera Minister
ifhe doesn'twant to know?
But how could he ask
ifhe doesn't know?
Quite so.
It's not that I'm questioning
yourjudgement but...
- But?
- But why?
Because, Bernard,
the Solihull Report contained
a paragraph casting doubt
on the financial soundness
of Michael Bradley
and Sloane Enterprises Ltd.
And the report's foresight had some
insight in the light ofhindsight?
What?
If it said that Michael Bradley
was going to go bust?
Please, Bernard,
watch your language.
The point is that, by the time
the Report came out, I was so...
orratherthe Department
was so committed to Bradley
that it seemed worth taking
the risk to see the project through.
If the Ministerknows
this partnerwas going bust,
he wouldn't make
a broadcast about it.
Ministers should neverknow
more than they need to know.
Then they can't tell anyone.
Like secret agents.
They could be captured
and tortured.
By terrorists?
By the BBC, Bernard.
The bank doesn't know
whetherornot to foreclose.
I'll dine with Sir Desmond
Glazebrook, theirChairman.
We might manage
to cook something up.
Why don't you go
to a restaurant?
Anyway, in the meantime,
come what may,
the Ministermust not refer
to the Solihull Project on the air.
Sir Humphrey,
this is a bit of a coverup, isn't it?
Certainly not.
It is responsible discretion
exercised in the national interest
to prevent unnecessary disclosure
of eminently justifiable procedures
in which untimely revelation could
severely impairpublic confidence.
Oh, I see.
It's like Watergate?
Bernard!
If you wish to leave the Service
and become a BBC interviewer,
- you have only to apply.
- I'm sorry, but...
Howwas Watergate
different exactly?
Watergate happened
in America, Bernard!
Oh yes, yes. I see.
- Good morning, Minister.
- Good morning.
Morning, Bernard.
Sorry I'm late.
Put them on the desk, George.
I don'twant to be late
at Broadcasting House.
What's the broadcast all about?
NATO, wasn't it?
No, partherships in industry.
Oh, yes. I knew
itwas something like that.
- Who else is in it?
- It's all in there.
An Employer
and a Trades Unionist.
Joe Morgan?
Wasn't he the TUC representative
on the Solihull project?
Er, Minister...
Yes, Humphrey?
You are not proposing to refer
to the Solihull project on the air?
Yes. It's a shining example
of cooperation
between the Government
and industry.
But I would be much happier
if itwere omitted.
Why?
Don't you think
it's ratherpremature?
Certainly not.
Building started months ago.
Exactly.
Ratherout of date, in fact.
Premature and out of date?
Well, untimely.
Would it be uninteresting
to the general public?
No. It's something
that's going on.
- Extremely interesting.
- Yes. Quite so.
So interesting
that there is a danger
that it might obscure
yourmain point, perhaps.
What is my main point?
Bernard, what's the Minister's
main point?
Private projects are more socially
responsible with government money,
and government projects are more
efficientwith private investment.
You see?
It underlines my main point.
You really are a wet blanket.
Just go about stirring up apathy.
Minister, I must seriously
advise you
with all the earnestness
at my command,
not to referto the Solihull Project
on the air.
Why?
- What?
- I said, why?
- Why?
Well, Minister...
Are you planning to take
the credit forthis yourself?
At the European Convention
of Government administration.
Yourspeech will make
very good reading.
Well, a fewfacts of life.
Politicians are responsible
ultimately to the people,
and we get the credit.
Not Civil Servants.
I would be happyforyou to have
the "credit" forthis project.
But, I must beg, beseech
and implore you not today.
No, it's no good.
I'm not going to fall for it.
I'm going to get
all the political capital of this.
I know a good thing
when I see one.
- Please, do listen to...
- No. No. No.
- Minister, p...
- No,
Humpy.
- What?
If it had been up to me,
I'd help out like a shot.
Quite so.
It's not the bank's fault
if some idiot Minister
gets into bed with a kid,
who runs with the money.
That Ministerwasn't
entirely to blame.
There were extenuating
circumstances.
This Bradley chap looked
very sound at the time.
But you wouldn't have done
a damn fool thing like that.
Would you?
When it looked like Bradley
wanted a loan thatwas one thing.
But nowhe can't pay his bills.
Well, he is unlikely
to fulfil his financial undertakings
to Her Majesty's Government.
Can't pay his bills, you mean.
And Her Majesty's Government's
undertakings go down with him.
Yes.
Unless a reputable bank were
to take overthe contract
from Bradley with a view
to participating in a project
which Her Majesty's Government
is determined to make profitable.
Quite so.
More Sancerre
for Her Majesty's Government?
Well, like I say,
it's up to my Board.
Could go eitherway,
quite frankly.
- Could go eitherway.
- I see.
Incidentally, to change
the subject completely,
you rememberthe new
Ministry Copartnership
Commission you mentioned?
Indeed.
The Chairmanship
hasn't been filled yet?
- Not yet, Desmond.
- Because if itwere to be...
should one be offered...
not forthe money,
I mean, what's 8,000 a year?
160 a week. Part time.
Quite.
But itwould be a fascinating...
Has anything been decided,
informally?
You're looking around
fora couple of quangos,
and I can tell you,
in complete confidence,
that yourname is
on the shortlist.
On the shortlist?
Quangos can't suddenly
be in short supply, can they?
There's report
in today's Telegraph.
"The Quango Jungle:
There are still around 8,000
paid appointments
within the gift of Ministers
to Quasi Autonomous NGOs,
- at five million pounds a year".
- You'll have two orthree spare.
There's certainly
a lot of them around,
the point is finding
one that is appropriate.
There has to be some reason
to appoint you.
What about the Advisory Committee
of Dental Establishments?
- Know anything about teeth?
- I'm a banker.
And that rules out
the Milk Marketing Board, too.
Right.
How about the Dumping
at Sea Representations Panel?
- Do you live nearthe sea?
- Knightsbridge.
Just behind Harrods.
Not nearenough.
That more or less rules out the
Clyde River Purification Board too.
- Rump steak?
- That's forme.
Meat Marketing Board.
Know anything about meat?
I eat it.
Not enough.
It rules out the Meat
and Liverstock Commission.
- Doversole. Sir?
- White Fish Authority?
Potatoes?
Potato Marketing Board?
The Governors of the National
Vegetable Research Station?
The National Biological
Standards Board?
Is that my salad.
Thank you, Robert.
The Arable Crops
and Forage Board?
The Food and Drink
Training Board?
Some French mustard, please?
What about the Food Additives
and Contaminants committee?
I know very little
about any of those.
- Well, what do you know about?
- Nothing.
Nothing really.
I'm a banker.
This is not easy.
The Fire Services
Examinations Board?
St. John's Ambulance?
- French mustard, sir.
- Thank you.
What about the Plant Varieties
and Seeds Tribunal?
Dammit, Humphrey, I'm a banker.
Thank you.
There must be some minority
group that you can represent.
Bankers.
You see, the ideal quango
appointee is a black, Welsh,
disabled woman Trade Unionist.
We're all looking
around forone of them.
- You don't happen to know any?
- No.
No. Well...
It all boils down to the Industry
Copartnership Commission.
I'd find that quite acceptable.
Well, it is within the gift
of my Minister.
And you need only put
in appearances twice a month.
Lots of papers?
Yes, but itwouldn't be awfully
necessary to read them.
I wouldn't have anything to say
at the meetings.
Splendid. You're just the chap
I'm looking for.
Broadcasting House, please.
Sorry to keep you, George.
When you drop me, please
take Mr. Wooly on to the House.
Why Humphrey wants to stop me
mentioning
the Solihull Project on the air?
Didn't you think he gave
6 or 7 convincing reasons?
No. Did you?
I think he knows
what he's doing.
Sure he does.
I only wish I knew
what he was doing.
I'm sure if Sir Humphrey
advises something, then,
whateverhe does advise
is advisable.
- What do you advise?
- It's not forme to advise,
but I would advise you
that you would be
well advised to follow
Sir Humphrey's advice.
Why?
Well, it's just that...
certain projects have
certain aspects which,
with sensitive handling,
given reasonable discretion,
when events permit,
there is no prima facie reason why,
with appropriate give and take,
if if all goes well,
in the fullness of time,
when the moment is ripe, er...
You're blathering.
- Yes, Minister.
- Why are you blathering?
It's my job, Minister.
An example of this
is going on up in Solihull now.
Government money
and private investment
working together
in a real partnership.
Claptrap.
And it's symbolic of the way
this Government is working.
I've taken a personal interest
in the Solihull Project because...
Not justwords, it is actually there
in bricks and mortar.
A concrete example,
if I may put it like that,
of the fact that ourprinciples
really work.
Thank you, Minister.
One lastword, Mr. Conway?
There's nothing wrong
with the principle of partnership...
Provided
that there's no interference
in management decisions
from the State orthe workforce.
Thank you, Mr. Conway.
Joe Morgan?
Dear, oh dear, oh dear.
We all know
that Mr. Conway is talking
out of date capitalist claptrap.
If partnership is to mean
anything, it must mean
an equal partnership between
unions, government and industry.
- In that order.
- Afinal word, Minister?
- There's no need to be offensive.
- Gentlemen, please.
We're all in agreement.
We've shown
that if we can work together
we can forge a new Britain.
And it's a pleasure to talk
to two of the principal forgers...
principal participants.
Thank you.
James Hacker, Minister
forAdministrative Affairs,
was talking with George Conway,
from the Construction Federation,
and Joe Morgan, from the Commercial
and Administrative Workers Union.
Splendid. Thank you all.
Jean will take you to Hospitality.
- Was it really all right?
- First class.
Most interesting, Minister.
Can we edit that awful Hacker
waffle down to two and a half?
Leave the Solihull bit.
- Joe, see you later.
- Yes, George.
I hope you won't mind
my mentioning it,
Mr. Harker, but could
you put a word in
formy members' claim for
a special Birmingham allowance?
I don't think I can conduct Trade
Union negotiations in a BBC studio.
And that's a matter
forthe Employment...
- But a word from you...
- No, I'm sorry.
We'd have a Manchesterallowance,
Plymouth allowance,
Chipping Sodbury allowance...
Afterthis broadcast people might
ask about the Solihull project,
wanting to knowmore about it.
I hope they do.
But as we know, there are
some things betternot found out.
I'm sure we understand
one another.
Do we?
Something in youreye?
- Just a gleam.
- What?
Oh, come off it, Hacker.
We've got you
by the short and curlies.
And I'm asking
10 % below London allowance,
and we'll settle for 30 % below.
Give you the credit
forbeating us down.
No allowance. You'd better
resign youself to that.
I'm not the one
who will have to resign.
- What are you talking about?
- The Solihull Project.
I could hardly believe
you took all the credit for it.
Great courage, of course,
but whateverpossessed you?
"Cannons to the right ofhim,
Cannons to the left ofhim,
Into the Valley of death
rode Mr. Hacker".
How did it go, sir?
Oh, very well. Very well.
I was talking about government
industry cooperation.
There's a very interesting project
in the Midlands.
I don't suppose you'd have heard
about it, but it's very interesting
if you know the background.
You don't mean
the Solihull Project, sir?
Yes. You have heard about it.
- What are you laughing about?
- Nothing, sir.
- What have you heard?
- Nothing really, sir.
It's a shining example
of collaboration
between government
and industry.
What do you know about all this?
37 journeys between the Ministry
and Mr. Michael Bradley's office,
44 Farringdon Street, and
129 Birmingham Road, Solihull.
37 journeys? Who with?
Yourpredecessor, sir,
and Sir Humphrey, mostly.
Very cheerful they were,
on the first few trips.
They kept talking about
shining examples
of successful collaboration
and such like.
Then the gloom started
to come down.
- Gloom?
- Well, no not gloom.
More like desperation, really.
Desperation?
What about?
You know the background, sir.
Well, yes, yes...
Any bit of the background
you were thinking of?
No. When something's fishy,
it's just fishy, isn't it?
You don't knowwhich bit
the smell's coming from.
- Fishy?
- Well, I don't really know.
Forall I know,
Mr. Bradley may be quite kosher,
despite everything
Sir Humphrey said about him.
You knowmore about all that
than I do.
I'm just the driver.
Quite. Quite.
I'm just the Minister.
An allowance for Morgan's union
is out of the question.
But howwas the broadcast?
Well, all right, I think.
You think?
I talked
about the Solihull Project.
And then I had second thoughts.
Any particularreason?
No... Humphrey, is everything all
right about the Solihull Project?
Yes, Minister.
The building works
proceed satisfactorily.
No, no, no,
that's not what I meant.
- Is something going on?
- Building is going on.
No, no, Humphrey.
Something's up, isn't it?
- Yes indeed, Minister.
- What?
The 1st floor is up,
and the 2nd flooralmost up.
I'm talking about the whole basis
of the thing.
Oh, I see.
- What can you tell me about?
- As I understand it...
The basis is an aggregate
of gravel and cement on
six feet ofbest builders rubble.
You know I am talking
about the finance.
Ourcontractwith the construction
company you mean?
The stage payments are
in accordance with all the usual...
Humphrey!
What is it that I don't know?
- What precisely do you mean?
- I don't know.
That's just it, I don't know
because I can't find
what questions to ask you,
and I don't knowwhat to ask you
because I don't know.
What is it that I don't know?
Minister, I don't know
what you don't know.
It could be almost anything.
- Your're keeping something from me.
- Yes indeed.
It is the Department's duty
to protect the Minister
from the great tide
of irrelevant information
that beats against the walls
of this Department.
There is something
about the Solihull Project
that I know I don't know
and I know you know.
I know Bernard knows.
Joe Morgan knows.
My own driverknows
more than I do.
Only poorJoe Soap who has
to tell the public about it
hasn't got a clue
as to what's going on.
Will you answer
a simple question?
Certainly, Minister.
What is it?
I don't know!
If you tell me, I'll ask it!
Well...
- Yes, Frank?
- Ourmeeting.
- About my quango paper.
- Come on in.
- You've read Frank's paper?
- Yes indeed, Minister.
What did you think about ending
the ministerial patronage?
All those thousands
of jobs forthe boys.
Most original and imaginative.
You liked it?
Those are two of Humphrey's
most damning criticisms.
Itwould be a very popular
political move.
Hand the quango appointments
overto Parliament.
The best men forthe job instead
of old chums, partyhacks.
It should be legislated.
- It is a novel proposal...
- That's the otherkiller.
But when a system
is working smoothly...
Smoothly! Look at this!
Proposal forChairman
of the new Industrial
Coparthership Commission,
Sir Desmond Glazebrook,
I ask you!
He's neverbeen in industry,
and he's said unpleasant things
about this government.
Is that a smoothly
operating system?
- He would be an excellent...
- He's a blithering idiot!
- Yes, but an excellent Chairman.
- I'm sorry, Humphrey.
I am not going to appoint
Sir Desmond Glazebrook.
- Minister, you must.
- No, no, no...
- Please, Minister...
- No way. No Glazebrook.
Overmy dead body. Right?
Minister, before you make
yourfinal decision
I think perhaps you ought
to see this.
"Report on the Solihull Project".
Why is it top secret?
"7.5 million pounds...
probably bankrupt proceedings...
inminent collapse of project"...
well...
Imminent collapse of project!
Why didn't you tell me?
I am conscious of the heavy
burdens of youroffice.
But this'll be
all overthe front pages.
It's a public scandal,
a disaster. It's...
- It's appalling...
- Jim.
It is dated before the election.
You're in the clear.
Yes, but unfortunately
underthe convention
of Ministerial responsability,
the blame must fall...
- Everyone will know itwasn't Jim.
- Quite so.
The principle of democratic
accountability requires
the occasional human sacrifice.
When the pack
is baying forblood...
- Isn't that right?
- He'll point to the dates...
Oh, a lesserman might try
to wriggle out of it.
But there is only
one honourable course open.
As the Minister is well aware.
Frank might have a point?
Only today you have publicly
identified yourself
with the success of the project.
The broadcast!
When's it going out?
It's due fortransmission
about now.
Get on to the BBC at once.
- Stop it!
- Stop what? Oh yes...
I wish you luck but you know
what the BBC are like.
This is a crisis,
this is a scandal...
If you were to put it like that,
they might...
- Might what?
- Move it to peak listening time.
Any luck?
Aperfect example of what can be
done is going on up in Solihull.
Government money and private
investment in real partnership
to me, symbolic of everything
this Government is working for.
I've taken a great personal
interest in the Solihull project.
It's not just words, it's actually
there in bricks and mortar...
"Symbolic of everything
this Government is working for".
How could you let me say
all those things?
Minister, I can only advise.
I did advise.
I advised most strongly.
But when the adviser's advice
is unheeded...
All right, all right.
Advise me now.
Certainly, Minister.
It is possible that the bank
may take over
the contract from Bradley
and Sloane Enterprises Ltd.
And all will be well.
- The bank! Fine! Well...
- The bank, however, is hesitant.
But it so happens that
the Director in charge
is to retire next year
and he's anxious
to find anotherappointment...
a chairmanship of a quango,
for instance.
Give him one!
Give him that one you were
reserving forthat idiot
Sir Desmond Glazebrook.
Who is the Director?
Desmond Glazebrook.
He's not a bad chap, really.
He's always attacking
the government.
It does us good sometimes
to appoint ouropponents.
It's democratic, statesmanlike.
Yes, that's
a very good appointment.
- But you can't.
- Do shut up, Frank!
Anybody else know about this?
Apart from ourselves
and the bank and Michael Bradley,
the Union representative.
Joe Morgan!
Of course.
That's whatwas behind his special
Birmingham allowance claim.
- Blackmail.
- Quite so, Minister.
Humphrey, I've been thinking.
Desmond Glazebrook
will need some support.
A Deputy Chairman,
someone with real
experience of Industry.
An excellent thought.
Is there anyone you could
advise me would be appropriate?
ATrade Unionist, forexample?
What about Joe Morgan,
Minister?
Joe Morgan!
What an excellent idea.
Well done.
It takes two to quango, Minister.
Get on to them both immediately.
This is what's wrong
with the system!
It's jobs forthe boys,
quid pro quo corruption.
What about my quango
abolition paper?
Very good, Frank.
Original and imaginative.
- Novel.
I'm serious about it.
What are you going to do?
You're not going to suppress it.
I'll get it adopted as party policy.
If the Press were
to get hold of this...
Yes, if the Press
were to get hold of this.
- What a story!
- Frank, I've been wondering.
Have you everthought
of serving on a quango?
You're not corrupting me.
No, no, of course not.
But perhaps
betterthan abolishing
the entire system
would be to make itwork.
Humphrey and I were thinking,
if we were to set up
a special commission
to investigate and report
on the composition
and activities of all quangos,
that might be the answer.
The answer!
Itwould have to be very senior,
mostly Privy Councillors.
But itwould need too
some very able people
who have studied quangos
and knew the abuses
of the system.
And in the light
of yourknowledge and concern,
Humphrey suggested yourname.
- Didn't you, Humphrey?
- Mr. Weisel, I said.
You're not going to change
my opinions.
- There is such a thing as integrity.
- Of course.
Youropinions and your integrity
would make you
such a valuable member
of this quango.
Mind you,
itwould be very hard work.
Service to this SuperQuango
would involve you
in some very arduous
foreign travel,
to see how these matters
are managed
in other important
government centres.
Japan, Australia,
California,
the West Indies...
- Tahiti...
- Tahiti.
Yes, thatwould be fairly arduous.
Dreadful. Dreadful.
But serving the public's what
it's all about, isn't it?
- Absolutely...
- Serving the public.
Serving the public.
And my quango paper?
Invaluable, take itwith you.
I'll keep a copy,
if I may, on the files.
With the Solihull Report.
Yes, Minister.