♪ We face the music together ♪
♪ And throw our hats
in the ring ♪
♪ Facing all kinds of weather ♪
♪ And not afraid of anything ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When the sun comes up,
we'll be on our way ♪
♪ And we don't care
where we land ♪
♪ And the waves are high,
but we won't turn round ♪
♪ 'Cause your hand
is in my hand ♪
♪ And, oh-oh ♪
♪ You make me feel invincible ♪
♪ 'Cause it's you and me ♪
♪ Through the wind and hail ♪
♪ Setting sail into the world. ♪
♪ ♪
[doorbell buzzes]
[Margot sniffles]
RADIO HOST:
Beautiful day out there,
but there is
a thunderstorm forecast
for later this afternoon.
So if you are going out,
remember to bring an umbrella.
Here's Schubert's
"Serenade No. 4"
from theSwan Songs.
♪ ♪
[buzzes]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [sniffles]
[sighs]
- Hi, Mom.
- Hey.
Did you sleep?
A little.
It's 11:30.
[sighs]
I know.
I'll put on some coffee.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[exhales, sniffs]
MARGOT:
Poor guy.
- Who?
- Him.
I noticed him at the start.
JANICE:
I'll bet you did.
No.
I mean, I noticed
that he went out too fast.
Well, he's paying for it now.
He looks done.
MARGOT: Maybe he just needs
a bit of encouragement.
Come on, buddy. You can do it.
Hmm. I'm getting worried.
Do you think it's possible
that something
could have happened to him?
Well, surely
someone would have noticed.
I'd be very disappointed
if he died
before I had the chance
to ask him out.
Don't even joke
about that, Margot.
- I'm not.
- PARAMEDIC 1: Go on, Ken.
PARAMEDIC 2:
You got this.
[breathless]:
Thanks...
for the escort, fellas.
Sorry for keeping you so late.
PARAMEDIC 1:
But seriously, Ken, uh, golf...
is really gonna be your thing.
- [chuckles]
- Don't listen to him, man.
- Get a massage.
- MARGOT: Whoo-hoo!
[both chuckling]
Well, that was humiliating.
Not at all. It's just a fun run.
That was the opposite of fun.
[panting]
They were... genuinely worried
they were gonna
have to break out
- the defibrillator.
- Don't be silly.
Oh, no. Oh, they kept asking...
if they could...
drive me the last bit. I said,
"No. I'm gonna
complete the course."
Good for you.
[panting]
How come you're still here?
You must've finished ages ago.
We're just, um, warming down.
I love a good long warm-down.
Huh, smart.
[exhales]
Were you jogging on your own?
Or you have a buddy?
Oh, on my own.
Maybe you'd like
to think about joining our club.
Oh, well...
I-I think... I'd enjoy that.
- Yeah, thanks. [panting]
- [Margot chuckling]
CHRIS:
Do you mind if I open a window?
It's like a sweatbox in here.
Oh, sure.
Ken likes the thermostat way up.
His blood runs
a little colder than mine.
Have you decided
what you're wearing?
Uh, well, there should be
a black pantsuit
in the... dry cleaning bag
in the closet.
Got you.
Shoes?
I'll pick them.
- I got it.
- Oh, thank you.
[sighs] I'll leave you
to get ready.
♪ ♪
[laughs]
- Are you okay?
- No pain, no gain.
That's right. No guts, no glory.
- [chuckles]
- You're doing great today.
Oh, I'm using a pacemaker.
Really? The heart kind?
No, no. The people kind.
Uh, I pick a runner
doing a nice gentle pace,
fall in behind
and they tow me along.
[chuckles]
Now when you say "they,"
do you really mean "she"?
[stammers]
No, th-that makes me sound...
- Sleazy?
- [laughs]
I was gonna say superficial.
- I was teasing you.
- [chuckles]
It could be argued,
though, that...
the only thing that motivates
men to do anything
- is chasing women.
- Oh, is that true?
Are you like that?
Well, uh...
I was, I suspect.
Till I met my Betty.
When did she die?
If you don't mind my asking you.
Six years ago.
- Cancer.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
I was lucky.
We were married 36 years.
Ken, um...
it's obvious that you
loved your Betty very much,
and I have great respect
for your marriage,
but I think you may have room
in your heart for me, too,
or someone like me.
I don't know anyone like you.
Six years sounds
like a lot, but...
I'm more tortoise than hare.
Well, maybe if I slowed down,
you wouldn't have to chase me.
We could run at our own pace.
Well, could you though?
I was able to get someone
to cover at work, by the way,
so I can stay on a few days.
Middle of next week, at least.
Then it's gonna
start getting tricky.
I'm glad. Thank you for that.
KENJI: Are you gonna run the
10K in Newport next week?
MARGOT:
I was planning on it, yes.
Would you like to go together?
That-that would be nice.
I mean, not just
as jogging buddies.
Okay.
W-What I mean is,
if I made a reservation
for a room with one bed,
would that be okay?
That would be lovely.
♪ ♪
Oh, Ken.
Ooh.
Oh!
You didn't have to do all this.
You realize I won't ever want
to travel separately again.
That's fine,
'cause I don't either.
Oh, I got that.
- Hey!
- [chuckles]
Ah, no going back now.
No going back.
Hi. [chuckles]
Oh, God, are we becoming
like one of those really
self-satisfied couples
that you see in ads for
insurance or walk-in bathtubs?
Is that what you're afraid of?
No, what? No. It's...
what I want. [chuckles]
I mean, is anybody in life
really happy like that?
We are, right now.
We're that happy.
I am, anyway.
[chuckles]
FUNERAL DIRECTOR:
I will now call on Margot
to share a few personal memories
of Kenji.
[sighs]
The last time
that we were all
together like this
was our joint
140th birthday party
when we announced
our engagement.
I'm sorry now that we didn't
have a bigger wedding reception,
but I suppose I imagined
we would have
many opportunities.
Ken was not so certain of that.
I remember him saying once
that at our age,
"until death do us part"
didn't seem like
such a big commitment.
[light laughter]
Old love is different.
More realistic maybe.
Um, when Ken and I met,
we had already been through
many ups and downs in life,
and we had learned
how to compromise,
and we had survived
loss and mistakes.
And somehow we felt
if this relationship failed,
we would survive this, too.
I'm not so sure
about that anymore.
Old love
is different,
yet it is also the same
because Ken and I did everything
that young people do.
We fell in love, we traveled,
we remodeled a house together,
we planted a garden,
I finished a memoir,
he called me "sweetheart."
And on nights when we
were out in company,
all I had to do was glance
across the room,
and he'd intuit that
it was time for him
to take me home where we could
sit on the rim of the bathtub
and floss our teeth
and gossip about the evening.
Every time we passed each other
in the house, Ken made a point
of stopping to kiss me
or squeeze my shoulder
or stroke my hand.
I never had that
in my life before,
and sometimes it irked me,
but now I think it's the thing
that I will miss the most.
He and I often told each other,
"We are so lucky,"
and we were.
Young love,
even for old people,
can be surprisingly bountiful.
Many of you know that Ken and
I met when we were running.
The geriatric Olympics,
he called it.
You know, in the beginning,
I chased him
and then he chased me,
and finally we found a way
to run in lockstep.
And the tough uphill bits,
the bits with illnesses
and setbacks,
went a little easier,
and the pleasant downhill parts
were that much more joyful.
And now Ken has...
run the course.
I just, um... I don't know
how I'm going
to manage, frankly.
Right now it feels like
a bit of a slog.
But wherever he is,
and however long it takes,
I hope he'll wait for me.
RINA: Are you going to
join us for some food?
We'd love you to come.
WOMAN:
I wouldn't miss it.
RINA:
Great. I'll see you there.
Mom, the car's ready.
I think that I'm going to walk.
- You sure?
- I need some air.
At least take an umbrella.
I think it might rain.
Don't fuss, Chris.
I'll be fine.
- Do you want some company?
- No, thank you, Janice.
I'll see you in a bit.
[distant siren wailing]
[horns honking]
[both laughing]
♪ ♪
[panting]
Just tell them
you changed your mind.
I haven't changed my mind.
I'm just... just not sure.
I mean, I get it.
Two gay men bringing up a baby.
It's some pretty wacky stuff
right there.
It's not that, you fucking rube.
It's just... I just want
to make sure
they're gonna stay together.
Why?
My dad left when I was three.
You never saw yours.
Seems like everyone
on the street
basically raised themselves.
I just... I just want a couple
that's gonna stay together
for a while.
How can anyone guarantee
something like that?
Look... you go on up.
If you get spooked,
I'll be here.
You don't have to do this.
- You got lots of options.
- Like what?
Hell, I'll help you
raise the little guy.
We can live right here
in the van.
- Don't go anywhere.
- I will not.
Homer. Homer, this way.
- Hey.
Welcome.
Oh, both of you!
- [chuckles]
- Hey.
Three of you!
I've turned Tobin's study
into a baby room,
and I've painted it half blue,
half pink, you know,
covering both bases.
Not that we want to impose
our gender stereotypes,
- God forbid. [chuckles]
- Let me ask you a question.
TOBIN:
Oh, great. Yup. Go.
- Baby quiz, you ready? Yeah.
- Baby quiz.
Yeah, that's true.
You're hearing it right.
- ANDY: Yeah.
- TOBIN: It's a fun thing.
ANDY: I'm asking a question.
So, what does it mean
when the baby's poo is green?
- TOBIN: I don't know.
- What do you mean, "pass"?
- Pass. I don't know.
- Means the baby is sick.
- TOBIN: Why don't we just...
- [whistles]
ANDY:
You want us to just find out...
[engine starting]
So where's my room?
[thunder rumbling]
♪ ♪
Hey! Hey!
Guzmin!
What are you doing here?
Are you following me?
No. Not in that way.
You left without an umbrella.
I told you the whole week
it's going to rain.
It's not going to rain. Okay?
'Cause my phone says
it's passing.
I am doorman.
I never get weather wrong.
Well, I hope that you are
not here to lecture me
on what it is you think
I should do. Okay?
'Cause I was just meeting
with someone in there,
um... to talk.
I was just talking.
I actually...
No. I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna sit here
and defend myself.
Um, I was discussing my options,
because I dohave options,
and I am allowed
to change my mind,
and I don't have to do anything
that you say.
Or that my parents say,
or that anyone else says.
I promise you I am here
for no reason.
You do whatever you need to do.
Nothing will change me.
Or any people
who really love you.
I'm just here with the umbrella.
[crying]:
Did you say you loved me?
I said it is going to rain.
And it isgoing to rain.
Whatever you decide to do,
you'll need your strength.
And you will not need a cold.
Yeah. [chuckles]
Well, it's not going
to rain, actually.
Guzmin, okay, I don't know
how many times...
- Oh, my God...
- [umbrella opens]
[chuckles]
[mouths]
♪ I happen to like
New York... ♪
[applause]
[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ I like to drink of it ♪
♪ The more I know New York,
the more I think of it... ♪
- Oh, my gosh!
- [laughs]
- Oh, no.
- It's so good to see you.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh...
Oh, my gosh, and you, too.
- This is...
- I have so much to tell you.
- You do?
- Yeah.
What?
Emma and I got
back together again.
No.
[laughs]:
That is fantastic.
Are you kidding?
Who-who-who is Emma?
- I wrote a piece a-about him a while back.
- Yeah.
- It's a long story. I'll tell you about it.
- And then, she-she,
- she read your piece and we...
- She did?
- We met up, and...
- Oh, my gosh.
Thank you so much.
Thank you. Uh, because...
- [laughs]: I-I have you to thank for this.
- No... my app?
- Yes.
- You're using my app?
- Yeah, yeah. [laughs]
- See?
And you're, you're gorgeous.
- Jesus.
- I know.
- That's amazing. Look after this one.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Anyway, look,
I-I don't want to interrupt,
so I just... you know.
- I'll e-mail you.
- Want you to meet Emma.
- Oh...
- And-and rate my app, all right?
- All right. Goodbye. Bye.
- Yeah.
♪ I don't want
to go to heaven... ♪
- Catch you next time.
- Bye.
[laughs] Oh.
[indistinct chatter]
- [thunder rumbles]
- ♪ I happen to love ♪
♪ New York. ♪
[cheering, applause]
[clears throat]
Yes.
Rain. Of course.
[whoops]
[chuckles]
I love these summer storms.
It's like, uh, all the heat
and the tension of the city
builds up and has
to be discharged, huh?
Uh-huh.
You're a pretty chatty guy, huh?
Honestly, it's very nice
that you're confident enough
to talk to a complete stranger,
but right now,
I'm just sort of happy
to stand here
and stare out at the rain.
Is that okay?
Are you usually
this misanthropic?
Actually, no.
I've just been stood up
by someone
who I really thought
might lead to something.
And I don't mind
if it's after a first date
or something, you know,
you meet someone
and they're not for you,
but... without meeting you?
You don't even have a chance
to make an impression.
I'm sorry that I'm not
more magnanimous
and big-hearted right now.
- Have a nice day.
- Uh, wait.
Look, I can't imagine what you
just said feels like.
I've literally never had anyone
not go on a date with me.
No kidding.
But I'm thinking,
like my mother used to say,
whenever anything bad happens,
you should try
and recalibrate the universe
or whatever you want to call it
with its opposite.
Right. Universe, recalibration.
- Got it.
- Wait, w-wait.
If somebody cuts you off
in traffic,
you just are extra generous
with the next person
who wants to get out.
If somebody steals your wallet,
you go to the poor box
and make a donation.
You've just been stood up.
You feel like shit, right?
What if life gives you
another date?
Right now?
♪ And it's alive ♪
♪ And it's waiting for them ♪
Are you for real?
♪ At the lost and found ♪
♪ Blood-orange sky ♪
♪ Red taillights on the river ♪
♪ Ten stories high ♪
♪ Some things
don't last forever ♪
♪ She was July ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ He fell like leaves
around her ♪
[thunder rumbles]
♪ But they made
a storm together ♪
♪ Yes, there's a light... ♪
Shit.
Want to keep going?
♪ Once it dies... ♪
Yeah. Your serve.
♪ Oh, and it's alive ♪
- ♪ And it's waiting for them ♪
- [laughs]: Wow.
♪ At the lost ♪
♪ And found ♪
♪ At the lost and found ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh♪
♪ There's a light ♪
♪ You never get back
once it dies ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ And it's alive ♪
♪ And it's waiting for us ♪
♪ At the lost and found ♪
♪ Yeah, at the lost and found ♪
♪ There's a light
shining all night ♪
♪ Open every hour
of every day ♪
♪ There's a sign lighting up
your way ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ In every city,
every small town ♪
♪ There's a heart waiting
to be taken down ♪
♪ Try it on, try it out ♪
♪ Don't wait another minute ♪
♪ No, don't hang around ♪
♪ 'Cause we're the lost
and found. ♪