My brothers and I
are the first vampires.
In all of history...
The Originals.
300 years ago,
we helped build New Orleans.
Now we've returned
to find a city at war.
The vampire Marcel leads an army
against a coven
of desperate witches.
My brother Klaus
is playing against both sides,
hungry for power
and hoping to protect
the werewolf carrying his child,
but Marcel has an advantage.
He holds our brother
Elijah captive
with the aid of a secret weapon.
Now in order to get back
the brother I love,
I have no choice but to side
with the one I cannot trust.
August 1359.
I have noticed a difference
in my siblings.
Our bond strains beneath
the pressure
of our life as vampires.
Each day removes them further
from the humanity
they once possessed.
My sweet sister Rebekah
has grown quite indifferent
to brutality.
However, the true problem
remains by brother Niklaus.
He continues to hide
his loneliness with cruelty.
Still, I cling to the hope
that I, as their eldest brother,
can lead them
down the correct path,
a path charged with the power
of a family united...
For if I fail,
our family's legacy will end
in darkness.
I cannot
believe you disposed
of those vampires
without me.
You know how I love
to set things on fire.
Was I supposed
to leave them
in the front yard
to rot?
Besides, they were
my responsibility.
They attacked the helpless,
pregnant girl
who's carrying
my child.
Oh, I am so moved
by your newfound sense
of fatherly duty
towards the werewolf
carrying
your hybrid bun
in her oven.
Ha!
The werewolf would like
to know what the plan is.
Well, that depends
what plan you mean, luv...
My plan
for global domination
or Rebekah's plan to find love
in a cruel, cruel world.
Hmm.
The plan
to rescue Elijah,
you know...
The good brother,
the one who is now
in the possession
of your mortal enemy
after you stabbed him
in the back.
In the front,
if we're being specific.
You two said that
you would get him back.
So is there
a plan, or what?
Ok.
Well, firstly, Marcel
is not my mortal enemy.
He's my friend,
albeit one
who is unaware that I
am trying to sabotage
his hold over
the supernatural community
of the French quarter,
but a friend nonetheless,
and secondly,
I daggered Elijah
in order to gain
Marcel's trust.
If I had known he would
place my brother
in the hands of a particularly
nasty teenage witch,
I certainly would have
weighed my options
a bit differently,
and thirdly, sister, please.
And thirdly, the plan,
as you have demanded,
is for Niklaus to
simply asks Marcel
for Elijah back.
That's not
the whole plan, is it?
Oh, please.
Klaus may be
a miserable excuse
for a sibling,
but there is none
more diabolical.
That's only
the plan "a," luv.
There's always
a plan "B."
And what's
plan "B"?
War.
♪ Well,
I'm a long way from home ♪
♪ With some pressure
all my own ♪
♪ Such a long way from home ♪
♪ But I'll be back soon
♪ Yeah
Damn, I do look good
in a suit.
Joshua Rosen, 18,
had recently arrived
in New Orleans as part of...
My guy and the docks
is gonna come forward
as an eyewitness,
say he saw those two
drunkenly fall
into the Mississippi.
They'll be dredging
for weeks.
No one will come
looking around here.
That's good,
considering one
is dead in a dumpster
behind the county morgue
and the other one
is a vampire now.
Anything else?
Ow!
Allow me, darling.
One thing.
I sent 4 nightwalkers
to look into
a werewolf sighting
in the quarter.
I haven't heard
from them since.
That makes 10 dead
nightwalkers
in the last week.
You think the werewolves
are back in town
trying to start
some trouble?
Look. I know you
and Klaus are friends,
but the fact is, since
the Originals showed up...
Oh, come now,
Thierry.
You're not still upset
about that little,
toxic werewolf bite
I gave you, are you?
I thought we
were at by
I see you've given him free rein
of your compound now, too.
Yes. Well, seeing
as my family and I
lived here, built
the place, in fact...
All right.
Come on.
You both
know the drill.
Thierry is my guy,
inner circle.
Klaus is my old-time
friend and sire.
He's also
a guest here.
Peace, all right?
All right?
What you need,
my brother?
I'm afraid my sister
Rebekah is insisting
I demand
Elijah's return.
She's quite worked up
about it.
I'll say.
We're not gonna have 3 Originals
walking around town, are we?
Half our guys think the sister
killed the nightwalkers.
Is that an accusation
against an original?
What did I say
about peace?
Come on.
Walk with me.
Your inner circle man
lacks a sense of humor.
He's a little
overprotective,
but loyal to a fault.
I saved his life
back in the forties,
found him dying
of a war wound
outside a VA hospital.
He'd kill for me
and die for me.
Plus, that boy
can play the trumpet
like you
would not believe.
Maybe I'll see if he
can play a little
tonight at the party.
You're coming,
right?
How can I miss my chance
to meet the city councilman
as he accepts your gigantic
charitable donation?
Oh, he's a schmuck,
but he lets us
do our thing
in exchange
for certain
community services,
like keeping our fangs
out of the locals.
Listen. About
your brother,
I would love
to help you out,
but Thierry
is right.
My guys are on edge.
They see the original
family moving in,
vampires dying,
it makes them nervous.
If I hand Elijah
back now,
it might give
the wrong impression
about who's really
in charge here.
You know
what I mean?
You understand
I had to ask.
Hey, Klaus, for the love
of Mary Magdalene,
how long does it take
to ask a simple question?
Much longer
than you'd think,
considering the answer
was, as expected, no.
Marcel's man Thierry
is suspicious.
He thinks you killed
10 nightwalkers.
Well, that's a lie.
I only killed 8.
Should I make
Thierry the ninth?
Marcel
is playing friendly.
We can't kill
the favorite son,
or he'll catch
onto us.
So war it is, then.
Indeed.
Do you know what to do
with the witch?
I believe I do.
Good.
You manage
Sophie Deveraux.
I'll take care
of the next step.
I ordered you to drain
him of blood.
What's taking so long?
Sorry. I'm not medieval
torture expert guy.
Ah...
What did he
do to you, anyway?
It's not about
what he did.
It's about what
he's going to do
when we're done here,
which is
whatever I want him to,
just like you.
For example, drive this
through his torso.
That is crazy.
I didn't want to do it,
but I did it, anyway.
It's called
mind compulsion.
Vampires can
compel humans.
Originals like
my siblings and I
can also compel
vampires,
and no one can
compel Originals.
You following? Good.
That is how a brand-new
nightwalker
such as yourself is here
doing my bidding
with no one
the wiser.
But I never had my guts
drained out of me.
Yes. That, young Joshua,
is because I got to you
before you had
even a drop
of herbal vervain
in your system.
You see, it prevents
compulsion.
Marcel has had his whole
crew taking it
since I returned
to town, and that is why
our friend here needs
to be bled dry of it
so I can compel him to
follow my every command,
and with my brother
currently in captivity
awaiting rescue,
we can't afford
to be gentle about it.
Come here. Yah!
Oh, so glad
you could make it.
Elijah only lies
daggered and rotting
whilst you
dillydally.
You're lucky
I came at all.
What do you want?
Hayley was attacked
last night by Marcel's crew
because somebody
told him there was
a werewolf
in the quarter.
She only made
one stop.
Whoever saw her here
ratted her out.
Watch and learn.
Hey, Soph.
Hey, Katie.
That's filled
with marigold,
great for attracting
the opposite sex,
would look
awesome on you.
I very seriously
doubt that.
Do you have any others,
one with, say...
I don't know...
Wolfsbane, perhaps?
Wolfsbane?
Why would you want that?
Please do not
play dumb with me.
Rebekah!
I just sold the werewolf
some herbs. That's all.
Are you lying to me,
Katie?
I suggest you answer
my question honestly.
Just answer the
question, Katie, please.
Yes. I told someone,
but you don't understand.
I... I love him.
Then tell me, who is this
vampire Romeo of yours?
Shall I count to 3?
Be quick about it.
I have an army to build,
and one compelled minion
does not an army make.
Well?
You were right
about the traitor.
Luckily, she's just a kid
and she doesn't know
anything about us
and what we're up to.
Do you want
to hear the part
that's gonna
please you the most?
Oh, do tell.
She's in love with someone
in Marcel's inner circle.
Guess who it is.
Right-hand-man type,
favors silly caps?
Two points for you.
Thierry is fraternizing
with the enemy.
Well, that means he
just unwittingly became
the key to
our entire plan.
I told you
you'd be pleased.
Oh, to be young and
in love in a city
where witches and
vampires are at war.
How very tragic.
Are you out
of your mind?
No way.
It's very simple.
We need you to perform
a teeny, tiny locator spell
to help us
find our brother.
Witches who practice
magic in this town
get caught, and
they get killed.
Yes. About that,
it seems you left out
a crucial detail
when we made our deal...
Marcel's secret weapon,
the way he knows
when a witch
is using magic.
Girl about yay high,
cute as a button, anger issues.
Davina?
Where have you
seen her?
I don't know.
The little brat
erased my memory
right after she threw me out
a window with her bloody mind.
Let me cut
to the chase.
Davina has Elijah.
You witches, I assume, want
to get Davina away from Marcel.
We don't know
where she is.
Ergo, we need magic.
Davina
would sense it.
Unless, of course,
another witch...
Say, a traitor
to the cause,
Katie, for example...
Was to perform
much more powerful magic
at the same time.
That would create
a smokescreen
concealing your very small
spell from Davina.
Katie doesn't
deserve to die.
Sophie Deveraux...
You're in no position
to be so principled.
You can't win a war without
a few strategic losses,
no matter how regrettable
they may be.
How many times
have the vampires
been one step ahead,
known something they shouldn't,
your sister executed
in the public square
for practicing magic
who knew she'd be caught?
Did she even
attempt to flee?
She was caught hiding
in a cargo hold
of a freighter
before it set sail
down the Mississippi.
And who, pray tell,
in Marcel's valued
inner circle
manages his business
at the docks?
Katie's boyfriend
Thierry.
You're right.
He's good.
Right? Music man
I call him.
Ladies love him,
but he's spoken for.
He knocks around with
this pretty, little witch,
says he loves her,
but I don't know.
Yo brightest soldier
is fraternizing
with your enemy,
and you don't care.
Well, of course I care,
but Thierry is a grown man.
He makes
his own choices,
and I get
some good intel.
Besides, he's not
gonna do anything
to jeopardize what
we're doing here.
I mean, check this out,
a vampire hosting
a ritzy charity event.
We have a community here.
No one is gonna mess that up.
Still...
You don't want the
witches to get too bold,
given that a witch's tip
about a werewolf in town
led to the disappearance
of your nightwalkers.
I'm sure you've
considered
the possibility that it
could've been a trap.
Maybe I'll send
a little message.
Thierry...
Take a team
of nightwalkers
to the cauldron
tonight,
do a little
rousting...
Oh, and, Thierry,
make it nasty.
And so with that,
I moved back here
to be closer to my brothers
because... let's face it...
Family is important,
right, Camille?
Cami. I have to change
this name tag.
Drunk guys keep hitting
on me in French.
You sure you haven't
been in here before?
Your face looks
so familiar.
Oh!
You must have seen me
out and about.
Aren't you dating
Marcel Gerard?
He's a pal of mine...
Sort of.
I heard he had a crush
on the blond bartender
at Rousseau's.
I would hardly
call it dating.
He's wooing me...
Sort of.
I don't know.
He's very charming,
which probably means
I should run
for the hills.
I'm kind of in an
on-again/off-again thing
myself at the moment.
Those are the worst,
aren't they,
the ones
you can't shake,
even though
you know better,
and you always
know better?
I like you, Cami.
Most girls have
the unfortunate tendency
of being whiny,
little twits.
Thanks... I think.
Hey, I'm supposed to go
to this posh charity thing
thrown by this
philanthropist tonight.
He's a bit of a Gatsby,
throws a mean party.
Any interest?
Little sister.
Well, brother, I believe
I've made certain
Marcel will be properly
distracted tonight.
Dare I ask?
Let's just say his attention
will not be on us.
I did my bit. What are you
doing to ensure
Elijah's
safe return?
Currently, I'm
preparing insurance
against
the tender-hearted.
Meaning?
We need proper
motivation for Katie
to cast a powerful
spell tonight.
I'm creating
that motivation.
Marcel has ordered
a rousting of the witches.
No!
I, in turn, have
arranged for things
to go tragically wrong.
You understand
what you're to do?
Good.
Aah!
Hey.
Mm.
What's happening
out there?
Oh, it's Klaus.
He's convinced Marcel
that the witches
are planning to make
a move against him.
Marcel wants us
to send a message,
and if he thought
I was playing favorites
just because I'm in
love with a witch...
Say that again.
I love you, Katie,
and all this is gonna
be ok, promise.
Marcel may not
be concerned
with Thierry's
romantic entanglements...
I already got
that one.
But there are other crimes
which he'll be
less inclined
to so easily forgive...
Aah!
Thierry! Aah!
Leave her alone.
Get off.
Killing a vampire,
for example.
That would be
unforgivable.
If Katie hopes to save
her one true love
from Marcel's punishment,
well, a rescue mission
like that will require
something positively magical,
but then...
What's worth dying for
if not love?
♪ Don't cry mercy
♪ There's too much pain
to come ♪
♪ Don't cry mercy
Well, this certainly
is a fitting backdrop
for tonight's events,
I must say.
♪ Hey
What's she
doing here?
What better way
to distract Marcel
than to put his very
human, new girl
in a room chock full
of vampires?
Hello, darling.
You look precious.
This party
is ridiculous,
but I think I could get
to enjoy this place.
Is he the infamous
on-again/off-again?
He's the brother,
actually,
and my sister
is right.
You do look
stunning.
You clean up
pretty well yourself.
Well, don't
be fooled, luv.
I'm the devil
in disguise.
You two chitchat.
I need booze.
Shall we?
Ok.
Scotch, please.
You trying to be cute
inviting her here?
I think
she's darling.
I can tell you fancy
her pure heart.
Perhaps I'll
feed it to you.
Hmm, jealousy looks
good on you, Bekah.
The guy of hers Rebekah
was talking about...
I'm sensing
that would be Marcel.
I wouldn't
worry about it.
Ancient history.
I'm beginning to think your
sister is a bit of a bitch.
Ha ha!
It's as though she
invented the term.
Listen.
Pardon me
for a moment.
Cami.
Hey, killer party.
Oh, it's more
of a work thing.
I would've
invited you...
Oh, no. We've been
on one date.
No explanation
necessary.
You do your thing.
I'll entertain myself.
What, leave you alone,
looking
the way you do?
Hell with that.
You're not
supposed to be out here.
Who are you?
Sorry. I didn't mean
to scare you.
I'm Sabine. We met.
I'm one of
Sophie's friends.
You're one
of the witches.
Sophie just
asked me to come
keep you company
while everyone is out.
You know,
it's drawn to you.
The child
you're carrying
is part vampire,
part werewolf.
You and Klaus made
something special.
You sound like Elijah.
He thinks this baby
is gonna make us
one big, happy family,
but now he's gone,
and I don't even know what...
It is.
You know,
I can do something
about that
if you want,
I mean, find out if
it's a boy or girl.
I thought you couldn't do
witchy stuff around here.
It's not magic,
just an old trick
my grandmother
taught me.
Come on.
You have to be
a little curious.
♪ And there's
no remedy for memory ♪
♪ Your face is like a melody
♪ It won't leave my head
♪ Your soul is haunting me
and telling me... ♪
I thought you said you
were in community work.
Community fundraising.
Throw a party,
folks open their wallets.
It's kind of my thing.
Guess I'm what you call
a necessary evil.
And Rebekah, she's
one of your donors?
She's an old friend.
Can't be that old.
She looks
younger than me.
You'd be
surprised.
I was a kid
when I met her.
Enough about her.
I just want to be
right here with you.
You really
are a hideously evil
little thing,
aren't you?
Nonsense. They're
perfect for each other.
You wanted Marcel
distracted. Voila.
♪ Your face is like a melody
♪ It won't leave my head
♪ Your soul is haunting me
and telling me ♪
♪ That everything is fine
♪ But I wish I was dead
♪ Every time I close me eyes
My cue to leave.
♪ It's like
a dark paradise ♪
♪ No one compares to you
♪ I'm scared that you won't be
waiting on the other side ♪
♪ Every time I close me eyes
♪ It's like a dark paradise
Excuse me.
♪ No one compares to you
♪ But there's no you except
in my dreams tonight ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♪ Ha ha ha ha...
What the hell
did you do?
Not here.
No, not here.
♪ oh, oh, oh, oh
♪ Ha ha ha ha
♪ I don't want to wake up
from this tonight ♪
I know you think
he's a monster.
It doesn't matter
what I think.
Thierry killed
another vampire.
He broke Marcel's
biggest rule.
You'll never
see him again...
Unless we
do something.
"We"?
I want to save
our people.
You want to save
Thierry?
There's only one way
we can do both.
You ready?
Marcel. Something
is coming.
Magic.
I want to hear
your side of it.
Hey, Marcel,
come on.
Your version. Go.
We were tossing
the cauldron.
This guy,
some nightwalker,
he attacked Katie
for no reason.
His name was Max.
I turned him.
As far as reasons go,
he doesn't need one.
She was a witch.
He was a vampire.
Now he's dead.
I didn't mean
for it to happen.
You broke my most
important rule.
Damn it, T.
How long we been
friends, 70 years?
Yeah.
I turned you into something
that would never die.
I gave you a gift.
And I have been loyal
to you all this time,
and I still am.
I'm still
your friend, Marcel.
I swear,
that hasn't changed.
You were right, luv.
He's got a temper,
doesn't he?
I guess this is the moment
I remember I know better.
We found this
at his girl's place.
Still my friend, huh?
That's funny because
it looks to me
like that little witch of yours
got her hands on a spell
that I keep locked away.
Marcel, I have
never seen that.
Shut up.
I see on your hand,
you still have
the daylight ring
I gave you.
So what would you need
with the recipe
for making new ones
unless maybe you and Katie
were gonna go off and start
a little kingdom of your own?
Marcel, no.
Here's a lesson
in friendship.
Friends don't lie to me,
they don't break my rules,
and they do not steal
what is mine.
Ohh...
For the crime of murdering
one of his own,
I sentence
Thierry Vanchure
to 100 years
in the garden.
And it begins.
You're doing
the right thing.
It's the only way
to find Elijah.
I'm doing
what I have to do.
Katie, no!
Like clockwork.
Oh!
Aah!
Hurry.
No!
You're here
to save your man.
Well, come on,
little girl.
Raagh!
Aah!
Die, you son
of a bitch.
No! Katie!
Something is wrong.
Katie's magic stopped.
I can keep going.
You can't.
She'll sense it.
No. I can find Davina.
I just need another moment.
You may be willing
to die to get
your witch back,
but Hayley and the baby
will die with you.
Elijah will never
forgive us,
and rescuing him
will be for nothing.
It's over.
We failed.
No. Katie. No, no, no, no.
No.
Just tell me this.
Was she worth it?
I loved her.
Uhhhngh!
Seal him up
and let him rot.
How much did Cami see?
She just saw
an argument, mate.
It's nothing
you can't fix.
You really like her,
don't you?
I like that she's not
a part of any of this.
Sometimes it's good
to see the world
the way the humans do.
I am sorry about
Thierry, you know?
I can tell he was
a good friend.
I made him
what he was.
Obviously, my trust
was misplaced.
Doesn't make it
easier.
You saved me tonight.
I guess I owe you one.
You asked for
your brother back.
Seems like
the least I can do.
Cami...
Don't even try it.
I get the bro code.
You're here to
smooth things over
for your friend.
It's very nice
of you, but...
But you've been
hurt before,
and you aren't taking
any more chances.
Something like that.
The guy I saw
tonight,
not the guy
I thought he was,
and if he can turn
on a dime like that...
Sounds like more than
just a broken heart.
Someone broke
your trust...
Camille, the brave
bartender.
I'm sorry...
But I need you to give
Marcel another chance.
Wow. I totally
misread that.
No. You read it
quite well,
but we all have
our roles to play.
You went to Marcel's.
You danced.
You feel badly hat he
had a row with his friend,
but otherwise,
all you remember
is that it was perfect.
Well, tonight
was an epic failure.
On the contrary,
sister.
Tonight was
a masterpiece.
Are you mad?
Katie died before Sophie
could complete the spell.
Oh, I'm well aware.
I killed Katie.
You what?
There's no way our
little suicide witch
wasn't gonna
try and take out
Marcel with her.
I saved his life,
and in doing so,
I now have him exactly
where I want him.
Sophie trusted you.
I trusted you against
all my better instincts.
Wake up, Rebekah.
The witches
are on no one's side
but their own.
This girl Davina,
that's all they want,
and when they have her,
what do you think
happens then,
a truce?
Of course not.
They will use
Davina's power
against all of us.
Even if you're right,
the plan was to find Elijah,
and you failed us.
You always did
lack faith.
By protecting Marcel,
I've cemented his trust,
so much so
that he's agreed
to return Elijah to us,
and when the time
is right,
when he has told me
everything
I need to know
about Davina,
I will have her
for myself.
I have all the faith
in the world
that you'll get
what you want, Nik.
You always do,
no matter what it costs
the rest of us.
You disgust me.
Are you ok?
I was so worried.
Thank you.
Whatever you did,
I felt it.
You helped me.
It was the old ones,
wasn't it?
Actually, Klaus is the one
that saved me tonight.
I'm gonna
make things right,
starting off by giving
him his brother back.
No.
What?
Davina...
No.
You said the old ones
were dangerous.
I won't give him back
until I know how to kill them.
I thought you might
like to know,
Elijah is
returning to us.
Congratulations.
I guess being diabolical
has its perks.
You hardly know him,
and yet you miss him.
What is it about my brother
that always inspires
such instant admiration?
He was kind to me.
There are
moments when I doubt
if my family
is capable of redemption...
Hey, I learned
something today.
I think it's a girl.
Elijah, voice-over
yet each time that I am tempted
to surrender, I see it,
the glimmer of goodness
that allows me to believe.
You're following me.
Maybe you're
just in my way.
I told you
no good would come
from this unholy alliance
of yours.
At least
I'm doing something.
What about you?
Sabine, tell them
what you saw.
It's the girl,
the wolf.
I think it's a girl.
No. Wait.
Wait what?
Please tell me I'm not
having a mini Klaus.
Hoc est infantima malom.
Nos omnia perdetu el eam.