["Peaches" by The Stranglers playing]
- [boy] Oi, oi, here comes Wiley.
- [boys jeering]
- Hello, Kermit. Nice legs.
- [boys laugh]
Have you got green pubes, Kermit?
What is that?
- [boy 2] Oh, she is such a freak.
- [boy 3] She's a creep.
You should be careful dressing like that.
And you should be careful perpetuating
old-fashioned patriarchal ideology.
It'll make it difficult
for people to like you.
[boys] Hey!
Come on, Kermit, show us your pubes!
You're a bitch!
Yeah, I am.
♪ Walking on the beaches
Looking at the peaches ♪
Mmm.
Come on then.
[Maeve laughs]
That's it.
[phone vibrating]
[sighs]
[groans]
- Good morning.
- Ah!
Why are you in my bed?
If you tell anyone about this,
I'll destroy your life.
Did we have sex?
Of course we had sex, Otis.
I'm not here because I enjoy your company.
But I can't find the condom.
We had sex without a condom?
- No, I'm pretty sure we used one.
- Well, where is it?
I don't know, it's vanished.
Mmm...
You don't think
your vagina swallowed it, do you?
- I heard about the girl...
- I can't believe I had sex with you.
Okay, Ruby,
we definitely used a condom, right?
Yes. I'm, like, 99 percent certain.
Oh! [retches]
- Sorry.
- [Jean] Otis!
Come down.
[bottles clinking]
[approaching footsteps on stairs]
Hello.
- I'm Ruby.
- Hello, Ruby.
I covet your pant suits.
Oh.
- Thank you. This one's...
- I was just being polite.
I've gotta get to school.
[whispering] You said a small gathering!
- [door opens, closes]
- It was only supposed to be ten people,
but Eric invited a whole load more
and suddenly 150 strangers
were in the house.
- [loudly] A hundred and fifty strangers?
- It was not my intention.
Otis! I'm not hearing
a lot of responsibility being taken here.
I have clients coming this afternoon
and my house is trashed!
Oh, it's too loud, and I'm late,
and my head hurts, and I-I-I...
I will help you clean later.
- Later?
- Yes.
Later? Otis!
- Uh...
- [door opens]
[door closes]
See you, cheeky chops. Love you.
- [Joe] Are you spying again?
- I don't trust her.
- Who, Body Slammer?
- No, her mum.
What's she doing there?
Joe, have a look, would you? I can't see.
I don't know, she's watching TV.
I knew she was up to something.
Oh, yeah. Quick, call the police,
our neighbor's watching Bargain Hunt!
[gulps]
Oh! Oh! Ah!
Hey!
How are you feeling, Casanova?
Why is the world so bright?
Because you got very drunk,
offended your unrequited love
and ex-girlfriend, puked on yourself,
and danced really badly
in front of most of the people
at this school. [laughs]
- Eric.
- Mm-hmm.
- I had sex with Ruby.
- What?
- [groans]
- Are you sure you had sex?
Well, she definitely thinks we had sex.
The details are hazy.
I feel really strange.
I feel like I'm either having
an unusually long panic attack
or I'm just very, very thirsty... or both.
- [groans]
- Okay, calm down and listen to me.
Probably wasn't the romantic
forest glade fantasy
- you imagined with Maeve.
- I did not imagine that.
But you are not a virgin anymore! What?
- That's exciting, right?
- It's not.
- Sex has consequences.
- Well, it's not like you're gonna father
Ruby's evil spawn. [laughs]
You did use a condom, right?
Right?
Otis, I have noticed
that you've not answered my question.
Oh, my God.
Hi, Maeve.
[clears throat]
I'm really sorry about last night.
- I said...
- I heard you shagged Ruby, dude.
Who knew Sex Kid was such a player!
[boys laugh]
Congratulations.
That was withering.
[girl] Oh, no, no, no!
I'm embarrassed!
- [boy] Mate, have you seen this?
- [girl 2] What's happening?
[laughing]
I was drunk.
- Yes, yes, you were, mate.
- Seriously!
I can't believe
you told Dr. Milburn I had crabs.
- I said you might have one crab.
- Holy shit.
Miss Sands loves doing dirty talk
with Mr. Hendricks.
- Amazing.
- [girl 3] That is amazing.
What did Jean do?
Your mum said I was normal.
She lied.
"Connor Pearson admits to masturbating
up to 17 times a day,
- which is borderline obsessive."
- I'm a monster!
This is bad, very bad.
How could Jean leave her notes
lying around?
Well, I have to go anyway.
I've got Swing Band practice.
Seventeen times?
Dirty, dirty pig.
[crying]
What on earth?
[girl] I thought it was confidential!
I promise you we will
get to the bottom of this.
Jackson, wait!
- I had to tell them.
- We're not friends, Viv.
You said some pretty horrible things
to me too, you know?
Fine. We were never friends
in the first place.
Aimes, you're covered in mud.
Yeah. I am.
- Can we talk?
- Not right now, Steve. I'm late for gym.
Aimes, guess what?
- Otis had sex with Ruby last right.
- I'm sure it didn't mean anything.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm sure he didn't mean it.
He was really drunk.
Yeah.
[girl sobbing]
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Jean speaking.
[Mr. Groff] Hello, Miss Milburn.
I need you to come into the school
at 4:00 p.m. today.
There's been an incident.
- Can you tell me what it's concerning?
- Just be here at 4:00 p.m.
I'll be there.
Shit! Guys, come and take a look at this.
[girl] Oh, my God!
No dillydallying, girls.
It wasn't me.
- It was not me.
- I wouldn't have the time.
Someone is in very serious trouble.
[dog barks]
Ah. You're on time. That's odd.
I have an errand to run,
so will you be all right with Jessie?
- Uh, yeah, I like dogs.
- Are you sure?
[Jessie whimpers]
She's very annoying.
You know, she can't even sit.
[barks]
We'll be fine.
[door opens, closes]
[sighs]
[thud at window]
[mouthing]
Um...
Sir, can I go to the toilet, please?
Can't it wait, Milburn?
lt's almost the end of the day.
No. Sir, I...
[whispering] I have hemorrhoids.
Oh, yes. I feel your pain.
[chuckles] Hemorrhoid Club.
[sighs]
Otis!
Uh...
[sighs]
- What?
- Shh.
Okay, so...
you know how I said I was 99 percent sure
about the condom?
- Yes.
- It's more like 96.5.
The details are a bit hazy
and I think I remember
putting it in the bin,
but I can't be sure.
Okay. What should we do?
[bell ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
- Shall we go play Smash Bros?
- Oh, I can't.
I've got to go to a service
at my church tonight.
- Is church boring?
- No.
It's actually quite fun, you know.
There's singing, there's plantain,
and if you're lucky,
sometimes this auntie called Gloria
- starts speaking in tongues.
- Cool.
- Can I come with you?
- You don't want to come to my service.
I think it will be interesting,
unless you don't want me to.
No! Okay, sure.
But, um... [laughs]
...I have to be a bit different there.
Like, a bit more serious,
if you get what I mean.
Yeah. That's okay.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Let's go to church.
[laughs]
[Jackson] What are you doing here?
We've made an appointment
with your counselor.
- Can't we do this another time?
- No, we're doing it now. Get in.
Get in the car.
Well, well.
Here we are. I don't like keeping you
after school, girls, but this is serious.
I had nothing to do with this,
and it'll look really bad on my school CV,
- so may I go home, please?
- No, you may not.
Somebody in this room
thought it would be funny
to write something very cruel about me
on that mirror.
We're going to sit here
until they admit it was them.
No one has anything to say?
Fine. You will circle
every "A" in the paper
until one of you owns up.
- That's not very productive, miss.
- Neither is slut-shaming your teacher.
Get circling, girls.
I'll be back to check on you.
Have you ever done this before?
No! What are you trying to say?
You slept with me too, you know.
I know, I'm not trying to say anything.
Look, I'm not having your pale,
unusually long children, okay?
- So just go in and get it already.
- Me?
I can't be seen buying
the morning after pill, Otis.
People will talk.
Go on. Go on.
[Roz] It's important
to tell Dr. Aiken everything.
You might need to up your meds.
You are taking them?
[Sofia] Your mum just asked you
a question.
Yes. I'm taking them.
Well, why didn't you answer her then?
[loud pop]
- [Roz] Shit. Oh, God. I think it's a flat.
- [Sofia] Brilliant, we're gonna be late.
- [Roz] I can't control it, can I?
- [Sofia] You drive too fast.
[Roz] I don't need this right now.
So, who's changed a tire before?
It wouldn't be good for my hand.
Brilliant.
Very sensitive sinuses.
[register beeping]
[muffled] And can I get
the morning after pill, please?
- Excuse me?
- [slurred] The morning after pill?
- I can't hear you.
- [slurred] The morning after pill.
- I still can't hear you.
- [loudly] The morning after pill.
I can't sell it to you.
- Why not?
- You don't have a vagina, sir.
[door chimes]
It's not... It's nasal spray.
- You need to buy it in person.
- [door chimes]
What? Why? Ugh!
This is so humiliating.
It's not humiliating.
Okay? I mean,
stuff like this happens all the time.
Condoms break,
or people forget to use them,
or they just go missing.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
I also want you to know
if you are pregnant
and chose to keep the baby,
I'll quit school, get a job
and provide for you both.
[door chimes]
- When did you last have sex?
- Last night.
- Obviously.
- Did you use contraception?
Yes.
- I think so.
- [Otis] The prophylactic's missing.
Sorry, I'm not here.
- When was your last period?
- Two weeks ago.
Have you taken
the emergency contraceptive pill before?
No. Why do people keep asking me that?
I'm not a slut.
Does anyone in your immediate family
have any health problems?
My dad has MS. He was diagnosed last year.
It's quite bad.
So, can I have the pill or not?
That'll be £25.
It's his penis, he's paying for it.
I am. I am?
- Please don't tell anyone I was here.
- I've no idea who you are.
That's impossible.
Everyone knows who I am.
[register beeping]
Mm.
- Right, you've gotta be kidding me.
- Look, I'm just saying,
if you push it in first...
- [Sofia] Mind your hand out of the way.
- Oh, just push it in first, and then...
[Sofia] Oh, my God. This is stupid.
I'm calling them.
- I said we don't have to.
- This is so typical of you.
Why can't you just admit you can't do it?
I can do it.
Well, if you can do it
then why isn't it done?
[laughs]
And why are you laughing?
Because you both just need
to get a divorce.
Why would you say that?
Because it's true.
You fight all the time.
You're so angry at mum,
but you pretend that you're not.
And you're so scared
I won't love you like a biological mum
that you just spend most of your time
pushing us both away.
I just think we'd all be a lot happier
if you just get a divorce.
Yeah, I'll go get her.
Mum!
[Aimee] I'm finished too.
I think you're supposed to circle
all the "A" s,
- not just the singular ones.
- You're so dumb sometimes, Aimee.
- Olivia, do you want this pen in your eye?
- [Viv] You guys are such clichés.
Except for you, Lily.
You're genuinely weird.
- Thanks.
- What category are you in, Pythagoras,
- other than freak?
- The really, really intelligent one.
Oh, really? [blows raspberry]
Olivia, Mr. Groff wants to see you.
- [Viv and Maeve] Ooh!
- Shut up.
Anyone have anything to admit?
- You can circle the "I" s next.
- Please, Miss Sands. This is pointless.
Okay, you want a challenge?
You can spend the rest of detention
preparing a presentation
on what binds you together as women.
One or all of you wanted to tear
a fellow female down,
now you can spend some time thinking about
what you have in common instead.
- You are joking, right?
- No, I'm not.
You have two hours to enlighten me.
Unless you want a month
of detentions instead?
[Mr. Groff] I'd like you to know
we take these issues
very seriously indeed.
Olivia, come in.
Were you aware that Malek had received
sex advice from Miss Milburn?
Malek Amir talked about his girlfriend
wanting to incorporate...
- fetish...
- Those are my private notes,
and they're not meant to be read
by anybody else.
And I'm sorry,
but I don't know how they were misplaced.
Olivia, do you know
how old your boyfriend is?
He's... He's 16.
Fifteen.
- Fifteen?
- Yeah, I skipped a year in primary school.
- What do you mean "fetish"?
- Amir is not an Indian surname.
We are Iranian.
- Iranian.
- You're 15?
You could go to prison for statutory rape!
This is very serious.
- [man] Iranian?
- Fifteen? What the fuck, Malek?
Okay, Mum...
[muffled arguing]
- [man speaking indistinctly]
- We are not going to press charges.
But how could you give sex advice
to children? It's despicable.
I didn't give sex advice.
I answered a question
about a possible fetish.
And I gave the correct information
concerning that subject.
- I... I didn't tell them to do anything...
- You shouldn't have been talking
to 15-year-olds about fetish at all.
This is not what you were employed to do.
And I made that very clear.
- Yes, but my report...
- Is no longer welcome on campus
and nor are you.
[mouthing]
[indistinct arguing]
- Back to detention, Olivia.
- For God sake!
Can we talk about how exactly
my private notes
got distributed around your campus?
I have no idea.
I could just tell them it was Sex Kid
who gave us the actual advice.
I'm sorry, what?
You know, Otis. His advice
was super strange, but it worked.
But he charges a lot for it though,
which sucks.
Well, that's why I came to you
because you're free.
This is so stupid.
Well, we have to come up with something
if we want to go home.
- Does anybody like fantasy gaming?
- I do.
- I love Dungeons & Dragons.
- Oh, I'm more into
dressing up as Ripley from Alien.
I don't get cosplay.
- What about shopping?
- I hate shopping.
- Me too.
- Can't we just pretend
we're all into shopping or cosplay?
That would be cheating.
We could try a mind map.
[approaching footsteps]
- [Viv] What did Groff want?
- I might be going to prison
because apparently, my boyfriend's 15.
- Anybody else also into younger men?
- [Olivia] What are we doing?
- Figuring out what we have in common.
- ...things we all like.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, are you?
- Yeah, I'm great.
- Great.
It's going well then.
Ugh.
[moaning]
[horn honks]
How long have you got?
I gave them an impossible assignment
about female solidarity,
- they won't finish for ages.
- You're so evil.
Say it again.
You're so evil.
Mmm.
[moaning]
- [panting]
- [bagpipes wheeze]
[vocalizing]
The church is very beautiful,
Mrs. Effiong. It's not what I thought.
- Do you attend the mosque?
- Anthea. You can't ask that.
Sorry, Rahim. Just ignore my sister.
- I thought you were Muslim.
- Anthea.
Eric, I don't think
your sister means to be rude.
- I just wanted to know.
- Just... You don't have to answer that.
No, it's okay. My family's atheist.
What's an atheist?
It's someone who believes
that there is no God.
Okay? Shall we be quiet now?
We can't touch each other in church.
♪ We shall meet on that beautiful shore ♪
Don't come over here.
I don't want to talk to you right now,
- hence why I walked away.
- It's ridiculous, Mum.
[sighs]
I just... I need a moment alone, Jackson.
I'm not going anywhere
until we talk, so...
That was the most hurtful thing
you could possibly say to me.
Yeah, I know.
- That's why I said it.
- [scoffs]
- I didn't mean it, I was just angry.
- No, you did mean it.
- I didn't mean to make you cry, Mum.
[sighs]
I've just always been so afraid
that you would say I wasn't your real mum,
and now you've actually said it,
I'm almost relieved.
- Of course you're my real mum.
- But you didn't come through me.
- So?
- That's why I was so happy
when you said you wanted to swim
because that's my passion,
something we could do together.
I thought it was because
you couldn't compete anymore...
and you were living your dream through me.
Well, maybe there's a bit
of truth in that.
- I genuinely thought you enjoyed it.
- I did enjoy it...
a lot.
Do you know what I enjoyed most
about swimming when I was a kid?
Spending time with you.
You were my hero, Mum.
When we were together,
I felt like I could do anything.
[chuckles]
Why did you have to grow up?
- I don't want to swim anymore.
- I know.
It just doesn't make me happy.
But it's got nothing
to do with our relationship, okay?
You've gotta let me figure out who I am
and what else I like to do on my own.
But you'll always, always...
be my real mum.
[Sofia sniffs]
[sighs]
I got a part in the school play.
- What?
- Yeah.
Playing Romeo.
[laughs]
- Well, you were very believable as Joseph.
- [both laugh]
- [Jessie barks]
- Jessie. No.
[barks]
- Sit.
- [barks]
[barking continues]
[Jessie barks]
[whimpers]
Wait.
[Jessie whimpers]
- Sit.
- [whimpers]
Here you are.
[door opens]
[clears throat]
How are you you, New Kid?
Since when do you ask questions?
I'm trying to work on my small talk.
How is he?
[scanner beeps]
Eric?
He's confused.
I don't know what's going on between
the two of you,
but if you hurt him, I'll...
I'll mess you up.
I don't want to hurt him anymore.
Then don't.
I said fucking diet.
[piano music playing]
♪ He is my friend ♪
♪ Oh, Lord ♪
[man] Hallelujah!
♪ Through thick and thin ♪
Jesus is with you.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Thank you, Pastor.[chuckles]
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Jesus is with you.
Oh, sorry. I don't believe in Jesus.
[chuckles]
Jesus is with you.
I hope I didn't offend him.
- No.
- [man] Hallelujah!
♪ He's my friend ♪
[pastor] Hallelujah!
You did give me consent, right?
I'm kind of worried you didn't.
Yes, Otis. I definitely said yes.
When I'm sad, I make out with nerdy boys.
It was 100 percent intentional.
Why nerdy boys?
Because they think they're in love
with me, which feels amazing,
until they get clingy
and want to show me all their things.
I don't think I'm in love with you.
Sure you don't.
Was I... Was I okay at the sex bit?
- It was kind of my first time.
- You're a virgin?
Well, I was.
You weren't great,
but you weren't terrible.
You kept asking me if I was okay.
- It's important to check in.
- It was every ten seconds.
Were you sad because of your dad?
Yeah, a bit.
He had to quit his job,
and my mum's really stressed about it.
But mainly I was upset
because I over-plucked my left eyebrow,
and I'd just got them symmetrical.
They look very even to me.
Thank you for checking in.
A lot of guys don't.
There must be something we all like.
- Chocolate?
- Yes.
No.
Let's just tell Miss Sands that we resent
being grouped together
and forced to bond on the basis
of our gender.
Or I could pretend I like chocolate.
I know you are comfortable
with being dishonest, but I'm not.
What's that supposed to mean?
You pretend to be all radical
and feminist,
when you're just a girl who goes around
stabbing other girls in the back.
- It's not true.
- So, you didn't try
- and steal my boyfriend then?
- Can we not fight?
Shut up. It just got interesting.
I didn't try and steal your boyfriend,
Ola. I had to tell him how I felt.
You didn't have to, Maeve. You chose to.
Did you even like Otis?
Or did you just want to win?
You're a snake.
[Maeve] Yeah? At least I don't pretend
to be so sweet and nice all the time.
[Maeve and Ola]
You don't know anything about me!
Stop fighting over a stupid boy!
Aimes, why are you crying?
[breathing shakily]
Because I can't get on the bus.
[Maeve] Oh, Aimes. It's okay.
It's okay.
[sighs]
Um, can I come and see you?
I... I'm...
I didn't know who else to talk to.
You can all stop looking at me now.
[Viv] So you can't get on the bus
because you think
that man's gonna be on it again?
No. It's more that he had
this really kind face.
I remember because he smiled at me,
and he didn't look like
some wanking psycho killer.
So it's, like, if he could do something
like that, then anyone could.
I always felt safe before,
and now I don't.
- Probably sounds stupid.
- It doesn't sound stupid.
I was groped
at the train station last year.
We were going to a gig in the city,
this group of guys walked past
and one of them grabbed my tit.
[laughing]
And it really, really hurt.
So, I sometimes feel funny in crowds too.
It was like they thought
my body was theirs or something.
Yeah, like we're public property.
A few years ago,
some boys were catcalling me.
This woman told me it was my fault
because my shorts were too revealing.
So I went home
and I cut them even shorter,
because fuck them.
Good. Why should you have to change
your behavior because of what they did?
[Maeve] Exactly.
I used to go to the local swimming pool
all the time when I was a kid.
One day this guy flashed me his penis
in the pool...
and it looked all dangly
and funny under the water.
[laughing]
I told my mum about it,
and she wouldn't let me go back anymore.
It's sad because
the pool was my favorite place to go.
- That's so unfair.
- I guess,
but statistically, two thirds of girls
experience unwanted sexual tension
or contact in public spaces
before the age of 21.
So, it's not unusual.
Why are some men so obsessed
with getting their dicks out?
Sometimes I go on Chat Roulette,
and there are so many flaccid penises
on there.
There are long ones, short ones, fat ones.
There was once even one that looked like
it had a tiny face.
I think if I had an extra arm growing
in between my legs,
- I might want to show everyone too.
- [Maeve] Yeah.
- Maybe it's a power thing.
- Yeah.
I think the man on the bus
liked that I was afraid.
A man followed me home from work
about a year ago.
Every time I sped up, he sped up.
It was so scary.
He ran off when he saw my dad,
which made me angry
because I don't want to be dependent
on another man to protect me.
- I'm sorry that happened to you.
- You too.
Thank you.
At least we can go home now.
Dicks.
[chuckles]
- I'll tell you who loves ginger nuts.
- Yeah?
- Eric Clapton.
- Really?
- Absolutely loves them.
- Are you joking?
Stop!
[stammers] I only did it 'cause
I love you, and I found out you love him.
He can't offer you what I can, miss.
I have an innate appreciation
for older women,
and I can roll a joint
into the shape of a swan.
That is problematic on so many levels,
but I must say the lipstick
was an ingenious touch.
- You really think so?
- It's not happening, Kyle. Okay?
Follow me.
- I love you.
- [Mr. Hendricks] Now!
[Adam] Sit.
- Stand.
- I don't believe it.
Sit.
[whimpers]
It's a miracle. Ha!
You're a smart boy.
Why aren't you in school?
I'm no good at school.
Yes, well, you carry on like this,
you're looking at employee of the month.
Huh?
I'm going to go to the movies tonight,
so you can lock up for me.
I'm going to go and get ready.
[door opens, closes]
Girls...
I'm afraid there's been a mistake.
We've found the culprit.
You may go home now.
I'm very sorry for wasting your time.
[Viv] Well, great. I knew it.
Oh, out of curiosity,
what did you come up with?
What binds you together?
Other than non-consensual penises, miss,
not much.
- Are you gonna be okay?
- I think so.
I don't feel sad, I just feel angry.
I know something that might help.
[Rahim] I like your family. They're sweet.
What do you mean "sweet"?
The way they believe
in all that God stuff.
They think it's real.
I believe in it too.
Yeah, but not properly.
- You pretend to keep the peace, right?
- No.
No, I believe in God, Rahim.
How can you believe in a god
that doesn't think you should exist?
Okay, this is awkward.
No, my family had to leave their country
because of religion.
It just doesn't make any sense to me.
- I didn't know that.
- It's okay.
It's our differences
that make me love you.
We'll agree to disagree.
Love?
Does that freak you out?
No, no, no. Uh...
I... I love you too.
Ah, putain!
- I think my heart stopped for a moment.
- [laughs]
Let's go.
I just cannot believe
he's been taking all that money
from all those other students.
I feel like
I don't know him at all, like...
like I've got a stranger
living in my house.
I think we can't ever truly know
these creatures that we created.
- Well, perhaps you're right.
- Talk to him.
That's all you can do.
Hey.
Want to get something to eat after this...
with me?
I'm afraid I can't do that, Jean.
It was one stupid kiss.
You really can't forgive me?
You know...
I may not be as intellectual
as your ex-husband,
but I do know my boundaries.
I can't go through
that kind of pain again.
I'm not sure if I could get up.
- My girls need me.
- Mm.
Mm.
You're not ready
for the kind of intimacy I'm looking for.
Understood.
Goodbye, Jakob.
Yeah.
["Mystery of Love"
by Sufjan Stevens playing]
♪ Oh, to see without my eyes ♪
[breathing shakily]
♪ The first time that you kissed me ♪
♪ Boundless by the time I cried ♪
♪ I built your walls around me ♪
♪ White noise, what an awful sound ♪
♪ Fumbling by Rogue River ♪
♪ Feel my feet above the ground ♪
♪ Hand of God, deliver me ♪
♪ Oh, oh, woe-oh-woe is me ♪
♪ The first time that you touched me ♪
♪ Oh, will wonders ever cease? ♪
♪ Blessed be the mystery of love ♪
- [knocking at door]
- Come in.
- Dinner is in ten minutes.
- Okay.
[mother sighs]
Your thoughts are very loud, Mum.
- That boy is not right for you.
- You don't think any boy's right for me.
It's not him, it's you.
You act like a different person
when you're around him,
like you're trying to be something
that you're not.
He doesn't make you sparkle.
♪ Oh, will wonders ever cease? ♪
♪ Blessed be the mystery of love ♪
What do I do?
Think about something
that makes you really, really angry,
and then smash it as hard as you can.
Mmm.
I'm angry that I'm not very good
at baking cakes.
- Yes!
- Woo!
- Come on.
- [Maeve] Go on, Aimee!
I'm angry that Steve keeps trying so hard
to make things better,
but he doesn't understand.
- Yes! Come on!
- Woo!
I'm angry that a horrible man
ruined my best jeans
and nobody did anything,
and now, I can't get on the fucking bus!
- Yeah!
- [Aimee] Yes!
- This is amazing!
- Woo!
- Gonna keep smashing stuff!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Give it to them!
♪ But you've gotta make
Your own kind of music ♪
♪ Sing your own special song ♪
♪ Make your own kind of music ♪
♪ Even if nobody else sings along ♪
I did try and steal him.
- I'm sorry.
- I did like him...
but I kind of wanted to beat you too.
Let's get you home.
Wanna walk me home?
Yeah.
Hey, Mum.
Are you all right?
I heard about what happened.
Otis.
Have you been giving sex advice
to students at school for money?
What are you talking about?
- Tell me the truth.
- I am.
[sighs]
You look just like your father
when you lie.
- Let's talk about this rationally.
- I can't talk to you right now.
Mum.
Oh, shit!
I didn't think you wanted
to be my friend anymore.
This wasn't in my plan.
Boys that smell a bit sweaty
were in my plan,
not girls that smell like vanilla pods.
- I don't smell like a vanilla pod.
- Yeah, you do.
And car air freshener... sometimes.
You're very clean.
Sorry I confused you, but...
it really hurt
when you started avoiding me.
Fine.
We can still be friends.
I'll see you at school then.
Wait. I think I don't wanna be
just friends.
Why?
Because you smell
so much better than a boy.
I just...
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
- [Isaac] Hey.
So, your mum's lying about going to work.
I saw her pretending to leave this morning
and sneaking back into the caravan again.
Shit stirrer.
I'm only telling you what I saw.
Take it or leave it.
- Okay. Night, Isaac. [clears throat]
- Good night.
[sighs]
Why do you always double knot?
I don't want you running off, do I?
[laughs sarcastically]
You're funny.
[Erin] Ooh!
- Say bye-bye.
- Bye-bye.
[Erin] Bye-bye.
[sighs] All right, 007, enough.
God.
[sighs]
[upbeat music on radio playing]
- Hi, Mum.
- Fucking arsehole.
What you doing?
- I had to pop back...
- Isaac told me he saw you yesterday.
I got fired.
I didn't know how to tell you.
Um...
I felt so ashamed.
But... I am looking for something else.
- Are you using again?
- No, I am not.
I swear on my life.
I swear on your life, on Elsie's life.
I'm clean.
Please believe me.
I believe you.
[clears throat]
Lie to me one more time, and you're out.
[door opens]
[door slams]
["Seventeen" by Sharon Van Etten playing]
What are you doing here?
Getting the bus.
We're all getting the bus.
- [driver] Are you getting on or what?
- [Maeve] Give her a minute.
[whispering] It's just a stupid bus.
It's just a stupid bus.
♪ Downtown harks back ♪
♪ Halfway up the street ♪
♪ I used to be free ♪
♪ I used to be seventeen ♪
♪ La la la la la la la ♪
♪ I know what you're gonna be ♪
♪ I know that you're gonna be ♪
♪ You're crumbling up just to see ♪
♪ Afraid that you'll be just like me ♪